♪ I'm goin'
down to south park ♪
♪ gonna have myself a time
♪ friendly faces everywhere
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ I'm goin'
down to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my woes behind
♪ ample parking day or night,
people spouting howdy neighbor ♪
♪ headin' on up to south park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Yeah, yeah, do we rock?
Yeah, yeah,
take it to the top.
are we gonna stop?
No way.
- Cheer squad roll call!
- Heidi!
- Nicole!
- Bebe!
- Lola!
- Red!
- Annie!
lisa berger.
- Oh, god.
- Here we go.
- Ugh.
- Could we maybe
try one
Without lisa berger?
- You guys, stop it.
Okay, lisa,
that's great.
But you need to have
some more confidence, okay?
- But I'm the fat one.
- What?
Every cheerleading squad
has the fat, ugly cheerleader,
And that's me.
- See, that's
the problem, lisa.
You have a bad self image.
Just project all your sassiness
to all the boys out there, okay?
- There's only one boy
that lisa cares about.
- Yeah, lisa has
a crush on butters.
- Shut up.
- But, lisa,
that's great.
Have you told butters
that you like him?
- No way.
I'd just get made fun of.
- Lisa, this is exactly
what you need.
Take butters
to see a movie or something.
It'll do wonders
for your confidence.
- So then, uh,
the fella with the moustache
Eats all the cupcakes,
and the lady takes out a gun
And puts it in his face,
and she says—
- Uh, excuse me, butters?
- Oh, yes?
- Um, well...
I was just wondering
if maybe
You would like to go
to a movie this weekend.
- Oh.
Oh, like a date?
Oh, no thanks, lisa.
I really
appreciate the offer,
But you're
too fat for me.
- Okay, thanks.
- See ya, lisa!
- Ha ha, butters got
asked out by a fat girl.
- At least she didn't
try to sit on him.
- You guys, come on,
that's not cool.
You shouldn't rip on her
because she's fat.
You should rip on her
because she's ugly, okay?
She looks like someone hit her
in the face with a hot shovel,
And that's
why she sucks, all right?
♪ camptown ladies
sing this song ♪
♪ doo daa
doo daa ♪
♪ camptown race
is five miles long ♪
♪ oh doo daa day
- What the fuck
is your problem?
- Oh, hey, wendy.
- Are you just an asshole?
Is that it?
- Am I just an asshole?
- Yeah!
- Well, no.
I've got arms and legs.
I have everything.
- Lisa berger
asks you out,
And you call her fat?
Do you have any idea
how you made her feel?
She's a really nice girl.
- I think she's
a nice girl too.
She's just too big for me.
- She's a little overweight,
but that's pretty normal
For a girl
in the fourth grade.
- Well, kim kardashian
is skinny,
And she just
had a baby!
- What?
- I'm sorry, wendy,
But I have a different standard
when it comes to my women.
I want a woman
who takes care of herself
And knows how
to look good.
Who's got perfect skin,
And no splotches on her legs,
and perfect everything.
- This is a fantasy,
you moron.
You ever heard
of photoshop?
Kim kardashian is a short,
overweight woman
Who manipulates her image
And makes average girls
feel horrible about themselves.
- You're a liar!
- Look it up, stupid.
In real life,
kim kardashian
Has the body
of a hobbit.
You're gonna be
in real trouble
When the teachers
find out what you said
To that poor girl.
- Uh, take a seat, wendy.
I guess some
mean things were said,
And I need to get
to the bottom of it.
- Oh, good.
Lisa berger told on you?
Good.
- Uh, no, wendy,
apparently,
You called
butters' girlfriend a hobbit.
- Are you serious?
- You did!
You said kim is short,
fat, and hairy, with big feet,
And she's a hobbit!
- That's not his girlfriend.
It's kim kardashian.
- But—but, wendy,
kim kardashian
Is considered to be
extremely beautiful, mkay?
- Right, but she's not
in real life.
She's a hobbit.
- Oh, she said it again!
- No, wendy,
kim might be full figured,
But a woman's outward appearance
isn't all that matters, mkay?
Have you stopped to consider
that maybe, just maybe
You're jel?
- I am not "jel,"
and I happen to be
The biggest feminist
at this school.
- That may be true,
But there is
a very fine line, wendy,
Between being a feminist
and being a hater, mkay?
And you're gonna have
to find that line,
Because nobody likes
a girl who's jelly.
- Okay, kids, there have been
some hurtful and hateful things
Being said
around this school,
And so we are gonna hear
from a guest speaker.
Here to explain why
kim kardashian is not a hobbit,
Please welcome aquaman.
- Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, that's right.
- Uh-oh.
- Okay,
first of all,
I am not aquaman.
I am a recovering
gay fish.
Yes, I have met aquaman.
I have hung out with aquaman.
But the only thing I have
in common with aquaman anymore
Is my love for the sea.
Now...
There have been
malicious rumors
Started at this
elementary school
That my beautiful fiancee
is a hobbit.
That is not funny,
and it is not true.
All right?
Yes, kim is heavier than move
of her pictures show her to be.
Yes, she gets her hair
lasered off her body.
Yes, she has a friend
named gandalf
Who happens
to be a wizard.
- I'm sorry.
Excuse me a minute.
Bitch, how you not
the hobbit again?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right.
Right, right, right,
right, right, yeah.
Okay, yep.
Yep, let me—okay.
Yep, I got it.
Okay, love you too.
Okay, if my fiancee kim
is a hobbit,
Then how come it—
uh, how—then—
Okay, if she is a hobbit,
then how come
She don't live
in a hole in the ground?
Boom!
Aw, y'all just got lit up, cup!
She don't live
in no hole in the ground.
She lives
in a big-ass mansion with me,
In her room
that is slightly below ground.
So you can—
She—she is sexy
and womanly.
And she smokes a pipe.
She can blow them rings
That go up
over her head, and—
Hold up.
Bitch, you not
a hobbit, right?
No, I know, you just—
You smoke
that long pipe sometimes
When you sit
by the fire.
Oh, it's a—
oh, okay, got it.
What do you call it?
Yep, yep, got it.
Okay, yep,
love you too.
That is not a hobbit pipe,
for your information.
It is a personal
oral humidifier
To keep all the wrinkles
around her mouth from showing.
So ha, ha,
all you haters, ha!
- Butters, butters,
come here for a sec.
- Oh, no you don't,
wendy.
You're not trapping me inside
the computer lab to beat me up.
- Butters, would you please
let me show you something
So we can put this
behind us?
- All right,
but if you try to punch me,
I'll scream.
- I want you to see
just how easy this is,
So we can better
understand each other.
This is lisa berger's
class photo, right?
- Okay.
- Now, first thing we do
is just
Photoshop the bulges
on her sides.
We select the eyes,
make them a nicer shape.
Take off any blemishes
on the skin.
Lengthen the neck.
Add more to the hair.
Select the lips.
Make them fuller.
Take out any puffiness
on the skin here.
Add fullness to the breasts,
length of the torso.
Take away
that fold of skin.
Streamline the shoulders.
Put highlights in the eyes.
And there.
- That's lisa berger?
- Do you see
what I'm talking about?
- She's pretty!
- That's how people
like kim kardashian
Destroy the self image
of little girls everywhere.
- Hold on.
Are you saying that girl
Wants to go out with me?
- What—
what do you mean?
- And I said no?
Oh, man,
I gotta upload this,
And then go
buy her some flowers,
And then go tell her
I love her.
- Butters!
- Lisa?
Lisa berger?
Anybody seen lisa berger?
Oh, hey, eric.
Have you seen
Lisa berger anywhere?
- I saw that picture of her
you put on the internet.
- I know!
I'm gonna tell her I love her,
And we're gonna be together
and be happy forever.
- Uh, butters, I don't know
how to tell you this,
But lisa berger is
going out with clyde.
- What?
Since when?
- Dude, since, like,
noon or 12:30 today.
- Hey, token, token.
Check out my girlfriend.
- Wow, she's hot.
- Yeah, we just started
dating seriously.
You wanna meet
my new girlfriend, tweek?
- Oh, man, you're a lucky guy.
- Yeah, I know.
- Hey, clyde,
nice score dude.
Yeah.
- Oh, thanks, guys.
- Hey, stan, did you see
clyde's going out
With lisa berger?
- Yeah, dude,
she looks amazing.
Clyde sent me her pics.
She got really hot
all of a sudden.
- Yeah, I wouldn't mind
t—tappin' that ass.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, hey, wendy.
Clyde sent me these.
Don't be jel.
- Why would I be jel?
- Well, you got to admit,
Lisa berger's
pretty hot, wendy.
- She's not hot!
That's supposed
to be the point.
- She looks pretty hot here.
- Lisa berger is not hot.
She's fat and ugly.
- That's not
very nice, wendy.
- What's your problem, wendy?
- I'm sorry.
It's nothing personal, lisa.
- You're just a hater.
Why don't you mind your own
business instead of being jelly?
- I am not jelly!
I made that picture of you
to prove a point,
And it's being taken
the wrong way.
- It's okay, babe,
girls that don't have
What you have
are always gonna put you down.
- Thanks, babe.
- Now, wendy, I have tried
to be patient with you
Because you've always
been a good student, mkay?
But calling a little girl
fat and ugly is never mkay.
- Mr. Mackey,
I was trying to show kids that—
- No! No excuses!
You have a problem
being jelly, wendy, mkay?
Just maybe I should have you
sent off to jelly school.
- Jelly school?
- That's right.
In fact, I'm gonna call
the jelly school right now.
Mkay, I'm sorry about this,
but it's gone too far.
I've had it.
Hello, is this
the jelly school?
Mkay, I have a girl here
who's extremely jelly.
I was seeing if you could
take her in for a few weeks.
Mkay, you're full?
Okay, yeah, I guess she
dodged a bullet this time,
But she better watch
her jelly behavior.
- Mr. Mackey, I appreciate
the point you're trying to make.
- You—you do?
Mkay, well, I'm not
actually on the phone
With the jelly school,
wendy, mkay?
- Yes. I'm—
I'm a few steps
ahead of that, yes.
- Mkay, well, wendy,
I'm just trying to, uh—
Oh, bye, jelly school.
Uh, wendy, I'm just trying
to make you understand
How serious it is when you
lash out at other girls.
- Thank you, mr. Mackey.
I will change.
- Mkay.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
It is my honor to give
the person of the year award
To this year's winner...
Pope francis.
- Gracias, gracias,
all of my children.
- All right, hold up.
Hold up.
I'm sorry, pope,
but hold up.
I just gotta say this—
If my fiancee is a hobbit,
Then, uh—
Then what, bitch?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, if she was—
If she is a hobbit,
Then how come
she don't turn blue
When goblins are near?
Oh, you didn't
think of that!
Oh, I guess she's not
a hobbit then.
She must be
a beautiful, sexy woman.
- The hobbit doesn't
turn blue around goblins.
Just his sword does.
- Man, get the fuck
out of here,
You hobbit trivia bitch!
Who the fuck asked you?
Nobody is talking any more shit
about my woman, all right?
- She is gorgeous.
If she was here,
you could all see for yourself
How beautiful she is.
But she can't be here,
Because she has a movie
coming out on Friday,
Directed by peter jackson,
called the hobbit!
Hold up.
Bitch, that movie you got
coming out is called the hobbit?
Yeah, but it—
it's what?
Oh, yeah, yep,
yeah, I got it, yep.
Yep, let me tell 'em.
Love you too.
Kim is not even
in that movie.
That movie is just loosely based
on her television show
Keeping up
with the kardashians,
Which is a show about short,
loud little people
Living in a fantasy world.
Hold up.
Bitch, if you the hobbit, you
need to let me know right now,
Because I'm making a fool
of myself out here.
Yeah, yeah, do we rock?
Yeah, yeah,
take it to the top.
are we gonna stop?
No way.
- Cheer squad roll call!
- Heidi!
- Nicole!
- Bebe!
- Lola!
- Red!
- Annie!
- Lisa berger!
- And I'm your captain,
wendy!
- Look, wendy, we are all
very happy for lisa, okay?
Nobody here is jelly.
But the boys aren't even
noticing the rest of us anymore.
All we're asking is that
you do for us
What you did for lisa,
and help with our imperfection.
- I won't do it, you guys.
I'm sorry.
- Why?
Don't you care about us?
- Because it's wrong.
If you guys aren't happy
with the way you look,
Then that's your problem.
- Hey, girls.
Don't be sad.
If you want to look
really hot like me,
You just gotta be
willing to sweat.
Get down
to the gym and work.
- All right, girls,
we're gonna trim that fat
And tone those bodies.
Let's do this.
You first.
Get right up there.
All right, now,
look here.
Come on!
Burn it off!
You got this!
♪ you wanna look pretty
♪ you want a boyfriend
♪ you want a nice ass
♪ you better work out slut
♪ you want nice things
♪ you want boys
to give you nice things ♪
♪ you better work out, slut
- Look at those thighs.
Come on,
you gotta push harder!
♪ now get to work, slut
♪ party in the cookie trough
♪ you better work out, whore
- Wow.
- Wow, she looks great.
- Whoa, look at bebe.
I had no idea
bebe was that hot.
- Yeah, but did you see
token's girlfriend?
Wow.
- My bitch is still
the hottest, you guys.
- No way,
go back to annie nelson.
She's built like a slim-jim.
- Yeah, clearly annie nelson
Is the hottest girl
at our school.
Look at those eyes.
- Did you not see
erica smith's boobs, kyle?
They're like perfect
water balloons.
- I do love water balloons.
- Hey, wendy,
could I ask you a big favor?
- What?
- A lot of the pictures
I have of you are kind of
Outdated and, you know,
I want to be able
To show everyone
how pretty you are—
- So you want a photoshopped
picture of me
To take away any imperfections,
is that it?
How dare you, stan?
- Wendy, why is it
such a big deal?
- Because people should be
okay with the way they look.
I have pimples on my forehead.
My bottom teeth are crooked.
So what?
You have short legs.
- I do?
- Yeah, and jason
has freckles,
And billy turner
has narrow shoulders.
The cheerleaders—
bebe has acne
Lola's arms are too short,
nicole's eyes are puffy,
Annie has thin hair,
and heidi turner's butt is flat!
Oh, god damn it.
- You hater!
- Wendy, in my office
right now, mkay!
- Oh, yeah, babe.
Oh, yeah, baby.
♪ one thing I know
my girl ain't no hobbit ♪
♪ she might be stumpy
that don't mean she a hobbit ♪
♪ she's not a hobbit
'cause she couldn't be ♪
♪ she got no bagginses
in her family tree ♪
♪ yes on occasion she hangs out
with her dwarf friends ♪
♪ but she never went on
no quest ♪
♪ with her dwarf friends
♪ except for one time
she went to kill that dragon ♪
♪ she took his gold and she—
Hang on a minute, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Bitch, remember
when you went off
To kill that dragon
with them dwarves?
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Right, right,
right. Yep, I got it.
Yup, love you too.
♪ it wasn't no dragon
so my girl ain't no hobbit ♪
♪ that was a quiznos
and my bitch went to rob it ♪
♪ 'cause they got that ham
that she rubs on her cellulite ♪
♪ while she drinkin' her grog
and singin' those merry songs ♪
♪ at night
♪ my girl ain't no hobbit
♪ please god tell me
I'm not engaged to no hobbit ♪
♪ kim is not a hobbit
♪ who are you
yelling for south park ♪
♪ let's go cows
♪ who are you yelling for
♪ south park
let's go cows ♪
- Heidi!
- Nicole!
- Bebe!
- Lola!
- Red!
- Annie!
- Lisa berger!
- Wendy.
- she sucks.
- Oh, god!
- Ugh!
- Can we try this
without wendy?
- I agree.
- Hey, come on, you guys.
She just needs
more confidence.
It's okay, wendy.
Who cares if no one likes you?
Maybe you should
go out with butters.
- Let's just get back
to cheering, okay?
- I don't think so. We don't
want to cheer with a hater.
- Yeah, you have
a bad self image, wendy.
You need to get down to the gym
and get a better one.
- Yeah!
- That's right!
- See, the problem with having
fake pictures of yourself
Is that you start to
believe in your own bullshit!
This has gone way too far.
And if society won't fix it,
I will!
- What're you gonna do?
- Something that should've been
done a long time ago.
- It's the morning news
with tom and tammy thompson.
- A little girl
is making big waves
With her fight
against photoshop.
- Nine-year-old
wendy testaburger
Has started a campaign,
And tomorrow, will speak
before the state senate
To ban the use
of photoshopped images,
Saying they're harmful
to young girls.
Young lady,
what is your message?
- Watching what photoshop
is doing to society...
Little girls are aspiring
to have bodies
They can't possibly have!
We have to put a stop to it.
- And you're not just
being a hater?
- No.
- 'cause sometimes girls
who aren't well-liked,
You know, lash out
at pretty and popular girls.
Are you well-liked
at your school?
- Not lately, no.
- Uh-huh.
But you're not being jelly.
- No, that has
nothing to do with me
Wanting to protest against
photoshopped images.
- Okay,
because I do understand
That the jelly school
in aurora
Is ready to take you in,
is that right, rick?
- Tom, I'm standing
in front of the jelly school
Where officials claim
they do have room
For this little hater girl.
We're being told
if she doesn't stop the—
- That's not a jelly school,
that's a dunkin' donuts.
- Well, okay,
but you are a hater.
- That's fine!
People can call me
whatever names they want to.
I don't care.
There is a cancer
in our country,
And I am not going to rest
until photoshopped images
Are required to be labeled
for what they are—fake.
And nothing in this world
is going to stop me!
What do you want?
- "once upon a time
there was a little hobbit
"who lived in the forest.
"and all the hobbit ever wanted
was to be beautiful.
"and even though she was
short and fat and hairy,
"this little hobbit
dreamed that one day
She could be pretty
like beyonce."
"and then one day,
Along came a magic power
called photoshop.
"and just like that—poof.
The little hobbit was beautiful.
"and even though she still
couldn't sing like beyonce,
"or dance like beyonce,
or act like beyonce,
"or be a decent human being
like beyonce,
"the little hobbit
was looked up to and loved,
Just like beyonce."
"soon she had money
and adoration
And a hip-hop fiance
who loved her very much—"
I'm sorry, hold up.
hold up. I'm sorry.
"everything was good
for the hobbit.
"but then this mean little girl
called the jelly monster,
"she was so jelly
of the hobbit
"that she told everyone
she was a liar
"and the hobbit's fiance
realized she was just a hobbit.
"and you know what he said?
"he said, 'I don't care!'
"and then
the jelly monster came
"and tried to take
the magic powder
"away from the little hobbit.
"so the hobbit prayed to god,
and god said,
"'don't worry, little hobbit,
"I will go find
this jelly monster girl
"and I will read her a story
and melt her icy heart.
"and the hobbit said,
'thank you.'
"and the hobbit and god
lived happily ever after
In the shower forever
'cause I love her so much."
I'm sorry. Hold up.
Hold up. Hold up.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry
that I have been jelly.
- So hold up,
I'm sorry, it's okay.
Hold up. I'm sorry.
- No, no, I've been a hater,
and I really am sorry.
- I'm sorry, that's okay.
I've been jelly before too,
I'm sorry.