Unless we come together as a country
and realize that refugees from Syria
should be considered in...
Booo!
Boo, Wendy.
Boo Wendy Testaburger, boo.
Refugees from Syria should be considered
in need of international protection.
Booo, Wendy, boo.
Boo, Wendy.
The vast majority of refugees from Syria
are likely to meet refugees
boo Wendy Testaburger, boo.
Boo, Wendy.
Liar.
Instead of boooing my opinion
why don't you make
a constructive argument.
I'm not booing your opinion,
I'm booing your report topic.
No one even knows what a refugee is.
Booo. Booo.
Mr. Garrison can you do
something about this, please?
Mr. Garrison.
Sorry, Wendy.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
Next report let's have Peter Mullen.
Ugh, Jesus.
My report is on the vial
and despicable trash
that our parents are watching
on television.
Fellow students, there's a plague
of smut on our cable boxes.
Shows that figure reenactments
of unsolved crimes
and spousal homicide.
I'm talking of course
about murder porn.
Murder porn?
That's more like it.
According to the Neilson ratings
viewership in shows
like Cold Case Files,
Date Line Murder
and Deadly Affairs is sky rocketing
among married couples.
The increased viewership has brought about a
whole new slew of shows that use graphic sex
and innuendo to make spousal murder
more titillating
shows like Southern Fried Homicide,
Sinful Secret and
On The Case With Paula Zahn
and it's all smut
and garbage and it's trash!
Your parents are watching this stuff.
Go home and ask them.
And as we ask them
we must ask ourselves
if they're obsessed with
this stuff then how long.
How long before one of
our daddy's dressed up in lingerie
and bashes mommy's
head in with a brick?
Oh, crap!
Who could that be?
It's probably fucking Stan.
Hang a second, bud.
Come on in.
Hey, Stan, what's up.
His wife is having
sex with the neighbor
and when her husband comes home
he wants more than just a divorce.
You guys are watching murder porn?
Murder porn?
Stan, this is just
an investigative crime show.
I don't like documentaries.
Yeah, Stan. These are based
on real things like news.
It's informative. Parents
like informative stuff.
Okay.
Oh, we missed the murder?
Did he cut them up?
What's up, dude?
Dude, you know Aaron Hagan?
Yeah, the first-grader?
You should come down to his house.
His dad just killed his mom.
What?
Hey, that kid should
not be seeing this.
What happened?
You're making a mistake. Let me go.
It wasn't me I tell you.
A burglar broke in.
He was black.
He's the one who stabbed
that nagging bitch in her fat face.
He was black!
Guys, guys,
I know we're all concerned
but we have to work together.
How is this stuff allowed
to stay on the air?
The police found
hours and hours of murder
porn on the Hagan's DVR.
What more prove do we need?
I called them about
the smut out there
and they told me if I didn't
want my parents watching
then I should spend
more time with them.
Like it's my fault.
It's the result of a broken society
in which profit comes before morals.
Booo.
Booo, Wendy Testaburger, booo.
I know we feel our hands are tied
but we can do something about this.
There's an app to allow
kids to block things
their parents watch on television
and it's password protect
will with a security code
that only a child would know.
Tonight at 10:00 it's the tale
of love and seduction and murder
on sexy betrayals.
Then at 7, some like their murder
with a side of sexy ♪
on Southern Fried Homicide.
But now get ready for lust,
betrayal and murder on
Hot Load Case Files.
Oh, yeah, three of
the best shows in a row.
Is the lube over there?
It's over here.
Get over here, big guy.
Yeah.
What the... what the hell?
Yeah, hi.
We aren't getting
our informative murder porn.
No, none of the channels
with informative murder
porn appear to be working.
The screen says how do you
tame a horse in Minecraft.
Yes, we do have children.
A what?
A parental lock?
Stan!
How do you tame a horse in Minecraft?
What?
What is Minecraft and how
do you tame a horse in it.
You guys don't need to
be watching that stuff.
Come on, you can't
block your parents from watching
informative murder porn.
Think if we watch shows about
married people killing each other
we'll do it?
That's stupid.
I'm not going to go
out and kill your mom
because I watch
investigative discovery.
It'd be impossible to clear
all the DNA evidence anyway.
I'd have to kill
the person I hired too
because 99% of the time they tell.
I thought this through a lot.
Stan?
You're a lousy kid I wish
Jaden Smith was my son!
Who do our children think
they are blocking our TV content.
How are they able to do
this with their smartphones.
It's all right.
They think they outsmarted out but we
are the ones paying the cable company.
Can they remove it?
No, they did the usual
cable company runaround.
We'll see about this.
Excuse me,
our content is being
blocked and we need it now.
Sorry, sir, if you need it now
perhaps you should switch
to another cable company.
Oh, there's not another
cable company is there?
That's right,
we're the only one in town.
Look, if our kids can block content
then you must be able to block them.
As we told the other
sir we can fix it
but we just need to send
a technician to your house
to change out the cable box.
Great.
We just need a window
of time you can be home
how about between 6:00 A.M.
to 3:00 P.M.
all of November.
No, I can't wait around my house
from 6:00 am to 3pm all of November.
Oh, you can't?
Jeez, that's too bad.
You have to be home
for the technician.
Can you go to Direct TV?
I can't afford Direct TV.
Oh, you can't?
Geez, that's terrible.
I guess have you to work
within our time windows.
Well, any luck?
No, just the usual
cable company stuff.
Oh, well, I guess we'll
have to live without
our informative crime dramas.
Screw that.
Can we learn this Minecraft game
to get around
our kid's parental lock.
I tried.
It's unlike other video games
I don't get it
it's all retro like legos
and kids online called me
a grifer and kicked me off.
We can learn.
There's talk of a child
that he'll teach Minecraft to
anybody for the right price.
Hello?
Hi. Cory Lanskin?
Yes.
We heard that you're willing
to teach Minecraft to adults?
Fuck off!
We were told you're available
for hire and we're desperate.
You are still wrong, misser.
I'm a simple kit with a simple
passion for simple things.
We have 100 ounces of silver.
Wipe your feet and turn
off your cell phones.
Now, we're going to
select an empty world.
Selecting an empty world
will begin you being
dropped onto a beach.
Now you're free to roam around
and start punching trees.
Punching trees?
Why would we punch trees?
Just use your fucking brain.
How do you get wood?
Watching informative murder porn?
No, in the Minecraft forest
how do you get wood?
Punching trees?
Right.
You punch the tree to get the wood.
You get the wood to build the cabin.
Oh, I see.
When does the game start?
You are playing the game.
This is the game.
I don't get it.
That's because your think like a dad.
Minecraft don't have no winner.
No objective
you're just fucking building shit
and seeing if other things
can come and knock it down.
Now, let's click on the inventory
and build a ****.
Yeah, sir, I'm getting it now.
- You are?
- No!
Randy, it's getting late.
Let's just go to sleep.
I almost got it Sharon
I found out where the horse is now
I just have to figure
out how to tame one.
I'm not in the mood now anyway.
I miss being intimate with you.
Everything was so passionate
and then it just dropped off.
I feel like we're loosing our bond.
We don't have to have sex for
our relationship to be good.
I know but it's like
we're just good friends.
A marriage has to be more than that.
It has to have fulfillment of
fantasy and desire sometimes.
Magnacube? What the hell is that?
I'm going to sleep.
I'll wake you up if we get
our murder porn back.
There he is.
Hey Kyle,
the parental lock isn't working.
Our parents are still
watching murder important.
How do you know?
I caught my parents watching it.
from the cable company.
It's true. I walked in on
my parents watching **** ****.
They broke the parental lock somehow.
That's impossible.
Are you guys sure
you set it up right?
Guys?
Better get over here.
Butter's dad killed his mom.
Butter, what happened?
I was out by the lake and I saw
my dad out in this field.
He was holding sugar cane.
It didn't make sense
because he had a hammer.
I saw him take my mom
and yelled watch out for the creepers
but she fell.
Wait. You mean in Minecraft?
Yeah, then my dad went berserk
and threw me down a well.
I was trapped down there all night.
Your dad threw you down a well?
In Minecraft.
What the hell is that?
I was able to hoist myself out.
It was like I was frozen in the lake
he had no idea how to swim out of it.
It was terrible.
That's it.
That's how our parents
broke the pass code.
I never thought anyone
would stoop so low.
What do you mean?
Somebody's teaching
our parents Minecraft.
Hello sir.
Had an incident last night.
Wonder if you saw or heard anything?
No, what happened?
Someone broke into your next
door neighbor's backyard
dug up a bunch of holes
and punched his trees.
Punched his trees?
Yes, across the street,
someone built a cabin.
That's weird.
What were you doing last night?
I was just playing mine... my banjo.
I play the banjo too.
Well, thanks for your time, sir.
You may want to keep
the lights on in your yard tonight
in case someone tries to
build a cabin on it as well.
Will do, officer. Will do.
Calm down.
I know we're all concerned.
Concerned?
Thanks to you and your stupid app
parents are still
watching murder porn
and now screwing up Minecraft too.
I spent three hours
trying to get my parents
to stop create my castle.
When I finally got away from them,
I found they were taking all my ****.
Why did we agree to the stupid app?
We're trying to keep our parents
from watching murder porn.
Why?
Because one kid's dad killed his mom?
For all we know they were
doing drugs for year.
Maybe murder porn had
nothing to do with it.
I agree with Cartman.
Maybe we overreacted when...
Booo, Wendy, booo.
It's true.
Maybe we need to trust our parents
won't act out what they see.
That's enough.
Come on out and there
won't be any trouble.
Give it up.
You have nowhere to run.
Huh?
I'll never give up.
I don't even remember doing this.
Just leave me alone.
Nice one.
Your castle fucking sucks.
Go to hell you grifer.
All right. We have to do something.
Hello?
Cory Lanskin?
Yes.
We heard you might be
teaching Minecraft to adults.
Whassa Minecraft?
We're trying to keep our parents
away from graphic television shows.
It could be a matter
of life and death.
Don't be angry.
My mommy always angry.
Get back in the meat locker.
Ouchie, ouchie!
Mommy rape my no-no.
She loves me, right?
Mommy loves me?
I guess we have the wrong house, kid.
Okay.
Bye.
What, dude?
Something he said.
Did you hear him?
He said ouchie,
ouchie mommy rape my no-no.
If I'd be caught lying
that's exactly what
I would have said.
Now that you built a workbench
it's time to build something to
take care of those fucking sheep.
Stop using your grown
up brains and start...
Aha!
Son of a bitch.
Don't you think there
are enough grifers
in the world without
our parents being shown this stuff.
A kid needs to make a living,
don't he?
You have no idea what this is about,
do you?
We were using Minecraft
to block our parents
from watching spousal homicide shows.
Like Investigative Discovery?
So, you know it?
You have seen this stuff?
Real sick shit.
Your parents watch that stuff?
We put a stop to it
until you taught them Minecraft.
Your problem ain't with me, mate.
Sure, one or two people might act out what
they see in video games, but cable television?
People copy everything
they see people do on cable.
You got this all wrong.
You wants to protect your family,
you'll have to go fight
the cable company.
Hey, guys. Can I help you?
Hello.
There are certain networks
we see as harmful to our families
and we want them removed, please?
You don't want cable any more?
No, no, just I.D. Network,
A&E, Oxygen and Oprah's network.
All the ones with murder porn.
You don't like paying
for all the channels?
Our company actually
packages channels together.
Can you unpackage them
so we only get the channels we want?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Our company doesn't work that way.
You want me to give you the number
of a different cable company... oh,
wait, we're it, aren't we?
Dang it.
Guess you have to deal
with our packages.
Can we talk to your supervisor,
please?
Oh, sure.
Hey, David.
Is there a problem here?
We want specific networks
dropped from our cable.
You have to pay for the bundle
you can't just pay for what you watch.
Darn it!
You mean we're forced to
pay for the Oprah channel?
I guess if you don't want to be forced to pay for
Oprah you'd have to shut off your cable altogether.
Fine, then we'll shut
off our cable altogether.
Mitch, when can you get out
to shut off cable boxes?
Oh, man.
It's gonna be like three weeks.
There's a whole plug
I have to pull out.
It's like four inches long.
Three weeks, huh?
Is that okay with you guys?
No, that's way too long.
- Oh, it is?
- Geez, that's terrible.
Goddamnit I just don't want
my parents to murder each other.
Can't you see we're just trying
to keep our families safe.
I don't know if seeing
couples murder each other
on television will
make our parents do it
and we probably can't
stop them from watching
what they want to watch.
We're just trying to
make it more difficult
because cable makes it so convenient.
If they didn't have easy
access they'd be bummed out
but it's not
our responsibility to give them
what they want, is it?
Hey, say the last part again?
What?
What was the last part you said?
I said it's not our responsibility
to give them what they want.
The part about your parents got
getting the channels easily.
I said it would bum them out.
How much would it bum them out?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please Stand by for
an important message
from the president of
your cable company.
Hello.
In an effort to comfort the anguished
cries of children everywhere
your local cable company
has decided to drop
all networks
that **** spousal homicides
from regular programming.
Customers still wishing to
view true crime networks
will have to purchase
a separate package
which will require a technician
to service your cablebox every night
2:00 to 3:00 am and must include
the purchase of 300
channels in Portuguese.
We realize it may be
an inconvenience to you
and we hope you'll voice
all your concerns to us
because at your local cable company
the customer is always our bitch.
Jaden Smith lets his parents
do whatever they want.
You know what,
the guys at work took a bet
on who would win in a fight
you or Jaden Smith
and they said jadensmith.
He can kick your ass.
He does movies and he can sing,
and he's totally cool to his parents.
Then maybe you should go
live with Jaden Smith, dad.
I wish I could!
I wish I could with
him so I'd be rich.
I wouldn't have to live in
a boring sexless marriage
where all we do is
piss each other off.
Oh, crap.
Sharon, I'm sorry.
No, you're right, Randy.
Without any sex we just seem
to get madder and madder at each other.
No, you're right, Sharon.
We don't need murder porn to
find passion in our marriage.
We just have to get the spark back.
Let's go away somewhere, me and you.
Somewhere exciting and beautiful
where we can just focus on us.
Sharon?
Hey, sharon, are you here?
I'm here, Randy.
It's beautiful,
isn't it come over here.
I built us a fire.
Look what I got you.
Diamonds.
They're beautiful.
Thought I'd surprise you
and there's more where that came from.
I have a surprise too, Randy.
Oh, yeah, what's that?
Sharon what the effing fuck was that?
Sorry, couldn't resist.
Jesus, you stuck a pickax in my skull.
Oh, I did!
That felt really great.
- Felt great?
- Yeah!
Well, hold on, stay by the lake.
I wanna kill you know.
Okay.
Oh, my God. You put
that sword right through my face!
That felt so good!
- My turn again.
- Okay, hang on.
I've always thought about
murdering you in your sleep.
Can you go the cabin and get in bed?
Yeah, OK.
I'm in there now.
You lazy jerk!
You never do anything around the house!
You bitch!
- Oh, I love you, Randy.
- I love you too, babe.
Synced by yyets - Corrections by Mlmlte
WEB DL sync: VeRdiKT
www. addic7ed. com