Previously on
The Handmaid's Tale...
How was your trip?
I was in Mexico to coordinate
a trade delegation.
Something wrong?
You don't need to worry
about this.
We've got good men
working on it.
Don't you ever touch me like
that, when she's there.
I didn't mind it.
I don't think you did either.
Your time is running out here.
I was thinking maybe
we could try another way.
I couldn't say no when
Mrs. Waterford asked me.
I'm sorry.
We only wanted
to make the world better.
Now you have respect.
You can fulfill your
biological destinies in peace.
Biological destiny?
Children. What else
is there to live for?
Love.
Once.
Actually, twice for him.
Two times for me.
Almost three.
So close.
It doesn't matter.
It can never happen again.
Sorry, Nick.
Spick and span, girls.
He loves us for our labors!
Why do we have to do this?
It's fun.
Look, it's like painting.
They just want everything
to look pretty and perfect.
There are people visiting.
Foreigners.
Tourists?
That's kind of messed up.
No, like government people,
diplomats.
They'll be at
your house tonight.
How do you know that?
My Commander.
Small dick, big mouth.
It looks kind of weird without
all the dead bodies, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I guess you get used
to things being one way.
Hurry up in there.
Coming.
I left a clean dress for you.
Thanks.
As soon as you're dressed, Mrs.
Waterford wants to see you.
In her room.
Awesome.
I'll keep a good thought.
Mrs. Waterford?
All cleaned up?
Yes, Mrs. Waterford.
Good.
Now, we have some
important guests tonight,
a trade delegation from Mexico.
The Commander worked very hard
to arrange this visit.
We need to make
the right impression.
So, let's see you.
Turn around.
You're fine. Thank you.
Red's my color.
Well, that's lucky.
Our visitors may have
some questions.
They're curious about
our lives here.
I know that if spoken to,
you'll speak wisely.
I'll try to
speak wisely, Mrs. Waterford.
Please don't disappoint me.
Do you understand?
Yes, Mrs. Waterford.
You can go.
- You took your time.
- It's a good day for us.
I left as early as I could.
That's good, 'cause I have
a conference call at 4:00.
You know...
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm not your boy toy.
I need to be romanced.
Let us pray.
Maybe some flowers.
You could write me a poem.
It doesn't have to rhyme.
And the Lord God caused a
deep sleep to fall upon Adam,
and he took one of his ribs, and
closed up the flesh instead thereof.
Hmm. I like that skirt.
Focus, focus.
And the rib, which the Lord
God had taken from man,
made he a woman,
and brought her unto the man.
My bones, flesh of my flesh, she shall
be called Woman, because she was...
Therefore, shall a man...
Unto his wife.
They were naked,
the man and the wife,
and they were not ashamed.
May God bless this union...
And make it fruitful.
Amen.
They're through security.
Should be here any minute.
You look very handsome.
Thank you.
They're having dinner at the home
of a very powerful Commander.
Let them be nervous.
Blessed be the fruit.
May the Lord open.
How's your day going?
You look pretty.
Thanks.
I wore it just for you.
You shouldn't wear
anything for me.
Nick? Bring her in.
Deputy Ambassador Castillo, puedo
presentar our Handmaid, Offred.
May the Lord open.
No, Mrs. Castillo
is the Ambassador.
Mr. Flores is her assistant.
I'm sorry.
No apologies are necessary.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
May the Lord open.
We've heard a bit
about Handmaids,
but it's difficult to
separate rumors from facts.
That is why I'm so pleased we're opening
a dialog between our countries.
Offred, what is your given name?
From before.
I don't use that anymore.
Handmaids take patronymics, derived
from the head of their household.
Ofwarren, Offred, et cetera.
It's a symbol of their
sacred position.
Yes. I would like to know more
about your sacred position.
Did you choose to be a Handmaid?
Yes.
Well.
It's an enormous sacrifice,
what you're doing.
Handmaids are having children
for the entire nation.
Offred knows how grateful
we are for her choice in this.
Come.
Sir.
Pardon the interruption.
Ambassador, gentlemen, please
join us for some hors d'oeuvres.
Thank you, dear.
Shall we make our way, then?
Please, after you.
A pleasure to meet you, Offred.
Blessed be the fruit.
Under His eye.
Thank you for your time
and your thoughts.
You're welcome.
Might, may I ask,
and I apologize
if this is too personal,
but you have chosen
such a difficult life.
Are you happy?
I have found happiness,
yes.
I'm very glad, Offred.
Ambassador.
I'm so pleased and honored you've
traveled so far to be with us.
Por favor.
Everything looks delicious.
Gracias.
We've transitioned to a completely
organic agricultural model.
Impressive.
How is the harvest
in your country?
Ah, we have challenges,
like the rest of the world.
Most of our staples are not adjusting
to the new weather patterns.
Our citrus orchards in Florida
are doing really well.
Rita, could you check and see
if we have any oranges?
Yes, sir.
I believe we do.
Good.
I hope we'll find other valuable
resources to share with you as well.
God has blessed
our new nation...
Thank you... In so many ways.
Yes.
I'm curious.
Hmm.
How does the quiet half of
the room feel about Gilead?
It's absolutely wonderful.
Mrs. Waterford?
I am blessed to have a home and a
husband to care for and follow.
Traditional values are at the
core of everything we do here,
including trade policy.
"Never mistake a woman's
meekness for weakness."
Clever.
Yes, it is.
It's from A Woman's Place.
My wife's book.
I reread it on the plane.
Such a thoughtful argument for
domestic feminism,
as it was called.
Thank you.
That's very kind.
I heard you speak
once at a rally,
before the war,
you were very passionate.
Women were abandoning their families
and we needed to make a change.
We were running out of time.
You were arrested for inciting
to riot, if I recall?
I had a temper in those days.
Back then, did you ever
imagine a society like this?
A society that has reduced its carbon
emissions by 78% in three years?
A society in which women can
no longer read your book.
Or anything else.
No.
I didn't.
God asks for sacrifices,
Mrs. Castillo.
That has always been His way,
but He gives the righteous
blessings in return.
And I think that
it's safe to say
Gilead has been blessed
in so many ways.
Amen.
Shall we have dinner?
We shouldn't have
invited the wives.
It was a dinner at home.
Consider the optics.
If we don't make
progress on trade,
in six months our currency
will fall off a cliff.
Consider that.
Recounting your arrest record doesn't
do anything to help that problem.
You have meetings tomorrow.
You can talk about the issues, and
then we have the reception afterwards.
Waste of time.
I disagree.
Let's go over the details.
I'm sure you'll make it
all look perfect.
Hi.
You look tired.
We met until 3:00 a. M.
Colby and Harris had to
take the train in.
They're still being followed.
FBI?
I don't know.
Most likely.
Well, if they made it and you had
the full committee, what happened?
Nothing happened because all these
men know how to do is talk.
I honestly don't know if they have
the faith to see this through.
Hey, hey.
Come here.
We're going out.
No.
I have calls to make, and
I just wanna go to sleep.
I wasn't asking.
Thanks.
Thank you.
You sure this is big enough?
There is no problem that cannot be
solved with enough movie popcorn.
Did you make your proposal
to the committee?
Yes, if it did any good.
D6 and 7.
What about you? I've barely
had a chance to talk to you.
Did you turn in your article?
No, I'm still working on it.
But, you know, I was thinking,
fertility as a national resource,
reproduction as a moral imperative.
I think that's a really interesting idea
and it could make for a great second book.
Or not. I honestly didn't think that
I would ever write another book.
You should.
It's a great idea.
Okay. Okay.
Hold this.
What?
It's happening.
They issued the orders.
It's what we proposed.
Three separate attacks.
When?
Three weeks.
Congress first, then the
White House, then the Court.
Praise be.
Things have to change.
I know.
There's still going
to be a lot of pain.
There's pain now.
So much of it.
We're saving them.
We're doing God's work.
Hey.
He, uh... He wants to
see you in his office.
Okay.
It only makes it worse.
Did you see
the way she looked at us?
Like we were fucking freaks.
Who are they to judge us?
Half their population
is malnourished.
They've had four elections
in three years.
What are they doing
to save the planet? Hmm?
Not a single thing.
Can't they see the good work
we're doing here?
Am I boring you?
No. Sorry.
Being in here is a privilege.
I know that.
Time to go.
I'm sorry.
Can I...
Can I stay here
with you?
Please?
You want to stay?
Come.
Here.
Kiss me.
Not like that.
Like you mean it.
Sweet girl.
Big day tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
All right, girls.
When we are inside,
there will be
no wandering about.
You will stay
at your own tables.
We have tables?
Tonight you are guests,
just like everyone else.
This is not an excuse
to misbehave.
Girls, don't you all
look beautiful.
Mmm-hmm.
Line them up, please.
Now, Aunt, if you would.
All right, girls.
One line.
Neat as you please.
Very nice.
Lovely.
Please remove the damaged ones.
Mrs. Waterford, ma'am.
Whatever punishment these girls had
to endure was for the greater good.
They deserve to be honored
just like everyone else.
And we do honor them.
But you don't put the bruised
apples at the top of the crate,
do you?
No.
Quietly, please.
All right.
Come forward. Oflyle,
Ofthomas, Ofjohn, Oftim.
Ofwarren, you too.
Quick-quick.
Take them to the van.
No.
No, I want to go to the party.
- Ofwarren.
- No!
No!
Janine!
No, get off of me!
No, I didn't...
Janine.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I know.
I just wanna go to the party.
Ofwarren.
I know.
I didn't do anything wrong.
- Shh.
- I didn't do anything.
Janine.
It's not fair.
You're absolutely right.
But sometimes we have to do
what is best for everyone,
not what is fair.
Now, go with Aunt Dylan
and I will make sure you get
a whole tray of dessert.
You promise?
Cross my heart.
And hope to die?
Hope to die.
All right, girls.
Two lines!
Best behavior!
Praised be.
It's like a dream.
I think I went to
a Bat Mitzvah here once.
They won't let you speak.
I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
Thank you for trying.
I won't give up trying.
You should be a part
of these decisions.
I'm going to keep
telling them that.
No, don't. We need to work together
now, not argue amongst ourselves.
I'm going to see you at home.
We're moving on to the
security discussions.
Was she upset?
No, just frustrated.
She's been involved in this
from the very beginning.
Well, this is our fault.
We gave them more
than they could handle.
They put so much focus on academic
pursuits and professional ambition,
we let them forget
their real purpose.
We won't let that happen again.
Where are they?
They were supposed to be seated
when the Ambassador got here.
Patience. Even the righteous
need a little show business.
Good evening, everyone.
I want to welcome our guests.
Tonight is a celebration
of Gilead
and of what we have achieved.
We have made great strides
cleaning the environment,
and restoring a healthy
and moral way of life.
And we're very proud of what we're
leaving behind for future generations.
But we know that
none of it matters
if we cannot solve
our most pressing problem.
And we have finally begun
to do just that.
With God's blessing, and with the
devotion of a group of girls.
Please, stand.
Tonight we honor
your contribution.
And now, for our guests, we
have a very special surprise.
It is my honor to present
to you the children of Gilead.
All brought forth in this
district by our Handmaids.
Now, let's go and say hello
to the head table.
Looks like Waterford's
gonna get his trade deal.
What did they talk
about last night?
What?
I don't know.
You didn't hear anything?
Schedules, dates?
Why do you care so much?
What did you hear?
What does it matter how many
oranges we trade with Mexico?
You think they want
to trade oranges?
Don't be an idiot.
Gilead only has one thing
to trade that anyone wants.
Red tags.
What?
They want to trade us, dummy.
They want to trade
for Handmaids.
This can go to the trash.
This can come in here.
Just by the closet.
And those can go, too.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Does it, does it fit?
Well, you look very important.
Are you heading in?
Senior staff
meets at 10:00.
You should be coming with me.
So, what are your
plans for today?
I'm going to make
this place a home.
Tired?
The opposite, actually.
I don't think that I'll
be able to get to sleep.
I'm just glad that it went
so well. Congratulations.
You, too.
You should discuss
with the other Commanders.
See the best way
to move forward.
No.
They can wait.
The timing for implementation is the
most important thing right now.
You're an amazing woman.
I forgot.
We should...
We should stop.
No.
Hey.
Hey, what's going on?
I should've said something.
I should've...
I should've told her.
I should've told her
what they do to us.
You're being too hard
on yourself.
You were in a room full of Commanders.
No, I should've...
I said I was happy.
What choice did you have?
I can't be here.
Sit down for a second.
I can't. No, I can't.
Talk to me. Hey.
Offred.
If they find us here.
If they find us...
Offred.
If they find us together, I'm
gonna get sent to the colonies.
You're an Eye.
You're untouchable.
It's...
That's not true.
Fuck you, Nick. Fuck you!
They don't rape you, do they?
He doesn't come in here once a month
and read you a little scripture
and stick his cock up your ass?
I said I was happy!
Offred.
Don't call me that!
It is not my name.
Can I get you a glass of water?
It's June.
My name. It's June.
It's nice to meet you, June.
Here.
I'll let the Commander
know you're here.
Thank you. No rush.
We are a bit early.
Oh, good morning.
Blessed be the fruit.
You must be going on
one of your walks?
Yes.
Well, I better not keep
my partner waiting.
Of course.
Oh, um, I just wanted
to give you a gift,
um, to thank you
for your candor.
It was invaluable.
Mexican chocolates,
from my home town.
Thank you, for helping me
understand your world a bit.
Under His eye.
But you don't understand.
I lied to you.
This is...
A brutal place.
Offred?
We're prisoners.
If we run,
they'll try to kill us.
Or worse.
They beat us.
They use cattle prods
to try to get us to behave.
If we're caught reading,
they'll cut off a finger.
Second offense,
just the whole hand.
They gouge out our eyes.
They just maim us
in worse ways
than you can imagine.
They rape me.
Just every month.
Whenever I might be fertile.
I'm...
Sorry.
I didn't choose this.
They caught me.
I was trying to escape.
They took my daughter.
So don't be sorry.
Okay?
Please don't be sorry.
Please do something.
I...
Can't help you.
What are you going
to trade us for?
Hmm?
What?
Fucking chocolate?
We're human beings.
How can you do that?
How?
I am from Xipica,
Ms. Offred.
It is nice city,
maybe the size of Boston.
There hasn't been a child born
alive in Xipica in six years.
My country is dying.
My country's already dead.
Ambassador. There you are.
Is everything all right?
I was just giving Offred
a farewell gift.
I have one for
Mrs. Waterford as well.
That's very kind of you.
Please.
Straight ahead.
To the right.
Offred?
I have to go.
I want to help you.
I don't know where
your daughter is,
but I think I can get
a message to your husband.
My husband's dead.
Lucas Bankole,
born 29 April, 1980, in Nyack,
formerly New York State.
He's alive.
No.
I heard shots.
We don't have much time.
Please...
June.
Write something.
I'll try to get it to him.