♪ Edelweiss, edelweiss ♪
♪ Small and white ♪
♪ Clean and bright ♪
♪ Blossom of snow, may you bloom and grow ♪
♪ Bloom and grow forever ♪
♪ Edelweiss, edelweiss ♪
♪ Bless my homeland forever ♪
Come on. Sit down.
Hey, look at me.
You're going to be okay.
Here.
Drink this.
Come on.
What have I done?
You did what you had to do.
I killed a man once.
He was a... a hijacker.
He was going to shoot me.
He didn't know I had a gun in the truck.
How do you live with that?
It changes you.
But you go on.
You have to, Juliana.
You read my letter.
I got worried after you said you might not come back.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Look, you just, uh, try and get some sleep.
Yeah.
In the morning we'll get you home.
I can't go home.
Juliana, has it ever occurred to you
that maybe there is no contact?
That your sister would have walked
into the same trap you just did?
I got to do this.
I got to.
You know, that guy tonight
was most likely a Nazi agent.
I know.
Then you know both of us would be killed
if anyone found out what happened.
I never meant for you to be there.
I know you didn't, but I was.
Somebody's going to come looking for that man,
and we can't be here when they do.
Your sister Laura and her children
will be exterminated.
It's a lie, Frank.
That film can change the world.
Where is Juliana Crain?
Stay strong.
a woman who thinks you are a failure?
Tough choice, Frank.
Is it worth dying for?
What's wrong?
I lost something.
A drawing.
We got to get going.
Clerk's not up yet.
Here's your key.
Why? What are you doing?
Checking out.
Oh, no. That man dies,
and suddenly we just disappear.
How's that going to look?
Like we left.
We can't wait around here.
We'll leave— not in a hurry and not together.
Look, what if you drive out of town this morning
and I stay at the diner till after lunch?
Then I'll meet you.
Okay.
I'll wait outside town.
Where are you going?
To get ready for work.
Hope I didn't scare you.
- No.
- You okay?
Yeah.
Your door was open.
This was on your step.
Oh, Jesus.
They really did a number on this place.
What's it say?
You confirm these as the bodies
of Laura Frink Crothers,
Emily Alice Crothers, and John Thomas Crothers?
Sign here.
Mr. Frink?
As enemies of the state,
they've lost all burial rights.
They will be cremated
within the next seven to ten days.
You'll receive notice in the mail.
Hey.
Have you got a cigarette?
Yeah. Sure.
Hey. Hey, let me.
Here you go, pal.
What was that about?
It's better not to ask.
Jesus. Here by popular demand,
your occupying overlords
the Crown Prince and Princess.
Fuck 'em.
Come on.
We got to get to work.
I'm not going.
Frank, you didn't call in sick yesterday.
You miss today—
All right, I'll tell them that you're so sick,
you can't make it to the phone,
that you're puking up blood and organs and shit.
Sir.
Captain Connolly.
Joe Blake with a progress report, line 2.
Good morning, Joe.
Good morning, sir.
Still no word from our contact?
I don't know what else I can do
except show myself and wait.
What about your, uh, S.D. man?
The one who makes the origami?
No. He seemed to have left town.
Good.
So should you.
What? Why?
It's been two days, Joe.
If they were going to contact you,
they'd have done it by now.
So the mission's a failure?
Not necessarily.
You still have the film.
But just getting the film wasn't my objective, sir.
No.
No, it wasn't.
I don't understand.
What did I do wrong?
Perhaps nothing.
You'll have a full debriefing when you get back.
Do you understand me, Joe?
My orders are clear?
Yes, sir, very clear.
Heil Hitler.
Hello.
Frank, it's me.
Hello?
Yeah, Jules.
I've been so worried about you, Frank.
I tried to reach you a few times.
Uh, but there's no phone at the campsite, is there?
No. No.
Uh, there isn't.
You know, you left your necklace.
I figured if you saw it, you'd know I left.
I— I'm sorry, Frank.
Are you okay, Frank?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Frank—
I miss you so much.
Look, I got to go.
I— I love you, Frank.
Hello.
Uh, excuse me.
You know where I can find the attendant here?
Yeah, thanks, buddy.
Bucket.
Oh. Hey, Marshal.
What can I do for you?
Gas.
Hey, can I get s—
Who are you?
Nobody.
Is that your truck, nobody?
Yeah.
Let me see your I.D. papers.
There aren't any cops around here,
so the way I see it—
Okay.
Just let me get it out of the truck first.
What's in the truck, Joe Blake?
Coffee makers.
Right.
Hey, can I get some of that?
Bucket, you seen this fella?
I don't think so.
Who is he?
He's a friend.
Lot of guys look like him.
This guy makes little paper animals.
Oh. Yeah. I seen him.
Where?
Talking to Carl over at the bookstore.
Where are you going?
To get a cup of coffee.
Hey, Bucket, fill it up, will you?
I thought you were leaving.
Pour the coffee.
What's going on?
There's a man out there
with a sawed-off shotgun,
and he's looking for a friend of his.
That didn't take long.
He's going to figure out pretty fast
that that man's dead.
So what do we do?
We leave.
First we have to get rid of something.
I'll meet you out back.
Yeah.
You know, you should be careful
who you should make friends with out here.
You're not so bad.
Trudy, I'm not your friend.
Ah. There you are.
12 marks.
Shew.
You know how much a tank costs in the Reich?
You're lucky I got any gas at all.
Hey, who is that guy?
Calls himself the Marshal.
He's just a dirty old bounty hunter.
Likes to call himself that.
You'll want to steer clear.
Yeah. Thanks.
What is that smell in here?
How would you describe it?
I couldn't say.
Hmm. You couldn't say.
You probably spend so much time in here,
you don't notice.
The old books.
They got the stink of their owner.
Cigarettes and coffee, cat piss, smell of decay.
I'm looking for a friend of mine
who was supposed to meet me this morning.
He didn't show.
You seen him?
Y-Yeah, I did a couple days ago.
What did he want in here?
You don't want to lie to me, Carl.
Yeah.
H-He bought a Bible.
Tsk tsk tsk.
You're going around selling Bibles?
I need to find my friend, Carl.
I don't know where he is, I swear.
Hmm.
He send anyone else in here buying Bibles?
Um...
a girl.
Uh, she's in her 20s...
brown hair,
pretty.
And you wouldn't know
where I could find this pretty girl, would you?
No, I don't.
Selling Bibles is a risky business, Carl.
There isn't a law against it.
Only because there's no law around here,
it doesn't make it right, does it?
How many you got back there?
Six, maybe seven.
I— I'll burn them.
That would be wise, Carl.
That is your name, right?
Carl?
Y-Yes.
You sure?
You sure it isn't...
David?
David P. Frees?
Salem, Ohio,
escaped from a camp outside New Berlin in '54?
No, sir, that's not me.
I think it is.
I'm going to kill you now.
There's nothing you can say or do about that.
But I'm going to need something first.
Mr. Baynes.
Trade Minister.
It's a lovely day and a long time coming.
And you intend to proceed?
I need the name of my contact.
That man over there—
suit and blue tie.
He's Shimura, Science Minister.
What have you told him?
Nothing yet.
Is this some kind of a joke?
Mr. Baynes, you have not exposed yourself,
and neither have I,
nor will I until I must.
Which is when?
During His Highness' speech.
The Nazi Embassy.
In front of all those people?
The crowd will provide cover.
It's the only opportunity.
Hey, buddy, what are you doing out here?
Let me tell you,
12-hour flight from Tokyo,
I could use a belt.
Jesus, what happened?
You run into a pole or something?
They're gone, Bill.
You sure?
Laura's usually home by now.
They're not coming home.
What?
God, Bill, I am so sorry.
What are you talking about?
The Kempeitai, they killed them.
They— They just killed them last night.
The Kempeitai?
Yeah.
That makes no sense.
What the fuck are you saying?
The kids?
They— They said they were Jews.
But they're not.
Our grandfather was Jewish,
Laura's and mine.
So that means you're a Jew, right?
Why didn't they kill you?
I— I don't know.
Bill, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Get away from me, Frank.
- Please, Bill.
- Bill!
- I said get the hell away from me!
Listen up!
When I'm done,
tie him off.
Leave him here.
You understand?
Nobody cuts that body down
till the birds pick it clean.
We administered
200 micrograms of D-lysergic acid
30 minutes ago.
Advanced interrogation technique.
It's intended to break down inhibitions,
psychic barriers,
inducing a sensation of oneness.
Oneness?
Some describe it as an oceanic experience,
a unity with all things.
I fail to see how that would lead
to the disclosure of information.
In such a state,
the subject feels no reason to hold anything back.
There is no reason since he is
connected to everything and everyone.
Mr. Meyer.
How did you know the route
my car would be taking yesterday?
Do you have an informant in my office?
You have a halo.
The medication often induces hallucinations.
Tell me the name of your informant.
You're an angel.
Enough.
Will you bring him out of this?
I am deeply sorry, Obergruppenführer.
- I cannot do that.
- You can't?
Once administered,
it takes hours for the medication to wear off.
I see.
So this man tries to kill me,
and we reward him with an oceanic experience.
Will you tell me when this
little fantasy has worn off?
♪ Summertime ♪
♪ And the livin' ♪
♪ Is easy ♪
♪ Fish... ♪
I'll take care of this.
No, I can deal with it.
I did this.
♪ And the cotton is high ♪
We need to find his keys.
Do you think they're still on him?
They'd better be.
We need to move his car.
♪ Your daddy's rich ♪
♪ And your ma is— ♪
♪ ... good-lookin' ♪
♪ So hush, little baby ♪
- All right.
- Okay.
♪ Baby, don't you cry ♪
♪ One of these mornings ♪
♪ You're gonna rise up singin' ♪
♪ You're gonna spread your wings ♪
♪ And you'll take to the sky ♪
♪ You're gonna ride ♪
Got a light?
Uh, sorry, I don't smoke.
That's good.
You live longer that way.
Uh, look, I don't want to be rude,
uh, but I'm not in the mood for small talk.
I understand.
I don't blame you after what you've been through.
Sake cocktail, please, and some matches?
You're lucky to be alive.
That Kido released you,
but only because he still wants
to find your girlfriend.
Just get the hell away from me, all right?
I don't want any part of your movement
or whatever the hell it is.
If they saw me—
Jesus.
Tell me what Randall said to you
and to them.
Randall—
Well, Randall was in the next cell.
- He didn't say anything.
- You sure about that?
That's why they shot him.
Hey, relax, Frank.
We're on the same side here.
I am not on your side.
Your side got my sister killed and her kids.
My side didn't kill them.
The pawns did.
A lot of us paid a price like you, Frank.
I lost my husband and two brothers.
They— They come at us with guns and gas chambers,
and you, hmm?
You just aim a movie at them.
How about you put some of their
blood on the streets for a change?
It's not that simple, Frank.
We weaken the Japs too much,
and we're just begging Berlin to drop another bomb.
So you just watch old movies.
The films are more important than you know.
♪ So hush, little baby ♪
♪ Baby, don't you cry ♪
We are honored that you found time in your schedule
to visit with us, Your Highness.
The solidarity between our nations
is foremost in my mind, Ambassador Reiss.
And it's time we greeted our subjects
in the Pacific States in person.
Yes, which makes my next request very difficult.
We respectfully request
that the Crown Prince cancel his public address
outside the Embassy.
This is not a proper request
to be made in the presence of His Highness.
No, Trade Minister.
I want to hear why.
And I want to hear it from the person
actually making the request.
I have received word from New York.
The Resistance are stepping up their attacks.
I understand and thank you for your concern,
but my Imperial Guard and the Kempeitai
provide excellent security.
We have obtained evidence
that the Resistance are in
possession of false travel papers.
You have knowledge of such a threat
against the Crown Prince?
Not direct knowledge, no,
but the safety of Your Highness
is our paramount concern.
Thank you, Ambassador,
but I will address my people in person.
We ask that your guards remain vigilant, Mr. Tagomi,
because we certainly will.
Thank you for the tea and your hospitality.
Are you aware of any threats
such as Oberführer mentioned?
There are many threats, Trade Minister,
not least from Nazi agents seeking to destabilize us
and blame their crimes on subversives.
So you're comfortable with
the Crown Prince proceeding?
The Imperial Guard vouch for his safety.
And the false travel papers?
What about them?
Who might be carrying them or if in fact they exist.
Matters of internal security
do not concern the Trade Ministry.
Obergruppenführer, the subject is recovered
from his exposure to the D-lysergic acid.
He says he needs to see you and only you.
Hey, Mister.
Look at you.
You're looking for that man,
the one who makes the paper birds?
What if I am?
I know where he went.
Give me 2 marks, and I'll tell you.
You tell me or I'll kill you.
I saw him drive down that way
late last night.
What kind of car?
An old one, black.
Where was he going?
I don't know.
All right, let's go.
Hey, is this far?
It's a couple miles, maybe.
He marked it on the map.
What do you think it is?
I know what you're thinking.
We do not have time for this.
You don't have to come.
I'm doing this.
Hey, haven't you had enough?
Captain Connolly.
Mr. Connolly, please join us.
Yes, Obergruppenführer.
As you can see,
Mr. Meyer has recovered from his hallucinations.
He's just told me something very interesting.
I'm sorry.
What did he tell you?
He's named you as a conspirator.
That's r—
That's ridiculous.
It's obviously a lie.
Why would he name you?
I don't know.
I've never met this man.
An informant doesn't have
to meet his co-conspirators.
Sit down.
No, he just has to pass on the information.
What information?
The route of my car, Captain.
I've only been loyal, Obergruppenführer.
Whatever he said, he's lying.
Tell him now.
This— This man is lying.
I don't think so, Captain.
Mr. Meyer has given me a very detailed account
of how you passed on the information.
Explain yourself.
Obergruppenführer, I—
I-it's not true.
Just tell him it's not true.
Th-There's no proof,
just the word of this Semite.
Tell me, Captain.
I have nothing to confess.
- Tell me now.
- Please, this is a trick.
It's a lie.
Are you saying I'm a fool?
I've allowed myself to be deceived?
No, of course not.
So he's telling the truth.
He's not!
Please tell him you're lying.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You knew he was lying.
No. I suspected.
You may be relieved, Captain,
but we still don't know how they got to us.
Can I come in?
You want a drink?
I've just been to the Kempeitai.
They didn't tell me exactly what happened,
but they did say it wasn't about Laura and the kids.
It was about your crazy fucking girlfriend.
- It wasn't like that.
- This is her fault.
She and that sister of hers did something
and dragged the rest of us into it.
That's the only reason they're dead.
They tortured me.
They beat me.
For what?
For, uh, information I couldn't give them.
Couldn't or wouldn't?
I did not kill Laura and the kids.
The Kempeitai did.
This is their country, Frank!
Don't you get it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
You always wanted to have kids, didn't you, Frank?
Well, I hope you do one day,
and I hope they're taken away from you
like you took mine from me
so you could feel the same pain I'm feeling.
sail upon this ship do their duty
with honor and integrity
for the betterment of our glorious empire.
His Royal Highness the Crown Prince
and Her Royal Highness the Crown Princess
began the day at the Shinto Temple
in the Pan Pacific park
by making their offering to Amaterasu,
the Goddess of the Sun.
In one of the highlights of the Crown Prince's visit,
he will speak in front of the
Nazi embassy in a public address.
All subjects of the Pacific States are invited.
Pretty girl.
It should just be up through those trees.
Thanks for coming with me.
We shouldn't be doing this.
I don't understand you.
You would if you saw that film.
Yeah? A film that shows another world?
So what?
So it means that maybe things
don't have to be this way.
Maybe the world can change.
I don't see how.
You sound like Frank.
Well, I'm starting to like Frank.
You ever think how different life could be
if you could change just one thing?
Like what?
My dad died during the war.
And I don't know who I'd be if that hadn't happened.
Come on.
Hey, hold up a second.
Listen, I lied to you, too.
Maybe I'm following in my father's footsteps,
maybe I'm not.
I've never even met him.
He wasn't married to my—
my mother, and—
he doesn't live near us.
He never took any interest.
I'm sorry.
Whew.
Yeah, well, I don't know
why I felt I had to tell you this.
I'm glad you did.
You know, m-maybe you're right.
Maybe if I'd met you sooner,
my life would be a whole lot different.
Well, now you have.
Maybe it will be.
Hey, Frank.
What are you doing here, buddy?
I got to work to eat.
Well, good. Great.
Uh, did you tell Mr. Wyndam-Matson you're here?
Yeah, yeah. I told him.
Well, good. It's, uh,
good to have you back, Frank.
Really good.
That's got to be it.
Oh, my God.
Ugh.
That's a woman.
What is it?
It's their names.
Trudy Walker.
There's another name here.
Lemuel Washington.
That's my boss at the diner.
♪ Oh, it's ♪
♪ Nobody's fault ♪
♪ But mine ♪
♪ It's nobody's fault but mine ♪
Hey.
I want some meat.
♪ It's nobody's fault but mine ♪
♪ My mother— ♪
Ahem.
What kind of meat you got back there?
♪ My mother taught me how to read ♪
We got pork chops.
Pork chops?
I thought your people didn't eat pork chops.
The Koran says don't eat it,
not don't serve it.
Okay, then.
Very well done, like shoe leather.
And while you're there,
you can think about why you lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
You told me you didn't know
what happened to my friend.
I don't.
I suppose you don't know who this girl is, either?
Ahem.
Yeah. I know her.
I thought maybe you did.
Maybe you saw her with my friend
and clean forgot about it.
She used to work here.
She served him, I don't know, a couple of times.
- She worked here.
- Mm-hmm.
Where is she now?
Beats me, man.
She up and ran out of here this afternoon.
♪ I know it's nobody's fault but mine ♪
You can get my pork chops now.
♪ Nobody's fault but mine ♪
♪ Oh, good Lord ♪
♪ It's nobody's fault but mine ♪
Hey, Frank, what are you doing?
What does it look like?
I'm working.
That's, uh,
that's not a replica.
What are you going to do with that?
Go back to your station.
Buddy.
I said go back to your station now.
♪ It's nobody's fault but mine ♪
♪ If I die and I go below ♪
Who do you think that woman was?
She must have been a part of the Resistance.
Probably tortured her to get those names.
So then Lem's part of the Resistance.
Yeah, I think he's supposed to be your contact.
Why didn't he say anything?
I don't—
Ohh.
Get out of the car!
Run now!