"DUNKIRK"
Subbed by TobiHyde GuavaBerry
Edit timing by makoto77
You.
We surrounded you.
I'm English. Do not shoot.
Go there, take the weapon.
Do not be here.
Where is the air force?
The Navy asked for this.
We'll be back in 1 hour.
That was before.
Do not make a mess of
that stuff over there.
It's only for the English.
- Can not.
- We can not do this!
You have your own ship, back!
Back, you got your ship
Myself, this is a english ship.
Bring them here, quick! Move out! Move out!
Quick, fast, fast!
He will die!
Step aside, step aside, watch everything!
Get ready!
All in one! Give more space!
Move out!
It's medical, give them a way.
- Lower the rope.
- Yes, Sir!
Their fullness, no
Can you transport them?
I have something to say.
I thought you were cornered.
Give the room!
Go ahead.
Get ready up front.
Do not we wait for the navy.
We're just waiting for
orders, I'm not the captain.
OK.
Thank you George.
Heydrick, do you know where we are?
- France.
- No need to wait.
How is it there?
He's behind me.
I'll take care of him.
Go to the line.
You two go.
- Go away!
- We should check the damage.
You see..
Whose party is it?
Our plane, George.
3, 2, 1 now!
Did he fall?
Yes, he was destroyed.
Our fortress defeated him.
Fortress do you hear me?
Force 2 I have
See the plane, replace it.
Understanding Force 1.
Hello, lieutenant.
- We have to do that, sir.
- Well do that.
Go.
General, you have to decide how many
Many more have to carry the wounded.
No, tell them to
Line up here. Excuse me.
- Let me help you.
- Commander.
- What about our territory?
- Minimizes every day.
I have ordered troops
France to hold its ranks.
And his tanks were trapped.
Why get stuck?
They think the tank is too
Worth to leave the island.
How long do you think they can
Hold it before we get back?
Back? Nothing stops here,
We must bring back his troops.
- the next UK and other countries.
- Of course.
We will trust the troops
Bodyguards start from here.
- What?
- Home..
What about France?
We are asked to meet
At the meeting place.
Prepare the troops
We go together.
- And his new troop?
- We're leaving all.
How many troops
Who's he talking about, sir?
That's only one, 20,000
And we can give 45.
There are 400,000 troops
on this beach, sir.
We just have to do our best.
We can not stay here.
We have troops of distance
Far to the western part.
If there is anything else,
Bodyguards are here.
They will always be able
Prevent this place.
But it is not possible. Too low.
If there is anything to be able to accommodate They
though a small boat, will not Can make them a destroyer.
We will have to reduce that, gentlemen.
Hey!
Hey! Can you swim?
I can not reach it!
Hold on.
What is your name?
- There's a ship falling down below.
- Did you see anyone?
No .. We'd better leave it alone.
- You think he's okay?
- Maybe he should be all right.
Recording position
- 1071285.
- 10000?
Let's say 12 to 100 feet.
- Force 2, how much is your fuel?
- 50 gallons, replace.
50 gallons?
All right, keep telling me.
Because mine is broken.
- Do you think your fuel is enough?
- I do not know .. I can not see it.
- It will be destroyed!
- Thomas!
Go!
- It will be destroyed!
- Thomas!
What about the injured?
Hurry up! They will
Sink his ship!
Do you want to go inside?
It was much warmer.
A lot of wind here.
Leave him alone, George.
He feels safer here.
He wants to tell us
If we will be in bomb.
Human..
I'm still human.
Come and help me, George.
OK. We're out for 15 minutes
So it will climb to 2000, replace.
We need more fuel.
No, I do not want to be pursued again.
We'll go up and land there, change.
Understand. Angle 2, replace.
All right, up the stairs .. Let's go
Find you another ship.
Welcome.
Keep going down. Down.
Warm and comfortable down there.
Go downstairs.
Grab the blanket.
Make a space. Take a break.
Keep going down there.
So where's your friend?
Maybe we should Find a way out.
This place will be ruined.
Where are our goals?
Dunkirk.
No, they will
Waiting for us there.
We have to go to Dunkirk first.
I will not go back there.
I will not be back...
Look, if we go there.
We will die.
I understand, let's change
the direction of the ship.
I'm talking to you, hello?
You hear me?
- We have to change the direction of this ship.
- Yes.
This.
Your place over there.
Take a break.
It's safe here.
He seemed terrified.
He's in shock, he is
not like usual.
Maybe he will not
Back as before again.
This.
I have to lower my height.
40,000 feet.
Moves towards 9 o'clock.
Do not let them get mine.
- OK.
- You have to take the right side.
Let's go up first.
Now...!
Oh, my God!
I will fall.
Get out of there.
I'll try to land it.
Yes!
Please!
- Help us!
- Please!
- Please, someone!
Please..!
Please!
Torpedo...!
No!
What happened?
- Everything goes to the deck.
- Climb to the deck!
There!
Please!
Hurry up, George.
We do not have time.
- Did you see that?
- Like a Rolls Royce engine.
The sound is normal here.
Hello?
Open the door?
Hello, can you hear me?
Open the door!
You hear me?
- What is wrong?
- You're the one who locked him up.
Let him out.
I'll talk to him.
Let me out!
When I was your age, I went to war.
I'm still alive today
To see the children beperang.
There is something strange.
I will continue to follow him.
It decreases to a height of 15,000 feet.
Okay, I understand.
I've recorded it.
Gomez, you accept?
Hey, come on.
Come up.
Up!
- We'll help you.
- Please!
- They will attack again.
- No!
- Come here!
- They've drowned the ship.
You have to stay calm,
There are many ships here.
You have to help them all!
- You got a buoy?
- Correct.
The water is not too cold,
Just swim to the beach.
- There's still a place!
- Just go back to the beach and wait for another boat.
Or just wait here,
We will be back for you guys.
All ready?
Paddle!
You can not hide, son.
What do you want to do
there? Seriously.
You're not just an employee there.
Everything is drowning.
Not just you are stranded.
- We have guns.
- Yes, from the exchange of goods.
You can help us
On a rescue boat.
You fools.
I will not go back there.
- Playback.
- I will not spin.
Playback!
You're gonna kill us all!
- It is okay...
- Come on, turn back!
George?
George...
She fainted.
Okay, I'll take the medicine.
You'll be all right.
Hold on. Okay...
Okay, I'll keep him here.
This will stop the bleeding.
Yes, so...
Are you all right, George?
Push...!
It's okay, this is it
Part of his war.
You know, that's what I said.
How do you know?
His body was back.
Hey.
Hey, how's it going?
- Hey, how's it going?
- Do not worry.
Come on! It's tied up.
There's no way it can escape.
Do not be afraid.
Hey, young master Dawson.
You never Heard about them.
Are you ok.
Are you alright.
I let him go.
That's the only thing
I've done it for him.
It is okay. Drink.
I said I got him.
I did what I was taught.
I know one day I will do it.
You know, we can come back.
Maybe they'll see it.
Okay, take a break.
I want you back to
Deck as soon as possible.
- Uh ..
- What?
I can not say that.
Sir?
The French army already
Beaten back in the west.
- That's a good development.
- For now.
I want you out of the way.
Get out of the way!
- Where are they?
- They're coming.
No.
What? What?
I think we lost a ship.
The help is here. For
Do they save him?
The next troops,
Who helped England.
They sent her to the same place.
But it's there.
They can do it.
Silence alone will not
Helps us to return.
They have to send More ships.
If we are silent,
His enemy will draw near.
Back to the base,
Collect his soldiers.
- What for?
- At least that's what we can do.
Civilians? They
Will destroy it.
The more troops, We can win.
But not in this condition.
I prefer like
It is rather than dead.
They're here, they are
Will come here.
They come from the north.
At least we can get ready
To face them.
We're leaving in 6 hours.
I think in three hours.
That's good for your troops, right?
Yes. Of course.
- Where's the crew?
- Maybe apart after being stranded.
Let's check the beach.
- Why?
- Just do my commands.
Anything can be there.
Okay, we check the part
That part. On the other side.
How long?
Maybe 3 hours.
Put pressure on it.
Clean out the blood.
What?
Conditions are bad.
We have to go back.
We've gone this far.
What is our ship?
Right, we're going there.
No, we have to get ready,
There may be survivors.
If we do that, we must
Save ourselves.
I'm going up, looking
Whether they have come.
Am I talking too much?
They almost arrived.
Calm down. We'll be back, right?
Yes, but how long?
That's them!
Spitfire plane!
No, no..
- See what they do!
- Yes.
They show us direction.
Yes.
No, no..
They're heading to the Spitfire!
Get ready!
Hey..
- No, no, no.
- Who is that?
- Are you German?
- No, Netherlands!
I'm Dutch.
- I'm here to help you guys.
- How can we be sure?
I know the Germans are coming.
They waited on their shores,
Waiting for the tidal wave.
We will back.
They will come. We must
Sailing in a few hours.
A few hours? Why are you back?
I do not have anything, because
That's me not so go.
Seriously!
How's it going, Collins?
His plane crashed.
No.
It's because of the engine,
the engine is dead.
No ships.
Dad, come on, no boats!
- Maybe he's dead.
- Be quiet! I heard you!
Do not be noisy, shut up!
Maybe we can help him.
Do not! They do not know
We are in here.
Why are they shooting at us?
We must hide.
Tommy, you can do this.
Where are you?
They're coming ..
Come on, come on, come on.
We have to close it.
How to?
Come on. Hurry up.
How do we get out of here?
We have to open this place.
Wait! We have to wait.
- Wait. Wait.
- Yes.
Someone... Somebody has to get out.
Who wants to volunteer?
I do not need volunteers.
I need someone who is brave.
You're the one who goes up.
He's a German spy. Let him alone.
He's a spy and we're not
Telling him who he is.
Do you agree?
You do not speak English.
If he survived to
Germany, we will be finished.
Certain. Tell him.
Yes.
Tell me.
Tell me, Gibson.
Tell me!
For God's sake, just let me know.
Austin, he's with Austin.
Shit.
Damn coward.
It belongs to Gibson, is not it?
It belongs to British soldiers
Who is brave, not yours.
It is not worthy of your use.
He's my friend.
Maybe he killed him.
He... he did not kill him.
How do we know?
How difficult is it to find a corpse
British soldiers on the beach?
He did not kill anyone.
He's just like all of us.
I think he gave Code to them.
Try all sorts, And I'll shoot.
This ship is still drowning.
Correct.
We must trust each other.
When we get out of here
I will interrogate you.
Hurry up.
Come up.
When your head comes out
We will know it.
Are you guys, Or a real soldier
That is not fair.
Something to hold on
Life is never fair.
That's bullshit.
Hurry up.
I will not hesitate.
It represents thousands of people.
Shit.
He sent something to Lars.
I knew it.
Somebody has to get out
So we can all live.
Do you know what that means?
No. I do not know.
This is the price of lies.
I'll go with
he. This is wrong.
Hurry up.
With or without me
Will make a lot of difference.
Of course, if you continue to defend him
I also do not hesitate to shoot you.
Hurry up.
You are stupid.
Turn off the engine.
Thanks.
Sorry, I do not understand.
Maybe you're not proven guilty.
You've done your best.
Stop wasting time.
I understand your frustration, colonel.
Johnny.
The ship was attacked.
Looks like they're gonna head over here.
Here it is.
What do you see?
Hope.
Is she all right?
Son?
No.
No. She's not all right.
Exit!
There are people at sea!
Oil.
Oil. You are all exposed to oil.
They keep coming.
Do not hesitate.
All right, crack your hand.
Leave the boat!
Catch him!
Do not leave him!
Under the deck.
Sergeant, we have to save people
As much as possible before the oil
Reach us and make us burn.
Keep up.
Be careful down there.
He's dead, man.
Then be more careful.
Are you okay?
Son?
Nice.
The plane returned.
The plane is back!
Come on, their opponent, come on.
The ship!
- He'll turn around and fight them.
- Come on ..
No!
Let's go.
Street! Street! Come on! Hurry up!
Come on.
Thank you very much.
Where are you from
North Dover.
Make a deal.
Yes, sir.
Enter the ship into the port.
And thanks!
- That's an enemy plane.
- Yes. And that's in South, take me there.
This is an instruction from me.
Sailing to the South.
Now!
The plane was gone.
Yes there is a bigger fish to be fried.
How can you know that?
My son is often here. Me
Knew he had done it.
You ever come here?
No. Not me, my brother.
Hailed by the storm, died
before going to war.
Please, stay below.
I just want to see it.
Beautiful.
Is that Dover?
No, that's Dorset.
It's home.
We're going to your town, huh?
Oh God.
How can you get there?
Where are we?
They know where you are.
Just wait.
Wait for friends.
Wait a second, guys.
Just wait.
All we do is survive.
That's enough.
Just wait.
The beggar does not even
want to see our eyes.
Is there an officer here?
Any news from the enemy?
This is not the time to be special.
Just wait.
We lost 30 people.
And some others.
Nearly 300ribu.
So far.
So far?
I stay here.
For French troops.
Hey! Where do we arrive?
Sardines, we'll include them in a minute.
What station?
Wigan.
Give me the paper.
Come on.
DUNKIRK 35000 PEOPLE DISEQUIRED
Back home.
Finally.
Back home?
I'm selling a house on that street.
And I left it before the invasion.
It was a battle evacuation.
Do not see.
It was a winner inside
Terrible situation.
What happens to our troops should be celebrated
Despite what happened in France and Belgium ..
Is a big military fault.
You should expect an attack
as soon as possible.
To fight in France ..
To fight in the oceans and oceans.
LOCAL CHILDREN, GEORGE MILLS: NEW BERID
17 YEARS: BEING PAH ALWAN DUNKIRK
We must fight with trust
A thriving self and power in the air.
- We must defend our island,
Whatever .. - What?
We must defend our island,
Regardless of price to pay.
We must fight at the beach.
We must fight at the landing site,
On the battlefield, on the road, we should
Fighting in the hills.
We will never give up.
And even if, mostly
Has been conquered and hungry ..
Most have been conquered and starved.
Then the area of ​​our kingdom across the ocean,
Which is on guard and armed By the British fleet.
Will continue its resistance.
So with the power of God, the New world,
With all his strength and strength,
Step forward to save
And free the old.