Back then, I'd sleep and
I'd lay awake thinking
about women.
My daughter... my wife.
I mean, it's like... something's
just got your name on it,
like a bullet
or a nail in the road.
Shit.
Sorry. I drift...
sometimes when I've
had a few. That's...
That's why I like
to drink alone.
One reason, anyway.
About that
sculpture thing.
Hmm.
Kind of strange
it turns up like that
years later.
Yeah, nobody knew why
that thing was in the playhouse.
I mean, the aunt reckoned
maybe it was something
she made in school, you know?
VOICE-To me,
it was like someone was
having a conversation, you know?
Girl's... school
shut down in '92.
It closed down after Andrew.
That mean anything to you?
Oh, we notified
the deceased's mother.
Do you remember the last time
you saw your daughter Dora?
VOICE-It was
a horrible, horrible thing.
We saw it on TV,
what we're in the clutches of,
and I prayed and prayed
for that woman's family.
And it's me.
It's me.
Mrs. Kelly.
Hmm?
What about her father?
Did they have a relationship?
Why?
What have you heard?
I heard he passed.
Is that correct?
Why wouldn't a father
bathe his own child?
Ahem.
We, uh, we were just wondering
how they got on, ma'am.
He died on the road.
He drove a Peterbilt,
and he took an exit too fast.
Rolled over
near Rowan, Oklahoma.
May 11, 1984.
When was the last time
you talked to her?
You know, she's always been
in some kind of trouble.
I thought things were
getting better.
Got away from Charlie.
She came by not too
long ago, maybe a month.
She didn't talk
about her daddy none.
Said she'd been going to church.
Do you, um,
do you remember where
that church was?
Oh...
Mrs. Kelly?
No.
Ow.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Hail Mary, full of grace.
Mrs. Kelly...
I... I get
these headaches.
It's like storms. Oh.
I worked in dry-cleaning
for 20 years.
The chemicals.
That's what's wrong
with my nails.
Piece of work, huh?
My mother...
Donna Reed type.
Packed lunches,
bedtime stories.
Your mom still alive?
Maybe.
Cohle ever talk
about his parents?
VOICE-No.
Little bit about his dad.
Alaska, 'Nam.
You know, my dad, I had
about 6 inches on him,
and even in the end,
I still think
he could have taken me.
Yeah, Marines, Korea.
Never talked about it.
You know, there was a time that
men didn't air their
bullshit to the world.
You know, it just wasn't
a part of their job.
Well...
family.
Well, I mean, I...
I think a part
of Rust's problem was
there was things he needed
that he couldn't admit to.
Afternoon, men.
So we talked to the victim's
friend next, I believe.
Miss Carla?
I guess she always
had her mom's place,
but, uh, I thought
maybe she'd gotten
into somethin',
you know, like, uh,
like gamin' again.
Havin' a rough time.
What all did y'all talk
about? How was she?
Thin, loopy,
like high,
usually on somethin'.
She says she
found a church,
but, uh... heh!
Her eyes.
Somethin' wrong with 'em.
Now, do you remember
where this church was?
No.
You know where she might
have been staying?
Her landlord said she'd
moved out last summer.
That's when I stopped
seein' her so much.
She mentioned someplace
down south,
like around Spanish Lake, a...
shelter, girls used
to stay there,
something, all she said.
Hmm.
She sounds sad, Marty,
like a torn-up person
on her last legs.
She was just
an easy target for him.
What do we know about him?
Hits prosts, artistic,
religious in some kind of way.
Every person within
a thousand miles of here
is religious in some
kind of way, except you.
How many DBs have antlers,
blindfolds,
painted symbols
on their back, hmm?
Yeah, you know what
tweakers get up to.
Shit, man, this dude
in New Orleans
cut up his girl, felt remorse,
tried to piece her
back together
with Krazy Glue.
That's just drug insanity.
Ah, that's not this.
This has scope.
Now, she articulated
a person with vision.
Vision is meaning.
Meaning is historical.
Look, she was just chum
in the water, man.
Days of nothing.
That's what it's like,
you work cases.
Days like lost dogs.
Goes on like that.
You know the job.
You're looking for narrative,
interrogate witnesses.
Wake up, Daddy.
Parcel evidence,
establish a timeline,
and build a story day after day.
No! No!
Hey, the other night,
when you were over for dinner,
why didn't you leave
when I had Chris call?
Mmm, I don't know.
I guess I had
sobered up a little.
Besides, it wasn't
as bad as I thought.
And being around your family,
I liked talking to them.
"Bad"?
Why'd you think that?
I was married, Marty,
for 3 years.
We had a... baby girl.
She died.
Car accident.
She was two years old.
Marriage couldn't handle it.
Your kid died?
Oh, I...
I'm sorry, man.
I am so sorry.
I didn't...
No, I mean, it wasn't
you guys. It was just me.
I was worried...
you know, being around
that kind of thing.
Hey, you were married
the once, just the once?
VOICE-Uh-huh.
Came close another time.
Laurie.
Maggie introduced us,
and it... it broke off.
It was for the best, you know.
I gave her cause.
I can be hard to live
with. You know, I...
I don't mean to,
but I can be... critical.
And sometimes
I think I'm just
not good for people,
you know, that it's
not good for them
to be around me.
You know, I...
I wear 'em down,
you know, they...
they get unhappy.
Hmm.
Yeah, I think the job does
that to a lot of guys.
Changes you. Some guys
just notice, that's all.
Well I can't say
the job made me
this way.
More like me being this way
made me right for the job.
And I used to...
think about it more, but...
you know,
you reach a certain age,
you know who you are.
Now I live in a little room
out in the country,
behind a bar.
Work 4 nights a week;
in between, I drink,
and there ain't
nobody there to stop me.
I know who I am.
After all these years,
there's a...
there's a victory in that.
Third day
on the job,
stopped this cutie for speeding.
52 minutes later,
back in her dorm room.
I got my...
uniform around my knees.
Ha! I'm occupied,
so I don't hear
anything.
I don't know that her
roommate has come home
and snuck up behind us.
Oh, shit.
You know how I knew that
she was in the room?
She stuck her finger up my ass!
Ruined me. Now I can't
do without it.
You miss some things on the job.
You know what I mean.
You got to... decompress
before you can go being
a family man.
What you get into working,
you can't have
the kids around that.
So, um, sometimes you got
to get your head right.
Mind if I stop by?
I don't know. Where are you?
Elks.
So you're drunk.
No, I'm not,
and I've hardly had
anything to drink.
You never hardly have
I have a surprise for you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Is that a yes?
I, uh, might stay up.
Ah.
It's for your wife
and kids, too.
You got to take your release
where you find it
or where it finds you.
I mean, in the end, it's for
the good of the family.
What's that?
Oh, well, I, uh,
got you a present.
Don't move a muscle.
I shan't.
Just the fingers.
The finger muscles.
Mmm.
Oh, stop.
Oh, you're very naughty.
Yes.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will
be held against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you can't afford an attorney,
the state will provide you one.
Do you understand your rights?
You definitely
have a career
in law enforcement.
Well, I thought I was
gonna put these on you.
You want this?
Ah.
Yeah?
You want it?
Yes.
Mmm.
Now, what do you mean, exactly,
these visions you mentioned?
Oh, shit. I thought you knew.
I told Marty about them,
you know, down the line.
Uh, chemical... flashbacks,
neural damage, you know,
from my time in the HIDTA:
as in High-Intensity
Drug Trafficking Area.
I spent 4 years undercover.
You know what that means?
That's where they got them
Fed rumors, I first come in.
What, you two
don't know about them?
Those files are still
sealed, huh?
Shee-it.
Just what have you two
heard about me?
You wanted blues?
Quaaludes.
Downers?
Dopey stuff.
Oh.
What's it run?
I'm thinking blue go
for three a pill.
We'll say 200 for the bottle.
I thought you might
just take 'em.
Or that you wanted
somethin' else.
Some kind of somethin' else?
No.
Then I was thinking,
you're a good-looking man.
You wouldn't need
a shakedown to get some.
What about
rough trade,
scary guys?
You girls talk.
Around here, they're rough
or whiskey-limp.
Seen plenty of guys
that get touchy.
Something sets them off
and they're like
little boys.
People always go away
around here.
Where would I look,
working girls might know
the blonde?
If she was gaming I-10
south side, I heard
of this place.
Kind of trailer park.
Girls work and stay.
They call it "The Ranch."
Where's that?
Like, south of Spanish Lake,
supposed to be.
You know the place?
What's your deal?
I don't have a deal.
I mean, what do you do?
Never mind. I thought
you were gonna bust me.
I told you, I'm not interested.
Yeah, I know.
Kinda strange,
like you might be dangerous.
Well, of course I'm dangerous.
I'm police.
I could do
terrible things
to people...
with impunity.
You know,
what'd you do
last night?
I called up here late.
What were you doing?
Working.
Was thinking about dropping by.
Where were you?
I was out with girlfriends.
Uh-huh. Well,
I don't like that.
What, you're jealous?
Don't be stupid.
I just mean that there's
a crazy man out there,
and he's killing women.
Wait, you mean that girl
again, that Satanic thing?
Everyone's still
talking about that
at the courthouse.
It's not just her.
There's more.
There's more?
Really?
Yeah, well, we're not saying,
keeping it out
of the press, but...
we're thinking that
he's been doing this
a while.
Wow.
Yeah, so no need to go out.
You just have a drink here.
I can't meet a nice man at home.
That hurts me
when you speak to me
in a passive-
aggressive way.
I always talk straight to you.
Excuse me. I meant that
since you're married,
I need to be
considering my options
as a young woman.
I want things, Marty.
I want things, too.
Yeah, you just want your cake
and to eat it, too.
How good is cake
if you can't eat it?
Mmm.
Morning.
Hey, I think I might have
found something good.
Bunny ranch down south,
round Spanish Lake.
I thought we were
pulling old johns today.
Yeah, we should do this first.
What?
You wash up.
You got some pussy on you.
Key to a healthy marriage.
Oh, that's Maggie, huh?
Hey.
What's with your fucking nose?
Nothing, man.
Sorry. Forget it.
I get a connotation
being implied here
about my wife?
Are you saying that's wife,
that high tide you're
walking in with?
You got some idea
how my wife's pussy's
supposed to smell?
No, I just meant you're
wearing the same clothes
as you did yesterday,
coupled with the fact
that I ain't stupid.
Wasn't making no comment
as to the...
particularity of the scent.
You don't say fuck-all
about my wife.
Don't say her name.
You got
some self-loathing to do
this morning, that's fine,
but it ain't worth
losing your hands over.
How would that work, exactly?
Well, I'd just apply
a couple pounds of pressure,
snap your wrists.
You're Senior Detective.
Think I'm lying?
You got a specific
location for this place
or are we just gonna
wander around
till we find it?
We got some names.
I'm gonna have to ask
for directions.
Maybe you could just
follow your nose.
Wherever he picked them up,
I mean, I won't lie.
However we left it,
he had some moves.
He knew a few Cis
from his narco days.
They knew these parts,
put us in touch
with some names,
people to talk to.
How we doing, boys?
Hey.
Hello.
We're looking for
a little bunny ranch
down around these parts.
Y'all know where
we could find it?
No, sir.
Never heard
about it?
Little whorehouse?
Nuh-uh.
Sorry, man.
Supposed to be stuck up
in the woods around here?
And I'll tell you this,
Rust had about as sharp
an eye for weakness
as I ever seen.
I'll be right back.
It's my bad, boys.
Think we got started
on the wrong foot there.
Aah!
You remember where that
little whorehouse is, huh?
Take 353 South.
Gonna exit off the shoulder
before we get to the 14.
From there, we take
a dirt fishing road
to Bayou Chenault.
OK.
That it?
Mm-hmm.
Cop car, y'all.
Just trying to get
some freebies.
I don't do no cops...
Hello, ma'am.
Martin Hart,
Rustin Cohle... State CID.
This your place?
It's my lease.
What is this, some kind
of hillbilly bunny ranch?
Excuse me?
You might want to talk
to Sheriff Bilson
'fore you start tossin'
accusations around.
No, I ain't got nothing
against hillbillies.
Relax.
That's not why
we're here. We, uh,
well, something
happened to a girl,
and we need
to know if any
of you knew her.
Yeah. That's Dori.
Somethin' happened?
You know about
that woman found
outside of Erath?
Oh, no.
Did something
happen to Dori?
Were you pretty good
friends with her?
She was nice to me when
I first came around.
Gave me tips and stuff.
Tips? About what?
Nothin'.
You know, just how to be.
You got any idea where
she might have been staying
the last few weeks?
I don't.
Her ex is in prison.
I guess maybe
she got a new place.
She'd been going to church.
I was hoping maybe
she just turned
things around.
We're gonna need
to question any girls
might have known her.
That's a tougher ask
than you think.
Folks'll be stayin' away,
they hear y'all
are out here.
Well, ma'am,
it's the best way
to get us to leave.
You said she left a bag.
Yeah.
Can I see it?
Sure.
That girl's not 18.
The sheriff know you got
underage working here?
What do you know
about where
that girl's been,
where she come from?
You want to know
Beth's situation,
'fore she ran out on her uncle?
There are other places
she could go.
Such holy bullshit from you.
It's a woman's body, ain't it?
A woman's choice.
Well, she don't look
like a woman to me.
At that age, she is not equipped
to make those kind of choices.
But I guess
you don't give a shit
what kind of damage
she's doing to herself,
as long as you're
making your money.
Girls walk this earth
all the time
screwin' for free.
Now, why is it you add
business to the mix,
and boys like you can't
stand the thought?
I'll tell you.
It's 'cause suddenly
you don't own it
the way you thought you did.
Ahem.
Ma'am, you've both
been very helpful.
We'll be in touch.
Yes, thank you...
for your help.
Do something else.
That a down payment?
Is shitting on
any moment of decency
part of your job description?
"I closed my eyes
and saw the king
in yellow moving
through the forest."
This is her diary, Marty.
Believe this shit.
A girl that young.
You know the sheriff
has got a stake
in this place, too.
Fucking Christ.
"The king's children
were marked.
They became his angels."
The yellow king, Carcosa.
Nut job.
Fried her brain on
whatever she was on.
Sounds like she
didn't have much
to begin with.
Well, it reads like a fantasy.
What if he was
dosing her regular,
and over a period of time,
upping the dose
little by little
without her knowing it?
We should stay out here
today, check around
for johns
maybe knew her.
Look at this.
Oh, yeah.
Man, a lot of these type places.
Expect the flock
to canvass for 'em.
You know, we should go there.
Could be the church
everyone mentioned.
Well, let's check
around for johns
while we're out here
and pick up the church
on Monday.
Most of your stuff's
still redacted.
Now, what's Northshore?
Northshore Psychiatric Hospital,
Lubbock, Texas.
I spent 4 months there in '93.
You feel like talking
about that?
Well, sure.
Who gives a shit?
Sofia... my daughter.
She was on her tricycle
in our driveway. Um...
We lived down a...
where a little bend
in the road, and...
They said that...
Anyway, afterwards, uh,
Claire and I turned
on each other, you know?
We... we resented each other
being alive, you know?
I transferred
from robbery to narco.
Started hitting it,
you know, 24/7.
Street rips, knocking down
doors, and within 3 months
I was ripping off couriers
or ending up in a Ramada Inn
with a couple
of fuckin' eight-balls.
Oh, yeah.
Somewhere in there, Claire left,
and somewhere in there,
I emptied a 9 into a crankhead
for injecting his infant
daughter with crystal.
Said he was trying
to purify her.
State attorney gave me
one chance to stay out
of jail.
He said, "You can keep
your profile, but we want to
make you our wild man junkie."
So they did. They made me
a floater, like a trick.
You know, any agency
or department needed
a deep undercover narco,
they got me,
and there was no fuckin'
expiration date, baby.
And they kept you
out there for 4 years?
Mm-hmm.
And then, February of '93,
I killed 3 cartel men
in Port Houston.
I took three 25s
in the side and ended up
at Northshore Psychiatric
Hospital in Lubbock, Texas,
which is kind of funny
in its own rite...
Psych ward being
in Lubbock, Texas. Heh!
You ever been there?
They offered me
a psych pension.
Jackpot, right?
And I said no.
I said, "Put me
on homicide somewhere."
By then, I was owed
quite a few favors,
and, uh, Louisiana was
what they had.
Yeah, for a long time after,
I... I didn't really sleep.
Nightmares, PTSD:
exhausted nerves, whatever.
Yeah.
Why homicide?
Oh, something
I saw at Northshore.
Quote from Corinthians.
"The body is not
one member, but many."
"Now are they many,
but... of one body."
What's that mean, though?
I was just trying to stay
a part of the body now. Heh!
The fishing
pole's not working.
Just ask Grandpa.
No.
Yeah.
Grandpa, I can't tell
if it's working.
You'll know, honey.
It'll yank at you hard.
OK.
Why don't you...
How's that case going?
The big one?
Working it, you know.
Things like that didn't
happen these parts
when I was young.
People said "ma'am"
and "sir."
Families stayed together.
Yeah, that's how
it was, huh?
Not all the time.
There was more dignity.
Everyone wasn't out
in the street, yelling
about their rights.
Well, if things were so great,
they never would have changed.
Hmm.
Nothing is going on.
I'm just saying,
if there's a problem,
you can talk to me.
You know that.
If I have a problem
with someone, I talk
to them, Ma.
Well, you should be able
to talk to me.
I know what it's like
to be married to a man.
You think they're all
the same, huh?
I don't know why you're
so rude to me.
If you're frustrated,
don't take it out on me.
I think that you need
to get your cable fixed
and stop confusing me
with your soap operas.
Well, you beat up on
what you can't control.
Makes it bad for everybody else.
I don't know how.
I don't care.
Just try.
You do it.
I can't.
You have smaller fingers.
Macie, just do it.
So you're telling me
the world isn't
getting worse?
I seen kids today, all in black,
wearing makeup,
shit on their faces.
Everything's sex.
Clinton.
You know, throughout history,
I bet every old man
probably said
the same thing.
And old men die,
and the world keeps spinning.
How are the girls?
I got this lead...
I got this lead
I wanted to check up on.
I told you about it.
Maybe your dad
could bring you back.
No.
You didn't tell me
anything about it.
This is a family day.
I did tell you about it.
I mentioned it.
It's the new case.
OK, well, how about we
all head back, then?
Hmm. All right,
sweetheart.
Come on! Let's go!
My line's tangled.
Just paddle in.
OK. Told you!
Thanks for
the lovely afternoon.
Oh.
Thank you.
Afternoon, sir.
How you doing
today, officer?
I have a question for you.
You ever seen this girl?
You never seen her before?
Never before.
Hm-mmm, not here.
Question.
I'm looking
for this young lady.
You recognize her?
I might need a memory jog.
Dora.
Young blonde?
Dora. Dora, Dora,
Dora, Dora.
Dora.
Have any guys come
around lately,
looking for anything
more than a good time?
You might be able
to remember for
a little more money?
I might.
You might?
Years we've been through this.
Sweetheart, listen to me.
There is nowhere else
I want to be.
I wonder if you even
know you're lying.
Oh, come on!
Shh.
Bad enough,
the shit I got to wade
through on a daily basis,
bring me this
"feel bad for me" crap
when I work 30 hours
straight and spent
the weekend
listening to
your dad's bullshit?
I come home, the one place
where there's supposed
to be peace and calm,
and you throw this shit...
Who told you that?
It's not always that way.
It's not supposed to be.
It's supposed to be
what I want, it's
supposed to help me.
We do help you!
All the goddamn time!
OK, well, what do you
want me to say?
You want me to talk about
the woman, had antlers?
Do you want me to tell you
about the kids disappearing,
and maybe you'll stop
with the "poor me"
little whiny bullshit?
Is that what you're saying, hmm?
That I'm trying to make
you feel bad for me?
Is that really how you
want to play this?
No, honey.
I think you're
the greatest woman
I ever met,
and you're the
greatest thing that
ever happened to me.
But, yeah, you know, sometimes
I think you might
have a penchant
for self-pity.
And right now,
I need you to be strong
so that I can do my job.
You have developed
some sort of
selective deafness.
You used to not be such
a chicken shit, I swear.
Even your mom thinks
you're a ball-buster.
Tell the girls dinner.
Mmm.
You don't have
a mommy or daddy anymore.
Yours just died in an accident.
How?
In a car accident.
Someone...
Dinnertime, kids.
Go to the kitchen.
Are you coming?
Yeah, of course.
I'm starving.
Really?
- Yeah, really.
- Good.
You know how I think
about my daughter now?
You know what...
what she was spared?
Sometimes I feel grateful.
Doctors said
she didn't feel a thing.
Went straight into a coma,
and then, somewhere in that...
blackness, she slipped off
into another,
deeper kind.
Isn't that a beautiful way
to go out? Heh!
Painlessly,
as a happy child.
Hmm.
Yeah, trouble with...
dying later is you've
already grown up.
Heh! Damage is done.
It's too late.
You got kids?
Mmm.
Well, you got the hubris
it must take to...
yank a soul out of nonexistence
into this meat.
And to force a life
into this thresher.
And as for my daughter,
she, uh...
she spared me the sin
of being a father.
Hey, Cathleen,
you little vixen.
Any chance
of some coffee?
Of course.
OK.
Who are these guys?
Some assholes
Quesada brought in.
Coffee on its way.
Hey, morning, Marty.
Hey.
Major's
introducing me.
New flying squad.
You know
Mark Daughtry,
Ted Bertrand.
Daughtry.
Ted.
Jimmy Dufrene.
What's up?
We've been tasked
with investigating crimes
with possible occult links.
There's been a rash
of animal mutilations,
cemeteries defiled.
And they want
to see what we have
on the Lange case.
Uh-huh.
Well, this task force is
important to the commander
and to the governor's office.
You know, a lot of people
are concerned about it.
You know, me, I don't
see the connection
between two dead cats
and a murdered woman.
But then, I'm from Texas.
Heh!
We're not stepping
on your toes, Marty.
We just got the mandate.
We got to compare notes
with what you got.
Yeah.
Here you are,
Detective.
No. Oh.
Thanks, Cathleen.
You got it.
Xerox all you want.
Make you feel like good cops.
You two, my office.
Cohle, we got
a new rule around here,
especially for you.
You got an opinion
about anything,
you hold on to it.
You hold on to it
or you tell it to Marty.
Otherwise, button
your big, fat mouth.
However smart you are,
you're not as smart
as you think.
Be serious, boss.
This God-bothering shit.
It's a political
circle-jerk.
You know this.
Is this a place you live?
Where are you, huh?
You had anything
in the last weeks?
You got a suspect?
Give us some more guys
to follow up KAs, track records.
No, our bosses don't want you
at all, you understand?
I don't want you.
You are upright only by
the grace of this man's
reputation.
Goddamn, Cohle.
How many ways
are there for me to say,
"Shut the fuck up"?
I mean, we work
under command, right?
Now, our betters want
a public, high-profile
show of response.
Shit, I got a state senator,
he's trying to label
Satanic graffiti
as a hate crime.
That has nothing to do
with our DB, and that's
the fact of it.
OK, OK. Fine.
Let's say that's true,
all right?
Let's say that you guys get
the case all to yourselves.
You ever solve a murder, been in
the red more than a week?
You ever clear one where
two rounds of questions didn't
hand you the fucking answer?
Oh, come on...
No, no, you got leads,
you got a timeline.
You know what I got?
I got a whodunit
where my two detectives
are stalling,
and I got a brand-new
task force wants to
take it off our hands.
We have a lead...
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Fuck off, Cohle.
Christ.
It's your call.
You want to dump this one off?
You know, I'd think about it,
given the spotlight.
You know, Teddy Bertrand's
a good detective.
You know him.
Well, you're a smart-ass
with your mouth shut.
I was just gonna say
we've got a lead on a church.
Our vic was spending
a lot of time there.
That's where we were headed.
It could be the break we need.
Inside, whatever they're
putting over you,
how much more time
could you get us?
Right now, it's up
for discussion, but,
you know, Tuttle's lighting
a fire under this.
Without a suspect,
they're just gonna
stop asking questions, Marty,
and they're gonna give orders.
That's that.
Give us the rest of the month
before they lump it
into whatever
the play is with
the task force, yeah?
I'll try.
Two weeks, and then you two
start catching again.
Yeah.
Let's cut to the point.
As the crow flies,
y'all are wanting to ask
about that big throwdown
in the woods, yeah?
Eventually, sure.
Right now,
we're just trying
to track the case.
How Cohle worked it, especially.
Which indicates you think
I'm too thick to realize
that y'all are trying
to jam somebody up.
You're on to something new.
So Cohle
didn't want to give it
to the task force.
Did you?
No, I did not.
It don't make sense.
There is nothing out here.
According to this map,
it should be within
these few miles.
Well... ahem... I guess
if it's one of those
tent revival places,
they move around.
Yeah.
Tents usually do.
There's no date on this
flyer, which is strange.
Something up there.
Wait, wait, back up.
Are you saying you were
hallucinating on the job?
Mmm.
No. I mean, I could
always tell what was real
or what wasn't, you know.
So when I'd see things,
like, man, I'd just...
roll with it.
You still see things?
No.
No, they stopped altogether
after I was clean
a couple years.
No numbers
on this place.
Fire must have happened
a long time ago.
OK.
Place is trashed.
This ain't no kinda anything.
Yeah, back then, the visions.
Yeah, most of the time,
I was convinced
that I'd lost it.
Marty?
But there were other times...
I thought I was mainlining
the secret truth
of the universe.