You look like you're
doing all right.
Father Time has
his way with us all.
Looks like you must
have pissed him off.
Ahem.
Why we here?
I got a thing
the State PD's asking about.
The Lake Charles murder.
I mean, shouldn't it
have been in the paper
to draw a line somewhere by now?
I mean, we can't trust them.
And, I mean, if they're
gonna cover something
like that up,
who knows what else
they've covered up?
What you think?
I think you don't look
particularly healthy.
Listening to you talk,
your eyes, you seem
kind of brittle, Rust.
Most of the last decade
I spent stone-drunk.
Functional, but hammered.
Went back to Alaska,
spent 8 years working
fishing boats, bars.
Oh, I thought you didn't
like the cold.
I hate it.
And then I come back
here to Louisiana for
the first time in 2010.
And why is that?
The same reason
I'm sitting across
the table from you now.
A man remembers his debts.
I don't dwell on the past.
Well, it must be nice.
I'm not interested
in whatever it is
you think you owe me.
Oh, I don't owe you.
We left something undone.
We got to fix it,
and I've been working
on this for two years.
Me, myself.
Never called you,
I never bothered you
with it...
Yeah, why would you?
Shit, man,
what did you do?
Alienate every other
person in your life,
and then finally
you came back to me
in the rotation?
You know, not for nothing,
but if you wouldn't have
clipped Ledoux back then,
we might have got
the whole fucking
story out of him.
You know, I think I'm
gonna finish this beer
and say so long.
Now, I'm not much of
a drinker nowadays.
In fact, I hadn't had
a drop in 3 weeks
till I ran into you.
Well, I don't need you
to drink, Marty.
I need you to help me.
Why would I?
They say you can't
account for your time.
They got eyewitnesses
placing you
at the Lake Charles crime scene.
You got some
storage shed that you
won't let them look at.
That's right.
Why not?
Why not shoot
straight with them?
You're innocent.
Help them stop
wasting their time.
Fucking since when
did guilt and innocence
define the State PD, huh?
Come the fuck on.
Now, I don't know
the sprawl of this
thing, all right?
The people I'm after,
they're all fucking over.
They're in a lot
of different things,
pieces, family trees.
The only way for you
to understand
what I'm on to here
is for me to show you.
You got to come see what I got.
No. You know what?
I don't think I've
been very clear
with you, Rust.
If you were drowning,
I'd throw you a fucking barbell.
Why would I ever help you?
Because you have a debt.
You got some fucking sack.
What's that mean,
I have a debt, huh?
Means the way
shit went down in '95,
this is on you, too, buddy.
What do you got to show me?
What you packing?
.38.
Hollow-point?
Yeah.
That'd do it.
You never be too careful.
All right.
Remember, there was
no physical evidence
connecting Dora Lange
to Ledoux's place
out in the woods,
meaning it probably
didn't happen out there.
Nobody was in a hurry
to bring that up.
Two... women and children
gone missing,
all taken from areas
within a 10-mile radius
of schools that were
funded by Tuttle's
Wellspring initiative.
We establish a connection.
Who's in, who's out, you know?
I mean, do people disappear
in equal numbers in
other parts of the state?
How many schools
were there?
14.
Now, I've covered
a surface area.
I pulled runaways in state
and missing persons,
and if you'll notice,
there's twice as many
along the bayous.
I don't know why.
Hell, someone should do
a study as to why.
Well, now you're just
throwing up stats.
Why was Tuttle
so interested in
the Lange case, huh?
Remember
Charlie Lange said
what Ledoux told him?
Said there's a group
of men, sacrifices.
Well, I think Tuttle
recognized the scene.
That's why he came down
there jiminy quick with
a fucking task force,
and that's why
he tripped out when
I talked to him in '02.
OK, so what happened to him?
I mean, I'm looking around here,
and I don't see or hear anything
that doesn't make this
all conjectural.
1988.
Accusations of child molestation
at a preschool funded by Tuttle.
Name of that school
is Shepherd's Flock.
It shuts down,
reopens two years later
on Pelican Island
under the name Light
of the Way Academy,
where Rianne Olivier went.
And I got
an enrollment list...
16 kids in the class.
One of them turned out
to be a young man
who'd just showed up
for solicitation in New Orleans.
Now, this is 2010.
His name is Toby Boelert.
Goes by the name
of Johnny Joanie.
Shepherd's Flock?
Why are you asking me
about that place?
You know, after that place
shut down, there was a lot
of talk going around.
You ever see that reverend...
Billy Lee Tuttle, around?
You know, I think so,
but who can remember
way back?
That's how it all started.
Memory be fucked.
I decided it all had
to be a dream anyways,
and I don't remember if it...
We'd go to sleep,
only sometimes I didn't
feel like I was asleep.
I felt like I was
still awake, but I
must have been asleep
because I couldn't move.
Just... sort of see
under my eyelids.
And what?
I don't know.
There were men...
taking pictures.
Sometimes...
other things.
Who were they?
I don't know.
They had animal faces.
That's why I decided
it had to be a dream.
They had animal faces,
well, it had
to be a dream.
Any other kids see this?
One girl.
I don't remember her name.
She first started
talking about it.
And she seen it, too, the faces.
I do not remember her name.
Marie Fontenot?
Maybe.
You ever see any of
these men's faces?
Once.
They didn't all have
animal faces.
Three younger men.
I don't remember them.
Just one.
He had bad scars
all around his mouth,
like the bottom half
got all burned up.
You know what?
I thought that man,
he was a dream, too.
No, I don't think
he was a dream.
I don't understand.
Are you saying that you think
that this hypothetical killer
was, uh, an old schoolteacher?
Or it might what,
involve State PD?
Goddamn. What happened
to you, man?
Remember him? Hmm?
Yeah.
Yeah. You and I were on
the case in Erath.
Girl comes forward
and says she was chased
through the woods
by a spaghetti monster
with green ears.
Now, I think
that this is our man
with the scars on his face.
We got 3 references
17 years ago: that old
revival church said
a tall man with scars
came through,
Kelly Reider in the hospital,
and now this hooker
from the quarter... Toby.
I don't know who he is,
I don't know where he
is, I don't know where
this whole thing
fucking starts,
but it ends with him.
All right, you know
the little township
down around Erath?
All right, that's
where the Tuttle
family is from.
Now, it used to be
a pirate hideout,
then turned
into plantations
and whatnot.
Had a very rural
sense of Mardi Gras,
uh, you know,
the men on horses,
animals masks, such.
Courir de Mardi Gras.
That's right.
Now, they had
an annual winter
festival.
Went heavy on
the Saturnalia,
a place where
that Santeria
and Voudon all
mash together.
Have a look.
From the winter festival.
Blindfold...
antlers, mask.
I got these from a series
an artist did in Kenner,
right after Katrina.
Says he kept
running across these
"stick things,"
as he called them.
Look familiar?
Think our man had a
real good time after
the hurricane...
Chaos,
people missing, and people gone.
Cops gone.
I think he had a real good year.
What do you need me for?
You got friends on the force.
You have access
that I don't,
databases.
I need case files.
I need missing persons.
I need homicides.
I need
title transfers,
auto and home.
I got a list of names.
I'm gonna need
background checks,
tax records,
anything we can get on Ledoux.
Jesus Christ, man.
I wouldn't have called
you and I wouldn't have
fucking bothered you
if State wouldn't
have pulled me in on
this Lake Charles case.
Well, if you need help,
why don't you just
give it to Papania and Gilbough?
No, they may be pawns
in this thing and not
even fucking know it.
Come on.
Look, Eddie Tuttle is
the goddamn senator
of this state.
The late Reverend
Billy Lee Tuttle
is his cousin.
I'm telling you, it's
a fucking family thing.
That's what I mean
when I talk about
the sprawl, Marty!
Eddie Tuttle's the reason
that the Lake Charles thing
never made the wire.
Look, man, you have
some compelling stuff here
and you might have something,
but...
all this... this...
The "sprawl,"
as you call it, which
I would call conjecture,
this shit about
the Tuttles,
the State PD.
Do you know
how fucking crazy
that sounds?
It's like you've been
alone too long, you know,
like you maybe told
yourself this story
and kept drinking
until you believed it.
Marty...
I had my time where I
wondered if this was
all in my head.
That time passed.
Really?
What happened
to Billy Lee Tuttle?
There's something you're
gonna have to look at.
No other way around it.
You still take
your coffee black?
Oh, uh, green tea,
if you have it.
I've been trying to stay
away from coffee,
you know,
a little bit healthier.
So, Mace... is she, uh,
back from Chicago yet?
Mm-hmm,
3 months ago.
3 months.
Uh... and what
was it, that...
Americorps.
Oh.
Teaching.
And Audrey,
how... how's she?
She's fine, at the moment.
She sometimes decides she
doesn't need her meds.
I like her boyfriend.
He watches out for her.
She had an art show
in New Orleans,
sold some paintings.
Oh, that's good.
That's great.
I should buy one,
I mean, if I can afford it.
So the reason I, uh...
I mean, like I said
on the phone, I...
I want to ask you
about those cops.
They just wanted to know
about you and Rust.
Mostly Rust.
They wanted to know about
the fight in '02.
Mmm, did you tell them?
No...
but they think Rust
did something.
I know.
He didn't.
I didn't think he did.
Have you...
talked to him?
No, not since.
Have you?
Yeah, I mean, after
they brought me in.
Yeah.
How is he?
Different, same.
I mean, he's lived rough
for a long time now.
He always did, it seemed like.
Taken a toll.
He needs my help.
Are you gonna help him?
Yes.
Why?
I have to.
Well, what is it?
What do the police
think he did?
I can't talk about that.
It's PI stuff.
He's hiring the firm,
I'm hiring him.
All this time, you two,
and just...
Just like that?
Oh, I took some convincing.
I looked in Billy's eyes.
He looked in mine.
He got me suspended.
Now, Billy Lee Tuttle
owns 3 houses in Louisiana.
One in Shreveport,
one in Baton Rouge,
one in New Orleans.
Also one in Florida.
I waited till he went
on his spring ministry
tour, 2010...
Look, Rust, I changed my mind.
If you did something,
I don't want to hear
about it.
Remember I told you
about my stint
in robbery?
I make a pretty ace B&E man.
Now, I staked
his places out for weeks.
Checked surveillance,
map security.
I found ingresses.
Now, here I am, you know.
My whole life is just one
expanding, circular fuck-up
and I think it's about
to close out with me getting
clipped in a home invasion.
I mean, what I'm saying is
I was aware that I might
have lost my mind.
But after the second home...
doubt got taken behind
the woodshed and put down.
Notice he never reported
the Baton Rouge break-in,
just the Shreveport house.
Found those in the safe there.
Paper stock's over 15 years old.
Goddamn it.
These...
they aren't as bad
if you don't know what
you're looking at.
Motherfuck.
And...
there's a videotape.
Take a look.
No!
God!
Jesus!
Ohh!
Fuck!
You watch all of that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I had to,
see if any of the men
took off their mask.
None did.
Oh, fuck.
I won't avert my eyes.
Not again.
Jesus Christ.
That little girl is
Marie Fontenot.
Did you kill Tuttle?
No.
I assume that
he was thinking he was
gonna be blackmailed.
And I think some
people took him out
after they found out
what was taken
from the safe, before
he had a chance to.
What... can I do to help?
We start by pulling
everything there is
on Dora Lange.
And I got names,
I got family members,
Tuttle connections.
Any information that we can get
on Reggie or Dewall Ledoux.
All right,
we can coordinate
out of your offices
if you want.
You shouldn't have that.
Nobody should have this.
I'm glad
that you're doing
good, Maggie.
It seems like
everybody's happy,
you know.
It's... ahem.
It's good to see.
Thank you
for everything.
I haven't seen you
in over two years,
Marty.
Did you come here
to say good-bye?
Thank you, Maggie.
I mean that.
There's not gonna be
a bunch of people
coming in and out of
this place, is there?
What do you think, Rust?
Practical terms,
we're doing an identify
and locate.
Now, I can't afford
to subscribe to all
the databases that I used to,
but I got Auto Track XP
for motor vehicle records.
I got Flat Rate Info
for the QI National
People Locator,
public records, of course.
All right.
That sounds good.
How you been? Ahem.
You know, besides work,
what do you do?
I'm sorry, I just...
I don't ever remember
you asking me
a personal question before.
Uh... you know,
I just stay busy, uh,
fish, girlfriends.
You seeing anybody?
Not really.
Some dates.
You know, it's all
pretty casual.
I did have something
going for a while,
this Filipino girl,
but that didn't pan out.
Quiet life.
I don't stay out late.
I just... I go home.
You?
Ah, I'm about the same.
No girlfriend.
Just go to work, go home.
How about that girl
you were seeing in '02?
What ever happened with her?
Yeah, that was never gonna last.
Never should have started.
Yeah. Boy.
She, uh, she had problems.
Oh, you always liked them crazy.
Yeah, that I did.
Why'd you quit, Marty?
Yeah, you could have
been boss, you know.
LT, at least, captain.
I did another 4 years
after you left, and I...
I guess the job
just kind of ran
its course with me.
How is that?
I was gonna play
baseball, ride bulls.
You know, you end up becoming
something you never intended.
Uh, I guess you never
really even know why.
I suppose I could
have been a painter,
you know, a historian.
Old scenes, new details.
Yeah, yeah. You do
much painting?
Nah.
Little late in the game
to start something
like that, I reckon.
Life's barely long enough
to get good at one thing.
If that long.
Yeah, so be careful
what you get good at.
What do you call
a black man who
flies a plane?
I don't know.
Pilot, you racist bastard.
What else would you call him?
Well, speaking of,
you know, I been taking
some writing courses?
Heh heh!
And, uh... no.
I have, and I been
tinkering around
with this thing off and on.
True crime.
And that's the genre,
not the title.
You serious?
Yeah.
You know, what happened
in '95 and some other
old cases,
and all I need from you, Bobby,
is some old copies
of case files.
You still like your
single malt, don't you?
Ah, I guess I do.
Oh, business gotten
so bad you got to
become a writer?
Nope, I've always
wanted to do it.
I just never had the time.
And regards the files,
I'd like to avoid
Fuck and Suck,
the two dicks I spent
last Saturday with.
Hmm. Papania
and Gilbough.
I hear ya.
'Course, man.
Whatever you need.
Ah!
Appreciate it, Bobby.
Not a problem.
Missing persons, mostly.
Maybe far back as the eighties.
Well, anything
before '05 that never
became part of an
official investigation,
it isn't gonna be
in the computers.
You're gonna have to
sort through the files.
Thank you.
Found something, background.
Dewall Ledoux
transferred title
on a truck
to a Jimmy Ledoux.
Appears like that
might be a cousin.
I found him in White Castle.
Owns an auto shop.
All right.
Did you pull that
Marie Fontenot file?
There wasn't one.
Report's gone.
Backtracking that.
Marty, this
is Robert Doumain.
He owns the place.
Hey, how's it going?
Nice spot.
He's not a cop no more, Robert.
You got something against cops?
Bob had a little boy.
Been missing since '85.
Sorry.
Jimmy Ledoux came up spotless...
3 kids, wife's a teacher.
He coaches his boys'
pee-wee football team.
Any relation?
So many Ledouxs around,
I never had to worry
about a connection.
But, yeah, my dad's
second cousin
or something.
My pops didn't like them none.
Said they weren't
white enough
to be white trash.
What's this about, exactly?
Man asked us
to locate his daughter.
It was a long time ago,
but it looks like she
might have known Dewall.
Sorry to hear that.
Must know what happened to them.
Sick shits.
Pop said they died too quick.
Is there anything
you remember that you can
tell us about these guys?
Just they were nuts.
Looked at you funky.
Reggie was always
asking about the
girls in my school,
and couple times I
saw Dewall, he just
said kooky stuff.
Any chance you ever saw
a third man with them,
a man who had a bunch of scars
on the bottom of his face?
It's weird you say that.
I remember that face.
My pop let them use
our deer camp once.
Took me with him.
I was, like, 11.
They were maybe
10 years older
than me.
They introduced us to the guy.
His face, underneath
his nose and cheeks,
scarred.
Gave me funny looks all night.
Every time
I glanced at him,
staring at me.
Any chance this man
with the scars was
another Ledoux?
No. I don't know.
I don't think so.
Next morning, men were
too hung-over to hunt.
Pop and I went home.
You, uh, ever see him
again, guy with the scars?
Never again.
I'd remember.
Fuck, I don't like this place.
Nothing grows in
the right direction.
Where'd this woman come from?
Tax records.
Drew a paycheck from
Tuttle's father.
Uh, some kind of domestic.
How'd you find her?
Well, had to get federal
income tax records
from '40 to '59.
I matched Social
with a credit check run
in the late nineties
for Section-8 housing
in Alexandria.
Mmm, good job.
Look at you. Heh!
Hmm.
High praise from a bartender.
Cops.
She gets tired easy,
'specially hot as it is.
Now, I don't understand
what this is about.
Thank you.
We're private investigators,
hired to do, uh,
ancestral research.
M-mineral rights
along the coast.
Hmm.
I never knew
them Tuttle people,
but I heard stories.
No, thank you.
You think she might get
some money out this?
Uh, quite possible.
Depends on what we find out.
Miss Delores?
You worked
for Mr. Sam Tuttle
19 years, right?
Yes.
Erath.
Mm-hmm.
Then Shreveport.
So you knew his son,
Billy Lee, right?
Mm-hmm.
A cousin, Eddie?
Little boys, mm-hmm.
I remember.
What about extended family?
Cousins, you know,
that might have been
close to the boys?
Those days,
families were bigger.
Oh, all sorts
of brothers, cousins,
kids just running around.
Did, uh, Sam Tuttle have
kids outside
his marriage that
you know about?
Hmm!
Don't you know it.
Now, people kept
their own back then.
I mean, a man's house
was his own.
Mr. Sam?
He had lots of children.
All types.
He didn't like a woman...
See, once she had it
done to her,
he didn't like them
but that one time.
Not after that.
Hmm, and out
of all these kids
running around,
you remember one
that maybe had scars
all across the
bottom of his face?
I... I think that was
Mr. Sam's grandchild.
His daddy did that
to him, that poor boy.
I... I think that child
was a... a Childress
or what, Fi, he was
a LeBeau or a Childress?
From Mr. Sam's
other family?
I shouldn't be talking
to you about this.
That's OK.
Miss Delores.
Could you have a look
at something for me?
One thing.
Just have a look.
See if you recognize it.
You know Carcosa?
What is it?
Him who eats time.
Him robes...
it's a wind of invisible voices.
Mineral rights, my ass.
What you all doing?
Rejoice.
Death is not the end.
- Rejoice.
- You need to leave, now.
Death is not the end.
You need to leave.
You know Carcosa?
You rejoice.
Carcosa.
Rest of the family,
they don't really
talk to Aunt D.
She crazy.
Dementia.
She never had any kind
of good life,
but most days, she can't
even make sense.
Yeah? She sure
made sense to me.
That should worry you, mister.
Sure hope that
old lady was wrong.
About what?
About death not being
the end of it.
Did some backtracking
on the Marie Fontenot stuff.
Got some old sheets.
Sheriff signed off on
the "report made in error,"
but he didn't take the
original complaint on her.
Deputy did.
Got a name?
You ain't gonna
believe this shit.
Steve Geraci.
So I did some
double-checking.
Before CID, he was
with Vermillion
Parish Sheriff's.
Erath was his beat.
If it got covered up,
Steve might know something.
Didn't say
a fucking word when we
asked about it in '95.
Oh, I never did like
that cocksucker.
Where is he now?
Well, uh, this is the thing.
He's from Iberia originally.
After CID, he went home.
He's Sheriff of Iberia Parish.
Shit.
Yeah.
Rust, the only person
can arrest the sheriff
in this state is the governor.
Well, we ain't looking
to arrest him, Marty,
just have a little chat.
Well, he ain't
gonna talk with you.
I got a car battery
and two jumper cables
argue different.
Don't even start with that shit.
What do you recommend, Marty?
Well, fuck, why don't
you talk to him?
You two always liked each other.
Well, what can I say?
I'm a people person.
Well, start with that, then.
Oh.
Oh, come on.
Just try to relax.
Take your time.
There you go.
OK.
Nice shot.
What was that, 15 on the green?
Ha ha ha!
I don't know.
Hey, you know, on the phone,
you were saying
something about
that Fontenot girl.
Yeah.
Why's that
on your radar?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just, uh,
extended family wants a locate.
I didn't remember at the time.
Back in '95,
I was hitting
the bottle a lot
back then.
Yeah, who wasn't?
20 years ago, you know.
My recall,
girl's mom was single,
drug charges.
Uh...
Little girl went to live
with her birth daddy,
I think.
That is, if I'm
remembering right.
Uh, Mama didn't make
a fuss after
the first notice,
so she was fine with it.
And you talked to
the family directly
back then?
No. Ted Childress,
the sheriff.
He knew them.
Childress?
Now watch this.
Whew!
You like that?
Seized it off
a good old boy, had a
quarter-bag of weed.
Ooh. You got to love
this country.
Good to see you again, man.
Good to see you.
Hey, uh,
that client you got,
asking about the Fontenot girl.
You let them know
I'll be happy
to talk to them.
Oh, yeah, distant relatives.
St. Louis.
Trying to settle
a tiny inheritance.
Don't worry about it.
OK.
Well, they want to talk,
you let them know.
Yeah. Don't go
too fast, Sheriff.
Not me.
Let's do it again sometime.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Hey.
Better get those
jumper cables ready.
The motherfucker's lying.
Rust.
It's good to see you.
Bullshit.
I talked to Marty.
I hear you talked
to the cops, too.
Yes, them, too.
How are you?
What'd Marty tell you?
He wanted to know what
the police asked me about.
He said he was helping you
with something. That's it.
How long you been back?
Hear you got a big house.
Marty says the girls
are doing fine.
That's good.
Rust,
just tell me it's
something that's not
gonna get him hurt.
Well, I can't tell you that.
It never sat right with me,
and it doesn't now,
you asking me to lie
to you about him.
Now, get on out of here.
You're classing the place up.
Why'd you quit, Marty?
What's the real reason?
What happened?
You tell me why you
come back, for real.
Mmm, you first.
Why'd you quit?
Well, I saw something.
Baby.
Tweaker tried
to dry the kid
in a microwave.
Saw that, what he'd done,
and I thought...
never again.
I thought I... I never
want to look
at anything like that anymore.
Ahem.
Your turn.
Why'd you, uh,
why'd you come back?
This.
Something I had to see to...
before getting on
with something else.
My life's been a circle
of violence and degradation
long as I can remember.
I'm ready to tie it off.
See you on the boat.
After the other day,
I was thinking,
"Why don't I see Steve
and the boys more?"
Ain't been out
to my camp in a while.
You know, if I
don't get out here
3, 4 times a year...
I'm a basket case.
I hear ya.
Ah.
I do love a reason to drink beer
first thing in the morning.
Oh.
Say, Steve, mmm,
I been wanting to ask,
you know that Fontenot girl?
Remember, going off
with her daddy?
I... I just wasn't clear.
Was it you knew for a fact
that she went with her daddy,
or somebody told you that
that's what happened?
The family talked to
Sheriff Childress.
The girl's aunt and uncle,
he knew them.
Mm-hmm.
Who were they?
Starting to think
this wasn't just
a friendly invitation
from an old pal, huh?
It's definitely that.
Well, then try this, then.
I said all I remember
about the girl.
Let's just have
a good time, and
don't ask again.
I'm with you 150% on that.
All right.
Thing is, Steve...
I ain't gonna ask you.
He is.
No, I wouldn't
if I was you, Steve.
You're out of
your jurisdiction, Sheriff.
You realize who I am
now, you assholes?
Yeah, I wouldn't
be here if I didn't.
Marty.
Don't look at me.
I ain't never been
able to control him.
Come on.
But you're done after this.
I'll have boss
crackers splitting
your ass in Angola.
Yeah, we'll talk about that,
and some other things.
Come on.
That church
Cohle talked about's
supposed to be right here.
We're lost.
We're not lost.
We're going in
the right direction.
We're heading south.
And that's gonna head us to 49?
No, we're not
looking for the 49.
We're looking for the church.
I know we're looking
for the church; we ain't
got to no church.
Ain't seen nothing that
even resemble no church.
Ain't nobody
out here to even ask
where anything is.
Let me know when
you see something.
There ain't nothing to see.
Hey! Hey!
Yes, sir?
You know there's
a little church
around here?
Pretty old?
Black minister?
You must mean Son of Life, sir.
That place shut down.
'05, I think, just after
all them hurricanes.
Mmm.
You live around here?
No, sir.
I live in St. Martin.
Got a parish contract.
Take care of some cemeteries,
public schools.
All right. Thanks.
Hey, you know
how to get to 49
from here?
Sure.
About a half-mile,
you'll see a left.
PR 1435.
Take that.
About... 7 miles
of fields.
You'll hit 49 before Crowley.
Know your way around, huh?
Oh, yeah, boss.
I know the whole coast.
My family...
Thanks.
My family's been here
a long, long time.