Subtitles by explosiveskull
No, no, no, bro! We're not here for you!
Don't even think about it!
Don't you move,
motherfucker!
Hands away from the weapon, bro!
Fucking relax!
3170. We're being held up.
Armor piercing rounds
are chambered in this firearm!
Please don't be the asshole
who forces me to use it.
Take your foot off the gas,
press the unlock button,
and step out of the vehicle,
or we will forcibly
remove you!
Fucking do it! Now!
Your choice! Go!
What the fuck?
He fucking went for his gun.
He spilled his fucking coffee.
Shit.
Gardena, 30 seconds out.
Copy.
Thirty out. Hustle!
- Pop it.
- Ready.
Man on!
Out of fucking time.
Prepare to engage.
Contact right!
Range 100. Suppressive fire.
Contact left!
Dispatch, 10-97.
LAPD is on scene.
We are under heavy fire!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Whoa, whoa.
I got you. I got you.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
What the fuck was that?
Did you see him
go for his gun?
I don't know.
I just saw Bosco lit him up.
Take the second left
into the tunnel.
Hug the airport.
Take the tunnel.
Go right on Doty.
Right on Doty.
Make sure you take care
of those weapons.
I don't want any
accidental discharges.
- What are you looking at him for?
- Ray.
I'm not talking to him.
I'm talking to you.
What the fuck was that?
What else
did you fuck up, huh?
You sure you were clean
all the way home?
Catch any tails?
Where did Marcus
take those rounds?
Femoral artery.
He's done.
Well, we knew the risks.
Shit popped off.
We handled it. That's it.
Hey, B.
Get back over there.
See who responded.
It was probably LASD:
They'll supersede Gardena,
but if it's Major Crimes,
we've got a problem.
All clear? No GPS?
It's one of the old models, man.
We good.
We've got to
get this patched up.
We need this clean.
You good?
We're cop killers now.
Come on.
Jesus Christ!
You scared the shit out of me, babe.
Can't do that.
What are you doing
right now?
You erasing
your recent calls?
My phone?
What do you mean?
I don't know how to work this
fucking thing. You know that.
"I don't know how to work this
fucking thing. You know that."
Come on.
Babe, we really have
to go through this right now?
Where you been?
It's 6:00 a.m.
Where have you been?
Been at work?
Surveillance? Robbing drug dealers?
Because you smell like a stripper.
Of course, I was at work.
It's funny
'cause I got this text.
What was so hot, then?
Is that a work text?
Huh?
You fucked up.
You text me instead.
Who does that?
It's street theater, babe.
It's not what it looks like.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Fuck.
We're going
to go to Auntie's house
because Daddy's got to do
a little work on the house.
And we have
something else to do.
- Come on.
- What the fuck?
Hey, yo.
It's gonna be too loud
for you guys, okay?
- Hey. Deb? Deb?
- Will you put this on?
- Can you help me with that?
- What are you doing, Deb?
What the fuck are you doing?
- It will be too loud for you guys.
- Wifey, wifey.
Seriously, what are you doing?
Is Daddy coming with us?
No, Daddy does not have
enough time for us right now.
- Seriously... That's nice. That's nice.
- Can you put this on here?
Hey, honey.
Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
Hey, sweetie, come here.
She didn't mean that, okay?
Sweetie, you okay?
Yeah, great. Great.
Hey. Come here, honey.
I'm not going to be able
to make it right now,
but I'm gonna come a little
later, okay?
All right. Come here.
Give me a hug.
Time to go right now.
- Christ sake.
Will you slow it down
a second?
Daddy's a mess.
He's real tired.
- Right, hon?
- What...
Deb. Deb. Deb, will you
slow it down a second?
- We're going to walk this way...
- Deb.
Okay, watch your step.
Here we go.
Deb, can you slow it...
Okay. Come on.
Let's go. We're going to
put your sister in first.
Here we go.
Okay, baby, ready?
Sweetie, it's going to be
okay, sweetie. Okay?
Let's go.
Okay, put your bags in there. You
wanna put your sister in the seat?
Where's the pink bag?
Have you lost
your fucking mind?
Oh, great language
right in front of my daughter.
Great fathering!
Nice. Nice. Dropping F-bombs
in front of my daughters.
- "My kids"? "My kids"?
- Great fathering!
Gonna find a guy whose cock
actually gets hard for me.
Deb, Deb, Deb. Stop!
Please don't do this.
Please.
This is a little hard. You're just
scared right now, okay? You're confused.
Okay...
Out of the way, Nick.
Get out of the way, Nick.
Get the fuck out of here,
you fucker!
You motherfucker!
You get back! You understand
me, you motherfucker?
- Stay away from us!
- Nice. Nice.
Good. Good.
Okay. Mommy's okay.
See you later.
Morning.
Yup.
Yeah.
You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
Well, that looks
like it hurt.
No?
Good morning,
fellow officers.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah?
I take it
he's a bad guy.
You mean the guy
with the black body armor,
shotgun, and gas mask?
That's very funny.
We know who he is yet?
Rough night?
Yes. Next subject?
You're not looking
so hot there, bubba.
I think
he looks amazing.
I've got enough toxins in me to turn the
Gaza Strip into a Gay Pride parade.
You better start downing the POM juice,
big man. We've got a piss test Friday.
Thursday.
What, like you Mormons have been
drinking wheatgrass all fucking month?
Please.
You got another one of those?
I'm fucking starving.
Yeah, there's a
couple that don't have blood.
I think it's one of the
pinkies with the sprinkles.
That's some real donut.
Those are horrendous, dude.
Hey. You guys push
back the perimeter.
Need to extend the crime scene, okay?
Too goddamn small.
You got it.
What's the tally?
We've got four dead, six on
the way to the hospital.
- But they'll be all right.
- Fuck.
Ambushed them as they
were coming to get breakfast.
Surrounded the truck.
This poor fool right here was trying
to do what he gets paid to do.
AP rounds blasted through the
windshield took him out.
They took the truck, Gardena police
lost them under Hawthorne Municipal.
They knew the route.
Picked it because it was
next to Municipal Airport,
knew the restricted air space
meant no ghetto bird air support.
We're dealing with a different
animal here, boys.
Talk to the armored car company?
What was the haul?
They were en route to a bank
pickup for a Fed drop.
But there was nothing
in the truck.
Nothing in the truck?
They stole a fucking empty
armored truck?
Yup.
Why the fireworks?
One of the vics said the messenger went
for his gun. That's when it popped off.
Genius.
Okay, the SUV,
what have we got?
That's a cold car.
VIN's been pried off. Plates are stolen.
No prints on it. They bleach-bombed it.
Right. Take it to SID. Tent that fucker.
Swab it. Detail it.
Fuck. I can't deal with this
retard factory this early.
One of you guys handle it?
It's all you, bro.
Thank you.
All right, witnesses,
donut shop guy?
He saw them, and they
looked right at him,
but, for some reason,
they left him alone.
Okay, pull all video surveillance and
plate readers. Do a Palantir run.
Talk to DOT, okay?
Pull it all together,
and meet me at the office.
And find me
that fucking truck.
Big Nick, original gangsta
cop in the flesh.
Lobbin' Bob. Huh?
How's that
mean tennis game?
Look at you, man.
Where'd you pick that up?
Nice suit.
Well, not where you're shopping.
I can't afford it.
I mean,
how does a county sheriff
pay for such a beautiful
piece of men's fashion?
You kidding me? This piece of shit?
Nah, this is garbage. Look at you.
This thing's tits!
You must pull all kinds
of ass sporting that, no?
Nick, you know what?
I can't. I can't.
It's too early in the morning
for your fucking circus.
You just threw a donut
in the hot zone.
- No. I did not.
- Yeah, you did.
I did?
That was fucking wrong.
It was. I don't like you, Nick, or
how you handle police business...
What's up with that?
I like you.
Aside from the fact
that you're a vegetarian.
Vegan! I'm a vegan.
- Vegetarians, they eat milk...
- Yeah, sorry to hear that.
What are you
doing here anyway, huh?
No legal tender was stolen.
It isn't Federal.
Yet.
You're pausing
for dramatic effect?
You're such a big,
bad lieutenant.
- I know. I know.
- Yeah.
Can I go now, Dad?
I'm kind of hungry.
So Gardena showed up,
and they secured the scene,
and then these clowns
took over.
Who are they, LASD?
Yeah, Sheriff's. They must be.
Look at this clown right here.
He seemed to be in charge.
You recognize him?
He played football
at South.
Remember Endo?
Filipino dude the cops killed?
Yeah.
That's the cop
who blasted him.
Runs Major Crimes.
Get to know your enemy, boys.
Who's running this crew?
Probably two, three guys
that can pull this off, max.
Why steal an armored truck
with nothing in it?
Bad tip,
they probably botched it.
Why didn't they
dump it, then?
- I'll take the salvage yards.
All of them.
And how'd they know about a transfer
from the casino to the Fed,
especially one that wasn't scheduled
through the regular carrier? How?
It was an inside job, bro.
It had to be.
Oh, fuck.
Give me the Pepto.
Okay, inside job, but where?
Right? Was it the casino, the bank, the
Fed, the fucking donut shop? Where?
What about Merrimen?
When did he parole again?
- Eight months ago.
- Eight months ago?
We need to find
that fucking truck.
Have we still got a tail
on that Wilson kid?
- Yeah.
The one who was hanging out with Merrimen?
What bar did he work in?
- Hofbrau.
- Ziggy's Hofbrau.
Let's pay him a visit.
some Wi-Fi? No?
We better check his videos.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Wolfgang, talk to me.
- Donnie, I'm tapped out.
- No problem.
Put it on my tab, all right?
- Of course, man, I got you.
- Thank you.
Have a good night.
Are we doing this?
Yeah, man. All right, man.
To money and women.
That we don't have.
How do you remember
everybody's order like that?
I can't remember
the last four of my social.
Lots of reps, man.
I'm in complete control of my environment.
People don't even know.
Hey, man, time to go.
- Okay.
Wrap it up.
- Just a little bit.
Yeah, yeah.
- Ziggy's going to kill me.
- Shit, not going to finish.
A gift.
How about a tip?
We got you last time.
Oh, yeah, you got me last...
That's not how it works.
Okay, really? Zoo animals.
Need change?
That's for you, Fraulein.
Thanks.
Are there always
so many cops in here?
Last place
I'd think they'd be.
Yeah, this their spot.
You know, cheap liquor.
Right.
Yeah, there also is a lot of
shady cats in here, huh?
Yeah, it's kind of neutral
grounds, you know?
Rick's in Casablanca
type shit.
You must've heard
some stories in this place.
You know, give them a couple
of drinks, steak on his plate,
some nice women around him,
he'll tell you
his darkest secrets.
- Loose lips sink ships.
Ain't that the truth.
Mmm, what about you?
Pull a lot of pussy in here?
Yeah?
Come on.
- I do well for myself.
- Yeah.
I'd fuck you.
Kidding.
All right.
I'm out.
See you later, man.
Yeah.
Look forward to it.
- Fraulein.
- Dude, what the fuck are you...
Fraulein, you're up. Yeah.
What the fuck?
What's up, gangster?
Oh, Peaches.
Sit down.
You sit right there.
What you walking
so slow for, nigga?
I want you to sit right there.
That's you right there.
- Look here. There's cigarettes.
- Yeah.
Borracho!
I think y'all got me
confused with somebody.
Hey, Sporto.
You want a blow job?
Why my pants wet?
Come on, man, if you and
your Uncle Tom over here
are into some homo shit,
I'm good.
Y'all just kill me now.
You pissed yourself,
bubba.
It happens.
I had one of the girls here
clean you up, so you're good.
But y'all got the wrong dude.
You got me confused
with someone.
But I'm going to let you know
now, I ain't the one.
What'd you say?
Dude something?
No, we're not mistaking you for anybody.
Don't be a fucking smartass.
Arrested at 17 for GTA.
Tried and convicted
as an adult.
We know exactly who you are.
Did a stint at county
for attempted manslaughter.
Fastest speeding ticket
in California history.
That's nice.
Fucking genius, man.
How fast were you going?
178.
Speed demon!
What did you say to the cop
who pulled you over?
What reason did you give him?
Told him they'd
just paved the road.
- I like him.
- Ballsy.
Me gusta.
You may have a little pecker
for a black dude.
You may be a bed-wetter, but you've
got some fucking style, buddy.
All right, girls, time to go.
Grab your shoes. Grab your shit.
Let's go.
Time to go home
to your babies.
- All right, thanks for stopping by.
- Excuse me.
You check this out, hot rod.
You're a two-striker.
You need to fucking look at
me when I'm talking to you.
You're one mistake away from getting
sex in the ass every time you shower.
Some of them niggas
got gas pumps.
Now, personally, that shit don't
sound like a lot of fun to me.
What you think?
How you feel about that?
Look, the dude in that picture
is not even a regular at my bar.
Like, I've seen him a few times, but,
you know, I don't associate myself...
Do you know what this means?
It means I am
a member of a clique.
It's kind of like
being in a gang.
Sort of like a gang,
only we have badges,
which means you are done.
He ain't lying.
Let me ask you this.
Okay, do we look like
the types who will arrest you?
Put you in handcuffs,
drag you down to the station?
Hmm?
I'm asking you
a fucking question.
No. Not at all.
Right, exactly.
We just shoot you.
It's less paperwork.
So tell me,
what the fuck are you doing
hanging out in that crew?
Hmm?
You're a pussy.
Those dudes are bad dudes.
Great thieves
but straight convicts.
What's Merrimen doing drinking
beers with the likes of you for?
Talk shop?
You gonna hit
the fucking Hofbrau?
Take the place down, score, like,
what, two grand in ones and fives?
Is that what's afoot?
I'll answer that for you.
No, it fucking isn't.
I don't know what crew
you're speaking about, man.
This dude just comes
to my bar where I work...
Stop. Shut up.
Come on, man. This is some weird shit.
Just...
You listen to me, fuckface.
We don't give
a shit about you.
You in Merrimen's crew?
Hmm?
Huh? You hit the stadium?
You talky-talky now?
Yes, please.
Fuck!
I'm just the driver!
They don't give me no gun.
I don't do no gangster shit.
They asked me to drive,
so that's what I do.
That's it. Fuck!
Why did Merrimen hijack
an empty armored car?
I don't know, all right?
They keep me in the dark
for shit like this.
If the cops come down on me,
I can't tell them shit
if I don't know shit.
Now y'all can hook me up
to a lie detector,
a fucking polygraph,
whatever y'all got.
I'm telling you what I know,
and that's all you'll get.
Please, just let me
the fuck go.
Fuck y'all, man.
Let me go.
Well, I thought that was
relatively convincing.
Good stuff.
All right,
when did you meet him?
What do I get out of this?
What do you get out of this?
Well, your freedom for one.
Two,
you're not the bad guys.
We are.
Couple months ago,
they came through the bar,
and I served them
a few drinks.
We started talking.
Hey, Donnie, come here, man.
This is my boy, Bosco.
My brother for life.
We deployed together.
Hey, the kid can drive.
Okay.
Donnie, tell him about
the Trans Am Series.
Drove Trans Am Series, like
he said, for about a season.
What were their names?
Hawaiian dude,
he had a homie,
Bosco, white boy.
He was in the military,
and he worked for DWP.
I told him I needed
some extra money,
so he gave me a job.
Who's that? Merrimen?
Merrimen.
Ray Merrimen.
So what's up
with this dude?
It's Marcus' boy.
Worked with him
over at the Hofbrau.
Say he did some time
with him at Wayside.
He was a Marine for a minute.
Say the nigga can drive.
He be cool.
All right,
let's check him out.
Real smart dude.
He had just got out of prison
from what I could tell.
You ready to roll, Ray?
514!
Come on,
let's cuff them up.
You want any of your shit?
No.
Let's go.
See you soon, Ray.
No, you won't.
You look great, baby.
All right. Come on.
For real.
Bring any sunglasses for me?
Baby, I'm sorry.
I forgot.
Here, take mine.
Take mine.
Come on.
They're good. They are.
They look great on you.
Look at that.
Where'd you meet him?
It was in Carson,
at the Hawaiian dude's house.
Through your body.
- What up? What up? What up?
- Fucking nice.
Yeah. Fool's in back.
You're mine!
- Donnie, what's good, man?
- What's up?
- Come on, man. Follow me.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey.
Oh, shit.
What's up?
- Donnie, beer?
- Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
So you spent
some time at Wayside?
Yeah, a little bit.
What do they serve
for breakfast on Fridays?
Silver dollar pancakes.
Three of them.
Where you from?
Hawthorne.
So you can drive, huh?
Oh, I can drive.
Drive.
You might want to
put that seat belt on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He liked how I drove, so, a
week later, I did my first gig.
We hit this rave at a stadium.
Got one.
Minus the dye pack,
is the count all good?
The count is on.
That's a lot of money
right there, bro.
Why don't we just
call it a day?
Really?
You want three
in hot bills,
you looking over your shoulder
for the rest of your life,
or would you rather
have 30 clean?
I'm just saying.
Let's just call it quits
while we're ahead.
Put it away.
We're trading up.
All right. Fuck it.
Let's do it.
What happened to the cash?
I don't know.
They don't tell me.
They don't talk much.
Yeah, people with things to
hide never have much to say.
So am I under arrest,
or can I leave?
Nah, you just keep
doing your thing.
We'll be in touch.
Yeah?
Horsepower, be at 1st and
Central at 0800. Don't be late.
You always
pick the same one.
Just go for it. I'm here.
Do whatever you want.
Woo-hoo!
Ran the prints on CAL-ID:
Got a hit on our dead guy
from Angel City.
- Check your e-mail.
- All right.
Name's Marcus Rhodes,
from Oakland.
ATF was looking for him
for gun charges.
And more to the point
that you were making before,
he was stationed at 29 Palms the
same time Merrimen was there.
This is good.
Give me the book on Merrimen.
Look to your right.
You know what that is?
It's the bank for banks.
Los Angeles branch of the
Federal Reserve.
It's the only bank
that's never been robbed.
All the surrounding streets
are wired for sound and image.
Stand across the street and stare
at the building for two minutes,
you'll have security on your ass
asking you politely to leave.
If they see your face again,
every Secret Service agent in the
country is going to be looking for you.
The place is case-proof.
There have been 53
break-in attempts.
Not one has got past
the lobby.
That's why we're
going to rob it.
Okay, here we go.
Laguna Niguel was in '06.
Got caught for that, get sent
up to USP Victorville SHU
until June of '16.
Now give me the unsolved book.
As soon
s you enter the lobby,
computers run you through every law
enforcement database in the country.
If you've got outstanding
parking tickets,
they're going to know about it before you
get through the first level of security.
All the employees wear
security swipe cards
that grant them access through
the first set of man-traps.
Access is severely restricted.
Two stories below street
level is the vault floor.
By the way,
uh, his crimey...
- Levoux?
- Levoux.
He serve with Merrimen?
Not only that, but they played football
in high school at Long Beach Poly.
- You've got to be shitting me.
- No.
Central Security, it's
the nerve center for the Fed.
This is where the armored cars
come in, drop off the money tubs.
Money tubs are handed off
to the Fed employees.
At any one time, there's anywhere between
500 and 800 billion dollars in there,
every millimeter of it covered by
cameras, sensors, and motion detectors.
Yeah. What did they
specialize in?
I got this from the HR desk
at 29 Palms.
Close Quarter Battle Unit. Both
saw combat in the Middle East.
Levoux specializes in explosives, where
Merrimen specializes in soldiering,
both MARSOC fast Marines.
But there's a hitch.
The serial number of every bill is
recorded in the Fed's database.
So, if a note goes missing,
they're going to know
exactly which one it is.
They're going to flag it.
If that bill comes up again,
whoever recirculates that cash, no
matter where they are in the world,
that person can be tracked.
Okay. Bosco,
the Peckerwood?
He's a Huntington Beach kid,
also MARSOC Marines.
He did comms with them.
He had a solid career.
But he didn't serve together
with the other guys.
He was the Wood Rep at Victorville
when Merrimen was there.
That's where they linked up.
Donnie was a Marine for a
year and a half, then discharge.
So, the way I see it,
that's the way all these niggas
ended up working together.
There's only two passports on the
streets, sports and military.
Every time the Fed receives
a deposit from a bank,
first thing they do is send that
money up to the count rooms.
They run the notes
through the counting machines.
They're accomplishing
two things here.
First, they're double-checking the
accuracy of the bank's deposit.
If the bank is off at all,
they're going to credit or
debit the account accordingly.
Two, they're separating newer, fit
currency from old unfit bills.
But most importantly, they're
erasing the serial numbers
of the old bills
from the Fed system.
Once those numbers are erased, to
the Fed, to the rest of the world,
that money
has ceased to exist.
Wait, let's look at
the unsolved cases.
In '04, you have the Boller
National Bank Hollywood job, okay?
They tunneled through
the sewer system.
Sophisticated, skill set,
someone with access, unsolved.
Okay, in '05, you have the
Fuerte armored car depot job.
Blew the depot vault
with shaped charges.
In the $100 count room alone,
an average of $30 million is
designated as unfit every day.
Between 4:00 p.m.
and 5:00 p.m.,
all the cash gets shot out
to the shredder.
It's all destroyed.
$30 million
turned to dust in seconds.
It's then picked up by the
Fed's waste management company
and brought out to the dump.
If we can get
to those unfit bills
before they go to the shredders
and get out clean...
You got $30 million
nobody is looking for.
Bingo.
In '06,
you have Laguna Niguel.
Same thing, only this time, Merrimen
gets unlucky with the tail-light.
Goes to prison till 2016. Now, in
that time, while he was in prison,
how many highly sophisticated,
well-executed heists do we have?
None, but you're on a roll.
Keep going.
The counter guy at the donut shop?
Witness to the whole thing.
They left him. Why?
Because they shoot uniforms,
not unarmed civilians.
Exactly what
they were trained to do.
Gangbangers, these are not.
Okay, these are our guys.
We nail these guys,
we solve all these cases.
This is the crew.
You still haven't told us how
you can get past that security.
We're not
going in this way.
We're going in that way.
What's going on
with Fraulein?
We can move on him
anytime we want.
- I pay minimum wage.
- Okay.
Plus $3 for delivery.
And you split the tip with me.
You start Wednesday, 11:00.
Thank you.
I don't really like the
food there, but I'm down to go,
- but you've got to pay this time.
I'm not paying it.
What?
- I pay every fucking time.
Get off
your wallet, buddy.
No, I forgot my wallet today,
boys. I'm sorry.
- Again?
- Yeah, again.
Got an alligator arm.
I sat down at blackjack
with $5, and I made $160.
Nicholas O'Brien?
Yeah?
I suggest you take these.
You're being served.
You kidding me?
I'm afraid not.
What's going on?
You all right, bro?
Yeah, I guess
I'm getting divorced.
He say "divorced"?
Yo.
Welcome to the fucking club.
Now, go handle your business,
big man.
Gas the jet.
Fuck.
There's a closer view.
There was a rolling blackout in
this quadrant four days ago.
Yeah, they've been happening a
lot over the last few months.
Okay.
They say they have full backup
power, but actually they don't.
- They go into brown-out.
- Yeah, prioritize the grid.
Priority, of course, is the vault.
So everything in there stays intact.
But anything that is peripheral,
like cameras in the hallway,
shredders in the count rooms,
everything else cuts out.
To time it during another rolling blackout
is going to be fucking impossible.
- So you want to simulate it?
Can we?
Break in, have them go brown
for about two minutes.
I'd say yes, but I'd like to
have data to be sure.
Great.
Once we breach the count room,
only thing left is the cameras.
They run on their own
power supply,
so they're unaffected
by the brown-out.
The solve here is we run
an EMP burst.
Should take out the cameras
and motion for about 30 feet.
Where you get all this
information from?
You don't have to
worry about that.
Just trust me
when I say it's solid.
How we doing
with the Telecal hook?
Couple days.
Shouldn't be a problem.
How many handlers do you need?
Uh, gate B right now.
Strolling right into
the Federal Reserve.
Force leaving loading dock B.
ID?
Sign in, please.
Keep this on you
at all times.
Second bay of elevators.
Cafeteria's level 2.
Buzz him in. He's good.
Smells good.
He's good. Let him in.
- Sharon?
- Mmm-hmm. That's me.
- How you all doing?
- Good. How you are doing today?
- He's fine.
- Thank you.
She ain't getting none.
Shut up. Really?
Y'all have a good day.
I'm gonna stay out of it.
- We will now.
- You have a wonderful day.
Lunch. Desert.
Bye, sunshine.
There he goes.
Fed's got 82.
Maybe it's part of his
regular route.
Delivering Chinese
to the Fed,
my left nut.
No. They're casing the joint
from the inside.
Okay, go back.
Other than cash,
what else do they take from
the casino in the stadium?
Fed deposit slips.
- But those were probably in with the cash.
- Or not.
Listen, what if they were
taking the cash
to disguise the fact that they were
really there for something else?
And then they take down an armored
car that's empty. Come on, guys.
Look, remember
what Donnie said.
It's trading up.
They're going big.
Hey, Nick, you can't
take down the Fed, man.
I'm sorry, Merrimen's no dummy.
It's impossible.
The Fed is the Olympics, and
Merrimen is Carl fucking Lewis.
I'm telling you,
Fraulein's holding out on us.
My gosh.
- Aw!
- Oh, he's here.
- Okay.
Damn, girl looking fine.
Thank you.
You look amazing.
How are you?
Looking good.
Thank you.
- This is my mom. This is Rolando.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you. Rolando.
- Hi, I'm Malia. Nice to meet you.
- I see where you get your looks from.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Can I take that?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Um, Rolando,
this is my dad.
What's up, Mr. Levoux?
Nice to meet you.
Let me holler at him
for a second.
Let me talk to you, bruh.
Honey, don't worry about it.
Okay? They're just gonna talk.
So here's what's up.
For the past 16 years,
my daughter's safety and protection
has been my responsibility
and my responsibility only.
Now, for the first time in her life, I see
I've got to hand you that responsibility.
Don't fuck up,
or your mama
will weep as she has
to wheel your ass around every
day the rest of your life.
Now I worked on this, because I want to
say this to you as nice as possible.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Yes, sir.
It's all right.
Listen. Listen.
All he's trying to say is,
it's wonderful to meet you,
and he wants you
to have a beautiful evening.
I'll see you at 11:30.
Yeah. Yeah.
- 11:30. Yeah. 11:30.
- Good choice.
I think he got
the picture, bro.
Psst.
Beers and sake,
let's go.
Have wine.
What the fuck?
Hey.
Buddy.
Donnie, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, spotted you at the gym
the other day, yeah?
Yeah, man. How you doing?
What's up, fellows?
You play football
at Long Beach Poly?
You look familiar.
No, I'm not from
around here.
What are you doing here?
You work around here?
Enjoying my dinner, man.
- Really?
Yeah.
Food here sucks.
Yeah. Yeah,
we come here for the ass.
So I'll see you
at the gym, man.
Yeah. Definitely.
Have a good night.
Number 55, right?
That's how I remember you.
We wore the same number,
55, right?
I went to South Torrance.
Yeah, we played you guys
a couple of times.
You and all those
fat-ass Samoans.
Yeah, they were big,
but, man, lazy motherfuckers.
Probably all that Spam.
Yeah, we fucking
crushed you guys.
Crushed you guys when I was there.
Crushed you guys when you were there.
Still crushing you guys.
We've got family here, bro.
Don't really appreciate
you popping off.
All right. All right, man.
No need to get all agro.
Was I being rude?
Huh?
- What?
- Let's go order, bro.
Hey, look, man, listen.
You've got a beautiful family.
Everything's all good. Excuse us.
Kampai.
See you at the gym, Donnie.
Have a good night, ladies.
You a cop?
No. Are you?
Get out of the car.
Go!
- Where's the wire?
- Come on, man.
I'm not wearing
a fucking wire, man.
Man, I'm not wearing
no fucking wire.
Get up.
How does he know you?
Don't tell me it's
from the fucking gym.
Look, I don't know him.
Smoke this punk.
Talk, motherfucker.
I'm no cop, all right?
Now he came to me.
He know you.
He know all of you.
But I ain't tell him shit.
He was sweating me.
I ain't seen him since.
I thought he'd
leave us alone.
So how much do they know?
Nothing.
I ain't tell them shit.
I don't know nothing anyway.
And you know I'm the last
person that would fuck this up.
Now, if we've got to
call it off, I get it.
But I know
I ain't tell them shit.
Friday. Make sure
he knows it's on.
- So good.
It's true, though.
It's true.
Okay.
How you doing, Nick?
Hmm.
- I'm Nick.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Good.
What's for...
- What's for dinner?
- You smell like alcohol, Nick.
Hmm?
Relax.
I already ate.
Give me a pen, stud.
Nick, I was gonna call you.
I was gonna take you
to dinner next week.
Just give me a fucking pen.
Thanks, Ruud.
- I'm gonna hit the...
- No, you're not.
How's the wine?
Good?
That's pretty fucking good.
So I imagine I just, uh...
What, just sign
anywhere, yeah?
Okay.
And I imagine it's assumed
that if you were ever
to touch one of my girls
or, say, talk to them
or, you know,
even look at them,
I go boom-boom. You
know what I'm saying?
But, I mean, that's
self-evident, right?
There's no need to put that
in the contract, is there?
- No, I didn't think so.
- Nick...
Can you please go, Nick?
- That's enough, Nick.
- Sure.
Come on.
Come here.
Give me a hug.
Come on. We'll save
a fortune in therapy.
Hmm?
Come on.
Give me a hug.
There you go, huh, hoss?
You've just always got to make
a spectacle out of everything.
There you go.
Yeah, pretty much.
All right, Nick.
I think it's time to go.
Come on, Nick,
let's go.
Hey...
- Call the fucking cops.
- That's what I'm saying.
- I'm sorry, but it's time for you to go.
Call the cops.
- I'm sorry...
- Don't fucking touch me.
- I'm sorry.
- Do not fucking touch me.
Come on, Nick.
- Just, please go.
By the way...
- What do you want?
- You hitting that from behind,
and you're wondering
what that thing is on her ass?
- It's a tattoo of my name.
Nick, please...
"Big Nick O'Brien."
Just a heads-up.
Psst.
Call me.
Take your time.
What happened to you?
Borracho,
what do you think?
What the fuck was that?
You spotted me
at the gym?
Tranquillo. All right?
Sit down.
I'll take it, Freddy.
Just give us
a minute, okay?
Look, they're not going to off
you with this much heat, okay?
When's this happening?
Friday.
Where?
I don't know yet.
All I can tell you is Friday.
huh?
You're protecting me on this.
Fraulein,
we got your back, bro.
Don't worry about a thing.
Fuck.
Better wear your vest.
We're in.
Z?
Pico Rivera Savings,
Montebello Town Center.
Copy that, boss.
See you at 0800.
Tell the crew.
I did what you
told me to.
You have fun?
He treat you right?
Maloa.
You know I love you, right?
I love you, too.
Come on, go to school.
There you go.
Good job there.
McKenna!
Hey, sweetie. Hey, sweetie.
How are you? Good?
What are you doing?
Well, you know,
I was on my way to work
and thought I'd come by and say
hello to my little monkey.
- Is that okay?
How's everything
at school? Okay?
- Yes, it's good.
- Yeah?
And what about
Auntie's house?
Mommy and Cassady,
are they good?
What about the honey-bear?
Honey-bear good?
- Yeah? You miss me?
All right, Pookie,
better get back to class.
When am I going to
see you again?
Soon, sweetheart.
I'm gonna see you soon.
I want to come home.
Me, too.
All right, you better
get back to class, okay?
But I'm gonna see you later.
Promise?
I promise.
Come on.
Recess is over.
Come on, kids. Come line up.
Go on, Pookie.
Bye, Daddy.
Come on, McKenna.
Come on, honey.
Jock up.
Tac up, brother.
No Fed?
Change of plans.
Pay attention.
Always keep your finger off the trigger
until you're going to shoot somebody.
If and when that happens,
safety selector switch.
One for semi,
two for full auto.
Mag release.
Out with the old,
in with the new.
Tug it. Make sure
it's in there good.
Slap the bolt home,
you're ready for round two.
Other than that, keep this thing
pointed at the fucking floor.
- You understand?
- Got it.
Go put your shit on.
- Magazine, Borracho?
- Yeah.
You good?
I'm good.
Suspects arriving on location.
We've got nothing for the DA. They
haven't committed a crime yet.
They clear the bank,
we take them down.
- Stand by.
- Roger that.
Broad fucking daylight.
They're packing big.
Ooh, shit. Look at
these motherfuckers.
Get down on the ground!
Down on the ground! Get
down on the fucking ground!
Freeze!
Freeze! Don't move!
Stay right there!
Freeze!
- You two! Move! Get over there!
- Get over here!
Hurry up!
Get out here, now!
Move there now!
Go! Go! Go!
Move back!
Stay right there! Now!
Eyes to the floor!
Listen up!
Everybody pay the fuck
attention!
Eyes to the ground!
'Cause I'm only
going to say this once!
If you cooperate,
if you follow directions,
you will not be hurt. We are
here for money, not for you.
I want everybody lined up
on the counter. Let's go!
Move down!
Move down! Let's go!
Everybody behind the counter,
come out front! Let's go!
Keep your eyes down
and your mouths shut.
On my command,
reach inside your pockets,
remove your cell phones,
and put your hands in the air.
Everybody take
two steps forward.
Now go down on your knees.
All right! Cell phones
right in here.
On me.
Let's go.
Put them in the box.
Tie them up.
Go! Go! Go!
There will be
no heroics today.
You guys go ahead
and get comfortable.
We're going to be here
for a while.
Anybody need to
use the bathroom?
Take a piss on yourself.
Hey.
You. Get up.
Stop.
Sit down.
All right, I need you
to calm down right now.
Hey! Look at me.
Take a deep breath.
Good.
I know you already triggered
the silent alarms.
So I need you to
pick up the phone,
dial 911 dispatch,
and explain the following.
Go ahead
and write this down.
There's a 211 in progress,
and we have hostages.
Within one hour, they need
to deliver $10 million
in unmarked small denomination
bills to this bank
inside a department helicopter
loaded with fuel.
Tell them we plan on killing one hostage
every hour until our demands are met.
No cops are to
approach the bank.
And if a negotiator
even tries to contact us,
we will automatically kill
another hostage.
Is that clear?
You got it all?
Go ahead and
pick up the phone.
Any available units,
we have a bank 211 in progress...
Shit.
at the Pico Rivera Savings
in Montebello
at 2891 Wilcox and Atlantic.
- Suspects are armed...
- What the fuck?
and have taken hostages
and are refusing a negotiator.
What the fuck is going on?
That's not their MO.
Call in, tell them we're on scene,
have suspects under surveillance,
and to back the fuck off.
This is LASD: we have surveillance
on the bank. Stand down.
I repeat, have all units
stand down.
It's bullshit.
I can hear them already.
What the fuck are they doing?
Stop!
Get out!
What the fuck
are you guys doing, huh?
Asshole!
What the fuck are you doing?
What's going on?
You were running surveillance,
and you let this shit go down?
It's our fucking case. We've been
surveilling these guys for weeks.
That's what surveillance is!
They commit a crime,
and then we stop them.
Go. Go to the vault.
Open it.
Let's go. Come.
Sit. Sit down.
I'm going to put this
on speaker phone.
You're going to answer,
but don't use any names.
You understand?
Hello?
Hello, this is the Los
Angeles Police Department.
Who am I speaking with?
This is the branch manager.
Sir, I need to speak
with the person in charge.
You are.
Okay, good. Well, let me introduce myself.
I'm Officer Parada...
I don't give a fuck who you are.
Are our demands being met?
Who am I talking with now?
Answer the question.
It's being worked on
as we speak.
But you need to understand...
You just killed a hostage.
Goddammit!
- Get up. Get up!
- No! No! No!
Come on, move!
I didn't do anything. Please.
What are you doing?
- Come on.
- No! No! No!
Fuck!
- You were on it, huh?
- Shit!
You're so full of shit,
O'Brien...
You heard the demands,
you stupid motherfucker!
- Yeah.
- You put a negotiator on? Christ!
- Fuck you!
- Fuck me?
Yeah, fuck you!
Fucking nice haircut,
you fucking idiot.
Who are you fucking
pushing now?
Are you fucking kidding?
- Get SWAT rolling right now!
- You stupid fucking pussy.
Fucking Lobbi"
Bob is angry!
- All right, boss, let's go. Let's go.
- Shitheads!
- Let's go.
- Fuck!
We've got a situation
going on...
Shit!
What the fuck
are you doing, Merrimen?
Yeah?
This is the Police Department.
Please don't hang up.
My name's Danny.
I'll be your only contact. Nobody
else is going to call you.
Is this the person in charge?
This is the branch manager.
I'm speaking on
the man in charge's behalf.
Do you have a name,
branch manager?
Listen. They've already killed
one of the hostages. A woman.
They will not
speak to you again.
If you call back again before their
demands are met, they'll kill another.
Just send what they want.
The money and the chopper
are en route,
but it's going to take
a little bit of time.
You need to give me at least 90 minutes.
Is this doable?
Okay. Don't call back.
What's the prefix here?
TONY Z: 562. It's Long Beach.
Hello?
You watching?
Yup.
So how the hell are you going
to get out of this one?
Not sure yet.
Did you get my number
from her cell?
I ain't cuffing up.
That's okay.
I didn't bring
my cuffs anyway.
Yeah, I can see that.
Was that who I think it was?
Yup.
We've got a chopper
that's gonna come down.
The chopper is going to land
right over here.
I've got two-door entry on one.
One-door entry on two.
Breaching!
Well, they just
blew the vault.
What the fuck?
Federal Reserve,
accounts receiving.
Hey, it's Al at Alameda.
We have a drop at Pico Rivera
we need to schedule.
How's Wednesday at 2:00?
That works. You're
confirmed for 2:00 p.m. The 18th.
AL: Great. Thanks.
- We're here, yeah?
- Yeah, that's us.
So what is this?
This is the sewer line,
and according to this map right
here, it's all cemented up.
Hey, where are we
with the chopper?
We're waiting on clearance.
Relax, they're not
going anywhere.
To hell with clearance.
We've got to move.
O'Brien, hey!
Is he off his meds?
Tell him to get
the fuck back here!
Will you shut
the fuck up?
Oh, fuck you.
We better go
back him up.
Nick's heading to the front.
We're on the move.
Here we go.
Fuck!
Is he serious?
Everybody okay?
Yes.
Please, Lord, please,
let me see my family again.
- Nick!
- Sheriff's Department.
Nick!
Clear!
- The fuck?
- Nick, what's your location?
What's your location?
Hey, this is Al
at Alameda again.
I forgot to schedule a drop
at Pico Rivera Savings.
What do you have open today?
Ghetto Bird, this is Silverback.
We confirmed?
Check. Appointment's at 2:45.
That's in two minutes.
Pico Rivera.
Horsepower all set?
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
They got you
on a new route?
Yeah. Yeah, they just
switched us over this week.
All right. Let me get
you guys' IDs, man.
Yeah, sure. There you go.
All right.
You're good to go.
- All right, thank you.
- Open the gate. Have a good one.
Alameda's coming down.
Oh, fuck.
Pico Rivera Savings? 2.2?
Yup, that's us.
Bring her up.
All right, ready.
One, two, three.
- Sign here.
- You got it.
You're new here, Mark?
Yes, sir.
You guys running
a little bit late.
Yeah, we ran into
some traffic, so...
I don't know where they had
you guys routed before,
but we run a tight,
tight ship around here,
so, if you're going to be
late, have base call it in.
Yeah, no problem.
That's my fault. I just...
Just have them call.
On me.
Hey, Luigi. Alameda's on deck.
Check them in.
Copy that.
New guys.
I'm going to step out
for a minute.
How you guys doing today?
- Good. All right.
- Good.
How you doing?
- All right, how are you?
- Good, thank you.
Sign that for me, please.
All hundreds?
The first one's all hundreds.
The second one is mixed.
We're a little backed up.
All right,
do what you can.
Guys want to hang out, get a Coke
or something? Appreciate you.
Thank you.
We're going to need access
to the recording off-site.
Can you get that to us?
- Understood.
- You need professional help.
Desperately.
My bad last time.
Your crime scene.
Silverback,
this is Horsepower. I'm in.
Greenpeace, this is Silverback.
Horsepower is in.
Roger that, Silverback.
Lights out.
Okay, here we go.
Johnny, we're fucking
brown again, man.
Got to shut down. Pull them
out of the count rooms.
We're going brown.
We've got to shut down for a bit.
All teams go ahead and take 10.
Luigi, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They went to brown.
They're clearing out.
Let's lock it down.
Copy.
Get ready to go.
Powering up EMP now.
All clear here.
Good to go.
You're clear. Go.
Shit.
Check something out.
What do you think it is?
Are the cameras
up in the 100 room?
Uh, negative.
555-0143.
It's taking too long.
Tasty Orders.
This is Sharon at the Fed.
Now, we ordered almost
an hour and a half ago.
Now, I only have so much
time on my lunch break.
It coming!
Be there in a few minute!
They just called
for the Chinese.
Hurry it up.
Motion is out in there, too?
Yeah, man, we're still brown.
You know, we better override.
Power it up.
All right.
Done.
Okay. Better get
that count, too.
Shit, here comes security.
Get down. Get down.
Hey, man, got to check this 100 count.
Motion went off.
- Luigi.
- Step on it. Step on it, quick.
Yeah?
- Luigi.
- Yeah?
Damn, dude! Luigi, you're
stepping on the line, man!
Say again? Russell?
Hey, dumb-dumb. You've got to
let go of the push to talk.
What the hell is
going on here today?
Luigi, man. He's stepping
all over the line.
He's hot like a motherfucker.
He's in the cafeteria.
Go ahead and get him.
All right. Roger that.
I'm stepping out.
You're clear. Go.
Holy shit.
Luigi, you're hot-micing.
You've got to let go of the talk button.
You're stepping on the line.
Dude, it's not me.
Come on, we've got to check the 100 count.
Let's go. Get Junior. Let's go.
Switch to line five.
You got about a minute and a
half, two minutes. Let's go.
They're back. Get out.
Luigi, you see
anything, man?
Yeah, we're good. There's
nothing back there but dust.
What am I looking for?
Don't worry about it, man. I'm gonna
juice up the room, run the count,
- and make sure we're good, all right?
- Copy that.
Where are you?
This is Horsepower.
I'm in the vents.
Greenpeace, you're done.
Cut out.
We are back up, brother.
All teams,
back to the count room.
Get on with LAPD Central.
Tell them we're running
surveillance at 8th and Grand.
Request a Code 5. We do not
wanna spook the suspects.
Copy that.
Putting in a Code 5.
Am I tripping or
was this full before?
Let's just
check the count.
$712,200.
Russell, the count is on.
All right, roger that. Go
ahead and clock out Alameda.
Take Alameda out.
The count was good.
But both of your bins
were half-full.
Sorry?
Your bins,
they were half-full.
That's how we got them.
Next time,
just put it in a cash sack.
Makes things a lot easier.
Try and work smart,
not hard.
Okay, sounds good.
Thanks for the advice.
We would tip you, honey, but that
just took too damn long, okay?
I'm the only guy they've got
delivering today. I'm sorry.
Sorry, guys, let me see
your drop confirmation again.
- All right.
- There you go.
Chinese food guy?
Go on. Buzz him in.
Hold him there.
2-4-5.
Yeah, send him through.
Come here for a sec, buddy.
Yeah, man, I don't
have you signed in.
I just started
my shift, but, uh...
Where's your name?
Come on, man, I signed my name with
a dude from the last shift, man.
I don't know
what to tell you.
Mmm-mmm.
Damn you finicky.
- I'm getting my money back.
- Okay.
That's all I need.
All right, you boys
are good to go.
- Thank you very much, Officer.
- Take it easy.
- You have a good day.
- All right.
- Go on. Get out of here.
- Thank you.
Yes, security
in the lobby, please.
Lobby.
Yeah, did you see
a delivery guy?
Red shirt, light skin.
About 6 foot.
- Wait, what?
- Stop him.
You got eyes on the 1-2 side?
We'll cover the 3-4 corner.
Copy that.
Got held up at security.
What's your location?
South on Grand,
just past Vernon.
Go right on Gage.
Right on Gage.
Copy that.
Move! Let's go! Get out!
- Come on, move! Move! Here we go!
- It's cool.
- Come on, get down! Go! Go! Go!
- It's cool. I'm cool, man.
Be cool, bro. Cool.
Fuck.
There he is. There he is.
Red shirt. Two blocks ahead.
Eyes on suspect.
Walking eastbound on 9th, approaching
Hill, south side of street.
Pull up in front of him,
in front of him.
Let's get this motherfucker.
Let's ram his bitch-ass
into the gate first.
Get in the fucking car!
Come on. Get in.
Fuck.
Hit him!
Motherfucker.
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's
get it done as quick as we can.
What the fuck.
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he, asshole?
Fuck.
Fucking... Fucker!
Give me the burner phone.
Where the fuck is he?
Pacific Horizon Salvage.
In South Gate.
That's the rally point.
Silverback, go.
Horsepower's burned.
Repeat that.
I can't hear you.
Horsepower is burned.
He's done.
I'm still clean.
Where am I going, bro?
Fuck!
Let's go. Let's go.
You guys got it all?
- Yes, it's all in.
- Pick it up.
It's good.
Pacific Horizon Salvage.
South Gate, Alameda Corridor.
10-4. Headed to you.
What happened
to the other two?
They got burned.
Eyes on suspects.
Black, four-door Suburban!
Heading southbound on Alameda.
Approaching Slauson Avenue. I need
you to parallel me on Santa Fe.
We got some traffic up ahead.
What's going on?
Corridor's backed up.
- We just turned down Alameda Corridor, heading south.
Shit.
Coming up on suspect,
6 o'clock.
Shit.
Right lane is
closed up ahead.
I repeat, right lane is
You guys see that?
Twenty, 30 cars back.
What is that?
Is that...
Okay, we're at
a stop, stop, stop.
Fuck backup.
We've got to move.
Fuck.
Yup.
That's them.
- Give me my vest.
- Yeah.
Yeah, here we go.
Okay, we've got them pinched in. We've
got to move before it opens up.
Cuff him up.
Be advised, suspects
wearing body armor.
No center mass shots.
Limb and head shots only.
Copy that.
Go around right here.
It's jammed up.
Good? Okay, let's go.
- Oh, shit.
What?
They're getting
out of the car.
Z, go down the right.
Gus, Borracho,
center with me.
Murph, stay on the left.
Don't come in.
- Pass me the saw.
Fuck.
Let's go.
Stay down. Stay down.
Get down. Get down.
- Sheriff's Department. Stay down.
- Get down. Get down.
- Get down.
- Sheriff's Department, stay down.
Get down. Get down.
Stay by the engine block.
Get down
behind the wheel.
Sheriff's Department.
Lady, get in the car.
Oh, shit.
Borracho!
Moving!
Gus, Murph, you two go across
and cut them off, okay?
Tony Z, you ready?
Let's go.
Moving!
Move!
Moving. Moving.
Mag change!
Moving.
Mag change.
Moving!
Go! Go! Peel off!
Tony, you okay?
- Yeah, go! Go!
- You okay?
Fuck!
Go!
Cover!
Move.
Fuck!
Brick wall! Brick wall!
Behind the brick building!
My kid...
You're in His hands now.
You hear me?
Fuck!
Don't do it.
Told you.
Yeah. You did.
What the fuck?
You see this?
Here. Do those.
Oh, shit.
So what? They were going to
make fucking snow globes?
Like 10,000 of them?
You check on the boys?
Yeah, I'm going to
roll to the hospital.
You gonna call
Borracho's wife?
Yeah.
All right.
This won't go to Harbor.
I'm sorry you lost
one of your guys.
Thanks.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Yeah.
Nick, you've got to stop
smoking, man.
Here.
It's organic.
You know everything was accounted
for at the Fed, right?
Apparently so.
Hey, is Donnie around?
He quit.
So you haven't
seen him anywhere?
I said he quit.
Two days ago.
You want a beer?
Very much so. Like 50.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Did you see that new chick?
Little fat-ass?
The new girl who works
down the hall?
What's going on, gentlemen?
- Gentlemen, good to see you.
- Yo!
- Good to see you.
- Your wife know where you are?
How did you get that job?
Can you actually count?
I'm in complete
control of my environment.
People don't even know.
Fucking Fraulein.
What's going on, boys?
How you doing?
You good?
Some beers?
Hey, guv.
A round of beers
for my mates.
And for you?
I'm easy.
I don't know.
Surprise me.
I can do that.
- Cheers.
So why you come to me?
You're a beast, man.
Plus, you're the only one
that can pull this off.
Listen.
We do this,
I call the shots.
My crew, my job,
not yours.
Got it?
- Completely understand.
- That's the way it has to be.
That's it.
It's my baby.
That's what I've got.
How did you get
a hold of all this stuff?
You got this all
at that bar?
Collected it over time.
Wow.
Job for Superman.
Cheers.
Thank you. I love when
you call me Princess.
You work across the street?
Yeah.
Diamond exchange?
That's right.
Beer's on me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull