Well, okay,
what would you do, Dee?
I'm saying that if I
were a cop, I would have an Uzi.
Well, but I'm saying that the
police force would never issue
you an Uzi, so now what?
That's not
her point, though.
That's not what we're talking about, that's not my...
Thank you, Charlie.
Listen, if you had the choice,
would you choose to carry one
gun that shoots one bullet or
would you choose to carry an
Uzi— one gun that shoots a
thousand bullets in one second?
Yeah, you're shooting
bullets everywhere.
I agree with her 100%.
- Right?
- I mean, she's absolutely right.
Got people coming at
you from every angle.
Frank, honestly, if you're going to join
in the conversation, will you swallow
your food and then speak?
It's disgusting.
Yeah, hey, Frank, what
are you eating over there?
A hoagie.
You are not eating a hoagie.
You are just jamming meats and
cheeses inside of your mouth.
I like to make it in my mouth.
It tastes better.
Frankie?
Gino?
You piece of shit!
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you, I'll kill
you, I'll kill you!
Now, this is interesting.
Yeah.
Now, do we break this up?
No, no, n-no, d-don't
break it up.
I want to see how this
whole thing plays out.
Oh!
Okay, well, that
seemed to settle it.
Yep.
Okay, all right,
okay, all right.
Jesus Christ, Frank, who
the hell is this man?
My goddamn brother.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com
Frank, I had no idea
you had a brother.
Yeah, what gives, Frank?
You told us your
brother was dead.
Yeah, you said that he had
his guts sucked out of his
asshole through a hot tub drain.
You told that to my
own niece and nephew?
Uh, well, technically, sir, he's
not our father, which would
mean you're not our uncle.
Yeah, we thought he was for a
long time, and then as it turns
out... You know what?
It's a whole thing, so...
Yeah, let's not get into it.
How could you do
this to me, Frankie?
Do what, Gino?
You know what I'm talking about.
You're trying to
steal her from me.
She's my woman.
You stole her from me first.
Well, you stole her back.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, who the hell
are you guys talking about?
The love of my life.
Well, this just got
more interesting.
I'm gonna pull up a
seat and get into it.
This just got very
interesting, Frank.
Why don't you walk
us through this?
No, I'm not dragging
this shit up again.
This is ancient history.
No, no, no, I think
they need to hear this.
I think they need to hear what a
liar and a cheat their father is.
Let me start at the beginning.
It was back in the '60s.
I'm gonna jump in for a
second 'cause it sounds like
you're about to launch
into a whole thing.
Is it going to
take a long time?
My attention span
is very short.
That's a valid concern.
It'll take as long as it takes.
Ah... okay.
Well, we might pop
in and out mentally.
Yeah, you know, our generation— it's like...
Yeah, you want to make it
funny or something?
Give it some flair.
Okay, it was in the '60s.
If you were looking for me,
you'd find me at a happening
little jazz club on the
north side of town.
It was an all-black joint.
Blacks played the best music.
Not that I gave a
shit— I got a tin ear.
It all sounded like a
bunch of noise to me.
See, I was running numbers
as a bookie for the club.
I'd take bets for
the owner Reggie.
Yo, Gino.
He had a temper.
He also had a weakness for betting horses
and a strength for losing those bets.
You see, Reggie owed me money, and when
he came up short, I called in a favor.
I need you to hire someone.
I ain't hiring another one
of your bimbos, Gino.
This bimbo is my little brother.
He's here every night
for the music.
He's more Negro-ish than
anybody else in this club.
Frankie.
Gino.
How would you like to work here?
Would I ever?
I love the music, sir.
He's just a kid.
How old are you, boy?
Nineteen.
Shit, you don't
look a day over 12.
I'll do anything.
I was looking out for
my younger brother.
I was keeping him
out of trouble.
I got Frankie a job
and he loved it.
That was a shit job.
I was mopping up puke, I was
busing tables and washing dishes.
It stunk.
♪ So far, so good...  ♪
But at least I had that sweet
music to keep me going.
♪ So far, so good...  ♪
And then one night I heard
the voice of an angel.
No, not her.
♪ So far, so good ♪
Keep going.
♪ I thought by now You
would be long gone... ♪
That's her.
♪ So far, so good...  ♪
Boy, she was the cat's meow.
That was Shadynasty.
Got to stop you.
Good time to stop.
Okay, so... The love of your life
was a black woman named Shadynasty?
Yeah.
So what's wrong with that?
Well, th-th-there's
nothing wrong with it.
Lots of things.
It's strange, it's strange.
It's just unexpected.
Yeah, that's strange.
Shadynasty.
Well, go on, though.
All right.
All right, so it was late one night, I
was cleaning up, doing my usual routine.
Are you out of
your goddamn mind?
I saw you with her.
Bitch, if I want to be with another
woman, I'll be with another woman.
Hey, hey, hey, relax.
Relax, relax, be cool,
daddy-o, be cool.
Gino, get this bitch
out of my sight.
You just be cool, man,
don't blow your top.
Breaking my dishes,
bitch, goddamn.
Hey, Frankie here is gonna take you
home and I'm gonna talk to Reggie.
He old enough to drive?
Sure.
For a while, we drove in silence until I
finally got the nerve to speak to her.
You got a huge set on you.
Excuse me?
Pipes— you got a great voice.
Oh, thank you.
You like black music?
Do I?
I'm gonna open a jazz joint of
my own someday— an integrated
place where blacks and
whites can get along.
No Orientals, though.
You got to have a
dream, I guess.
And you're going to be
my star attraction.
Child, I ain't nothing
but a backup singer.
Oh, no, you're the real,
true star, Shadynasty.
You just need a
sky to shine in.
If I didn't know better, I'd
think you were flirting with me.
White man. Get down.
Whoa, why were you
shoving her head down?
You did not want to be caught out in the
street in those days with a Negress.
They'd tear you apart.
Negress?
What?
Whatever the proper word was.
Well, it's not that,
it's a different word.
It wasn't that.
We're talking '60s terms.
Okay.
Okay, you used those terms.
You shouldn't have.
Did you open the club or what?
You bet your ass I did.
With hard work
and perseverance.
Bullshit. We opened the club
with my gambling money.
And that's when we became
business partners.
The point is, we opened the club, and
we named it after our star attraction.
Shady-nasty's?
Shadynasty's, asshole.
Whatever.
He's out of here.
Is that how you spell it?
So business was booming.
♪ Like fire needs the
air to breathe... ♪
Shadynasty was a star.
♪ Desire's coming over me I
wanna please you, babe... ♪
And every night, it seemed
like she was singing to me.
♪ Oh...
sometimes it gets me... ♪
'Cause she was.
Frankie's dreams
were coming true.
Mmm... But sometimes
dreams come at a price.
Well, well, well.
Ain't this some shit.
Hi, Reggie.
How you doing?
Not good, Frankie.
No?
I gave you everything.
Then you go and
take my best bitch.
I'm not anyone's bitch.
I left you, Reggie.
I'm with Frank now.
Oh, you with her now, huh?
Yeah.
I guess that don't leave
me with no choice...
but to be a mature-ass
adult about this shit.
I'm working on my temper.
But know..
that I strongly disagree with this!
She's your problem now.
Good luck, Frankie.
Gino, what are you doing?
Saving your life.
Run, Frankie.
No, don't...
The police carted off me and Reggie.
I got two years in the
slammer and Reggie got six.
Wait. Why did Reggie get
more years than you?
You beat the man half to death.
He was black.
Those were the days.
You sound like you yearn
for those days, Frank.
No.
I'm just saying those
were the days.
Huh.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Anyway, by the time I got out of
prison, the '70s had arrived.
♪ I was searching for someone to love
me Hold me close and put no one
above me... ♪
Ah, bro, so good
to have you back.
My brother.
I missed you, Frankie.
I really missed you.
Oh, I missed...
What the shit is that?
A little bump of coke.
Since when do you do drugs?
Prison. It's the '70s, Frank.
Everybody does drugs.
Gino, Gino, Gino, Gino, not, not...
not in my club.
No, no, no.
No, drugs are trouble.
I don't want no trouble.
Relax.
I got a gun for protection.
Wait!
What are you doing
with that gun?
You take a gun out?
No drugs, no guns... No trouble.
Hey, I could eat.
Give me something.
Help yourself.
Make a sandwich in your mouth.
It tastes really good.
I know how to do it.
I'm the one who
taught you to do it!
Oh, God.
This is insufferable.
Oh, my... Please, just continue.
I just wanted to make an
honest woman of Shadynasty.
Settle down, start
a life together.
I was building up the
nerve to ask her.
I want those peas.
Let me see that.
Okay, all right... While I was busting
my ass running the club, saving money
wherever I could, Gino was
just having one big party.
No, no, I never
danced with no guys.
Maybe you did, maybe you didn't.
No-no, no-no-no-no.
I'm going to tell
you how it went.
First off, I was banging babes
left and right, left and right.
But my past came
back to bite me.
Get lost, bimbo.
Gino.
Reggie, you're out of prison.
It ain't Reggie no more.
It's Hakim Mohamed.
What's with the getup?
Prison changed me.
I'm a Black Panther now.
We strong black men; we don't
take kindly to you slingin' dope
in our hood, you dig?
Are you threatening me?
You bet your ass I am.
But maybe this will
change your mind.
Ah, shit.
It's a goddamn petition!
What the hell?
I thought he was pulling a gun.
All right, I'm going to
take care of this, Frankie.
You got to disappear
for a while.
Disappear?
Where am I going to disappear to?
We're going to get you
to South America.
I got connections.
South America?
What about Shadynasty?
I'm gonna look after Shadynasty.
Frankie!
Shadynasty!
No! Shadynasty!
That's when I started
my new life.
Colombia.
What a dump.
Gino scored me a job all right.
I was quality control for his
Colombian cocaine connection.
I'd become everything I hated.
The only thing that kept me going
was writing letters to Shadynasty.
I wrote her every night.
But I never heard back.
Shadynasty!
I occupied my mind immersing
myself in the culture.
Taking in the cuisine.
But mostly doing cocaine.
Ah!
That part was a blast actually.
Weeks turned into months, and
months turned into years.
But I had to wean myself off.
I was living life just
going through the motions.
I knew I had to get back home.
Back to Shadynasty.
Yes!
You shouldn't be calling.
It's too risky.
The little birdie wants
to fly back to the cage.
It's too close to the stove.
There's too much heat.
The little birdie
can stand the heat.
He wants to migrate home.
The little birdie can't come home
on account of the attempted murder!
Why'd you say that, Gino?
You used my name.
I'm going to hang up now.
And don't come home, Frankie.
Now you used my name!
♪ Please don't talk
about being true... ♪
I had to get back.
So I snuck into the States.
And what I saw when I
got home made me sick.
♪ Please don't talk about
all the plans we had... ♪
What was once a clean, respectable
jazz club had turned
into a drug-filled
disco shithole.
♪ I want some action
I want to live! ♪
And that's when I
saw my brother.
♪ I want to give it I want
to get some, too... ♪
With Shadynasty.
♪ I love the nightlife I've got to
boogie On the disco round, oh, yeah
Oh, I love the nightlife... ♪
I'm sorry to bust up your party!
What?
I said I'm sorry to
bust up your party.
What are you doing here?
I was homesick.
But now I'm just regular sick.
Why?
You were gone!
He was here!
What?
She said that you were
gone, and I was here.
Oh, to get you hooked on drugs?
Shadynasty, you have a choice.
You can live a life with me, or you can
live a life with him, and with drugs.
What's it going to be?
Drugs.
Huh?
I choose drugs.
Drugs?
Drugs!
She said drugs.
You know, it's the way
things go in the world.
You understand.
You son of a bitch!
Frankie, no...
Stop it! Stop it!
You bald son of a bitch!
I was bald before you were bald.
You son of a bitch!
Break it up.
You could have had
any girl you wanted.
She was my one and only.
You stole her from me.
You're stealing her from me.
I found the new love letters you've
been writing to her, Frankie.
Talking about meeting up
again and running away.
What are you talking about?
I haven't written
to her in years.
Bullshit!
They're all signed, "Love,
your one and only."
I should have destroyed these, like I
destroyed the letters from Colombia.
What?
You destroyed the letters
I wrote to Shadynasty?
I intercepted and I
read every one of them.
They were poetry.
Each one was more
beautiful than the last.
Too beautiful, though.
I couldn't let
Shadynasty read them.
Not if she was going
to stay with me.
But these letters—
these are smut.
"I want to be in you.
My dick is a raging
bull for you."
And this one, here, "Meet me at the
airport, Friday, at 5:00, Terminal C.
Love, your one and only."
You are trying to steal her from me,
Frankie, and I ain't gonna let you.
Gino, Gino.
That's not me.
I'm telling you, I
never wrote those.
What?
I'm putting something
together here.
She's at the airport right
now meeting some dude.
So, like, if you want to try and
get her back, you got to move.
Guys, it's almost 5:00.
Now I'd like to see this
whole story play out.
It's appealing to
the romantic in me.
I feel like I want to see it.
Come on, man.
Let's go to the airport.
Let's do it.
All right, go.
This is the gate.
I don't see a black
woman anywhere.
No.
I mean, there's her, but...
That's her!
What?
Really? That is not at all
what I was picturing.
No.
No, right?
Shadynasty.
Frankie!
Oh, my word!
Oh, you're still as
beautiful as ever.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know, I wrote to you every
single day from South America.
I mean, I really feel like
we could still be together.
There's still a chance for us.
Shadynasty, I'm sorry
for whatever I did.
Please, don't go.
Don't choose Gino, choose me.
No, no, no, you choose me.
I have loved you all my life.
No, pick me.
No.
Our love was strong.
We were together.
Pick me, pick me.
Pick me, Shadynasty.
I'm sorry, but I pick him.
Ain't this some shit.
Reggie.
Reggie?
Whoa, everyone's a lot fatter
than I was expecting them to be.
Yeah.
Last time I saw you, Frankie,
you had me sent to jail.
But I forgive you.
That's all in the past.
Reggie is your one
and only, huh?
He was all along.
But because of you two,
he was always in jail.
I could never be with him.
Excuse me, Mr. Mohamed?
Yeah?
Your name came up
on a no-fly list.
I need you to come with us.
Oh, hell no.
I'm supposed to be
getting on this flight.
Sir, please cooperate.
Listen, I'm getting on that
plane with Shadynasty.
That's it.
Let's take him down.
Wait! Oh, hell no!
Times have changed!
It can't still be like this!
Leave him be.
Reggie? No!
Did you call that in?
No, that just happened.
Oh... Guess times kind of
haven't changed much, huh?
If I'm being honest,
she looked like shit.
Mm.
Yeah.
She did not age well at all.
No.
Did she ever look good?
She was never attractive.
I guess black can crack.
That's still...
still kind of racist.
Yeah, that's racist.
Is anybody hungry?
Yeah, I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
Well, let's go eat.
Hey, did Frankie ever tell you
about the time that I threw
him off the John
Wanamaker Building?
You son of a bitch.
He told us about that.
I can't— I can't listen
to another goddamn story.
I don't want to hear that story.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com