So from now on, we'll refer to each
other by our Spanish nombres.
There will be...
What's this?
It's okay, it's okay.
Do it.
Buenos dias, Winger.
Ah. Class dismissed.
[###]
Hey.
Shirley, look.
I'm Annie's backpack.
Mmm.
Stop it, Troy.
Annie, say there are two friends
and they're in the same class,
and one of them wants to ask
the other one out on a date.
Like a grownup date, but within biking
distance of his parents' house.
Well, they could do
something on campus.
Tomorrow, there's a picnic with
live music on the east lawn.
They're calling it
A Night Under the Stars.
Cool. I bet Randi would
love that type of thing.
Randi?
Oh, I thought...
Oh.
You thought...
I can't believe I misled you
like that.
Listen, Randi can be the name
of a guy or a girl.
And in this case,
it is definitely a girl.
Thanks for your help.
You're welcome.
And I hate you.
And I wanna have your children.
Damn, I picked the wrong
couple to follow this morning.
Jeff and Britta are dead air.
Are you okay? It looks like you
have actual bed head this morning.
In fashion, I'm what's
known as a tastemaker.
And you missed an entire side
of your face shaving.
And next month,
so will Gwen Stefani.
Here comes Vaughn. Bye.
Oh, crap.
Vaughn? Vaughn.
Oh, the guy with
tiny nipples you did it with.
Oh, God. Hi, Vaughn.
Can we talk sometime?
I'm sorry about how things ended.
Well, I'm sorry I can't accept your
apology because you're toxic, Britta.
You know what? You're like the
exact opposite of an antioxidant.
Yeah. Pssh.
I got band practice. Lates.
Can't we still be friends?
Isn't the word "later"
already short enough?
Let me talk to him for you.
It'll be better if it's man-to-man.
We won't be thinking about our chubby thighs
or whether or not we can have babies.
Don't talk to Vaughn.
Your hormones
are clouding your...
Don't talk to Vaughn.
That is girl for "talk to Vaughn."
[###]
Ooh.
Sure you don't want a piece of that?
Shirley.
What is he doing?
Oh, I know exactly
what he's doing.
My ex-husband spent
four weeks doing that
after his innocent mistake
of calling me Valerie.
That boy is living in his car.
I lived in my car for a stretch
in the '70s.
Nothing like bedding a woman
on the vinyl back seat of a Skylark.
Of course, we didn't have the same
safety standards back then, so... Heh.
No condoms.
I tell you, before AIDS:
sex was like shaking hands.
Hence, AIDS:
Oh, Brittles, I forgot to tell you.
I went and talked to Vaughn.
What?
Bad news is I could not patch up
things between you.
You really did a number on him.
Good news is I'm the new
keyboardist in his band.
I asked you not to talk to him
and you completely ignored me.
Hey, Tiny, you're missing
the headline. I'm in a rock band.
Oh, I'd like to be there
when the band finds out.
Oh, hi, Jeff. We were just talking
about how in today's economy...
Mm-mm! Living in your car. Living in your car.
You are living in your car.
I'm sorry, I'm not good
at being coy. Ahem.
Guys, I'm not living in my car.
I'm just sleeping in it
for a couple of days
while I work out some problems
with my condo.
It's a very temporary issue.
Gotta pay some meaningless fees.
They'll put my locks back
on the door and that'll be that.
How are you gonna
get the money?
Believe me, kitten,
Winger's got moves.
Jeff, do you need
a place to stay?
I'd offer,
but my dad's kind of racist.
You could stay with me in the dorms.
My room has a bunk bed.
A misnomer,
because it's the real deal.
The next person that offers me
charity or pity
will be mentioned by name
in my suicide note.
Oh.
[###]
Annie, Annie, thanks for your advice
about A Night Under the Stars.
Of course. Anytime, ever.
Now I've just gotta figure out
what to bring to the picnic.
This is my first college girl,
so I really wanna impress her.
Would you mind helping me
shop for this stuff?
I'd love to.
Really?
Sure.
No.
Thanks. Later.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey. Wanna see my place?
I can see it from here.
Two girls are making out on the hood.
No, my real place.
Look at that.
Condo board's trying to bluff me
by listing my place as available.
But look at those faucets.
Handcrafted in Italy.
One hundred percent expensive.
Those faucets are beautiful.
You know what they would
go great with? A home.
Which you no longer have.
You need to move on with your life.
Move on with my life?
Shmove shmon shmith shmy shfime.
This condo is all
that's left of me.
Every part of it
is a part of who I am.
Is that a bidet?
That part's for resale value.
And Saturday afternoons.
You know, downgrading your lifestyle
is your chance to grow as a person.
Maybe even become one.
You know, the less you have,
the more you can be.
You know what I'm saying?
There's a silver lining here,
isn't there?
You're attracted to bums.
Good night.
Come on. Why don't you
have dinner at my place?
I got a hotplate that plugs
into a cigarette lighter.
Yeah, but your kitchen's
being towed.
[###]
Stop! That's my house!
Can I live with you?
Yeah, cool.
Do you want top bunk
or bottom bunk?
Top.
Me too. Race you for it.
I win.
[###]
Look, I really need to
liquidate some assets.
It's an emergency situation.
What kind of offer is that?
These are mint-condition issues.
I mean, the premise
alone is priceless.
The guy has the powers
and strength of a spider.
MAN
Your incredulity perplexes me.
No, your incredulity
perplexes me, nerd.
Did I say anything in my sleep about
farm animals or Brian Williams?
I don't think so.
Cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Lucky Charms?
How are you so satisfied all the time?
I mean, don't you ever want anything
more out of life than cereal?
Sometimes I pour
hot cocoa mix into cold milk
and drink it like a cold hot chocolate.
I call it special drink.
Someday you will know it by
its true name, diabetes.
You're Goldie Hawn, Jeff.
I'm sorry?
You're Goldie Hawn.
Is it the lips?
No.
In Overboard,
she was just like you.
Wealthy, assertive, arrogant,
got manicures all the time.
She fell off her boat
and it was good for her.
She realized she was happier poor,
raising unruly boys with Kurt Russell.
Can I not be Kurt Russell?
Do whatever you want.
You just have to know
what that is.
For me, it's Lucky Charms
and TV.
I could use a break.
A picnic blanket. Genius.
I was gonna lay down newspaper.
It's the blanket my grandmother
used to court my grandfather.
Yeah? That's pretty hot.
Thanks.
Oh...
Tell that boy how you feel.
It's scary.
If he's not interested,
I could lose the friendship too.
You could. Love is a gamble always,
but waiting won't change the dice.
You either roll them
or you lose your turn.
I'm going to roll them.
I am.
I just... I need
a few more shakes.
Mm. Shake them
in your mind, okay?
If you'll excuse me,
Pierce's band is playing.
And I wanna record
the train wreck.
Kind of hoping for
a Michael Richards situation.
This is for you.
Oh, they're pretty good.
This isn't weird for you?
No.
Just wanna show Vaughn some support
to help smooth things over.
♪ Saying goodbye to Britta
Was the hardest thing to do ♪
♪ But when someone's a bitch
And a liar ♪
♪ There ain't nothing left to woo ♪
♪ I'm getting rid of Britta ♪
What am I doing?
♪ I'm getting rid of the B ♪
♪ She's a no-good B ♪
♪ I'm getting rid of Britta ♪
♪ I'm getting rid of the B ♪
♪ She's a GDB ♪
Take it, Pierce.
Same as a 45-year-old,
except he doesn't get as tired.
We can pick them from
the cream...
Great to have somebody
to watch stuff with.
My dad never wanted to watch
anything, so I was raised by TV.
TV's the best dad there is.
TV never came home drunk.
TV never forgot me at the zoo.
TV never abused
and insulted me.
Unless you count
Cop Rock.
Cop Rock. That sounds cool.
Doesn't it?
Hey.
Wow.
You guys are really
dorming it up in here, huh?
Yeah. In the last two days,
I've spent a quarter.
We're having the time
of our lives.
See? Who needs
platinum faucets?
Do you guys even have
faucets in here?
There's a communal bathroom
down the hallway.
It actually helped me come
to terms with losing my condo.
You don't sit on a toilet like that until
you've left the material world behind.
Pavel!
Hey, bros.
This is Pavel. He lives next door.
He's from Poland.
Britta?
♪ I'm getting rid of
Britta Getting rid of the B ♪
Excuse me. I have a future
murder victim to visit.
Cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Sorry?
Guys, what the hell?
"Getting Rid of Britta"?
That song was
disrespectful to me
and to the definition
of rhyme scheme.
Wow. If you don't like my song, you
don't have to listen, all right?
I'm an artist
and I write what I feel.
And I feel that you suck.
Oh, oh. All right, hold on, Vaughn.
Can I have a word with you?
Could you come here,
please, for a second?
What did you just say to her?
Listen, I know Britta's your friend,
but my song is more important.
Your song?
We wrote it together.
Are you trying to Garfunkel me?
Maybe, assuming
to Garfunkel someone
is to put up with them even
though they're a fat, lazy cat
who hogs the spotlight
and eats all the lasagna.
I get it. You're jealous of me.
What? Why?
Maybe because when
I put on these skinny jeans
my ass looks
like a baby pumpkin.
Or maybe because I'm not
a small-nippled credit-hogging jag
who only knows
three power chords.
My band, my song.
You want that, huh, Pierce?
How do you like that?
Aah!
You get on that horse.
Lates!
Pierce, did you just defend
my honor?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Totally.
You'll light the candles
and you'll take a bite
and she'll take a bite
and you'll laugh.
And you'll offer her
your letter jacket
after you notice this funny way
she shakes when she gets cold.
And she'll feel like
the luckiest girl in the world.
Right.
[###]
I couldn't have done this without
your help. You're really nice.
We should've hung out more
in high school.
Remember when you pretended
to be my backpack?
Oh. Yeah, yeah.
I'm funny.
All right. Ah.
I gotta go get ready.
Troy, wait. I have to tell you.
My appendix is bursting.
What?
Yeah. Yeah.
My appendix is bursting.
Oh. Oh, no.
Okay, two young students.
I think I've been
to this dance before.
You guys are
sexual partners, right?
Us? No.
No, he's my very good friend,
and I have appendicitis.
Oh.
Thanks for bringing me here.
Guess I ruined your date, huh?
Okay.
Doesn't seem to be
anything wrong with you.
Cool. I'll see you.
God. Where does it hurt?
Everywhere.
We have to quarantine you.
We gotta get you to a safe distance.
My date's on the east lawn.
East lawn, perfect.
Great.
Wait, wait. This is a date?
Yeah, you need these.
Nice. I'll be thinking of you.
Okay, I need to go.
No, we...
We have to observe you
overnight. It's policy.
We don't want another
Vanessa Parsons on our hands.
She was the Typhoid Mary
of herpes.
I'm kind of the Hawkeye
around here, so it's kind of a...
Are you seeing anybody?
[###]
You guys weren't
in Spanish class.
Knight Rider marathon.
The shadowy flight into the world
of a man who does not exist.
Britta, may I have a word?
Has this always been here?
You need to take Jeff back.
Mmm. Never had him,
don't want him, especially now.
He's got a real Phil Spector
vibe going.
He's like E.T.
He crashed in my place
and we're friends now,
which is great for me,
but bad for him.
He needs to get back.
What am I supposed to do?
Use your lady parts.
Abed.
Don't be naive. The charge between
you two is keeping him going.
Tell him you'll make love to him if he takes
a shower and finds a nice place to live.
I'm heading back.
Pavel's making bobka.
Do it, Britta. Seduce him.
Draw the tapeworm of Jeff's old self out
with the milk that is your sexuality.
No.
Then say goodbye to E.T.
[###]
Abed, it's open.
And your wife is married to an idiot.
What's wrong now, woman?
You.
You can't see further than them...
What are you doing?
That was The Jeffersons, honky.
I was wrong, okay?
Material possessions are important.
How much happier were the Jeffersons
than that family on Good Times?
Yeah, but they had good times.
Do good times really matter?
What about good cars,
good lobster?
What about that sport where
the British people ride the horses
with the really long hammers?
Jeez, you are way out
of your element here.
Yes, and I do not believe
a single word I am saying for me.
But for you?
Maybe you're one of those rare people
with nothing underneath the surface.
Maybe if you put stain remover
on a turd, you don't get a diamond.
You just get a turd
with less direction in life.
Thanks, coach.
Can you turn the TV back on?
Faucets.
Italian faucets. Handcrafted.
These look like...
Wait.
I made this notch to indicate
optimal cleansing temperature
for combination skin.
These were mine?
For a fancy condo,
you've got awful security.
Install those in a new apartment
so that every day,
when you spend
too much time on your hair,
you can look down and think:
"I was a huge phony before.
I can do it again."
Yeah.
You're into me.
I beg your unbelievable pardon?
Look at all this work you're doing
just to have me around again.
You were more attracted to me
than you were willing to admit.
I was doing this all for Abed.
You are the worst.
Yeah, clearly.
[###]
Sorry.
Greendale, thank you for...
I want you to know I haven't changed
my mind about the band. I'm out.
We wanna recognize
a couple of sponsors.
First off is Anderson Septic.
Also, do me a favor,
will you? Lay off Britta.
I mean, she may walk
like she just got off a horse,
but underneath all that clown
makeup, she's a good kid.
Mm-hm. No worries, man.
I've moved on.
Lates.
Lates, okay.
Snakes. What...?
Greendale!
♪ Pierce, I don't
need you In my band ♪
♪ I don't need your heart
Or your hand ♪
♪ I am my own person ♪
♪ And, Pierce, you're a B ♪
Yeah, you heard me say it.
♪ Pierce, you're a B ♪
No!
Before you two proceed,
I have one thing to say.
Did you say it already?
I want my nana's blanket back.
Do you guys mind?
Could you scoot over?
It's an heirloom. I want it.
Thank you.
Have a nice date.
I don't care what you think.
For me, that was huge.
I know, sweetie.
Let's go find you some pants.
Okay?
Yeah, cool, thanks.
♪ This a song
for Pierce Him so old ♪
♪ His body made
Of wrinkles and folds ♪
♪ Stupid and ugly
He smells like a fart ♪
♪ Poo-poo in his pants
And poo-poo in my heart ♪
Hey, look what the cat dragged
out and licked clean.
I saw how much you missed me,
and smelled what happens
to Pavel on cabbage night,
and realized the world
was better off with me in it.
Thanks.
For caring.
Hey.
You looked like you moved out.
I checked into a motel
and I'm looking for apartments.
You would've been fine
with me staying forever?
Yup.
You're pretty cool, Abed.
You're a huge nerd.
Thanks.
ALL # Pierce, Pierce,
Pierce Pierce, you're a B ♪
I'm Pierce.
Yeah, song's about me.
♪ Pierce, Pierce, Pierce
Pierce, you're a B ♪
Yeah!
Come on, sing it for me.
♪ Pierce, Pierce, Pierce ♪
♪ Pierce, you're a B ♪
Yeah, he is.
♪ Pierce, Pierce, Pierce ♪
♪ Pierce, you're a B ♪
Ow!
We are Some Worries!
Good night, Greendale!
♪ East side, west
side North side, south ♪
♪ Vaughn's breath is so bad
His butt's mad at his mouth ♪
♪ This rap is by Pierce
Vaughn is dumb ♪
♪ He wears diapers to bed
And sucks his mother's thumb ♪
♪ And when he wakes up stupid
Wishing he was me ♪
♪ He has a big poop breakfast
With a glass of pee ♪
♪ Then he goes to school
Where he's stupid again ♪
♪ And everybody hates him
Even all his friends ♪
♪ When you come after Pierce
Then the battle is on ♪
♪ So this rap goes out
To stupid Vaughn ♪
Uh-huh. Well played, Pierce.
This isn't over.