A small, fading remnant of a star.
A white dwarf.
That's right.
I used a memory technique.
Dwarves hate being called midgets,
and midgets are small.
Good.
And what does a star turn into
after it collapses?
A movie of the week.
A black hole.
Right.
Troy, you could be an astronomer.
As far as I'm concerned, there's only
one black hole worth studying.
It's called Sagittarius A.
It's located in the center of our galaxy
and it has the density of 40 suns.
Just like my wiener.
Ha-ha.
You said "wiener." That's funny.
Pierce and Troy didn't get along at first but
now they're bonding through mutual adolescence.
Shut up, fart head.
Will you shut up, poo-poo head?
Hi, everybody. Ha-ha.
Well, look at this group.
Having some kind of meeting and
being so diverse. There is just...
Boy, there is just one
of every kind of you, isn't there?
Well, we are missing a pipsqueak
but we don't want one, so beat it.
Uh, Pierce, that's the dean.
You kidding?
Sorry. Just my luck.
It's all right. Don't let me interrupt.
Sometimes, I just roll around campus
like a little football.
I can't believe this.
Here I am in a random conversation
about football,
and I'm talking to Troy Barnes, star
quarterback from Riverside High. Whoa. Heh.
Troy, did you know Greendale
has a football team?
Did you know they had a football?
Ah. Heh. Good. That's very funny.
Troy, I was so sorry to hear about your
injury, but now that you have recovered,
we would love for you to play
for the Human Beings.
The team's name is
the Human Beings?
Yeah. My idea.
It was the Greendale Grizzlies
but I thought that, um...
Well, a lot of these students
have been called animals their whole lives.
Unfortunately, I don't
know what to do about the mascot.
Oh. I could help with that,
Your Honor.
I have a wealth of experience
in image management,
icon development,
and Y2K preparedness.
How about you?
Troy isn't interested
in football anymore.
Getting injured in that keg stand
was the best thing
that ever happened to him.
Whoa. Yoko Ono much?
Ha-ha-ha.
Bros before ho's, Troy.
Heh. Listen, man, no offense,
but I was the best
and I finished on top.
I wouldn't play for this school
with a 10-foot pole.
Dean, I'm sure Troy will sign up
for football,
if and when some accident damages
the part of his brain that feels pride.
Until then, would you excuse us?
All right.
Well, uh, if you change your mind,
the field is always open.
Oh, figuratively speaking. You know.
Wednesdays and Sundays
it's used as parking overflow
for the megachurch. Okay. Heh.
Now let's meet the minimum requirements
for a language credit, shall we?
Yes, but I need to go
to the bathroom first. Uh, Britta?
Oh, no, I don't have to go.
I'll go with you.
What? She's offended?
Girls go in groups.
Did you learn nothing
from standup comedy in the '90s?
I'm familiar with the concept,
I just... Uh...
Fine. If it's important to Shirley,
I'll go next time.
I'm willing to try some more
mainstream feminine stuff.
Then you should know nothing says,
"I'm a woman"
like doing it with me.
Nothing says, "I'm a pig," like you.
Will they or won't they?
Sexual tension.
Abed. It makes the group
uncomfortable when you talk
like we're characters in a show
you're watching.
Well, that's sort of my gimmick.
But we did lean on that pretty hard
last week.
I can lay low for an episode.
Are you sure you made the right
call on the football team, Troy?
It looks like
they won something once.
"Most Valued Customer,
Henderson Trophy Cases."
We should still study
a little more astronomy later, right?
Maybe over some Milky Ways
or some Mars bars.
Or pancakes.
"I'm Jeff and I'm a
student at Greendale"?
Well, that's not good.
Wood undergoes rapid oxidation
because it reacts
spontaneously to...
Okay, guys. Seriously.
We've talked about this.
Okay, you have got to turn off
your cell ph...
That's mine. My bad.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Would you like to come with me?
Well, yes. Yes, I would.
That's nice.
Okay, what's it called?
Antoni...? Hold on.
Does anybody have a pen? A pen?
No one has a pen.
Why would you not bring a pen
to class?
Idiot. No, you're not an idiot.
Ha-ha-ha.
I had my blinker on about five
minutes and this no-good,
"clearly bald but trying to hide it
with a bandana" loser swooped right in.
I couldn't believe it.
Maybe he didn't see you.
He saw me.
Maybe he had his blinker on too.
Maybe.
So you got any family, Britta?
Yeah. Whatever.
My mom might visit this weekend.
She and I are gonna get makeovers at that spa...
Makeovers. They sure have us
programmed right.
I am a female pleasure unit.
I require a new coat of paint.
Just something
I thought might be fun.
Here's
something I think might be fun.
Let's find out the number of makeup
companies that are owned by women.
I'll save you the trouble. It's zero.
Of course, you're saying,
"Britta, aren't you a hypocrite?
You're plastered with glitter and goo
from head to toe like the rest of us."
Well, I also pay income tax
and pull over for cops.
But that doesn't mean I support
a country that oppresses citizens,
restricts voting rights...
Thanks for offering to help design
the new mascot.
I, uh, have been a little stumped.
Heh. That's no problem.
By the way, I took the liberty of
thumbnailing a Human Being prototype,
uh, which I modeled
after Da Vinci's Vitruvian Man.
Oh. You're offering it but...
The penis is a little small, I think.
Oh, okay. It looks a lot like you.
Okay.
Um, here's the thing.
If we are the Human Beings,
you know,
and we have a mascot
that's just a white guy,
what message are we sending?
Our symbol needs to reflect
the diversity of our school
and our species.
So, black?
No, because we're not the
Greendale Blacks, Mr. Hawthorne,
or the Greendale Asians,
or any other creed.
We are
the Greendale Human Beings.
Yeah.
Sorry to disturb you guys.
Who are clearly looking at a clearly naked
drawing of Pierce doing jumping jacks.
Dean, a quick download, please?
Uh... Absolutely.
Excuse me.
Okay. Fill me in later.
Whoa-oh.
Ah. Good, a pencil.
First of all, I'm flattered.
Oh, well,
you're a very photogenic man.
Is that real bed head, or do you
put something in there? Can I?
Oh. It's crispy.
I was thinking about
the four disembodied heads
and I thought,
Where's the heart?
Where's the soul?
Where's the different poster design?
You know I did think those
were less than personable.
Which is why
I went with the full bodies
in these mailers we have going out.
Ta-ta-ta.
Mailers?
I didn't give permission for this.
Jeffrey, did you not read
the release agreement
on the back of your registration form?
Heh-heh-heh.
I'm starting to see why someone
used to be a lawyer. Ha-ha-ha.
Look, if someone from the outside
were to find...
Okay, if someone from the outside
were to find out
that I am a student
at a community college,
that could have a negative impact
on my future career.
Oh.
Goodness.
Look what we have stumbled onto.
An opportunity to help
each other out.
I suppose I wouldn't need
this promotional campaign
if I could announce to the press that
Troy Barnes is playing football here.
I think he's been pretty clear
about declining that offer.
I think if you said jump,
he'd say, "How high?"
If you said stop,
he'd say "Hammer time."
You starting to get what I mean?
Hmm?
No, I need another example.
You know, I didn't realize before,
but we should send those out
to local businesses.
Law firms, lawyer companies,
legal gatherings.
You trying to blackmail me?
I think so.
Gentlemen, I present to you
the Greendale Human Being.
That's a falcon with a gun.
Now it's a falcon with an erection.
Oh, hi, Abed.
Hmm.
Bye. He's just laying low.
Oh, are you going to the bathroom?
Uh... Yes.
I'll go with you.
You know what? I'm good.
She probably just, you know,
had to go number two.
Okay, what's the closest planet
to Earth?
Planet Hollywood?
Ha-ha-ha.
That's not the right answer but
it shows how fun astronomy can be.
Hey, Troy,
can I talk to you for a sec?
We're studying, so Troy's busy.
Well, the galaxy's
not going anywhere.
I'll bring him back.
You ever miss being
a quarterback, Troy?
I miss being the best
at something.
I miss having a coach.
I miss knowing what to think.
You still know what to think, Troy.
Oh, good.
For instance, after the dean
talked to you about football,
you and I were thinking
the same thing.
That dude looks like Moby.
We were thinking, what if
Troy did play for Greendale?
You'd be surprised at how many of
your favorite football players
got started at community college.
Really? Name one.
Who's your favorite player?
Me. Whoa.
Maybe you and I should go check out
the Greendale Thunderdome.
The dome arrives later.
It comes with thunder.
Let me tell you
a little secret about me, Troy.
Every day, on my way to school,
I drive through downtown,
past the courthouse,
just to get a glimpse of the world
that I once ruled.
And I just wanna jump out of my car,
run up the steps,
and exploit the legal system
for profit.
But I can't.
I'm locked out of my old kingdom.
You're not.
You see what I'm saying?
You're saying I could be a lawyer.
I'm saying you're a football player.
It's in your blood.
That's racist.
Your soul.
Your eyes?
That's gay?
That's homophobic.
That's black.
That's racist.
Damn.
When you played, you were a god.
Now you're not playing
and you're not.
I'd tell you to do the math,
but math isn't important.
The only thing
that's important is this.
Yeah, but Annie said...
Annie said that Benjamin Button
was compelling. Look, she's a smart
girl but sometimes she's just wrong.
Eighty-five, go long.
It's like a drug, isn't it?
Feel it, Troy. Throw it.
The scoreboard lights up.
There will be a scoreboard there.
It's complete. Nice catch.
The girls, the glory,
the scouts, the career.
It starts when you join this team.
Is that linebacker
a pregnant woman?
Look, you can meet them later,
but this decision has to be yours,
T-Bone.
And this decision has to be yes.
How did you know my nickname
was T-Bone?
Because you're a football player
and your name begins with T.
Your name begins with T.
Britta?
Oh, are you finished?
I mean, I have to go, but apparently,
I failed yesterday's tryouts
for the position
of bathroom companion.
Oh, Britta, I wasn't trying
to hurt your feelings.
Heh. You didn't hurt
my feelings, Shirley.
I don't need to go to the bathroom
with other people.
I was just trying to throw you a bone
because I like you.
Oh. You can keep that bone.
Listening to a story about a stranger pissing
me off and taking the stranger's side?
And then you can't talk
about your own business
but you insinuate
my mama's a robot
because she and I want makeovers.
That is the ladies room, Britta.
A place where ladies go to share,
listen, support each other,
and discretely eliminate waste.
And I like you too.
I even like that you're a little hard,
but if you can't learn
to be soft in there,
you need to pee alone.
I've peed alone my whole life.
Women have always hated me.
I don't even know how it started.
Maybe it was when I got boobs
before everybody...
Shhh.
Not out here.
In there.
Whoo! Ha-ha.
Troy, Troy, the wonder boy.
You dropped your books,
Poindexter. Heh-heh-heh.
Troy, I've been waiting for an hour.
It's all right. I'm worth it.
♪ Hip hop, body don't stop ♪
♪ Riverside got the broom
Don't need a mop ♪
♪ Put your team in a box
Put a ribbon on top ♪
♪ We're not John Kerry
Because we don't flip flop ♪♪
Troy, why are you doing our politically
conservative high school's
shamefully outdated fight rap?
Have you been playing football?
Threw the skin around
a couple of times. I still got it.
Uhn, uhn, uhn. Doosh! Uhn.
But you knew
we had an Astronomy test tomorrow.
Class blows. What I need to know
about the universe
is that I'm at the center of it.
♪ Oh Bing, bong, sing along ♪
♪ Your team's Al Gore
Your views are wrong ♪♪
Troy, stop.
Don't become this person again.
This isn't the real you.
This is the arrogant jock
that totally ignored the only people
that truly liked him
for non-superficial reasons
but weren't allowed to say anything
because their parents are bigots.
Huh?
Football is bad for you, Troy.
Jeff said you'd say that.
Jeff... What now?
Troy. Troy, Troy, Troy.
That's my name.
I think if we add in a little bit of
Phylicia Rashad, we'll be in better shape.
Yeah, you're right.
That beige is a little light.
Um... Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
We are developing
the perfect mascot.
No stereotypical identifiers
from any race or gender.
You see, Jeff, this is a chart of the
features we're staying away from.
Pan-Asian eye folds, uh,
Irish chins, women's breasts.
Is that Seal?
Oh, that is our human color wheel.
It goes from Seal to Seal's teeth.
What do you think?
I think not being racist
is the new racism.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What happened to the prototype?
Ooh. I left the nose in the kiln.
Oh.
So Troy is gonna play football.
Yes.
Which means
I'll be getting rid of these.
No, uh, I won't mail these out
but they are staying with me
until the press announces
that Troy is a part of the team.
And I want him at that pep rally tonight.
Reporters are gonna be there.
We're gonna unveil
the new mascot
and things are finally
going to start turning around.
Oh, and my ex-therapist
is gonna think twice
before he makes fun of my job!
Here it is. Still hot.
Ooh. Ow.
Oh, Dean, I'm gonna get some
more coffee. You want anything?
Yeah, uh, a Desmond Tutu with just enough
cream to make it a Lou Diamond Phillips.
La Bamba. Got it.
Aha!
I've been following you.
How much did the dean pay you
to make Troy play football?
I'm not having a conversation with
someone who emerges from a bush.
Because I'm right?
No.
Because I'm not in a commercial
for breakfast cereal.
Look, the dean has pictures of me,
okay?
Horrible pictures of me.
Attending his school.
And for that, you've convinced Troy to flush
his life down football's toilet again?
Britta's right. You are the most
selfish person alive.
And all that is gonna end right now.
I'm telling him what kind of friend you really are.
Maybe you should tell him
you're hopelessly in love with him.
High school must have been tough,
huh?
Waiting for a superstar
to notice you.
But here, here, he's all alone
and he needs so much help.
Did you enroll in all his classes or were
you worried that might freak him out?
The important thing is
that you are there for him.
The important thing is that you
are the only one there for him.
And you don't really care
what he wants,
just as long as you don't have
to share him with the world.
Because, really,
you are just as selfish as I am.
You're just not as good at it yet.
You're right.
I could never be as good as you.
Probably because I actually care.
Profound
but technically meaningless.
And don't bother trying that thing
women do where they walk away
and make the guy feel like crap,
because it won't happen.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Shirley, will you
please come to the bathroom with me?
Where's Shirley?
Shirley's not coming.
But, uh, I'm here to listen, girl.
Why do we inflict so much pain
on ourselves for men?
I don't
know, sweetie.
Maybe it's because
men make the world go around?
Kleenex?
I've been infatuated with Troy.
Now he's joining football.
Now he'll have his pick of the litter
and I'll never get to be with him.
Oh, Annie, screw him.
There are guys out there
that would kill to be with you.
If Troy isn't one of them,
that's him failing your standards.
You got that?
You're right. I can't control him.
And if I truly cared about him,
I wouldn't want to.
Thanks for talking to me, Britta.
It really helped.
Seriously?
Yes.
Who's my girl?
Excuse me.
I did it. I did it.
Yes, you did.
Human Beings,
Human Beings, Human Beings.
Troy. Troy.
Don't go in there, man.
What?
You got the most you were ever going
to get out of football in high school.
A life of disillusionment
and depression
begins on the other side
of that door.
Hey, man, is this your first pep rally
or something?
You told me football was the most
important thing in the world.
Well, buckle up, Troy
I was exaggerating.
It's kind of my gimmick.
Let me tell you something.
No, let me tell you something.
You know that keg flip
that cost me my scholarship?
Yeah.
I hurt myself on purpose.
What?
There was a scout coming
to the final game at Riverside
and I couldn't take the pressure.
So I took the easy way out.
When you showed me that field,
I saw there was nothing
to worry about here.
I could just play football
for the fun of it.
I mean,
have you seen these guys?
There is nowhere to go but up.
Dude, we have feelings.
I don't know about you,
but I know I ended up here
because things
weren't that great out there.
You should try accepting
where you're at, man.
Take a pottery class or something.
♪ Greendale, we're number one
Nancy Pelosi is no fun ♪♪
Hey.
I've decided to support Troy.
They deploy things in football.
I went for rhyme over clarity.
Look, I'm, uh...
I'm really sorry about before.
I just think we were both wrong.
Really?
Because I'm an 18-year-old girl
and you made me cry in public.
Hmm. Okay, maybe I was
a little more wrong.
I should grow up
and make peace with being here.
I mean, it's not like Greendale
is gonna kill me or anything.
Holy crap.
Oh!
Sorry. Hey, say hello
to our ethnically neutral mascot,
the Greendale Human Being.
The costume makes it difficult
for him to see.
He can't move his mouth either.
But take it from me,
that's human for "hello."
Let's get you into the pep rally.
Great idea. Let's do it.
We've solved racism. What's next?
Let's do something for
little people. Or albinos.
How about little albinos?
Well, this has the potential to be
a uniquely Greendale experience.
My lady?
My lord.
Attention, students, this is Abed.
And the disco spider.
Here at Greendale.
Greendale.
Say what?
A few quick announcements.
Announcement number one.
All announcements will be cool,
starting right now.
Announcement number two,
butt soup.
Announcement number three,
I am not Hadji from Jonny Quest,
Jeff Winger.
On security news, you guys gotta
start locking the dean's door
so guys like us don't get in.
Hey.