Before we wrap up,
I would like to thank you guys
for filling out these
anonymous evaluation cards.
I found your feedback to be
largely constructive and flattering.
- So, gracias Abed.
- De nada.
You don't have to sign
your name anymore.
Got it.
But there was one evaluation
that was so harsh, and hurtful, and racist...
that I took the time personally to analyze
that handwriting against past exams.
And this particular coward...
dots her I's with tiny,
itty-bitty, little circles.
Boop. Boop.
Isn't that precious and cute?
Who's erratic and unstable
now, princess gringa?
- Nice day out today, isn't it?
- Yeah. Shoot!
- You forget something?
- Yeah.
I forgot to stagger the timing
of my exit with Shirley's.
We both have a class
across campus, and I can't go
that kind of distance
with "ooh, that's nice."
- That's mean.
- No. That's not nice.
I find Shirley very easy to talk to.
And besides, aren't you supposed to have,
like, an olympic gold medal in jibber-jabber?
Yeah, but I'm a sprinter.
I'm at my best during
high-speed bursts of wit.
On a Shirley walk, I'd be winded
by that stoner tree.
Hey, Britta. Hi!
What's up?
- Hey, Vaughn, how's it going?
- No worries.
Interesting. 'Cause I might be worried if I
was playing hacky sack a decade too late.
- My class is that way.
- All right.
But I just wanted to point out that
we easily walked more than 100 yards
with no awkward pauses. And
that is the sign of a true friend, so...
I'm really glad that you're
not hitting on me anymore.
There's the awkward pause.
Sync, corrected by vNaru
Excuse me! Oh, sorry, ladies.
Professor Duncan!
Oh, sorry.
- Annie Edison. I'm in your 101 lecture.
- Hello.
I've heard about your special psych lab.
- The Duncan Principle.
- Yes.
And I know it's limited
to second-year students,
but I had a 4.0 at Riverside High,
and I'm not looking down
But they actually made me lose
my scholarship and virginity.
- Right.
- If you would let me take your lab early,
it would be a real feather
in my transcript.
Okay, I've actually been
in this situation many times,
so I'm just going to be up front.
I'm not allowed to date students.
Even though you're an eight.
Which is a British ten, so I'm angry.
But if, in spite of that,
you are still interested,
then you may join the lab.
Okay. You need to bring
two human subjects.
And it would not hurt your chances one
bit if you could lend me a fiver.
I seem to have left my purse in my duffle
and my duffle in the boot of my lorry, so...
I asked politely, and then
panda took his pants off...
I never even knew
that's what asexual meant.
I wonder what this
express package could be?
Somebody had to get
something to me very fast.
You brought your mail to campus?
Oh, yes. My ear-noculars.
What is that? It looks like
your bluetooth thingie.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is my cell phone headset.
And this is 'ear-noculars'.
It's for spies and whatnot.
It gives you sonic hearing.
- All hearing is sonic.
- What's that?
So, who wants to be
in a psych experiment?
Hey, guys, guys, guys?
Annie is talking about
some kind of experiment.
She's behind you.
Not interested.
Please? You get paid.
- Do they do stuff to your butt?
- No.
Do you get paid more if they
do stuff to your butt?
- No.
- That's fine, I'll do it. I'm in.
How about you, Abed?
It's tomorrow.
Tomorrow? They're showing all four
Indiana Jones at the vista.
I'm really looking forward
to the first three. I bought a whip.
This is really important to me, Abed.
Could you please go as my friend?
My really good friend?
I didn't realize we were
really good friends.
I figured we were more
like Chandler and Phoebe.
They never really
had stories together.
Sure, I'll do it, Chandler.
Thank you, Abed.
I'm gonna go save Britta
from that dude.
Yeah, she looks like she's in trouble.
Hope he doesn't try to
"handsome" her to death.
- And panda has no pants.
- Hey.
Hey, hi, what's up, man? I'm Vaughn.
- You in line?
- Oh, no, no, no.
We're just, uh,
we're just chillin'.
Hey, you're not gonna
order coffee?
- No, I was just gonna see if Britta...
- I mean, no judgment, bro. I used to do coffee.
Then I made the switch
to green tea. It's, like...
It's like filled with these
antioxidants and stuff.
- It's pretty tight.
- Tight, yes!
I've heard that about green tea.
I like green tea. I should make the change.
Up top, sugar bear.
- Yeah, give me some of that.
- There it is.
Small coffee, please.
Britta's making the change to green tea.
Oh, that's good.
It's good for your skin.
Welcome, research assistants.
If you turn your attention to the
monitor, you will see that our subjects
are waiting for the
experiment to begin. But...
it's actually happening right now.
You see, the waiting is the experiment.
The Duncan Principle is simple.
Namely, that the more control
lost by the...
yeah, I'm gonna write this down
too, actually. That's a good point.
The more control lost by the ego,
the more gained by the id,
resulting in a surprisingly predictable,
emotional eruption or breaking point.
Known to Ma and Pa as
a good old-fashioned tantrum.
Annie, why don't you, uh,
go and tell our subjects
that we're going to be starting the
experiment in five minutes, okay?
And Annie...
It's never actually
going to start.
Let's do this.
Hi, everyone.
Hi, Troy.
Hi, Abed.
Hi, señor Chang.
What, a Community College
Spanish teacher can't use 80 bucks?
Well, we're just running
a little bit behind,
- so we'll probably start
in about five minutes. - No!
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
It's unacceptable, all right?
You lied to me!
When you say something
starts at nine, it starts at nueve!
No!
- No!
- Houston, we have an idiot.
Did you know we walk
the same way after class?
I'm sure you didn't or else we
would've been walking together.
Unless you're a jerk.
Just kidding.
- Let's do it.
- Mm-hmm.
Don't go too fast for
these dogs. Short legs.
- So, how do you like...?
- You've got a kid, right?
- What's that?
- Nothing.
So, Pierce isn't exactly
right in the head, is he?
I know a lot of grown men with radar
dishes coming out of their ear.
- He's like inspector gadget.
- Yeah, go, go, gadget incontinence.
And how about that guy that's always
around, flirting with Britta?
- I know! He's the worst! Vaughn?
- I know, and what is it with his hair?
It's perpetually moist.
Okay, we're three hours in,
so let's review what we've seen.
And pay close attention to
every subject's breaking point.
We've got... a shouter.
That one's a stomper.
Bye, hippie.
There's a generic whack job, bouncing
up and down like a six-foot child.
Shaking. Write that down.
Visible shakes.
Look, look at the little one
chase the big one.
Look at him go. I'm gonna make him
go quicker. It's like benny hill looks.
Whoo, ooh, ooh, get him. Come back
again. Whoo, ooh, ooh, get him.
All right?
There's a bit of fun.
It lightens the mood.
And back to the present...
And then, there were two.
Break... Break...
No, no, no! Annie!
What is going on in there?
Why...? What is taking so long?
I've wasted all day here, for you.
The soul train awards
were tonight.
You promised butt stuff!
And... he's out. We got him.
- Strike three, you're gone.
- There's so much dust in here!
Do you know what?
The longer they wait,
the harder they break.
Buckle up, students.
Do you see how often
hacky sack takes his shirt off?
He'd play shirts and skins
in a game of checkers.
I'm so glad to be able
to talk to someone about this.
I wanted to say
something to britta about it,
but we're supposed to be friends now,
and she'd think I was jealous.
I don't see why you
and Britta aren't together.
Two cute white people going
to school together. Just seems right.
Shirley, we're not pandas in a zoo.
Oh. Oh, dear.
That is not what I want to see.
And there goes the shirt.
Hey.
Hey, I'm fine.
Want me to, uh...
Want me to check you
for grass stains?
I wasn't sure how or when to bring up
that I was hanging out with Vaughn.
I figured that you'd
make fun of him... and me.
Uh, first of all, friends do
not make fun of each other,
even if they're being tackled
in the quad by a hippie.
And secondly, Vaughn seems cool.
Well, you guys should
hang out sometime.
I gotta go. I... uh, that
was tacky out there.
- You won't ever see that again.
- Oh, no worries, brah.
Shirley, did you see
Señor Chang's socks today?
Tiny bullfighters.
I can top that. Did you see that
hacky sack wears an anklet?
Since when won't you
talk about Vaughn?
Look, I'm trying to be
a good friend to Britta.
She thought I was gonna make fun of
him, but I want to be unpredictable.
I'm gonna show her that I'm not
the jerk she thinks I am, and...
friend the hell out of that
green-tea-drinking drum circler.
Okay, but tell me you've noticed
how small his nipples are.
- Not engaging.
- What? It's not gossip when it's fact.
- My kids have got hamsters
with bigger nips. - No!
- Oh, well. Jeff!
- No!
- Is it on pause?
- No, that's just him.
Sorry you've been waiting 26... hours.
It's just gonna be
another five minutes.
Okey-dokey.
Oh, my...
Why won't he leave?
- Professor.
- What?
I'm sorry, but this guy's not moving.
I have classes to go to.
Go! Fine!
Go kill John Lennon again, you loser.
He's ruined my study.
He has... He has warped
the Duncan Principle.
Damn you, you outlying piece of datum!
It's you!
It's your fault!
- But you told me to bring subjects.
- Yeah, subjects! Not Rain Man!
I should never have let you into this lab,
miss Annie fanny panties in a bunch!
Oh, that's so hilarious!
Did you think of that the last time
you skipped a trip to the dentist?
Let me answer that
question with another question.
It's not fair! It's not fair!
Why, why, why?
What are you doing?
Put... Stop writing!
Put your pen...!
Give me that!
Get out!
Get out, you dorks!
You have destroyed
the Duncan Principle!
Go home!
Cool.
See ya!
So, uh, Britta said that you did
a lot of community service.
Ultimate frisbee at the Senior's
center. It is amazing.
And what makes frisbee ultimate?
If I had a nickel for every time I wished
somebody asked me that.
I'm gonna get dessert.
Want anything?
Carrots.
Oh, I'm good.
- Hey, you two.
- Hey.
Well, that's a cool shirt.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Where's it from?
- Oh, uh, I don't even know.
I guess it's...
Hey, look at that.
"Hanes Classic."
Oh, that's nice.
You know, people
underestimate the elderly.
You know, but you
see these guys out there
and they're throwing the bee,
and they're just loving life.
- It's just inspiring.
- You know, I'm gonna really...
- I'm gonna think about it.
- All right. I'm gonna go check on Britts.
- See ya.
- You are the devil.
- I know.
¿Adónde van ustedes los Sábados?
Domingo, plus...
- Oh, okay, I...
- Where do we go on Saturdays...?
- You said Sunday.
- I have a question for you.
You like Vaughn, right?
- Oh, he's very cute.
- I'm just worried
that he's thinking
a little bit more intensely
about this thing than I am.
He says stuff, you know, after...
School?
- After...
- Dinner mints?
- Not having sex?
- How was that?
- What? Forget that.
The problem right now
is that he's calling me "babe",
he's trying to hold my hand.
It's getting a little relationship-y.
And he gave me something.
Herpes?
No. This.
- A poem? - How do I respond
to something like that?
"Thank you"?
Well, it's a very good question. And
it's one I will answer. Uh...
Oh, I'm getting a text. I'm just gonna
read it, if you don't mind.
I am reading it... and it is read.
"Did you ever notice where
the ocean meets the sky, did ya?
It's the same wizard blue that
I see in your eye, Britta."
- "Wizard blue"?
- Yeah.
Thank you so much.
You just brightened my day.
I'm so glad we can rip on
that dude again.
Look at this, look at this.
That is the stain of a teardrop
over the word "rad."
Oh, he said "rad"?
I thought he said "bad."
Oh, that makes it worse.
- I'm surprised he can read. You know?
- I know.
Hey, sorry about bailing
on the psych experiment.
That was the experiment, Troy.
We were testing to see how long
people would wait in the room.
Oh, gotcha.
- "Gotcha"? That's all you have to say?
- Yeah.
You sat in a room for 26 straight
hours. Didn't that bother you?
- Yeah, I was livid.
- Then why didn't you leave?
Because you asked me to stay
and you said we were friends.
Wait. Is this still
part of the experiment?
He's more like a puppy
with a fish mouth.
Right, right, it's more like this.
That's right. Laugh it up.
You guys want to know
what they're doing?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
Making fun of all of us.
I heard you with my own
ear... noculars.
- Pierce, we are not making fun of you.
- Ah-hah. Calling me "hacky sack",
and ripping my six pack abs
and my moist hair.
And that face you made?
Well, I think it's pretty obviously, Annie.
Okay, this is definitely still
part of the experiment.
- Pierce, we were not
making fun of you. - Yeah.
We're making fun of Britta's
boyfriend Vaughn.
Oh, good. Well, in that case.
But if we're gonna do something,
let's do it as a team.
I'll get the ball rolling.
Maybe he has a tiny penis.
- Who is this guy?
- You all have got to see him.
Everything's all,
"no worries, no worries."
And he always says hello
three times in a row.
Hello, good evening,
how are you?
And... here, look!
He wrote a poem!
- Can I read it?
- We shouldn't show that.
- It's fine.
- So I'll be done in, like, an hour.
- Yeah, no worries.
- He just said it!
- Guys, you've met Vaughn, right?
- Hey. What's up? Hi.
- What a fool.
- This troop's got a case of the giggles, huh?
Wait... is that...?
Did you give them my poem?
No!
Okay, well, why is the dinosaur
rocking a picture of my poem?
Here, read it.
Oh, you guys are... right?
You guys are laughing at me, aren't you?
- Yeah.
- No.
That's, uh, wow.
This is the least tight thing
that's ever happened to me.
I can't believe you.
Honestly, Jeff, how dare you?
I can hear him outside. He's crying.
Now he's barking.
- Jeff, wait! I'm sorry I sold you out.
- Britta is never gonna forgive me.
I can't believe I showed you that
poem. Oh, my god, my life is Degrassi High.
Oh, Jeff, I have a gossip problem.
I stir the pot, Jeff. I'm a pot stirrer.
This isn't even the only study
group I've had this year.
You see those ladies over there?
I used to be in their group
till they kicked me out.
They called me "tattle-ina."
It's a bumblebee nickname.
It's cute, but it stings.
Hey, look at the size
of that woman's earrings.
It's like little dogs
should be jumping through them.
- This is never going to work. This has to end.
- Look at them.
Shirley, don't do this.
Look, we can still hang out.
It's just, you know,
we won't bag on people.
Come on, Jeff. What are
we gonna talk about?
My kids? Your doctor career?
- I was a lawyer.
- See? I'm already bored.
Well, we'll always have
"tiny nipples."
They were tiny.
Okay. Jeff, wait, wait.
I know I shouldn't do this,
but one last little piece of gossip.
Britta told me she had
a sex dream about you.
You still have a chance.
- Details.
- Mm.
Details! Details!
Abed, here.
I wanted to say sorry
for yelling at you.
Indiana Jones. Cool.
I just got the first three because...
- The fourth one blows.
We're cool.
- Britta!
- I do not want to talk to you.
No, I know and I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry,
- and I will go talk to Vaughn if you
want me to. - Vaughn broke up with me.
- You broke my trust. You suck.
- No, I know, and I'm sorry,
but I was in a tough position.
I couldn't handle
just being one of the girls.
What do you want to be?
Is there a spot on
the friendship spectrum
between total stranger and having
to hear about the guys you date?
And ideally, just a notch underneath, driving
you to the airport and painting your kitchen?
How about the friend level where you
sometimes have to cat-sit?
Done. And if I'm occasionally naked
in your dreams, I won't complain.
- Shirley.
- I know.
She's got a problem.
She stirs the pot.
She's a pot stirrer.
Sorry, dudes.
No worries, man.
Yeah, some worries, man.
Some worries.
Shirley would have said
something funny about that guy.
And so I told him...
Oh, hey, Jeff.
Shh.
Oh, no.
Pierce! Pierce,
give me your ear-thing.
Got rid of it.
You see, Jeff, there are certain things
man was not meant to hear.
We were designed by...
whatever entity you choose,
to hear what's in this range,
and really, this range alone.
'Cause you know who's
talking to us in this range?
The people we love.
He must have heard us
call him Inspector Gadget.
Oh, I think it's time for burning man.
Ew, I'm Saddam Hussein. Ew.
Nice to meet you, dude.
Oh, wow. I love reading and
being a desperate housewife.
Hey, man, coming through. I love
the desperate housewives.
I'm Dr. Doogie Seacrest. I think I'm better
than everyone else because I'm forty.
I'm not forty.
I can hear you through
the window, morons.
Just pretend like you're asleep.
Just pretend like you were sleeping.