Subtitles by explosiveskull
911, what is your emergency?
I just shot my brother.
Help me!
The girl is now recovering from a shooting
on the far South Side.
Breaking news, two teens,
the victims of deadly gunfire...
Chicago will end 2016
with a surging murder
rate as city leaders...
It's Sway in the Morning. Shade 45.
We gotta talk about what's
happening in Chicago.
You got...
on the line right now, man.
You wanna know what the problem is?
The problem is they
don't care about us.
The problem is we don't
got enough education.
Seventeen-year-old
boy who was shot and killed...
A 12-year-old girl
recovering from gunshot wounds
suffered in the shooting last night.
762 murders, more than 3,500 shootings.
There's no hope, guys.
The government ain't coming for ya.
Things are worse than ever
before. So sit there...
We gonna keep this topic goin'
because something has to give in Chicago.
Squad B-9116, emergency. 10-1 emergency.
Shots fired at the police.
We have an officer down.
I'm coming in from South Loop.
We're on Wacker Avenue.
We're heading toward Chicago North.
ETA about two minutes.
Multiple GSWs in his chest.
He's in critical condition.
Have a trauma surgeon meet us
at the ER entrance.
Be advised. Officer en route.
Multiple gunshot wounds.
ETA, two minutes.
We can do it! Stay awake!
Move! Jesus Christ!
Come on!
Come on, buddy, let's go.
Go!
What do we have?
Gunshot wounds to the chest.
Massive bleeding.
Clear the Trauma Room!
Come on, stay with me, buddy,
all right?
Don't close your eyes.
Out of the way!
No pulse! No pulse!
Jesus Christ!
Somebody help me!
Come on, buddy.
Stay with me, buddy! Come on!
You two.
Over here. Nurse.
Roger that, doc.
I'll be right there.
Get Dr. Kersey.
Get Dr. Kersey now!
Blue team to ICU, please.
Blue team to ICU.
fixed and dilated.
Dr. Kersey, you're needed in Trauma One.
Chris, switch with me.
Got it.
Thanks.
Gunshot wounds,
including one to the neck.
Vest?
Yep.
Doc, please.
Hold on.
Thoracotomy tray now.
Five units of O-neg, stat.
And five more
en route to the ER.
Get the OR ready.
Yes, doctor.
Let's call it.
Time of death, 12:24 a.m.
Got here in six minutes.
I couldn't go any faster.
It had nothing to do with you.
His heart stopped.
He's lost too much blood.
We did everything we could.
Sorry for your loss.
Shooter's in Two, doc.
Sorry.
Dr. Kersey, OR Two.
What? Now you're gonna go
save the animal that shot him?
If I can.
I think
it's running a little slow.
Maybe it's time for a new one.
No, I like this one.
Mmm.
They said 9:00.
She's going to get in.
I know. I just miss envelopes.
None of this online crap.
Oh, my God! Yes!
That sounds like a good scream.
That sounded like
a very good scream.
Oh, hey, guys, what's up?
Hi, baby.
You want some breakfast?
Mmm-hmm.
How are you? How you doing?
I'm good.
Yeah? You're hungry?
Yeah, I'm starving.
Want some eggs?
Mmm. Yes, please.
Are you excited for your game?
Eh. It's just a game.
Hey, I thought
I heard a noise upstairs.
Did you hear anything?
Yeah, I thought I heard
something, what was that?
Thank you.
I got in. I got in! I got in!
So happy, honey.
I'm so happy for you!
I'm gonna be living
in New York City!
I will fly home on weekends
to do laundry, okay?
I promise.
Okay, okay, good.
Oh, my God. I have to text
Sophie to see if she got in.
Our girl is going to college.
I'm happy.
Really.
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
I think you have to tell that to your face.
Mmm. Baby.
Mmm.
Don't stop! Come here!
Watch the defender.
Go, go, go!
All right, come on, Jordan.
Let's go, Jordan!
Jordan!
Let's go!
I guess I always had it
in my head
that she'd go to
Northwestern. Someplace close.
Yeah.
You think my dad was happy
when I wanted to leave Texas
to go to college?
Well, this is different.
How's it different?
It's just that now we are
the ones that have to let go.
That's a foul! Hey!
That was cleats up!
What the fuck, ref?
Oh.
Really?
I guess I didn't think
it would happen so fast.
That's a bullshit pass,
Brianna. You know that!
I think we're gonna see her
more than we think.
Because we've got, um,
Thanksgiving,
we've got Christmas...
Mmm.
And we get to go
to New York City.
Foul! That's another foul!
Jesus Christ!
Take it easy, pal.
You're gonna give yourself
a heart attack.
I wasn't talking to you,
Lake Shore Drive.
No, as a matter of fact,
you were talking to everyone.
Just dial down the language,
there's kids here.
Or what?
Uh, Paul, come on.
I would just shut the fuck up
if I were you.
That's a good idea.
Why don't you do that?
Be me, and just shut the...
Fuck up.
You think that's funny?
Say it again.
Come on, funny guy.
Now you're quiet, huh?
Come on! Come on!
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Come here.
Oh, that's right.
Get your wife to defend you.
Pussy.
It's all right. All right.
Okay, so then the guy gets
right in Dad's face, okay?
And he starts shoving him
and it literally stops the game.
Spitting right in my face.
I had to get in
the middle of it.
I was gonna punch
the guy. Right?
Why didn't you
whoop this guy's butt?
Like in the old days.
Thank God your mom came over.
Wait, Dad, the "old days"?
Yeah, your dad was a scrapper.
Yeah, I was a scrapper.
Really?
You never told me that!
He would've, back in the day.
Tell her. Tell her.
I used to fight my dad.
Oh.
Fighting all the time.
You know, he was screaming
and crying in the house.
And guess who was crying?
Me. I lost every fight.
Terrible.
I still love you, Dad.
You should take Krav Maga.
You study that.
This way, when you go
to college, and these guys,
when they get a little too
aggressive with you,
you know what to do.
Don't look at me like I don't
know what I'm talking about.
No, no. Yeah, I'm just saying,
like, maybe I already know it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Jordan!
All right, all right.
I tapped out.
Seriously, she trains Monday,
Wednesday, and Friday,
this one. Watch out.
Really?
I'm training.
And I actually found
a boxing gym in Tribeca
that all the supermodels go to.
So I'm gonna start going there.
And speaking of college,
how about your PhD?
Oh, that's very nice of you
to remember.
How about that?
Yes, 15 years in the making,
I am soon to be a doctor.
Cheers to Mom, right?
How about that? Come on.
Two Dr. Kerseys.
Can you believe it?
Two doctors.
Are you gonna call me Doctor?
Yes, I am.
You are?
I'm gonna call you Dr. Baby.
Cheers to Dr. Kersey.
Thank you.
How about two Kerseys
that aren't doctors?
How about cheers to us?
Non-doctors.
I wanna get the big puffy
jackets, UGG slippers...
How much?
Two grand.
What? Two grand, what?
Hey, man.
You know, I've been
convicted of a crime.
I mean, it's not like
I'm a criminal, but...
This cashmere?
It's okay.
All right, thanks, man.
Pauly, thank you.
No worries.
He's got the money. Not me.
Hey, thank you so much.
MJ.
Bulls fan?
No, it's my name.
Miguel Javier.
Ah.
I know, I know, I know!
La Bamba, at 1:00. I got it.
Love you!
It's La Fonda.
At 8:00, okay?
Three o'clock.
I got it.
Wednesday, 8:00, La Fonda.
All right, I wouldn't
forget a restaurant like that.
See you guys.
Bye.
Wow, you look nice.
So do you.
Do you like your present?
Yes.
Aw.
And I love you.
Oh, and who is this calling?
Oh, no.
Hi, Susan.
Yes, he's right here.
You guys ready?
Hi, Susan.
I was just trying on
my birthday present.
No, I had worked it out
with Terry.
He's...
Okay.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, see you soon.
Terry has a 104 fever.
So, no birthday dinner
at La Fonda?
Mmm-mmm.
I'll go tell Uncle Frank.
Sorry, Daddy.
Oh, it's all right, hon.
I just had my heart set
on that tres leches cake.
I know, me, too.
We'll have it soon.
All right, baby.
We will celebrate
tomorrow night.
Don't worry at all, I promise.
Try and stay awake.
Okay, I will.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I will. Bye, honey.
It's all right.
Hey, Paul.
Happy birthday, old man.
Oh, come on.
First baseline.
You don't get me anything.
You better be taking me
to that game.
Why can't we just Postmates
La Fonda? It's so much easier.
Our cake is gonna be
so much better
because we're gonna make it
with love.
Yeah, but La Fonda makes it
And we know that
Dad already loves it,
so it's kind of a win-win.
No, it's his birthday.
He's gonna love knowing that
we actually made the effort.
We did the work.
So we can make the effort
to dirty up the kitchen,
and then when he gets home,
we just pretend that
we cooked all night.
Honey, we're making the cake.
Honey, could you get me my iPad?
I think it's upstairs
on the nightstand.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hi, Soph.
I can't hear you.
Okay, so I've narrowed it
down to two options.
I'm thinking either
Third North or Seventh Street.
Third North has bigger bedrooms
but I think that
Seventh Street is just, like,
a way cooler area.
Honey, did you get that iPad?
Yeah, it was in your dresser,
not on it.
Jordan? Can you please
come down here? I need it.
Jordan, come down here,
right now.
Mom, I am grabbing a charger,
relax.
So what are you guys
gonna do tonight?
Jordan!
Oh, my God. Will you calm down?
I said I'm coming.
Now!
I'm gonna have to call you back.
My mom is being a total psycho.
No!
Mom.
Put the fucking phone down
right now.
No.
Please. Please don't hurt her.
Don't hurt her, please!
Shh.
Shh. Shh.
Now here's, uh,
here's what's gonna happen.
Mom, you're gonna save me
20 minutes
by opening the safe.
Okay.
Then I'm gonna tie you up
with your daughter,
so you won't be calling anyone
till we're long gone.
Okay.
Now if you could do that,
nobody gets hurt.
Okay.
You understand me?
Mmm-hmm.
Go on.
Mom, Mom!
Don't hurt her.
Do not hurt her.
Oh, that's entirely up to you.
It's okay, Mom.
Just do it. Just go.
Tie her up.
No fucking games.
We need to move.
Hey.
Hey, no fucking games.
What, are you deaf?
Put that thing away.
All right, man. Relax.
Jesus.
Just fucking watch her.
My husband has two watches,
there's cash...
You can take it all.
Whatever you want.
That's nice. Thank you.
Where's the rope, girl?
Check the garage.
Don't get amnesia on me.
I'm sorry. I'm just
not used to doing it
with a gun pointed at me.
Yeah, well, get used to it.
You play sports?
You look like you play sports.
No.
Shh.
No, no, stop.
Did you say something?
Please don't.
Oh, you can do it.
And then we're done.
Goddamn, you're strong.
That's good.
No.
No, no, no.
Please.
It's nice. It's nice.
It's good.
I got it.
Hey. Hey, what the fuck
is your rush, bro?
We don't have time
for this shit.
Just give me
two fucking minutes, please.
I'm begging you,
two minutes, please.
It's not that kind
of a party, all right?
Why don't you just stop
being such a fucking pussy?
What the fuck?
What the fuck, man?
God damn it!
Fuck!
Fuck! God damn it!
You motherfucker!
No!
No! No!
The fuck are you doing?
She cut my fucking face!
She can see your fucking face!
Mom!
Jordan, run!
Fuck it.
Trauma, two incoming, Level One.
Female, 17,
basal skull fracture.
Female, 43,
gunshot wound to the chest.
Dr. Simone, would you mind
closing, please?
Yes, doctor.
Put her on the monitor.
Get two IV's
and put her on oxygen.
Yes.
Jordan, open your eyes.
Open your eyes, Jordan.
She needs to be intubated.
Prepare 100 milligrams
of propofol...
Doc, hold up, man.
It's fine, it's fine.
Listen. Paul,
something's happened.
You can't go in there.
Where are they?
Paul. Paul.
Where is she?
They took your daughter
up to surgery, doc.
Your wife's in Two.
Lucy!
Paul...
We did everything we could.
Baby.
Our passports,
Jordan's birth certificate,
$2,000 in cash...
My Stanford class ring,
two Panerai watches on the desk.
Can you describe the watches?
One was all black.
The other one...
It was a birthday present.
Silver and black.
Were there any firearms
in the house?
No.
A lot of these guys,
they break in looking for guns
'cause they're easy to sell.
I had a couple of assholes
break in
to my house looking for mine.
So that's
what you think this was?
It was a robbery gone bad?
Well, there have been
a string of break-ins
along the North Shore.
So we're looking at
the possibility.
You said string.
How many in this string?
Uh, six,
in the last nine months.
Six? Six robberies.
Did you know about this?
No, I didn't know about it.
What, you don't think
it's important enough
to tell the residents?
We post every crime
on the Neighborhood Watch.
If it's big enough,
the media picks it up
and reports about it.
If not,
these are just burglaries.
Just burglaries.
Frank, that's not what he meant.
No, I'm just wondering,
if it's important enough
now, to go on their radar...
You're not helping.
You guys, it's been a long night.
I think we got enough
to start with.
Yeah.
This is my card.
Thanks.
It's got my cell phone
number on there,
if you've got anything else.
Thank you, Detective Raines.
You know, I... I get that
you're upset.
We're upset, too.
But we're gonna get these guys.
Again, I'm... I'm
deeply sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Thanks for your time.
Dr. Kersey, your daughter's
out of surgery.
Her surgery went well.
She's still in a coma,
but she's stable.
They were able
to evacuate the hematoma
and remove the bullet fragments.
I wish I had more to tell you.
So, I gotta take Mom home
to Grandpa today.
Uncle Frank's gonna take
over reading duties for now.
I love you so much.
Oh, so much, baby.
I'll see you soon, kiddo.
When Lucy's mother passed,
she turned to me and said,
"Why did God take her so soon?"
All I could say was,
"Honey, I don't know.
I think it's part of His plan.
And we have to trust
His plan."
We used to come up here
and visit her and...
Well...
Now here I am.
And I'm seeing something
I was never meant to see.
How is this part of His plan?
How is this part of any plan?
Thank you, Paul,
for bringing her home.
This is where she wanted
to be. With her mom.
One day, I'll join 'em.
There'll always be
a place here for you.
Thanks.
Have the police gotten anywhere?
One of the neighbors saw three
repairmen in a white van.
The police seem
pretty confident.
Oh, damn. Run!
Poachers! Come on!
Go, go!
People rely on the police
to keep them safe.
That's the problem.
The police only arrive
after the crime has taken place.
That's like...
Trapping the fox
as he's comin' out
of the hen house.
If a man really wants to
protect what's his...
He has to do it for himself.
All right, this is
The Loop. I'm the Mancow.
7:15, a quarter past 7:00.
Good morning.
Another great weekend here,
the city of death.
Forty-eight people shot
over the weekend.
Forty-eight
freaking people shot.
Thirteen dead. And, uh, this...
It's getting worse.
The numbers are up.
You wonder how much more
of this we can take.
I'm sorry, Dr. Kersey, nothing yet.
Nothing?
Don't be alarmed.
It's not uncommon.
Forensics usually takes a week
or two.
Uh, same with informants.
Hey!
I'm sorry. Some asshole's
trying to clean my windshield.
Hey, that's enough. Go on.
Run 'em over.
Doesn't count as a crime.
I can do that?
Look, I have someone
in my office right now,
but Detective Jackson and I
are all over this, okay?
Hey! That's it!
We'll get back to you as soon
as we have more information.
Come on! Just do something.
Yep.
Fuck you!
Yes, fuck me.
Spare some change, man?
Come on, man.
"Normative economics
and the art of economics,
on the other hand,
cannot be independent
of positive economics.
Any policy conclusion..."
Sophie.
Hi.
Dr. Kersey, hi.
The nurses let me come in here.
No, it's okay.
I'm glad you're here.
How are you doing?
I'm okay. How are you?
Doing okay. Thank you.
What are you reading?
Um, Essays in Positive
Economics by Milton Friedman.
I'm not sure that's
gonna help her wake up.
Yeah, I know, it's boring.
Um...
But it's on the NYU summer reading list
and I'm reading it anyway, so...
I thought, I don't know,
maybe this way...
This way, she won't get behind.
I can leave, if you want.
No, no. Stay. Stay.
It'd be good for her.
Dr. Kersey...
Do you think it helps?
I know it does.
I can't sleep on our bed.
So I sleep on the couch.
I watch TV until I pass out.
Even then I...
I'm just not getting any sleep.
That's to be expected.
I can prescribe sleeping pills
if it gets worse.
I feel like I'm in purgatory.
I can't go back to work,
I can't be around my house.
When I was a kid,
I used to ride the trains
to avoid my father.
And I would
even do my homework then,
just to stay away from him.
So...
I've been doing that.
Just riding the trains...
Just to think.
I wish I could say everything
I see reminds me of Lucy.
But everything I see
reminds me of them.
The men I've never seen.
The men who came
and took her from me.
This is Detective Kevin Raines
of the Chicago Police
Department.
If this is an emergency,
please dial 911.
Otherwise, please leave a message.
"It was a dream,
and that he might wake
up at any moment..."
I thank God for Jordan.
"And as they went on,
hour after hour..."
I try to stay strong.
Good clean cut right there.
With as many
as 90 shootings in a week,
violent crime in Chicago
is now at a 20-year high,
while the police...
It's hard to escape
the feeling that I failed.
Failed to protect my wife.
Failed to protect my daughter.
Failed at the most important
things a man does.
Here you go, kid.
Thanks, man.
No. It's not a "U."
"E."
K-E-R-S-E-Y.
Right. Kersey.
Detective Raines isn't in.
Would you like
to leave a message?
Yes.
This is a process.
And it's gonna take time.
Yeah, I know it's a process.
I'm just...
Starting to wonder
about the result, that's all.
Listen, I understand the process
takes a little bit of time,
all right?
Just fill out all the boxes
on this application.
Take a seat, and we'll get
to you as soon as possible.
Hello, sir.
Fill out this application,
every single box, please.
Sir, can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here
to see Detective Raines.
Detective Raines. Do you have
an appointment, sir?
No. No, I don't.
My name is Paul Kersey.
K-U-R...
E-R...
Sorry about that.
It's all right.
Hey, Dr. Kersey.
Dr. Kersey, come on back.
Thank you. Thanks.
Buzz him in, Willy.
Yeah.
What about the DNA
in the blood and skin
from the guy that got burned?
We got that test back.
It didn't match anybody
in our database.
But we can use it
to put 'em there
when we get one in custody.
Yeah, Raines.
Get a number,
I'll call him back.
CCA?
Cleared. Closed by arrest.
So all these other ones
are open cases?
Yep.
Most of these are gang-related.
Just asshole-on-asshole
violence.
Some banger posts some shit
on social media
and they retaliate
with an AR-15.
Last weekend,
a guy shot up a party.
One guy shoots 14 people,
no one sees anything.
They don't talk to the cops,
that's why these stay open.
Point is, your wife's case
is different.
You wanna have a seat?
Thanks.
I mean, that's three
burglars who panicked.
I guarantee at least one of 'em
is shittin' himself somewhere.
He's got a friend
who's gonna get picked up
on something unrelated.
He's gonna sell his buddy down
the river for his own freedom.
Okay?
I've seen guys
turn in their own mother.
What if I offered
some kind of reward?
We'll just get flooded
with false leads.
Me and my partner
are gonna have to
waste time tracking 'em down.
What about
a private investigator?
PI's good for cheating
spouses, missing persons...
But murder case,
they'll just take your money.
They can't get involved
in a police investigation.
It's tampering with evidence,
they could lose their license.
So there's nothing
that I can do.
Is that what you're saying?
You can have faith.
How'd faith work out for them?
This is Lake transfer to Orange...
Green, Purple, and Brown.
This is Red Line train
to Howard.
Oh, shit!
Damn, what's up, baby?
Hey, mama.
What's poppin', redbone?
Look at you.
Where you going, baby?
Can I come with you?
Look at your fine ass.
Look at them thick-ass thighs.
Can I get your number, baby?
Can I call?
Hey!
What the fuck you say, puto?
Just leave her alone.
Fuck you talking to?
What the fuck is your problem?
Punk-ass.
Who the fuck you think you are?
I don't shoot to kill,
I shoot to stay alive.
Law-abiding criminals
don't exist.
When seconds count,
cops are minutes away.
Come on down to Jolly Roger's.
We've got some badass deals
on our F-1 firearms.
Ooh, and right now,
we have a special
on our tactical furniture.
Surprise 'em.
Okay, here's a good one
for you. Easy on the...
No, no, hold it, son.
First gun?
Uh, yeah.
It can be pretty overwhelming
at first.
I'll say.
Don't worry, I got your
back. I'm Bethany.
Hi.
Welcome to Jolly Roger's.
Come on back,
let me show you around.
So over here we have
all of our bladed weapons.
Behind me on this wall
are all of our rifles.
Each one comes with
a free case and two PMAGs.
And if you follow me over here,
all of our new pistols
are over there.
And all of our used weapons
are right here.
Used?
Oh.
Not used in crimes, obviously.
But, you know, used.
I don't know where to begin.
Well, personally,
my very favorite
is right over here.
Forgive me for asking,
but what is the process
for all of this?
There must be
a lot of paperwork, right?
Oh.
Don't even worry.
We'll get you set up with
your FOID application
right here today.
State Police send it
pretty quick.
And then you'll just have
to take a gun safety class,
but don't worry,
no one ever fails.
You can do that anytime
within 30 days
of the time period you're
waiting for your city permit.
And then it's just 72 hours,
and you're cocked, locked,
and ready to rock.
Ooh, and we can set you up
with a gun safe.
If someone ever steals that gun,
those bullets can be traced
right back to you.
I'm gonna think about it...
And I'll come back.
Great, just ask for Bethany.
Dr. Kersey,
OR Two. Dr. Kersey, OR Two.
Put him on the monitor
and oxygen.
On my count.
Three, two, one.
And breathe. Good.
Blood's on its way.
Get an IV. Get his pants off.
Okay.
Take it easy, you're okay.
You'll be all right, sir.
This is the Glock 17,
arguably the most
iconic pistol of all time.
Today, I'm gonna teach you
how to take it apart.
Then put it back together
by simply reversing the steps.
Put slight backwards pressure
on the slide,
and the slide will release
forward.
Step three, remove the barrel.
Step three...
Brush from the breach end of the barrel.
I do this four
to five times or until...
Dr. Kersey to ICU.
Dr. Kersey,
please report to ICU.
She's had a seizure.
Is she gonna be okay?
The only thing we know for sure
is her odds get less every day.
She's in handcuffs.
My daughter is in handcuffs.
And the men who did it
are out there.
Free.
Look what these animals did
to my baby.
Yeah.
So...
Keys, now!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, man. Come on, man.
Give it up, bitch.
It's all right.
Come on, man.
Hey!
Ah!
It's okay, it's okay,
get out of here. Go! Go!
Move over.
A rainy July...
Tickets are now on sale for the...
Chicago's teacher's union
has taken the first step...
Hey!
I didn't know him.
He just came out of nowhere.
He saved my life.
Like a guardian angel.
I heard that girl screaming
and then
I heard tires squealing,
a whole bunch of shots
and then a crash.
What about the shooter?
He looked like a white dude.
He had a hoodie.
It's the same description
the couple gave outside.
White guy in a hoodie.
They called him
a guardian angel.
Yeah, more like a Grim Reaper.
I mean, did you see how
he stood over that guy
and shot him?
That shit was cold.
Did you see his face?
Mmm-mmm.
How about marks
on his arms or tattoos?
Mmm-mmm.
So nothing that can help us?
It was dark. He was shooting.
Um...
He kept waving his hand around
like this.
Like his hand got shot?
I don't know. Watch the video.
I mean, you've seen as much
as I did.
There!
Yeah.
It doesn't look like
it was shot.
Hmm.
No, that is the slide
kicking back
and cutting his hand
because he doesn't know
how to hold a gun.
So we're looking for a guy
who never fired a gun?
Well, not in anger.
Well, he has now.
Natasha, listen,
we're gonna need you to
keep this video
confidential, okay?
No posting on social media,
and all that stuff you guys do.
I uploaded that shit hours ago.
I'm getting hits
like a motherfucker.
Terrific.
Who wants gluten?
Oh, man, that's just cruel.
A little support.
You know you want a bear claw.
Hell, yeah, I do.
Donut hole.
It was a good time, but not
for the grass in Grant Park
after hundreds of thousands
of festival goers
romped through the area
for Lollapalooza.
It is estimated that there was
$300,000 worth of damage
done to the lawn in Grant Park.
As usual, the concert promoters
are on the hook
for paying that bill.
It's been worse in years
past, when muddy weather...
Whoa!
The water cooler talk today
on the Mancow Show
is everybody is watching
this video,
this viral video
of this guy in a hoodie.
They're calling him
the Grim Reaper
that shot these bad guys,
these carjackers,
according to witnesses.
Right or wrong, I don't know.
Good or bad, I don't know.
I go back and forth on it.
Is he a hero or a zero?
That's the debate.
We got calls coming in.
The phones are lit up
like a Christmas tree.
I say the guy's,
and some people are mad at me...
I say the guy's a hero.
He stopped the carjacking.
He is a hero.
Is he a hero or is he a zero?
What do you think, Chicago?
Call us right now.
It's the Mancow.
And we wanna hear from you.
He saw somebody
about to get jacked,
and a black couple at that?
Power to the Grim Reaper.
Yeah, but I don't know
about that.
I don't know.
And maybe that's the question
we put out to the listeners.
Okay.
Is he right for taking the law
into his own hands,
or is it wrong?
Give us a call.
Sway in the Morning. Shade 45.
Yeah, I saw that guy
earlier today,
but you should check on him.
I'll check that.
This poor kid.
Got shot on the way to school.
Tyler.
Mmm-hmm.
Hi, Tyler. I'm Dr. Kersey.
I'm here to look at
your wound. Is that all right?
I have my little flashlight pen.
Let's take a look.
That must've hurt.
A LeBron fan?
Me?
I'll always be a Jordan guy.
He had swagger, he had style,
he could fly through the air.
Still, LeBron might be
the best ever.
Maybe.
Yeah.
You got caught
in some crossfire?
The Ice Cream Man done it.
The Ice Cream Man?
Can't walk to school
if you don't work for him.
Selling ice cream?
Nah.
He said next time,
it ain't gonna be my leg.
Tyler,
you are gonna be all right.
I promise.
Thanks.
I'll see you
in a little while. All right?
Okay.
The cat, Tanisha.
Word?
Yo, that's it, MUBU.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Yeah, Tanisha.
That was next level business
she was doing.
Pimp out your crib?
That's it.
That's what I'm
talking about. Thank you.
Yeah, so,
brought her up to my crib,
show him the picture...
Of course I got mine,
but show him the picture,
you'll see.
Let's see that cat, man.
Hey, look here.
You're the Ice Cream Man?
Who the fuck are you?
Your last customer.
Oh, shit!
Yo, give me that shit!
Out my way.
He was, uh...
He was white.
A white guy, he had a hoodie...
And that's all I know.
Was he tall? Short?
Thanks.
He was not short.
Fat? Skinny?
He was taller than me, you know.
I don't know.
He just went over there...
He was just some white guy.
Let me guess,
white guy with a hoodie?
Yeah, exactly.
White guy with a hoodie.
Fucking bullshit.
Nine witnesses, one story.
The Grim Reaper.
They say
he didn't take anything.
Just walked up,
shot the victim and left.
That's Ray Shawn Core.
Multiple drug offenses suspect
and three shootings.
Mmm, real community leader.
Yeah.
You really think
it's the same shooter?
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Pull up that video.
Reaper?
Yeah.
What hand does he shoot with?
Hold up.
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Could there be
a vigilante in Chicago?
Rumors are circulating
after the second shooting
of a known criminal
in as many days.
Police are looking for this man,
the Chicago Grim Reaper.
Described as a white male
in his mid to late 30s.
This is straight out of
a comic book.
This dude has gotten so bold.
Grim Reaper has taken out
the Ice Cream Man.
I might as well
get a hoodie and just
start doin' somethin'
and fighting crime...
The Grim Reaper
isn't part of the problem.
The Ice Cream Man,
the drug dealer,
is part of the problem.
You're gonna side with
The Ice Cream Man?
You got a white guy in a hoodie
killing black people.
You don't have a problem
with that?
This is a drug dealer.
Hmm.
I mean, he's making it hard
for the people
that live on that very block.
Don't we need people like
this Grim Reaper
to keep the monsters at bay?
It's a slippery slope.
So now everyone's just gonna
take the law
into their own hands,
kill somebody that they think
is doing something wrong.
If you have any information,
you're asked to call this number
and contact the Chicago Police.
I'm getting calls from Houston,
Detroit, New York.
Everybody's nervous about
a copycat. Where are we?
Well, we assume
the carjacking was random.
Mmm-hmm.
And our subject was just in
the wrong place
at the wrong time.
But he got a taste for it.
Mmm-hmm.
So we were trying to figure out
how he selected
the second victim.
The drug dealer.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, we also know he's left-handed.
Um, and we're pretty sure
he's not in the system.
We figured that out
after the first shooting.
Um, he had
a lack of basic weapon skills.
To say the least.
Wow. Great.
You got it narrowed down
to about a million suspects.
Detectives,
get off your fucking asses!
He's pissed.
You wanna tell me
where we're gonna start looking
for our white needle
in the haystack?
Not where.
But when.
I mean, why now?
What, uh...
Lit the fuse
that set off our Mr. Reaper?
You look much better.
Thank you. I feel much better.
You exercising?
I do my push-ups.
Mmm-hmm. Good.
Getting out? Socializing?
Mmm...
Not so much.
It's like you said.
It's a process.
Takes time.
Well, whatever you're
doing, keep it up.
Okay. I will.
Keep on bagging.
Push the O-neg.
Got it!
Give me the ultrasound machine.
Hold compressions.
Give me the defib.
Charge to 300.
Jesus. I know this kid.
Charged.
Clear.
Continue bagging.
Charge again to 300.
Charged.
Clear.
Time of death, 9:35 p.m.
Dr. Kersey?
Wednesday, 8:00, La Fonda.
See you guys.
Hi. This is Detective Kevin Raines
of the Chicago
Police Department.
If this is an emergency,
please dial 911.
What?
You scared the shit out of me.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I can't check on my niece?
And her dad who doesn't
return my texts?
Yeah, yeah. Look, I'm sorry,
it's been a crazy week.
Yeah?
Still getting used
to being back.
You sleeping better?
'Cause I gotta tell you,
you still look like shit.
Thanks for your diagnosis,
Dr. Frank Kersey.
Go fuck yourself. Jesus.
Come on, let's go get a bite.
I'm buyin'.
What, now?
Hey, I'm back to work.
Union wages, no less. Come on.
Ah, no, no, I can't.
I got a meeting with
a bunch of hospital staff.
All right.
What about this weekend?
We go get a bite. Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, that's better.
That's better.
I'll call you later, all right?
What's up with your hand here?
It's nothing, it's a scratch.
Leave it alone.
Look, do you need somethin'?
Some cash? What, some help?
Is that what this is about?
No.
Frank.
Here, it's all right.
Look, this is the $2,000
I owed you. Here you go.
It's all right.
I wanted to maybe take you
to lunch, you know.
Celebrate that I can actually
pay you back.
It's all right.
Frank.
Later, man.
I'll see you.
Yeah.
Hey, hey, buddy,
you can't be back here.
I'm looking for Trebol.
Well, you found him,
now you can get out.
Miguel sent me.
Who the fuck is Miguel?
He works as a valet
at my restaurant.
He's got an MJ tattooed
on his wrist.
He said you could help me find
a gift for my wife.
He works for you?
Yes.
At your restaurant?
Yeah, all right. Sit down.
Hey.
So, uh...
Is this a "thanks for
the years of service"
kind of thing, honey,
or is this more of
a "sorry, I boned the
babysitter" kind of thing?
Neither.
So you're looking
for something...
Specific?
Very specific.
Well, how specific
are we talking?
Panerai watches.
You got any of those?
Well, why don't you just
let me check
the reserve collection
over here,
because I think
there's something here
that might interest you.
Drop it.
Fuck! It's dropped.
Kick it away.
I want my stuff.
It's in the back.
Keep moving.
Who's Fish?
He's just a drop guy.
Yeah. Your crew that stole
the shit out of my house!
You just described half
the shit in my shop, man.
And you killed my wife!
Look.
Who are they?
I just know Fish, okay?
I don't know the other
guys. I told you!
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
It's all here. It's all here.
I don't organize it by house,
just take whatever's yours,
all right?
What, are you gonna talk?
Or are you gonna tell me
where my shit is?
It's here.
Where is it? I'm gonna blow
your fucking head off
if you don't tell me...
What the... What is this?
What is this bullshit?
Now you're gonna tell me
where it is
in the next three seconds
or your head comes off.
All right. It's all there.
You see this? You know
what it is, don't ya?
It was on my wife's arm.
I hope it was worth it, asshole.
If I knew...
If I knew it was your shit,
I wouldn't have taken it, man.
All my love for my wife
and my family is keeping me
from putting one
right in your fucking mouth.
I'm not a killer, okay?
I don't kill people.
It's not what I do.
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Shit!
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Shit!
I didn't shoot her.
I promise, I didn't shoot her.
Fuck!
Who did?
It wasn't me.
Fuck! Please!
It wasn't me. It's Joe.
What?
Joe!
Joe who?
Joe Gannon!
The fat greasy fuck
at the auto body shop.
Where's Joe?
It's in my phone.
It's got pictures, everything.
I'll bring you to him.
Stupid motherfuck.
Watch what I do
in the next few seconds.
You might learn something
that could help you
solve your problem.
Grab this drill.
I'm going to drill several holes
around this circle right here.
And when I do that,
the information that's
inside of this metal box
will be a lot harder to access.
With any luck, your metal box
should now look
something like this.
Again, FBI, CIA, NSA, Interpol,
this video was strictly made
for entertainment purposes.
Stay out of trouble,
you crazy kids.
Morning, Paul!
Reaper alert!
Reaper alert! Reaper alert!
Where's the Reaper?
The Grim Reaper strikes again.
This time in the Pilsen neighborhood.
In front of this liquor store,
which was a fencing operation
for stolen goods.
Not anymore, when last night,
the Grim Reaper
paid them a visit.
Dude, I look over, I see
this dude walking out,
this old white dude,
and he's walking
with his hood up,
looking super suspicious.
Just like, you know...
Kind of idolizing him.
Man, right now,
this dude is all over
the Internet, man.
There's memes coming up.
Get outta here.
Yeah, there's memes.
Like, people are making memes.
Look at this one right here.
Oh, that's too intense.
He's become a folk hero.
He's a real hero
to these people.
They're being affected
by all this crime
in their neighborhood.
As long as it's not
in your neighborhood.
Clearly, if he didn't
just kill somebody,
I don't know what he did.
I still stand by my point that
we're normalizing
dangerous behavior.
You know? Should we be
policing ourselves
in our own neighborhoods...
I have said we need a guy
like Grim Reaper for years.
Are you Team Reaper or not?
Give us a call.
Sway in the Morning
at Shade 45, Sirius XM.
Dr. Kersey,
it's Detective Raines
and Jackson.
May we come in?
Of course. Come on in.
How you doing?
Sorry to drop in like this.
Oh, no.
Uh, something's
come to our attention.
We were hoping you could
offer some insight.
I'm happy to see you guys.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Okay, um...
Have you ever seen this man?
No.
Is he a suspect?
Well, his name is Tate Karp.
He goes by "The Fish."
He's a career burglar and,
we believe,
involved in
your wife's shooting.
How did you find him?
What did he say?
Well, unfortunately,
he was killed last night
before we had a chance
to question him.
But we did find this ring
at the crime scene.
That's my ring.
Yeah. That's what we thought.
Um, but this right here,
it's the break
we've been waiting for.
It's great.
Yeah.
Now that we have Karp,
it's just a matter of time
before we have the rest of 'em.
We'll run through his priors,
see who he liked to work with,
subpoena his cell phone
records, his texts.
Even the phone's GPS.
Great. Do you need
anything else from me?
Appreciate that.
I think we're good for now.
Um... I know you've been
frustrated and I wanted to
come by in person
to give you the good news.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I told you to have faith.
Thanks for your time.
Thank you.
Yo, we're closed, pal.
You're Joey, right?
Yeah. Who the fuck are you?
Hey, fuckstick,
I said we were closed.
What the fuck?
Get me the fuck outta here.
Fuck! Get me the fuck
outta here, man!
What the fuck are you...
Shut the fuck up.
You're gonna tell me
what I wanna hear.
You don't want this.
But guess what?
You'll get some.
I'm just gonna help you out.
Trust me, I know where to cut.
Now right back here,
don't move...
is your sciatic nerve.
Longest,
strongest nerve in the body.
Fuck!
God damn!
You're that doctor.
I am that doctor.
But right now, I'm your doctor.
Your friend, Fish,
is already dead.
You can thank him
for giving you up.
No. No, no, no, no.
What I want to know
is who else was there.
Nobody.
Who else was there?
No one, man.
What you're feeling
is a caustic agent
being applied directly
to a nerve.
In med school,
we were taught that
this is the most
painful experience
that a person can endure
without possibly going into
cardiac arrest.
Please stop. It hurts.
The bad news is
you've got a shit ton
of brake fluid here.
So we might be here all night.
Now you're gonna
start talking, aren't ya?
Knox! That's his name. Knox!
Knox. What's his full name?
I don't know anything else, man!
His name is Knox and he's
from the South Side.
Look, Fish planned
the whole fucking thing!
I never met the guy before!
Where do I find Knox?
You don't. He finds you.
Joe.
I don't know anything else!
I swear to fucking God!
I have no reason
to protect this asshole!
I don't even fucking know him!
You gotta believe me, please.
I fucking swear it!
I believe you, Joe.
I think you're gonna find
the propofol is wearing off.
Thanks for your help.
Fuck.
So you're not gonna kill me?
No.
The jack is.
Damn. Hell of a swing.
Lefty, no less.
Hey, Frank.
You know,
when I asked your supervisor
where you like to
hang out after work,
he told me here.
I thought he was
jerking my chain.
Then I looked you up.
You were a legitimate prospect.
What happened?
So you want my autograph?
We just wanna talk.
All right.
Have you heard of this
Grim Reaper fellow
that people are talking about?
Yeah, yeah. I heard about it.
Well, last night,
he went into a liquor store.
And he killed
one of the three men
that broke into
your brother's house.
Traffic cam caught him walking
in and out. White, fit...
Lefty.
Lefty. Yeah. He's a lefty.
So I ask myself, you know,
"What streetwise lefty
do I know?"
You know,
the kind of guy that could
put word out
he would pay for info.
Would want to
execute our suspects.
A real do-it-himself
kind of guy.
So you think I had something
to do with it, huh?
Well, you should talk
to my brother.
He'll tell you
that I don't pay for shit.
Of course. So, do you mind
if we see your hands?
Hey!
Tragedy struck earlier this
evening in West Englewood,
where police think
a 49-year-old father of three
was killed
while trying to commit
vigilante justice.
Police believe
this was a copycat
of the so-called
"Chicago Grim Reaper."
A guy who went out,
tried to fight crime,
and ended up a victim himself.
Police are still looking
for the shooter.
This is Paul Kersey.
I hear you're looking for me.
That's right.
Come to Blowout.
Last club off Ashland.
I'll be waiting.
Why would I do that?
Because it's safe. Public.
And I wanna tell you what
your wife's last words were.
You have 30 minutes.
Come on, Paul.
Paul, come on, man.
We gotta talk, Paul.
Hey, man.
Are you here?
Paul.
Get out.
Jackson.
What?
We're on our way.
Shooting at a club downtown.
Guy in a hoodie
pulled out a gun,
then got shot himself.
Ran out in the crowd.
Hey. Alert all the
local hospitals, all right?
Any gunshot wound being treated,
a male, 40s or 50s,
give us a call!
County reports they have no one
matching the shooter's
description.
One of the victims
is en route to Chicago North.
He says he saw the shooter.
The patient's this way.
How you doing?
Did you see the shooter?
Yeah, I did.
Can you describe him to us?
Fuck!
Open it.
Uh-huh.
Paul, what you gonna do?
Shoot me, too?
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What is this,
your little war room?
Don't you judge me!
I'm not judging you!
I'm worried about you!
You... You can't do this.
Paul, you're not a cop.
Then somebody has to do it!
My wife and daughter
just disappear.
And there's no consequences.
I did everything
I was supposed to do.
Everything.
I worked hard.
I obeyed the law.
I made a life for my family.
For my wife and daughter!
And what?
Just forget about that?
They're just gone now?
You need to leave now, Frank.
I don't want you
to be part of this.
No. Hey, hey.
I'm already a part of this.
Stay, stay.
If it isn't Chicago's finest.
Hello, Frank.
We were expecting your brother.
Yeah, he's out.
Dinner party. Why, what's up?
Well, he could be
in real trouble.
Believe or not, we wanna help.
That's so sweet. I appreciate
your concern, Detective.
Like I said, when I see him,
I'll tell him.
That was some bullshit.
He's in there.
But we're not arresting the surgeon
without an ironclad proof.
Well, the good news is
I'm not a suspect anymore.
The bad news is
Paul, this has to end.
It's gotta end, man.
I don't wanna have to bury
you next to your wife.
You're not gonna bury me.
All right.
We gotta figure this out
if you think there's
anything the cops can find.
There were cameras in the club.
I kept my head down
the whole time.
Where's your car?
Near the hospital.
Okay, you gotta get it,
before the police
start checking tags.
Okay.
Who'd be calling at 2:30 in the morning?
Let's see.
It's the hospital.
Hello?
Thank you.
I'll be right there.
It's Jordan. She's awake.
Oh, baby.
Daddy.
Hi, Daddy.
Baby.
Dad, they won't tell me
where Mom is.
Dad, they won't
tell me where Mom is.
Dad, where is Mom?
I wanna see Mom. Where is she?
Please, Dad, where is she?
Oh, Jesus.
Hey.
How's she doing?
Physically, I can take her
home in a week.
Mentally, she just found out
her mother died.
Jesus, Pauly.
It's a miracle though, you know,
that we got her back.
It's a miracle.
It was a miracle.
All that matters now is that...
You look after her.
Yes, of course.
You, though. Her father.
I will.
Not this other thing,
not this other guy. You.
It's over.
Okay.
Slowly.
Thanks.
You sure you got everything?
Yeah, I got it.
You got her, Dad?
I got it, Dad. I'm okay.
All right, I know you got it.
Easy does it.
I can't believe
I have to leave in this,
I feel like an invalid.
You're not an invalid.
Bye, Jordan.
Bye.
You ready?
Yes, take me home.
Hey, Dr. Kersey.
Dr. Kersey.
Jordan.
I told you guys, we'll call you as
soon as she remembers something.
It's okay, Dad. Um...
I wanna help you guys,
I really do.
It's just that...
I don't remember anything after
going upstairs to get the iPad.
Any little detail
you can remember
will really help us out
a lot, Jordan.
I don't remember a thing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Maybe over time,
you'll remember something.
Either way, we'll, uh, we'll
keep looking for the guys.
Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Dr. Kersey.
We'll let you know.
Bye.
Dr. Meredith,
Dr. Ronald Meredith,
please report...
Well, they seem okay.
Hey, hold that.
Thank you.
What happened to you?
Oh, um, I was in an accident.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you better?
Yeah.
That's nice.
You going home?
Yeah. I'm going home.
I'm going home, too.
Well, what happened to you?
I got shot.
Oh, well...
I'm glad you're okay.
Thank you.
Take care.
I'll see you around,
Dr. Kersey.
Dad, who was that?
Not a clue, honey.
Somebody else's patient.
Welcome to Jolly Roger's.
How can I help you?
I wanna buy a gun.
Don't I know you?
Yeah, I'm taking
Writing and History.
Mainly just
introduction classes.
I'm doing it online,
just a couple hours a day.
So that way, I don't fall behind
when school starts next fall.
Well, that's smart.
You know, I think you're
the smartest one in the family.
So how's your therapy coming?
'Cause you look like
you're getting around better.
It's good. You know,
boring. I'm almost done,
but I just had to teach my body
how to do basic things again.
It feels good to have you home.
Feels good to be home.
And that's him in the middle.
Him and the girl.
Good night, Uncle Frank.
Love you!
Okay, Frankie!
Dad, the kitchen's clean.
I'm going to bed.
Okay, honey.
Hey, can you help me with this?
Move this?
Slide it down a little.
Yeah, just a little bit.
Mmm-hmm.
Why are you moving this?
Because I need you
to come over here.
I just saw somebody run by.
What do you mean you just saw
someone run by?
You saw someone run by here?
Yeah, I did. I did.
I want you to
get under the stairs.
Dad, why are you putting me
under the stairs?
Call the cops right now.
Dad, please be careful.
Take your phone and dial 911.
Dad, please!
911, what is your emergency?
There's men, they're
breaking into my house.
They're on my front lawn.
I think they're coming
to kill me.
My name is Jordan Kersey.
I'm at 20 Dorset Road in Evanston.
I think they're here.
Jordan, I'm okay.
Dad. Dad!
Stay quiet.
Just wait for the police.
Do not come out.
Stay in there.
Sit down.
Dad?
I think they just shot my dad.
Dad! Dad!
Jordan, just stay up there!
Is that your little girl?
Now, you ever hear someone
burn to death?
You're in for a treat,
Dr. Kersey.
Dad!
So you're saying
you got both the cut
on your hand
that's almost healed
and the shot in the shoulder
tonight? That's your story.
That's what happened.
That's my story.
Hmm.
And the paperwork for
the pistols and the rifle?
You can call Jolly Roger's
Sporting Goods.
Ask for Bethany.
And you bought these guns...
The day my daughter came home.
Just in case something like
this ever happened again.
What about a Glock?
I had one for a while.
Decided to get rid of it.
Gone for good?
Yeah. Gone for good.
Well, I got everything I need.
Seems pretty straightforward.
Knox came back,
'cause he thought
Jordan could ID him.
And you defended your family
like any man would.
Thank you.
And Dr. Kersey,
stick to saving lives.
You're good at it.
I will.
Thanks for everything.
So, you satisfied?
No.
Now I'm satisfied.
Sway in the Morning,
Shade 45 at Sirius XM.
Hey, Grim Reaper,
we don't know where you
are, where you went,
or what happened to you,
whoever that is,
stay there. Peace.
Have I told you
how proud I am of you?
Yes, Dad, you've told me,
like, a billion times.
If you ever need anything,
I'm just three stops away.
I know, Dad.
I've got the number.
I love you.
I love you, honey.
Well, you can go now.
All right. Go be smart.
Bye, baby.
Hey!
Subtitles by explosiveskull