♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
All right, everyone.
Listen up.
Today we're going to have
a performance
by one of our students
who has written a song.
The song is about his feelings
towards the current political
climate with North Korea.
Put your hands together
for Tweek.
We're all gonna die!
They have nuclear missiles!
Aah! Aah!
Why are you just sitting there
doing nothing?
We have to get out of here!
North Korea
wants to kill us all
and our president
keeps making it worse!
Why are you all
just sitting there?
Why are all acting
like nothing's wrong?
North Korea is going to bomb us!
We are all dead!
We have to do something!
Do something! Do something!
All right, next up
we have Hannah Williams
with her rendition
of "Wheels on the Bus."
♪ The wheels on
the bus go round and round ♪
Dude, Craig, you've got to get
Tweek to get ahold of himself.
He's freaking everybody out
at school.
What am I supposed to do?
He's your boyfriend, dude.
He's not
gonna listen to me.
He never does
when he's emotional.
Craig, let me tell you
about relationships, okay?
If you don't have
some fuckin' balls,
you're not going to
get anywhere.
Doesn't matter if they're
gay balls or straight balls,
if you don't take control
of your side of a relationship,
you'll get walked all over... Hey, babe.
How you doing?
Oh, hey, baby.
What's going on?
We still on for recess?
Yup, I'll be there.
'Kay, babe.
Love you.
I thought you said
you broke up with Heidi.
I decided to give her
one more chance.
But you said
she was mentally abusive.
She is mentally abusive.
So then why did you
take her back?
Because she said
she was gonna kill herself.
All right, guys? There.
I broke up with her, and she
called me, being all like,
"I can't live without you.
I'm scared what I'm gonna do to
myself. Oh, God."
The bitch is crazy.
What am I supposed to do?
Aah!
Tweek.
Dude, come on.
You got to settle down.
I can't settle down!
We're all gonna die!
We're not all gonna die.
You're overreacting.
Everything's fine, okay?
Oh, God!
The president just tweeted
that North Korea doesn't have
the guts to attack us!
Why would he say that?
He's making everything worse!
Tweek... But North
Koreans are gonna think
we all agree
with the president!
Okay, so how about you write
your congressman a letter.
That won't help anything!
North Korea wants us dead!
Okay, so write a letter
to the North Koreans.
I can't write in Korean
and they all think
we're war-hungry anyway!
Okay, well, then why don't you
just send something nice
to the North Koreans.
It'll make you feel better,
babe.
Send something like what?
I dunno, like,
make them some
croissants or something.
I don't know
how to make croissants!
Well,
what do you know how to make?
Mm... cupcakes!
All right, go home
and make some cupcakes, honey.
Okay!
Hey, Stan?
Yeah?
Can I talk to you
about Eric?
Cartman? Okay...
I just wanna make sure
he's all right.
What do you mean?
I don't even know if
I should be saying this but...
Eric said he was thinking
about killing himself. What?
We broke up, and he called
saying he was about to do it.
I'm still
really scared for him.
Wait, Cartman said
he was gonna kill himself?
I'll send you the voicemail if
you promise to keep it private.
Totally.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
You have to take me
back! You have to!
I'm gonna kill myself,
Heidi!
I'll kill myself,
and then you'll be sorry!
You'll wish you could have me
back, but I'll be dead!
Please, Heidi! Please!
Okay, okay.
Really cool listening
to people's private voicemails.
You sound like
a dying pig.
That's great! I'm glad you guys
think suicide is so funny!
Entrée.
Yes, Eric.
How can I help you?
I don't think
kids at this school
take suicide seriously enough
and we need to raise awareness.
Well,
unfortunately this week
is Distracted Driving
Awareness Week at school,
so you might have
a hard time.
Distracted driving?
Who gives a shit about that?
A lot of people.
There's more deaths now
because of people
on their phones while driving
than ever before.
PC Principal,
someone's life is at stake.
If I have to compete
with distracted driving,
then that's what I'll do.
Huh? Oh!
A young homosexual boy
known only as Tweek
has touched
the hearts of many
by sending cupcakes
to the North Korean government.
The little rascal
apparently made a dent
with the North Korean dictator,
who is said to have loved
the cupcakes so much
that he is started
to make his own...
Oh! Ahh.
Huh?
"U.S. President
responds to cupcakes..."
The human interest
cupcake story
has apparently be heard
by the president.
Just moments ago,
the president tweeted,
"I know that kid Tweek."
He's fucking with you,
North Korea. Get a clue.
"I'll bet he took a dump
in the batter."
What? Why would he say that?
Tweek, calm down.
The president!
He tweeted about me!
Why would he do that?
Did you see that?
Yes, I did see that.
So I went and got you something
to make things better.
What?
It's a fidget spinner.
It's supposed to help
with anxiety. See?
A fidget spinner? Did you read
what the president tweeted?
The
president of the United States
just tweeted again,
this time saying...
"I hope all children of America
will stand with Tweek in saying,"
'Go ahead and bomb us,
Kim Jong Dong,
"we fucking dare you!'"
Hey, guys. Take a minute to read
about distracted driving?
Talk to
all the grownups you know
about staying off their
mobile devices
when they get behind
the wheel.
Hey, guys...
Got a second to help
stop distracted driving?
Thanks.
- Hey, guys...
Hey, guys,
let's a take a minute
and talk about
suicide prevention.
There's probably someone
right now at this school
thinking about killing himself,
and it's not funny.
You better take it serious
or he might actually do it.
♪ I've been feelin' sad,
I've been bein' sad ♪
♪ Can't talk to my mom,
don't even have a dad ♪
♪ I can't go on,
what is living for? ♪
♪ My heart screams
"I don't wanna live no more" ♪
♪ Eric,
we don't want you to die ♪
♪ Eric, give life a try ♪
♪ Eric,
we don't want you to die ♪
♪ Eric, oh, God, no, Eric ♪
I don't wanna live no more!
♪ But Eric,
we don't want you die ♪
♪ You're so cool,
we'd be sad at school ♪
♪ Yeah, but you guys,
you don't understand ♪
♪ With my girlfriend, it's
like I'm living in quicksand ♪
♪ Conflicting thoughts, I need
a battered wives' shelter ♪
♪ my girlfriend is messed up,
but all I wanna do is help her ♪
♪ I'm suffocating,
I'm drowning in sorrow ♪
♪ Gonna kill myself prob'ly
around 2:30 tomorrow ♪
♪ But, Eric,
we don't want you to die ♪
♪ Eric, give life a try ♪
Everybody!
♪ Eric,
we don't want you to die ♪
♪ Eric, oh, God, no, Eric ♪
But it's so hard!
♪ Eric,
we don't want you to die ♪
Only you guys
can make a difference.
I don't care if you're black,
white, gay, straight or trans,
I am going to kill myself
unless you all
start taking it seriously.
♪ Eric, please don't die... ♪
Distracted driving
my asshole.
Hey, Tweek.
Aah!
How's it going
with the fidget spinner?
Great! You seem a
lot less anxious.
Things are
finally turning around
for my little
homosexual son.
What is that?
I'm not sure.
Aah! Aah!
Yet no agreement
has been reached
between the parties involved.
Breaking news now
out of Colorado,
where the North Koreans
appear to have fired a missile
over Tweek's house.
Tweek, of course,
the young boy
who got the attention
of Kim Jong Un last week.
The news media in North Korea
is calling the missile test
a victory for its people.
Today the great
country of North Korea...
has proven its determination
and fortitude...
by successfully firing a missile
over Tweek's house.
Perhaps now Tweek...
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Why's this happening to me?
They have to know
this isn't my fault!
In response
to the North Korean test,
the president
of the United States
has just tweeted
this statement...
"You really think
Tweek is scared?"
Tweek will single handedly
go to North Korea
and fuck all you slanty eyed
bitches doggy style.
What?
Why would he say that?
The president also tweeted...
"If you even think Tweek
is worried about"
a bunch of dipshit poor ass
third world rice pickers,
"think again."
Oh, my God!
What is he doing?
- Tweek, Tweek. Calm down!
- Why won't he just stop? Why?
Tweek! Tweek,
h-here's your fidget spinner!
Why does he
keep making it worse?
Your fidget spinner, Tweek!
Come on, son!
Aah!
Focus on
the fidget spinner.
Oh, geez, looks like North Korea
launched another missile.
Oh, really, like another test?
Where are you looking?
I'm on Drudge.
You see what the president
tweeted about it?
- No, what'd he say?
- The president tweeted.
"North Korea
is the butthole of Asia and..."
Innocent child!
Aah!
I know. I
know, it's so sad.
Well, how nice.
That's a little more like it.
Well, guys, what happened?
Change of heart?
Yeah, you didn't hear?
Gary Borkovec got ran over
by a distracted driver.
What?
Gary Borkovec? Is he dead?
Yeah, dude, he's dead.
Oh, that son of a bitch.
I'm gonna talk
to the principal!
Put down the candle,
Kenny!
Like you ever gave a shit
about Gary Borkovec!
Entrée vous.
PC Principal, I'm trying to
raise suicide awareness,
but everyone's preoccupied
with this "don't be on your
phone when driving" crap.
Gary Borkovec
was a good student.
He didn't deserve
to be taken away
by someone not paying attention
to the road.
Yes, but Gary Borkovec
is already dead.
There's nothing
we can do for him.
Students need to focus on people
thinking about dying.
I don't know
what more you want from me, bro.
I can't just get people to care
with a stupid rap song.
I need a full orchestra...
Woodwinds, strings...
I need black people
in white robes,
white people
in black robes,
and a thousand doves
to release into the air.
I can give you two student
volunteers and one pigeon.
Do you have any idea
how serious this is?
As someone who deals
with suicidal thoughts,
I cannot believe the lack
of concern at this school!
Maybe I should just take
the awareness of my suicide
out to the public
on the streets!
Maybe you should.
Maybe I will!
Ugh.
Hey, Tweek.
Look at what the president
tweeted now!
What time is it, dude?
Just read it!
"North Korea doesn't have
the balls to attack Tweek.
They have
little tiny rice balls."
They're gonna get me, Craig!
Look at what's on CNN!
And the President's tweets
have certainly caught
the attention of North Korea,
who have been spending
the past several days
viewing possible targets
for a nuclear strike
if war were to break out...
What am I gonna do?
You gotta calm down.
How am I supposed
to calm down?
North Korea is gonna get me!
They're gonna get me!
Tweek. Tweek. Tweek.
Let's think
this through logically.
North Korea isn't going
to attack anyone, okay?
They're not going to start
a war they can't win.
Okay?
But, Craig, I...
Tweek.
You have to stop thinking
about it.
Tell you what,
we're gonna go somewhere fun
and make you feel better.
Give a minute of your time
for suicide awareness?
Suicide is serious.
Help tell people like Kyle
it's not a joke.
Hey, good for you guys,
trying to help.
Yeah, make sure everyone
you know gets involved
or else I'm gonna do it.
We're getting a lot
of attention, Eric.
Our website's already
full of kids
saying they feel
the same way as you
and want to get help.
They want to get help?
For what?
For wanting to take
their own lives.
No, this is about me
killing myself.
But, babe, there's a lot of kids
who feel the same way you do.
They're full of shit,
Heidi.
They're just trying
to get attention.
What, are you actually talking
online to these asswipes?
I thought this was about raising
awareness and helping people.
So you're just gonna e-mail
with every every guy
who has a dick and a deathwish?
Are we just your type?
Eric, come on.
No, look, Heidi.
I'm sorry, but you're the one
who started all this
by telling everybody
that I was suicidal.
Okay?
Now I'm under
a lot of pressure to do it.
So the only option I have
is to make sure
that suicide prevention
becomes this entire town's
number-one priority!
Oh, God, did you see
what the President said
about Asians now?
Look out!
Oh, are you freakin'
serious?
Okay, babe,
what do you wanna ride first?
Ugh!
What are we doing here, Craig?
We're gonna get your mind
off politics and have some fun.
Now, what's your
favorite ride?
The Ferris wheel!
Isn't this lovely, Tweek?
Just look at that view.
Oh, God!
Another tweet
from the president!
Oh, come on.
"Why would the U.S. be scared
of North Korea?"
Tweek is so not scared
he's at an amusement park
"in Denver right now."
Jesus Christ!
We gotta get outta here!
Tweek!
Tweek, use your brain.
North Korea isn't going
to attack an amusement park.
You're safer here
than anywhere.
Oh, geez.
The president just called
Kim Jong-un a fat midget.
Oh, and now North Korea
is saying that they're gonna...
Dad, look out!
Oh, shit!
Ride attendant:
All right, everyone,
please wait
for your bumper cars
to come to a complete stop.
We hope you enjoyed
Crazy Cars...
Mommy, look out!
Oh, my God,
what is that?
What is that?
It's probably nothing.
Everything's fine.
Will you please stop
saying that?
I can't take it!
I'm trying
to make you feel better.
Well, maybe I don't wanna
feel better right now!
Okay, but think about that.
That actually doesn't make
any sense.
Why do you have to be
so logical?
I don't need you
to problem-solve all the time,
I need you to... Agh!
I don't know!
Tweek, honey, all week,
you've been freaking out,
and I've been the one
forced to deal with it.
You haven't been dealing
with it,
you've been trying
to make it go away
because my emotions
are freaking you out!
Tweek, North Korea
isn't bombing anyone.
They would lose
the support of China,
and that would be...
There you go again!
Stop preaching facts
to me!
It's not what I need!
Well, I'm sorry that
I'm actually in control
of my goddamn emotions,
ya baby!
Oh, see, now you made me lose
control of my emotions.
God damn it.
Hey Craig, how come
Tweek's not at school?
How should I know?
Uh-oh.
Trouble in paradise?
Look guys, Tweek doesn't
want help, okay?
He just wants to overreact.
Hey, guys,
could we have your attention?
Tomorrow night, we'll be having
a memorial service
for all the students we've lost
to distracted driving.
We hope you can all bring
your families.
Cool, yeah.
Hey, guys, and there's also
gonna be a suicide awareness
pot luck
at 7:30 tomorrow night
in the school gymnasium.
We're gonna have lots of games
and face painting,
and what are you guys
gonna have?
We're gonna have
some guest speakers
and also provide
grievance counselors
for those who need it.
Yeah, grievance counseling...
That sounds super fun.
Listen, guys,
there's a very real chance
I might actually do it
right in front
of everyone tomorrow,
so you don't want to miss it.
Suicide prevention pot luck,
everybody.
Eric, you need to stop.
What they're doing is important.
They're doing a memorial service
with speeches and crying.
What's that gonna solve?
It's not about
problem solving, Eric.
It's about people
getting together
and feeling
what they need to feel!
People need help sorting out
their emotions sometimes.
And the best thing
isn't always quick answers,
But just being there,
supporting each other.
And talking through
those feelings.
You are so up and down.
I don't know what you want
from me, Heidi!
Come on.
There has to be a way.
We can all work together,
here.
So, now
you're on their side!
Oh, my God, I'm seriously
gonna do it right now!
Eric!
Tweek!
What's going on?
What? What do you mean
what's going on?
The same shit
that's been going on!
Nothing's gotten
any better?
Oh, my God,
how does that make you feel?
I feel scared!
I feel alone!
That must be horrible
to feel that way!
It must be hard for you
to even think!
It is!
It's terrible!
I bet it's terrible!
What else are you feeling?
Like I have no control
over my life.
Like I'm just a pawn
in a big game.
Oh, that's a terrifying
thought.
You must feel trapped.
Yeah, like, trapped,
But, like, completely unable
to even move.
Jesus!
It's like there's
no solution to any of this!
What are you gonna do?
What can you do?
I don't know.
It's... It's like maybe...
Maybe I have to find a way
to feel a little in charge
of me again.
That sounds
so insurmountable, though.
How would you even start?
I don't know, but I-I gotta do
something about this.
There's gotta be
a way I can...
Thank you, Craig.
I've got it.
People aren't focused
on the right thing.
I know what I should do.
All right, everyone,
listen up.
Tonight, one of our students
has put together a song
about a very important issue.
It's a song about how
there are certain times
to not be on your phone.
I hope you all listen carefully.
♪ People are dying ♪
♪ The fault is our own ♪
♪ You can do lots of damage ♪
♪ When you're on your phone ♪
♪ We all have to agree ♪
♪ To change it somehow ♪
♪ Let's all make a pledge
to end it right now ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
♪ Don't be on your phone ♪
♪ While being President ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
♪ You might do something dumb ♪
♪ And cause an accident ♪
♪ Let's all agree here today ♪
♪ That if we're leader
of the USA ♪
♪ We'll put it down ♪
If at any point today,
you're being a president,
put down your mobile device.
♪ Put it down ♪
If I'm on the phone,
I will not get behind
the desk of an oval office.
♪ Put it down ♪
I'll take the pledge!
And I'll take the pledge.
♪ No one cares ♪
What's that?
I was just elected president?
Well, then, goodbye!
♪ Put it down
if you're President today ♪
♪ If you find yourself
being President today ♪
Hey Brian, look!
I was just elected President.
That's great, Nancy.
Now, put down your phone.
Right!
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah-ah-ah,
put it down ♪
♪ Give a standing
ovation for suicide in our nation ♪
♪ Or I will rip my own guts out
without one hesitation ♪
♪ Dedication,
that's what it's taken ♪
♪ To waken people to care ♪
♪ And still my future's
so hazy ♪
♪ My girlfriend's
making me crazy ♪
♪ But still
I'm working so hard ♪
♪ You know,
just trying to hold on ♪
♪ Cuz I know that you don't
miss me so much if I was gone ♪
♪ And all the voices
start solo ♪
♪ But every day,
I hear them grow ♪
♪ Saying, Eric, don't do it ♪
♪ Don't do it, nooooo ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
♪ Don't be on your phone
while being president ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
♪ You might do something dumb
and cause an accident ♪
♪ We all agree here today ♪
♪ That if we're leader
of the USA ♪
♪ We'll put it down ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
I'm not gonna do it,
you guys!
It worked!
I'm not gonna do it!
Cartman said he was gonna
kill himself?
I'll send you the voicemail
if you promise
to keep it private.
Totally.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
You have to take me back!
You have to!
I'm gonna kill myself, Heidi!