♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Okay! Okay!
Can everyone hear me? Hello?
Thanks, everyone, for helping us
celebrate Marcus' birthday.
As a special birthday surprise
for you, Marcus,
we got you
your favorite entertainer.
Everyone please welcome
Chuck E. Cheese!
Hey... Check.
Check.
Yes!
Thanks... celeb...
Marcus' birthday...
What's wrong with him?
Can't you tell?
He's high on painkillers!
Ugh. Ugh.
Hold on.
Shit.
Okay, let's...
Let's do this.
♪ I never meant
to cause you any so... ♪
All right, kids...
Uh, why don't we head back
to the party and cut the cake?
I don't want cake!
Who could eat cake
at a time like this?
Another drug overdose?
Most likely.
Percocet and OxyContin
found wrapped
in his cheese cloth.
Prescription drugs
but with no prescription.
You guys know where all these
illegal meds are coming from?
Most likely
from the prisons.
Whenever there's
a drug epidemic,
you can usually trace it back
to people who've been
thrown away by society
and forgotten about.
♪ All day,
I sat in my cell ♪
♪ Just stressing, sitting back,
reading my mail ♪
♪ Reminiscing about
the good times I had ♪
♪ Trying to relive
all the good memories I have ♪
♪ Hate the sound it makes
when they close the gates ♪
♪ Wake up at 6:00
to eat nasty cornflakes ♪
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here
to visit my grandpa.
Oh, how nice of you.
All right.
Arms in the air.
What's the present?
Just some Hummels.
More Hummels?
Why are senior citizens
so infatuated
with these little
German statues?
All right. Go on.
You got 10 minutes.
♪ They call you in the morning
and you gotta get up ♪
♪ Play dice, old timers
gonna teach you about life ♪
♪ Get religious, start reading
about Christ, pray to God ♪
♪ Feels like I'm living in hell,
but I'm stuck in a cell ♪
Grandpa?
Billy!
Finally you're here
to visit.
Did you bring grandpa
a present?
Yeah I got
what you wanted.
Aw, Merry Wanderer
and Happy Traveler?
These Hummels suck!
That's what
the guy gave me!
It's okay, Billy.
I'm just gonna need you
to deliver another one
of Ms. McGullicutty's
crochet pillows.
Aw, come on, Grandpa!
Isn't it enough I come to visit? You
don't understand how it works in here!
Ms. McGullicutty
is top bitch.
You do what she says
or you pay the price.
No, please,
I-I don't want no trouble!
I'm sorry!
I'll get better Hummels!
Dude, Stan!
Come on, dude.
We're gonna go set off fireworks
at Kenny's house.
I will. I just got to do this
for my grandpa first.
Again?
Dude, how many crappy
crochet pillows
do you have to
give out for him?
I don't know.
It's what he wants.
I feel bad for him, all right?
I think he's miserable.
He's old.
He's supposed to be miserable.
Look, I just got to
make this exchange for him
and then we can go.
Oh, oh, I think this is her now.
Are you Stan Marsh?
It's me, Swiper.
Cool.
Do you have the Hummel?
This is it.
Ride into Christmas.
Limited Edition.
Now give me
the pillow.
I have to get
to a birthday party.
'Kay, fine.
All right. Peace!
Dude, that's
really weird.
Old people
love Hummels, dude.
Students, faculty,
and staff,
today, we are facing
an epidemic of
catastrophic proportions.
I know I am not alone
in mourning the loss
of one our greatest
entertainers, Chuck E. Cheese.
Had we known the personal hell
he was going through,
perhaps we could
have helped.
But too many were
more than eager
to supply Chuck E.
With the opioids
that caused
his untimely death.
Chuck E. Was not the first
entertainer in our community
to die from this epidemic.
Let us not forget
Dinkie Dook the clown,
dead of a Roxanol overdose
at Tommy Schneider's
bar mitzvah last March,
Shimmer and Shine,
who both collapsed
from massive amounts
of oxycodone in their systems
at Nelly Anderson's
birthday party,
Spiderman, cut down
in his prime by Demerol,
and just recently,
Swiper the Fox,
dead of multiple opioids
found inside his crochet pillow.
How many more entertainers
must we lose
before we take action?
It is time to declare war
on opioids in our society!
Dude, what
the fuck, Stan?
I didn't know,
all right?
You didn't know you were
slinging drugs for your grandpa?
It didn't occur to me
as a possibility.
Dude, did you hear
everyone in school?
They're coming after you!
You killed Swiper the Fox,
and we were
standing there with you!
You got to tell people
we had no idea
what was going on!
had no idea
Hey, fellas!
Boy, that Marcus kid
is on the warpath, huh?
He's really motivated.
I mean, screw that kid,
but I guess it's good
somebody's finally
doing something
about these goddamn
drug dealers.
Well, see ya, fellas!
Our only way out
is to go to the police right now
and turn Stan's grandpa in!
No, we don't have
to do that.
Let me go talk to him.
I can put a stop to this.
Grandpa, what the
hell have you gotten me into?
Shh! Quiet,
they'll hear you!
There were drugs in the crochet
pillow, weren't there?
Do you know
people are dying?
What do you
want me to do, Billy?
You see Mrs. McGullicutty
over there?
Whoever has
the best Hummel collection
is top bitch in this place,
and she's got the best.
She's ruthless, and she
has those old lady farts.
You know
old lady farts, right?
Where they're so loose
they don't even acknowledge
they happened?
Oh, hello,
Mr. Marsh.
Ah! Mrs. McGullicutty.
How are you feeling today?
I'm doing very well.
Have they given you Percocet
for that knee of yours?
Oh, uh, yeah, here.
I just got it.
Here you go.
Oh, you'd almost think
you were trying
to keep them from me.
Oh, uh, ma'am?
My grandpa actually
really needs those drugs.
He's in a lot of pain.
Ooh, and who is
this little rascal?
That's just my grandson.
He... He's worthless.
How sweet.
Hmm? Coming to visit
your old papa
in the joint, huh?
You love your papa,
don't you?
You'd hate to see him suffer
even more than he already is.
You watch
your ass, Marsh,
or I'll have you
sent to the quiet room.
Wh... What is she talking about?
What's the quiet room?
I told you... She has
all the pull in here.
You go against what she says,
you end up in solitaire.
No. No, please!
I-I didn't do anything!
It's all right,
Mr. Standish.
You just need
a little quiet time.
I don't even know
how to play solitaire! Please!
I understand that, today,
they are performing
Chuck E. Cheese's autopsy?
Oh the kid's
party performer, yeah.
As a concerned member
of the public,
I wish to be present.
Uh, sorry, children aren't
really allowed in autopsies.
Then I shall wait here
to learn the coroner's findings!
Toxicology report
shows subject
had massive amounts of opioids
in system at time of death.
Now proceeding.
Have these
put in the garbage.
What did you find,
coroner?
Who is this?
There is an epidemic
in our community, sir!
Some of us actually
care to confront the problem.
Now, damn it,
what did you find?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
The subject died
of a simple overdose.
We found nothing else
except for two Hummels
in the subject's
rectal cavity.
Hummels?
In his rectal cavity, you say,
and you do not find this
'out of the ordinary'?
Not at all.
We've found Hummels
in nearly all
the birthday entertainer's
anal cavities.
It's very common
in our overdose victims.
Hmm...
A bit too common,
don't you think?
Guys, why does grandpa
have to be in the nursing home?
Can't he
live with us again?
Stan, grandpa has
a lot of needs
that we can't
provide him here.
He needs professional
supervision.
Is that really it?
Because I-I just feel
like we kind of
threw grandpa away
and forgot about him.
Oh, really?
Do you have any idea
how much money we pay
to have grandpa
in that place?
Your grandpa
is styling.
Can you imagine being able
to just sit around all day
and not have to do anything
but eat and watch TV?
Yeah, I'd probably go crazy
and want to kill myself.
Jesus, Stan, it's not like
he's in jail.
Yeah, it's kind of
like jail.
You should go visit him.
I can't.
I'm too busy
busting my ass
to pay the bills
for that place
and to pay for
your guitar lessons.
I don't have
guitar lessons.
I don't want to go there.
It's depressing.
Aw, you tricked me.
Hello?
Dude! Did you give Butters
a crochet pillow to drop off?
Dude,
I don't have a choice.
I have to get the Hummels
for my grandpa.
Well, you need
to get Hummels
without making Butters
a drug dealer.
Drug dealer?
All right.
I think I know
another way.
♪ They got me
locked up in here ♪
♪ And I'm sitting,
doin' hard time ♪
♪ Pissin' in a metal bowl ♪
♪ Eatin' shit
from a lunch line ♪
♪ They got me locked up ♪
♪ In here, nobody knows you
by your name ♪
♪ You just a number ♪
♪ Livin' under bitch-ass rules
of a broken game ♪
♪ They put me here to die,
left me angry and alone ♪
♪ For the crime of being old ♪
♪ They threw me
in this nursing home ♪
♪ They got me
locked up in here ♪
♪ Rotting in my cell ♪
♪ They got me
fake plants and waterfalls ♪
♪ It's a living hell ♪
♪ They got me
locked up in here ♪
♪ So they can throw away
their troubles ♪
♪ All that I have now
are my little German Hummels ♪
♪ Hummels, Hummels,
Hummels, Hummels ♪
♪ They got me ♪
♪ Brand new bitch
was just admitted next door ♪
♪ Hot piece of ass
'cause she's only 84 ♪
♪ Next bingo night, I'll pound
that pussy black and blue ♪
♪ As long as I can get her
before Tommy's grandpa do ♪
♪ They got me ♪
♪ Man, I can't handle
these old-people activities ♪
♪ Tour group on a bus,
children come to sing to us ♪
♪ 3:00 p.m. Canasta,
They put me out to pasture ♪
♪ Death row stops this,
I think they call it hospice ♪
♪ Hospice... ♪
Hey, we have this week's
delivery of medications.
Bring 'em in!
Aah!
Hello, Mr. Marsh.
Oh, he-hey, Marcus.
I understand you've become
quite the Hummel collector
lately.
What's the fascination
with Hummels?
Nothing. I... Look, I just
really like Hummels, okay?
I'm just...
I'm really into Hummels.
Ah. I see.
So then you should be able
to tell me what
this Hummel is called.
That... That's, uh...
Come on!
If you're a Hummel expert,
then you should
know it's name!
It's... It's
Whistling in the Rain.
Wrong!
It's called Stormy Weather.
Do you know where it was found?
No.
It was found deep in the anus
of one Chuck E. Cheese,
the renowned entertainer
beloved by millions!
If you know something
about the epidemic
that is killing artists,
then you better cough it up.
Marcus, trust me, you don't
want to get involved.
I became involved
when Chuck E. Cheese
collapsed like a rag doll
before my very eyes!
If you had any involvement,
I will bring you down!
Well, it was really great
seeing you, Dad.
Guess we oughta
hit the road soon.
You finally come to visit
and leave after 10 minutes.
Oh, Jesus, now we know
where Stan gets
his guilt trips from.
Mmmm.
It seems somebody's been
a little naughty lately.
Oh, Mrs. McGullicutty,
how are you?
Mmmm.
My, what a lovely
Hummel collection
you're starting
to amass.
Almost smells brand new,
doesn't it?
Like it was purchased
right from the factory.
Ooh, and who are
these lovely people?
Family that came to visit,
no doubt?
Yes.
Yeah, we love coming here.
Ah, family.
I remember
when I was a little girl.
My brother used to play
such tricks on me.
Try to fool me.
Try to get out
from his responsibilities.
I'm giving you Hummels.
What's it matter
where they come from?
Oh.
It doesn't matter to me,
but it matters to them.
The big guys.
You see, what they want is
more people who are addicted.
To crochet pillows.
Got it?
Nice to meet you fine folks.
We're never
visiting here again.
Oh, ho!
You're dead, Butters!
Aw, geez.
Guys!
Guys, I need your help!
If it has to do
with your heroin operation,
count us out.
I just talked to my grandpa.
There's more at work here
than just old people
pushing pills.
Stan, we told you
we don't want to be involved.
The head bitch
of the nursing home
is gonna take
my grandpa down...
Maybe my whole family!
Get outta the way,
dude!
But I know what to do!
Whoever has the best Hummels
controls the nursing home.
We gotta steal this lady's
Hummel collection
and give it
to my grandpa.
Dude, Stan, even
if we wanted to help you,
which we don't,
there's no way.
We can sneak into
an old folks home,
distract
all the old people,
and take
an old lady's Hummels.
Oh, wait, there totally is
a way you could do that.
Yeah? What... What is it,
Cartman?
Dude, we're not
getting involved!
Cartman, if you have an idea,
please tell me.
I need you.
I know how to distract
old people.
Aw, shit.
Yes?
We're at
Mimi Thompson's party.
Peppa Pig just collapsed
on stage!
Oh, my God! Don't let anyone
near Peppa Pig until I arrive!
Move aside!
Let me through!
Aw, Peppa.
Peppa, can you hear me?
My name is Marcus Preston.
Can you understand me?
Where did you get
the drugs, Peppa?
Was it from Stan Marsh?
Yo, man,
what you talkin' 'bout?
Get me
a fucking ambulance.
Shh!
Peppa, focus.
Soon you'll be
in Heaven,
jumping in all the muddy puddles
you can imagine,
but first,
you must tell me...
Where do the Hummels go,
Peppa?
All right, let us through.
Get away, kids.
Peppa, now!
Why Hummels?
You've got to squeal!
Old people!
Old people...
love Hummels.
It's okay.
She's with
Chuck E. Cheese now.
Can I help you?
Oh, yes, hello.
We are adorable children
here to entertain old people.
Didn't think we had
anyone scheduled tonight.
Are you with
the Protestant youth group?
Yes, that's right.
We are young prostitutes
here to volunteer
however we can.
Fine.
Round 'em up!
We got another kids choir!
Come on!
Let's go!
Children's choir
in the commons.
- Aw, damn it.
- Shit.
Darling children
are gonna sing for you.
Move your asses!
Aw, not again!
All right, seniors,
how are we feeling tonight?
Our youth group has come
to lift your spirits
with some songs to take you
down memory lane.
We hope you can enjoy
some nice old-people music.
♪ I'm ♪
♪ Insane
in the membrane ♪
♪ Insane in the membrane ♪
♪ Insane
in the brain ♪
♪ Crazy insane,
got no brain ♪
♪ In the membrane ♪
♪ Myyy ♪
♪ Milkshake brings
all the boys ♪
♪ To the yard ♪
♪ And they're like ♪
♪ It's better than yours ♪
♪ Damn right ♪
♪ My hot milkshake ♪
And now,
here's our own take
on that oldie but goodie
by Nirvana.
♪ In the cool, cool winter ♪
♪ Rape me ♪
♪ In the hot, hot summertime ♪
♪ Rape me, my friend ♪
- You suck!
- Hey! Hey!
We are
adorable children
trying to bring sunshine
into your lives!
Fuck you!
♪ If you ♪
♪ Want to call me baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
Hello, Mr. Marsh.
Marcus.
I told you
I'd bring you down.
Marcus,
it's not what you think.
I'm trying to make things
better here.
Oh, I'll bet you are.
You, your grandpa,
all the people here
are going to jail!
I'm calling
the police.
You can put an end
to this place,
but you won't be
stopping the problem!
These people are
victims too, Marcus.
Victims of
a way bigger game
being played
by way bigger people.
Oh, you're a fine one
for speeches...
When it comes to saving
your own ass.
It's not for me,
Marcus.
Look, I know you loved
Chuck E. Cheese.
I know
you'd do anything
to bring down the people
who took him from you.
That's why you have
to go further, Marcus.
Take it to the people
who profited
from Chuck E.'s addiction.
He was just a mouse...
who wanted
to make people happy.
I know.
♪ No time to search the
world around ♪
♪ Bum-bum ♪
♪ When I come around ♪
♪ Bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
♪ I come around ♪
Hey,
where y'all going?
Back to our rooms.
You kids
are absolutely awful.
What the...
Someone is in my room!
Whaaaaat?
Billy, what are you
doing here?
Surprise, Grandpa.
I got what you needed.
Huh?
Billy!
Mrs. McGullicutty's
Hummel collection!
You got it for me!
Yeah, Grandpa.
Now you can put a stop
to all this, right?
Yeah.
I just might be able to.
What are you doing,
Grandpa?
I told you, Billy...
These Hummels hold a special
power with old people.
You!
Go on,
get outta here.
You really thought
stealing my Hummels
will make YOU the head bitch
in this place?
Yeah,
I think it will.
Ooh!
Aah!
Ohh!
Ooh!
Now you know how we do shit
in the nursing home.
That's pretty sweet.
You get your paws off of me,
young man!
There, there,
Mrs. McGullicutty.
Everything's
gonna be all right.
No! Not Solitaire!
I won't play it!
You can't make me!
Congratulations on becoming
head bitch, Grandpa.
Thank you, Billy.
Now, if only
we could take down
the real douche bags
who profit from all this.
Aw, don't worry.
I have a feeling
that's about to happen.
Ladies and gentlemen...
My name is Marcus Preston.
I have some questions.
Shit.
Okay, let's...
Let's do this.
♪ I never meant
to cause you any so... ♪