♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Okay, guys, it's November,
and who can tell me
what that means?
Yes, Francis?
It's time for
the Special Ed Science Fair!
- Yea!
- Science fair!
That's right! The Science Fair
is this weekend,
and I know you are all
very excited to show
the projects
you've been working on!
- Yea! - All right!
Science Fair!
This week, we'll be hearing
all about your projects,
and first up we have
Nathan and Mimallah.
For our science fair project,
we will be showing
the destructive force
of nature by simulating
a volcano!
- Ooooh!
With vinegar and baking soda,
we will make this
papier-mâché volcano explode!
- Aaah!
With the power and fury
of Mount Kilauea!
Our science fair project
is sure to be a blast.
Get it? A blast.
All right, what do you
guys think of Nathan
and Mimallah's
project idea?
- Yay!
We've done it, Mimsey.
We're gonna win
the science fair for sure.
And then every chick
in this school
is gonna want to have
sex with us.
Oh, gee, boss, I don't know
about sex with no chicken.
Not those chicks, numbskull.
I'm talking about bitches.
You know what girls like?
They like winners.
And when we win
the science fair,
we're gonna be up to our ears
in pussy.
Is it just me,
or are things around here
getting worse and worse?
It's definitely
not just you.
I think everyone's is shock
that Heidi went back to Cartman.
What keeps driving her
back to him?
It's so weird.
And she's so...
Mean and angry these days.
People change.
They say you become
more and more like
the person you're with,
and I guess it's
true with Heidi.
Hey guys, wassup?
Hey, Heidi.
What are you guys
talking about?
Nothing.
Bullcrap, you're all
talking about me again!
'Cause you're
judgmental bitches.
Eh.
Heidi...
Are you okay?
It's just...
You look...
I look what?
You know,
you just look...
What, I look fat?
Is that what you wanna
say, Wendy?
Fuck you, bitch.
She's just concerned,
Heidi.
Meh, myeh,
meh, meh, meh, Heidi.
I'm just trying
to enjoy my lunch here.
Can I do it without you guys
shitting all over me?
All right good,
Timmy.
Test 42-A is successful!
Let's move on
to the next phase.
Well, hello, gentlemen.
Oh, hey, fellas.
We're doing great.
Timmy!
Thought we'd stop by
to see how
your science fair project
was going.
I thought we was comin'
to rub their faces
in how good our science
fair project was, boss!
Shut up, Mimsey!
So, what are
you guys working on?
Oh, it's fantastic.
This year, Tim-Tim and I
are doing our project
on water bears!
Ohh, water bears.
You hear that Mimsey?
Like there's any such thing
as water bears.
That blue Science Fair Ribbon
is as good as ours.
Well, we gotta get back to
our lava volcano.
Good luck finding your
water bears.
Oh, would you like
to see them?
Wha? What are you
talking about?
Timmy and I have gathered
thousands of water bears.
Take a look into
the microscope.
Water bears are water-dwelling,
eight legged micro-animals.
Timmy!
They are one of nature's
most resilient animals.
Studies have shown
they can survive lava
and even the vacuum of space.
What... How...
Where the fuck did you
learn about these things?
Where all good scientists
learn from... Octonauts.
Octonauts!
Some scientists believe
the study of water bears
is key to human survival.
Aw, gee, that sounds
a lot better than
a lava volcano,
huh, boss?
Well not really,
because a science fair
is supposed to be an experiment.
I fail to see what
the experiment is here.
Oh, that's easy! You see,
for the past several weeks,
Tim-Tim and me have
been training the water bears
to respond to different
sound waves.
We've found that they respond
best to Taylor Swift.
Hit it, Timmy. ♪ Oh, look
what you made me do ♪
Take a look!
♪ Look what you made me do ♪
♪ Look what you
just made me do ♪
just made me ♪
♪ Ooh, look what you
made me do ♪
We still have some
training to do,
but we're excited
about the results.
I have to admit your lava
volcano is pretty great, too!
Maybe we could tie
for first place.
Come in.
You wanted to see me,
Mr. Mackey?
Oh, yes, Heidi! Uh,
we just wanted to see
if you have transportation
to the Special Ed Science Fair
this weekend or if you wanted us
to set something up for you.
What?
Uh, Saturday
is the science fair,
and you're the judge
for the competition.
Judge a special needs
science fair?
Ugh, no, thanks.
Well, Heidi is there a problem
with you being the judge
this weekend?
Uh, yeah, it's Saturday,
and I don't wanna be at skewl.
But you're always the judge
of the Special Ed Science Fair
because you're
our best science student.
So, now I'm gonna be punished
by being forced to judge
a bunch
of handicapped kids?
But... M'kay. You see
the problem is that
you volunteered last month,
Heidi.
You said you wanted to do it,
M'kay.
Well, how can you
expect students to commit
to things a month
in advance?
I don't even know what
I want for dinner tonight!
Look, the kids have
worked really hard
and have done some
amazing projects.
You're gonna force me to
come to skew on a Saturday?
Heidi...
Is everything all right?
Oh, what are you gonna
call me fat now, too?
It just so happens
I'm a vegan!
Which means it's difficult
for me to get enough protein
so my body doesn't burn fat,
it burns muscle,
which makes it look like
I'm fat, but I'm actually
way healthier than any of you!
Heidi, you're judging
the Special Ed Science Fair
this weekend.
Aw, God damn it!
Mimsey! Come on!
Okay, Nathan!
Shhhhh!
Shut the fuck up!
Gee, we could get in
a lot a trouble.
Y-you sure we should mess
with Jimmy and Timmy's
science fair project?
Mimsey, do you know
what Jimmy is?
He's a cockblocker.
Arr, what's a cockblocker?
Every time I come up a way
to score with the ladies,
there's Jimmy
trying to one-up me.
This science fair is
supposed to finally make us
successful enough
to get chicks.
Aw, gee, I don't know
if we should use
our position of power
to exploit women.
I'm not letting those assholes
win the science fair.
That's why I say...
The only good water bears
are dead water bears.
Let's go!
This is bullcrap!
How can they force me to be
the science fair judge?
Now I know how it feels
to be a slave!
It's... not exactly like
being a slave, Heidi.
Yes, it is! Am I being paid
to judge the science fair?
No!
Do I have a choice?
No.
Ooh, yes, massa!
Lemme judge that science fair
for ya, sir!
God, will you stop?
Theresa, don't get all aggro
on me because you're pissed off
you're family
lives in a trailer.
My family doesn't live
in a trailer.
We live in a tiny home!
My parents downsized
to make a smaller footprint
on the environment.
That's what I said... your
family lives in a trailer.
There's lots of progressive
people living in tiny homes.
There's five others
on our block!
Right.
That's called a trailer park.
I don't live in
a trailer park!
Just don't even
respond to her.
Just ignore her.
I'll try, but she's
such a bitch.
She wasn't talking
to you, Heidi.
Oh! Looks like Isla has
something to say, you guys!
Hold on, I'm sure this is
going to be really profound.
Go ahead, Isla, knock us out
with your wit and satire.
This should be good,
you guys!
Hey, Heidi!
What's up?
Oh, hey, babe,
what's going on?
What are you up to?
Nothing just talking to my
girlfriends about tiny homes.
Well, hello there,
ladies.
Oh, hi, Nathan.
We just wanted to
remind you that this weekend
is the Special Ed
Science Fair.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, that's right.
Pretty sure you'll all be
impressed with what you see.
Hope you can make it.
Did you see that,
Mimsey?
The way those girls
bit their bottom lips
when I said Science Fair?
We're about to be
drowning in muff.
Nathan, Mimallah!
You gotta get to Special Ed!
Special Ed class
isn't for another two hours.
No, no!
You gotta see this!
Jimmy and Timmy's
water bears!
They've changed!
What?
- Whoa!
- Ooooh!
- So cool!
- I can't believe it.
Jimmy and Timmy,
this is incredible!
You've somehow made them
even smarter!
What's going on?
Nathan!
It's amazing!
The water bears we've
trained are starting
to display
social advancements!
But they're supposed
to be dead!
Oof!
What social advancements?
They've actually evolved
to the point of doing
the hokey pokey!
The hokey pokey?
♪ You put your right foot in,
you put your right foot out ♪
and you shake it all about ♪
♪ You do the hokey pokey
and you turn yourself around ♪
♪ That's what it's all about ♪
You gotta be fucking
kidding me.
Boys, this might be
the single greatest.
Special Ed Science Fair
project I've ever seen!
Butters.
Oh! Hey!
How would you like to be the judge
for the Special Ed Science Fair
this weekend?
Uh, I can't.
I'm going to a birthday party.
Butters, don't be a dick!
Yeah don't
make up excuses
because judging handicapped
students sounds terrible.
Yeah, Butters. God!
He's not making it up.
It's my birthday party.
Well, then could you
invite Heidi, please?
She needs an excuse
not to have to go to
the special needs
science fair.
What's wrong with supporting
them, they're our friends?
Because nobody wants
to be trapped in a gym
with Special Ed science.
Actually, some of their projects
are pretty cool.
- Shut up, Kyle!
- Samesies!
Look, it's all just
a complete waste of time!
It's not like
a Special Ed Science Fair
is actually gonna
contribute to society!
Move! Move aside, kids!
Official business!
Move it, children!
Excuse me,
can I help you?
We understand that you're
about to have a science fair.
With some very interesting
experiments.
That's right. The science fair
is this Saturday
from 10:00 a.m. To 2:00 p.m.
We're here to help
however we can.
Your Special Ed department
has all our resources
and our support.
This science fair...
just might be
what saves us all.
What the hell
is going on?
Everywhere I turn, people
are being given handouts
while I'm forced
to work my ass off!
It's total bullshit!
Yeah. Uh, babe I understand
that you're pissed off,
but, um, you know,
it is recess.
Maybe we should relax
and have some fun.
Relax?
How can I relax?
I get straight A's!
I ace every test!
And who gets
all the support?
The Special Ed
department!
Good.
Bring it on in.
These kids need
to have access
to everything
they need.
Wow, look at this,
Tim Tim.
They've all been researching
water bears, too!
That's correct.
Like you,
we've come to realize
that water bears are
the the key to our future.
Are these
the special water bears
we read about
on your school message board?
That's right.
The water bears
we've been working with
appear to be evolving
somehow.
Then they are the key
to our survival, boys.
Gentlemen, perhaps I can
interest you in a lava volcano.
You won't believe
your eyes
when I add
some simple baking soda.
There's no time for that.
We need everyone working
on Jimmy and Timmy's project.
I'm gonna let you kids all in
on a little secret.
We don't want
to create a panic,
but the end
is very near...
and we have
very little time.
Fellow students,
I have asked
to speak today
because of the hypocrisy
and bullying
that is coming
from the administration
at this so-called skewl.
It is an outrage that
our principal and counselors
demand our participation
in frivolous programs
that are outrageously
overfunded.
Why is it that
the school allows funding
that only goes
to special-needs students?
Are the rest of us
not special?
If we are continually asked
to work for no money
and ask our parents
to pay for our programs,
then soon
we will all be poor
and forced to live
in a trailer park, like Theresa.
It's not a trailer!
Theresa, get over it.
You live in a trailer park.
It's not a big deal.
Oh, o-okay, honey.
You're kind of getting
off topic, sweetie.
What did you say?
I just... I just want you
to stay on point
so we can
get this over with.
"Get this over with"?
You're supposed
to be supporting me!
I am supporting you,
sweetheart.
Being supportive doesn't mean
you criticize me, asshole!
Just forget it!
My point is,
if the school administration
doesn't cancel
the science fair,
I will see to it
that they are all fired
for discrimination!
She's kind of
like Cartman
but with the ability
to follow through.
Oh, dude.
Bro.
Francis, could you hand me
the sound-wave generator?
This is bullshit.
The Special Ed Science Fair
is turning into a love-fest
for Jimmy
and Timmy's project.
They're gonna get
all the fame and glory.
Yeah, I guess we kind of shot
ourselves in the foot, huh, boss?
If it weren't for us,
those water bears
wouldn't have even gotten
smarter in the first place.
Hey, Mimsey.
That's right.
They don't deserve
the credit.
We do.
Uh, excuse me.
If you're all trying
to figure out
why these water bears
are different,
you're talking
to the wrong guy.
Wh-What do you mean,
Nathan?
Mimsey and I did
some experimenting
with the water bears
on our own...
We was tryin'
to kill 'em!
It was us
who made them evolve.
So we should be the ones
working for the government.
The government?
W-We aren't
the government.
Y-You're not
the government?
But you said you were here
to help stop us
from becoming extinct.
Not you, us.
We're with... the NFL.
Our fans are leaving
at an exponential rate.
We've been hit
with anthem protests,
protests
to those protests,
and, worse of all,
concussions.
The more reports
that come out,
the more people are getting
turned off by football.
We've been experimenting
with water bears
because we believe
they are our last hope.
Oh, I get it!
You've been experimenting
with water bears to see how
to make humans more impervious
to concussions.
No. We've been experimenting
with water bears
to try
and make them fans.
Sportscaster #1: A beautiful
night for football
here in Los Angeles
as the Chargers take on
the Buffalo Bills.
Sportscaster #2:
And a record sellout crowd
here at the stadium.
Football clearly
more popular than ever,
with a whopping 17 million
in attendance!
The NFL, of course, working
really hard to reach new viewers,
and it looks like
they've found their answer
in tardigrades.
The water bears are thrilled
to be here,
and, of course, love seeing
themselves on the jumbotron.
They're all ready
for some football,
and enjoying
the fan-favorite kiss cam!
And we're ready for kickoff
as the cheers of 17 million fans
rock the stadium!
We're running
out of time.
We have to see
if these water bears
truly are different.
Insert the box!
Gently.
What do you see now?
Uh...
I see the box.
What... What's
in the box?
What are
the water bears doing?
Uh, they're just walking around,
and... Oh, wait!
They appear to be interested
in the box!
These water bears
are different.
All right, everyone,
listen up!
Give me your attention,
please.
Due to circumstances
beyond our control,
we are canceling
the Special Ed Science Fair.
- Oh, no! Canceling?
- What?
You can't cancel
the science fair.
We're on the verge
of a breakthrough here.
It's canceled.
You guys can all get this shit
out of here and leave.
Thank you.
You don't understand!
The Special Ed Science Fair
is our only hope!
I'm sorry, but, uh,
our hands are tied...
by Heidi.
I think you all
fail to understand
the seriousness
of our situation...
Football is dying!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay.
Close the door!
Everyone back to work.
Nobody will stop
this Special Ed Science Fair!
Do what he says!
Aah! Okay!
Jesus Christ!
Are you just gonna stand there?
Do something!
What the hell
do you want me to do?
I want you
to have some balls
and act like
you care about me!
Heidi, you need to stop
being such a bitch!
Call me
a "bitch" again.
Do it.
Call me
a "bitch" again.
You are... acting...
like a... bad girlfriend.
That's what I thought!
Hey, wait a minute!
The water bears
have changed again.
I think it's working.
Let me see that!
Yes!
Yes, they're starting to adapt!
Son of a bitch. We just might
have ourselves some fans.
Now, quickly, children.
We must replicate these
water bears to create more!
If nobody else is gonna
do anything, I will!
Wha...
The water bears!
- Get her!
- Stop her!
She's over here!
Heidi! Heidi,
will you please listen to me?
Move it!
Get the fuck
outta the way!
I said get outta the way,
you assholes!
- Get her!
- She's over here!
We got the fat girl.
Front of the school.
Shit!
Little girl, stop.
It doesn't have to end
this way.
Move aside!
Heidi, seriously...
you need
to listen to me.
I don't... have to listen...
to anybody.
Yes. Yes, you do.
You need to listen.
Fuck you.
No fuck you.
Little girl, please.
What you have in your hand
is very special.
Well, I'm sick of everyone
treating me like shit.
Think about the NFL...
how much joy
it brings everyone.
Don't listen to them.
Give the water bears to me.
I deserve all the fame
and bitches.
Heidi, you gotta stop
being so angry.
Look, if you... if you don't
do it for the NFL,
what about humanity?
Those creatures are showing
the first signs of sentience.
Think about what they could
mean for science,
for medicine,
making people better.
Come on, babe.
We all want
the old Heidi back.
Screw all you guys.
Ahh!
Dude. Wow.
Is there something
you wanna talk about?
No, I was just
trying to figure out
why you decided to drink
20,000 micro animals
that were showing
signs of intelligence.
Whatever. It's Saturday,
and I'm not in school.
Yeah, you're... you're
not in school.
How come we never
snuggle anymore?
Wh-What?
We used to snuggle
all the time,
and it's totally
gone away.
What's happened?
Well, bunny, we still...
Snuggle!
Yes, yes, let's... let's
snuggle, yes.
God damn it!
How come there's nothing
to watch on Saturday
but kids' cartoons?
All right, kids!
Now let's do the hokey pokey!
♪ You put your left foot in,
you put your left foot out ♪
♪ You put your left foot in ♪
♪ And you shake it all about ♪
Ooh.
What's going on
in nya?
Whoa.
What is going on in nya?
I feel something
moving around.
Ahp...
Ew.
Snuggle!
Okay.
Okay, honey.
Agh. Ugh.
Well?
Did you have any luck,
Mr. Jones?
I'm afraid, Commissioner,
that the Special Ed Science Fair
failed to produce
more viable water bears.
Then the NFL
truly has no hope.
We're done for.
Not quite.
We were able to obtain
something else
that just might be
our future.
Ohh!
Call me
a "bitch" again.
Do it.
Call me
a "bitch" again.
You are... acting...
like a... bad girlfriend.
That's what I thought!