I'm so glad you're moving
out of this neighborhood Annie.
Some dude peed on my car
while I was parking it.
Oh, you met spaghetti!
- Yeah, I won't miss him.
- Speaking of missing people,
how did Jeff dodge this
bullet... Of friendship.
He said he was
under the weather.
- Pshaw!
- Thanks for helping.
Can you imagine how much fun
this is gonna be?
Me living with Troy and Abed?
Yeah, there'll be
a honeymoon phase,
but it won't be long
till you hate their guts.
What's this whittle guy's name?
I'll never hate Troy and Abed.
Oh, my God, I forgot.
You're 20.
Don't worry.
It's natural.
When you become
roommates with friends,
the things you love about
them become the things
that make you want
to smother them with a pillow.
But...
That's unacceptable to me.
Then... I'm lying?
Forgetting something?
Yeah.
Yeah, like I'm gonna
get sick of this.
Wh-what wh-what?
We're here to help you move...
on the dance floor.
- Nice! Tweet it!
- Tweeting it.
- What are you tweeting?
- Everything.
We're live tweeting
Annie's move on Twitter.
Hashtag #Annie'sMove.
How fun.
How was I supposed to know
it was a handicap space?
Because the man in
the wheelchair was yelling it.
Oh, yeah, and he doesn't
have an agenda.
Hold it.
- Where's Winger?
- Sick.
Pshaw!
Yeah, I'm calling him.
Hello?
So you're sick, huh?
That's what they tell me.
Well, Britta,
you got me all figured out.
Well I can tell
you're not in bed.
That's right, Britta.
I'm pretending
to be violently ill
to avoid lifting a few boxes.
Because I'm 13.
And who's your primary care
physician, Mr. Winger?
Uh, Dr. Schroeder.
S-c-h.
Um, do you want to see
my insurance card?
Please.
Wait, are you at a hospital?
No, I'm at The Gap.
You hear that?
That's not a heart monitor.
It's a machine telling me
I'm low on khakis.
Dr. Tarpenian to radiology,
Dr. Tarpenian.
Crap, I- I'm sorry.
I just assumed—
Whatever.
I don't blame you.
I've lied before.
It's probably karma
that I'm sick.
But believe me,
if you had what I have,
you'd rather be moving boxes.
Okay, feel better.
Sorry.
Yeah, I'll see
you guys on Monday.
You are fantastic.
So are you.
What are you doing after this?
Probably trying
a couple of boot-cuts.
But after that...
Maybe, like, a blazer?
♪ Give me some rope,
time in a tree ♪
♪ give me the hope
to run out of steam ♪
♪ somebody said
we could be here ♪
♪ we could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ one by one
they all just fade away ♪
sync by Sp8ky, corrected by susanaLC
www. addic7ed. com
How are we out of packing tape?
I don't know.
I think I left some
in the bathroom.
Nope, uh, nothing in here.
You guys!
You used all of it?
I had a big breakfast.
Nice. Tweeting it!
Okay, there might be
a slight danger
I will end up hating them.
Man children...
Can't live with them,
can't leave them alone
with your tape.
Britta, don't make jokes.
You're bad at it.
Also, I can't afford
to live anywhere else.
And everything is riding
on this, and I'm out of tape—
Annie, listen.
Breathe.
When I was in Amsterdam,
I met this guy
who ate too many shrooms
and fell out of a window
at the Anne Frank house.
Oh, no, no, he's fine.
The doctor said that the drugs
made his body just limp enough
to keep him from
breaking his neck.
Britta, I don't see
what your taste in men
has to do with my situation.
What I'm saying, Annie,
is that if you're gonna live
with two guys like that,
you've gotta learn to go limp.
Loosey-goosey.
Shake it all up.
- Limp...
- Loosey-goosey.
Okay... New Annie.
Going with the flow.
Loosey-goosey— Is it
loosey-goosey or goosey-loosey?
Is that hyphenated?
You know what?
Don't tell me.
I don't need to know.
Bro... Heim.
Okay, go.
- Aah!
- Didn't feel it.
What... a fun use
you found for my bubble wrap.
I know! We have to
sell this to the military.
Yeah, baby.
Yah, babuh.
Here's the other tape gun.
Think fast!
Ooh!
You broke my pluggy thing.
No worries.
That's what
the security deposit is for.
Hashtag #ThatlsAll.
Oh no, you're not
letting some slumlord
take your hard-earned money.
I'll fix it.
I used to do that
kind of thing all the time
- when I was a slumlord.
- Really, Pierce?
My landlord's coming by
to do the inspection at 5:00.
Do you think you're gonna
have it done by then?
Easy peasy, George and Weezie.
This is probably the last
that'll fit in our car.
I'll help you.
But not in an uptight way.
I'm very concerned about
this living situation.
I mean, I've seen enough
episodes of Friends
to know that cohabitation
leads to sex, drugs
and something a parade magazine
called Schwimmer-fatigue.
Good for you, Shirley.
What's the saying?
If you can't stop 'em,
judge 'em?
Well, somebody's gotta be
this group's moral compass.
And that somebody
has to be you, right?
Because by moral compass,
you mean Shirley's religion.
Well...
Want a ride?
Well, if this is a forecast
of the conversation,
I will ride with somebody else.
Don't worry, Shirley.
Keep me company while I fix this
and I'll give you
a ride over there.
Britta!
Well, hey there, stranger!
What a coincidence, huh?
This is just like that, uh,
Lake House movie.
I can only assume.
Even I have limits.
Dean Pelton.
Jeff, it's Saturday.
Call me Craig.
Off campus,
I'm just a craigular Joe.
Ooh, what'd you get?
Ah, now I feel like I have to
head back out there.
Dean—uh, Craig,
it's nice to see you
but I actually have to run.
Oh, yeah, you're probably
heading to help Annie move.
Right?
Oh, I follow Troy
and Abed on Twitter.
Looks like Annie's moving
and you're...
Sick at the hospital?
Curious.
I might head there myself.
I could tell them you said hi.
I'd rather you didn't.
Well, maybe I won't have time.
Especially if we're doing...
Lunch?
Yeah, but your religion
isn't the same as morality.
And calling me amoral
because I'm atheistic
is religious persecution.
How can I religiously
persecute you?
You don't have a religion.
Oh, look!
A hitchhiker.
A person in need.
Oh, my God.
What am I doing?
I'm pulling over
to help him out.
Do not help him out.
Why, because it
proves the existence
of secular morality?
No, because he looks stinky.
Judge not, Shirley.
Judge not.
I really appreciate it,
thank you.
Where are you headed,
fellow human?
Riverside Falls?
That's 40 minutes away.
Oh, I guess I'm just
a really good person.
I knew you were.
I could see the kindness
in your faces.
I assume you've both
accepted Jesus Christ
as your lord and savior?
Oh, that's nice.
Ow!
Needed a coat of paint anyway.
Welcome, Annie,
to your new home.
Okay... To reacquaint you,
there's the bathroom,
kitchen,
and, of course, our bedroom.
And if the room's a rockin'
please come a knockin'
because there's something
probably terribly wrong.
Yeah, we're pretty chill
in there.
Mm-hmm, now let's go
see your room.
What's that?
That is your room.
You said this was
a two bedroom.
It is, one, two.
Yours is a blanket fort.
An awesome blanket fort.
But still highly flammable
so no candles.
What do you think?
- Tweet it?
- Tweeting it!
I am not surprised
you're so taken aback.
This apartment
is where dreams come true.
We spent our whole lives
being told that blanket forts
are only for special occasions,
like sleepovers
or when uncles die.
But that's a lie, Annie.
You can live
in a fort of blankets
all day, every night.
It's so awesome.
I'm surprised you guys haven't
chosen to live in one.
Well, we'll be spending
enough time in yours.
I mean, it's where
we're gonna watch tv.
Right.
Uh, what's that door
over there?
That's not a bedroom?
- No.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Is it a linen closet?
Something like that.
What's a linen closet?
A siesta salad and an iced tea.
Excelente.
And for you?
Ahem.
- The gentleman...
- Oh...
will have
a top notch-os
and a watermelon Margarita.
Thank you, Jeffrey.
So, any brothers or sisters?
And we'll take the check too.
Oh!
What's the rush?
We're eating lunch,
and then I'm leaving.
Okay.
I just hope that I don't
bump into
your study group on Monday.
And I pray they don't ask me
who I saw at the mall
on Saturday.
Because,
unlike a certain someone,
I just don't think I could lie
to those sweet people.
Dean, this is blackmail.
Ah! Call me Craig.
And call blackmail
"a day at the mall with Craig."
Because that's all
I require, Jeffrey.
You and I are going
to have some fun.
And create a few memories.
And I suggest you get into it.
Because that counts.
A song for the señor, señor?
Adiós amores.
Oh, what a surprise.
Mmm!
Jeez.
This is actually
quite calming for some reason.
And that's when I realized
I had to forgive them.
That's a beautiful story.
So inspiring how he came
to find the lord.
- Isn't it, Britta?
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, I didn't exactly have
to find the lord.
He was inside me.
Amen!
What's your name, friend?
- Jesus.
- Oh.
Are you Latino?
No, my child.
I am him.
You're what now?
I am the one true son of God.
I was sent here
to save humanity.
Oh, no.
Well, it is a pleasure
to have you in my car, Jesus.
Britta, stop.
It's not funny now.
Hey Jesus, just curious, what's
your position on marijuana?
It was given to us by God.
It should be legal.
Oh, that's nice.
Hear me, hear me!
Presenting
the real-life fairy tale
of how princess Annie was saved
from bad neighborhood forest
by woodsman Troy.
And Bebad, his emotionally
unavailable unicorn.
Brought to you by
the girl-yogurt
Jamie Lee Curtis uses to poop.
There's
a package of it in the fridge
as a welcoming gift.
Now, once upon a time
there was a beautiful
princess named Annie.
Hi.
Who was harassed every day
by Count Spaghetti.
The evil cracksmith who lived
outside of her building.
Whoa!
I just stand here?
Oh, come on, Jeffrey.
Get in here!
This is gonna be fun!
Or else.
So we just punch in
the numbers?
That's right.
Okay, you know this one, Jeff.
We've sang it a thousand times
together in my mind.
Huh, huh?
Oh come on, Jeffrey.
Make or break time.
Unless you want to be
back here next Saturday.
♪ There used to be
a graying tower ♪
♪ alone on the sea ♪
♪ you became the light ♪
♪ on this dark side of me ♪
♪ and now that
your Rose is in bloom ♪
♪ a light hits the gloom
on the grave ♪
♪ Jesus loves marijuana ♪
Amen.
♪ and drinking
human blood, oh ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ I compare you to a kiss
from the Rose on a grave ♪
♪ ooh, the more I get of you ♪
♪ the stranger it feels, yeah ♪
♪ now that your Rose
is in bloom ♪
♪ a light hits the gloom
on the grave ♪
Ah!
That was great.
Yeah, might have been
a little fun.
Huh, see?
And you emailed your therapist
that you wanted to be
alone this weekend.
What?
Hmm?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Now, with your permission,
I'd like to sing a little song
about race-mixing.
This one's called
"Don't You Do It."
Get out!
Ah, good evening, senator.
Any requests?
What do you want to do next?
I paid for a full hour, so—
I email my therapist
from my Greendale account.
The same account
where I received an email
from physique25 telling me
about today's sale.
Is that why you're at the mall?
You read student emails?
Oh, oh, now the patriot act
says I can do it, Jeffrey...
Technically.
Need I remind you
the nation is at war— Ow!
- I'll kill you.
- No, Jeffrey, no!
Jeffrey, Jeffrey come on!
Just remember,
we were making memories!
No, Jeffrey, no!
Aah!
No, Jeffrey!
No, no, it's too violent!
You're scaring me!
Don't let the terrorists win!
And then the three of them lived
happily ever after!
And Bebad became
the little dipper.
The end.
- Kiss me, woodsman Troy!
- Mwah!
You guys!
Living here is gonna be
fun all the time.
Let's make
the entire apartment a fort.
I'll get more blankets.
This is a space we reserved
for virtual adventures.
Like a playroom but
only works in our minds.
We call it the dreamatorium.
But... it's a bedroom.
No, no.
There's only two bedrooms,
including the blanket fort.
This is the...
Dreamatorium.
All day, I've been
jumping through hoops
to fit in.
Including the literal hoops
you put in front of the toilet.
- Yes.
- And you guys are hoarding
this second bedroom
as some kind of playroom?
And making me sleep
on a pile of laundry?
Hey, we worked hard on that.
And it's a blanket fort.
It's an asylum
for half-witted children!
As the only adult
in this apartment,
I am making an ultimatum.
Me or this...
Stupid dreamatorium.
Dreamatorium is non-negotiable.
Read the lease.
Especially the part
we added in crayon.
You don't wanna
take this to court.
Trust us, this place
can be a courtroom
in the blink of an eye.
This doesn't work for me.
From the minute
I joined the study group
I've been worried
about how uptight I am
and how I'm no fun.
And then I was worried
that I wouldn't fit in here
or be able to hang
with you guys.
But you know what?
Why don't you ever ask
yourselves whether
you can hang with me?
Why am I always the one
that has to adapt?
I'm sick of this crap!
Enjoy your stupid dreamatorium.
We will!
Because this is
our apartment too!
And just because we're awesome
doesn't mean we're not adults!
Candy cigarette?
I don't want a candy cigarette.
- I want our Annie.
- Yeah, we blew it.
I picked the wrong week
to quit.
What the hell is this?
In security deposit terms,
it's a gold mine.
And you're lucky it's only
gonna cost you money.
Your friend nearly
killed himself.
Yeah, that's me.
Lucky Annie.
I'm really sorry, Annie.
I had some island girls over
and one of them must have
slipped me a Mickey.
I'm just glad you're okay.
You can pay me back
by helping me
get all my stuff
from Troy and Abed's.
You're moving again?
How long was I out?
Is napster still a thing?
You've been out long enough
for me to realize
that I'm gonna need
to keep living alone.
Come on.
Let's get you cleaned up.
Oh, what the hell?
I have brain damage.
Nothing I do counts.
Where is all my stuff?
Troy, Abed?
It's all yours.
We're sorry.
Sometimes we get stuck
in our own little world.
And then in that world,
we make even littler worlds.
And sometimes there are
tunnels between those worlds.
Or a subway.
One time a snake.
We're sorry.
Do you like it?
Of course, I do.
It's perfect.
I mean, I can rearrange
the throw pillows.
You have them arranged
by size instead of color, but—
What did I say?
But what about
the dreamatorium?
Oh, it's staying.
The dreamatorium is more
important than any of us.
But you're more important
than our bedroom,
so we put the bunk bed
in the blanket fort.
This is all gay code.
You sure I'm worth it?
Yeah, there's a couple of
things that we were hoping
that you'd help us with.
Yes, like where does
the water go in the iron?
And what's the iron for?
And what
gets out kool-aid stains?
Yeah, we already know
that the opposite
color kool-aid
doesn't work.
Also, Troy scraped me when
we were fork-jousting last week
and I don't think
it's healing right.
- Oh, Abed, that's infected.
- Ew!
Infected. That's the word
I was looking for.
- Hi, guys.
- I thought you were sick.
I was... n't.
I kind of made it up
to get out of helping.
Oh, that's okay.
- It is?
- Yeah, it is.
Oh, hey, Jeff, did you
know that when it snows
my eyes become large?
♪ and the light that
you shine can be seen ♪
He tweeted it?
- ♪ baby ♪
- He tweeted it!
♪ A kiss from a Rose
on the grave ♪
♪ and now that your Rose
is in bloom ♪
♪ a light hits the gloom
on the grave ♪
- Oh, look out, asteroids!
- That was close.
Thanks for getting us
to planet Greendalia
safely, horsebot 3000.
- Well—
- Oh, no!
Greendalia has been overrun
by evil King Blorgon!
- Look out, Troyborg!
- Pew pew pew!
Ah! I'm dead.
Horsebot 3000, no!
I love you!
I am King Blorgon.
And my plan is
to blow up the world!
Your lasers are
useless against me.
Aim for his butt.
It's his only weakness.
- Pew pew!
- Bam bam!
- Aah!
- We did it!
Peace and tranquility have
been restored to Greendalia.
And all thanks
to horsebot 3000.
He belongs to the stars now.
All right, five more minutes
and we should probably
put a stop to this, right?
Jeff, are you—
I liked horsebot 3000.
Sync by Sp8ky, corrected by susanaLC
www. addic7ed. com