How many of those fingers do you think
we could shove up his ass?
Depends if he's had any practice.
That the sort of thing
you and your sister go in for?
She loosened you up for us?
He's going to fall.
He's going to fall off ms horse Help hm
Water.
Water. Please, water.
Water. Water, please. Please. Please.
If I die, you won't be getting...
Oh, enough.
Here.
Can't say that I've ever seen a
man drink horse piss that fast.
Stop!
MAN Far enough.
Do that again and I'll
take your other hand.
Come on, you.
Oh Lord Tyrion. Come in, come in.
I hope we might speak in confidence.
Oh. Always in confidence.
About the events of the Backwater.
Perhaps this is the wrong time?
Oh no it's a wonderful time.
I thought one of your little birds might
Have knowledge of my
sister's intentions to...
End your life?
I didn't inherit Littlefinger's spies
along with his position, Fm afraid.
Which is why I'm coming to you.
I need proof.
Proof? Will there be a trial?
I need to know.
I have no proof, only whispers.
Before all this nastiness,
I was going to tell you
the story of how I was cut.
Do you want to hear it still?
I don't know. Do I?
As a boy, I traveled with a troupe of
actors through the Free Cities
One day in Myr,
a certain man made
my master an offer too tempting to refuse
I feared the man meant to use me
as I'd heard some men used small boys.
But what he wanted was far worse.
He gave me a potion
that made me powerless to move or speak,
yet did nothing to dull my senses.
With a hooked blade he sliced me,
root and stem. Chanting all the while.
He burned my parts in a brazier.
The flames turned We
and I heard a voice answer has call.
I still dream of that night.
Not of the sorcerer, not of his blade.
I dream of the voice from the flames.
Was it a god? A demon? A conjuror's trick?
I don't know.
But the sorcerer called
and a voice answered.
And ever since that day, I have hated magic
and all those who practice it.
But you can see why I was
eager to aid in your
fight against Stannis
and his red priestess.
A symbolic revenge of sons.
Yes.
I feel the need for actual revenge against
the actual person who
tried to have me killed,
which will require
a degree of influence, which...
You do not possess at the moment.
But influence is
largely a matter of patience, I have found.
Once I had served the sorcerer's purpose,
he threw me out of his house to die.
I resolved to live to spite him.
I begged.
I sold what pans of my body remained to me.
I became an excellent thief,
and soon learned that
the contents of a man's letters
are more valuable
than the contents of ms purse
Step by step.
one distasteful task after another,
I made my way from the shims of Myr
to the Small Council chamber
Influence grows like a weed.
I tended mine patiently
until its tendrils reached
from the Red Keep
all the way across to the
far side of the world,
where I managed
to wrap them around something very special
Ugh.
The sorcerer.
Hello' my old friend.
It's been a long time.
I have no doubt
the revenge you want will be yours in time,
if you have the stomach for it.
When people talk about the Night's Watch,
they never mention the shoveling.
Or the shit.
They tell you about honor,
pardoning crimes, and protecting the ream,
but shoveling really is most of it.
And getting attacked or killed or worse.
And that.
But when you're not getting attacked or
killed, usually you're shoveling.
Ah, look. More shit.
I was starting to wonder
what to do with the rest of me day.
We need to get out of here.
When the Lord Commander
says we go we go.
The Lord Commander
told us to go to the Fist of the First Men.
How'd that turn out for us?
He had no way of knowing.
We do now. We know what's out there.
Craster's been out here surviving.
So he's your
new protector now? Our good friend Craster?
We're like the sons he never had.
Mormont isn't gonna save you.
This lummox here isn't gonna save you.
When the Walkers come calling, Craster will
serve us up like so many pigs.
If we want to live,
we'll have to look out for ourselves.
You woke him.
I'm sorry.
- He's beautiful.
- Shh!
He's beautiful.
- Does he have a name?
- No
Are you going to give mm one?
Why?
- Here.
- Gilly.
You said to hold it for you
until you came back.
- You're back.
- I wanted you to have it
I don't want your stupid thimble.
I want to save
my baby's We Can you do that?
Can you?
I don't have time for you.
I don't have time for anyone but him
because he doesn't have much time.
You have to go after him.
How?
You know how.
Brandon.
- Mother.
- How many times have I told you?
No climbing.
Mother, I need to find it.
It's here. It's calling me.
I want you to promise me.
No more climbing. Promise me.
Promise me! Promise me!
Mother! Mother!
Promise me, Bran!
Promise me!
Is he very large?
No larger than usual, apparently.
And yet, they said that he was...
Extraordinary.
The most extraordinary man they've ever
had. And they've had a lot of men.
We're talking about the same Podrick?
The quiet boy in
Lord Tyrion's service? Seems a bit simple?
What did he do to them?
I don't know, my lord.
The girls are usually quite descriptive.
So what did they say?
They said it was hard to describe.
Huh.
Prodigies appear in the oddest of places.
And what did
Littlefinger say about this loss of income?
He was too preoccupied to notice.
He's leaving for the Eyrie soon.
I'm helping him prepare for his journey.
Ah, yes, to pursue his enduring love of the
Lady Arryn and the title
that comes with her.
Sad, really.
Is that all it takes to make our friend
Lose interest m poor Sansa Stark?
He hasn't spoken to her
since the last time, as far as I know.
Hmm.
But I don't think he's lost interest.
What makes you say so?
His shipboard inventory.
You can read
Rare for a woman in your profession
- Former profession.
- Of course
I'm missing something obvious
you're about to point out?
Two featherbeds.
He's bringing two
featherbeds for the cabin.
Who is important enough to Littlefinger
to merit a featherbed,
besides Littlefinger?
Could he be bringing one of his girls?
He's not interested in them, my lord.
How do you know?
Because I'm one of his girls.
Prodigies in odd maces indeed.
Rhaenyra Targaryen was murdered
by her brother or rather his dragon.
It ate her while her son watched.
What's left of her is
buried in the crypts right down there.
The ceremony
is traditionally held in the main sanctum,
which seats 700 comfortably.
There appears
to be a good deal of room elsewhere
on the premises for everyone else.
There aren't
more than 700 people of any importance.
No the rest are there
to look adoringly upon the 700
to remind them how superior they
must be to have the best seats.
Over there, in that urn,
the ashes of Aerion Targaryen.
Aerion Brightflame, they called him.
He thought drinking wildfire
would turn him into a dragon.
He was wrong.
And, of course,
there's the Mad King, killed by my uncle.
Would you like to
see where the last Targaryens are buried?
Are you sure Lady Margaery
doesn't find all this a bit macabre?
No, it's quite all right, Your Grace.
I'd love to see their tombs, really.
It's like taking a walk through history.
The tomb's just up here.
This is so exciting.
You were married here, Your Grace?
Yes.
Must seem like only yesterday.
Hmm. Seems like a lifetime ago.
Your husband was buried here as well?
No, he wanted his remains
returned to Storms End.
Such a tragedy.
A fairly predictable tragedy.
Hunting and drinking don't mix.
I should say not.
My son's a hunter. It helps him forget
he's never been within a
mile of a real battle.
I seem to recall he laid siege to Storm's
End for the better part of a year.
All he laid siege to
was the banquet table in the command tent.
I told him to stay out
of Robert's Rebellion.
He had no business fighting
an actual warrior.
We mothers do what
we canto keep our sons from the grave.
But they do seem to yearn for it.
We shower them with good sense,
and it slides right off,
like rain off a wing.
And yet the world belongs to them.
A ridiculous arrangement, to my mind.
The Gods have seen fit to make it so
My father didn't want them here.
He was going to have their bodies burned
and thrown in the Blackwater,
But the High Septon
convinced him otherwise.
I'm glad he did.
I'm sorry, Your Grace.
I know they did terrible things at the end,
but their ancestors built this.
Sometimes severity
is the price we pay for greatness.
I couldn't agree more.
Shall we go and see them?
If you give them your love:
they will return it a thousand fold.
I've spoken with them.
I know how they feel about you.
You led the defense of King's Landing.
They adore you.
Open the doors.
Jeffrey.
Wait.
Lady Margaery!
Bless you, Lady Margaery!
Margaery!
Long live Lady Margaery!
King Joffrey!
Gods bless King Joffrey!
How far is it to Deepwood Motte?
Not far, my lord.
Your sister is waiting for you there.
- She sent you to save me?
- Yes.
I sewed them'
the men who were torturing you
I did what they told and waited.
Why would you risk your life for me?
I grew up on Saltcliffe, my lord.
I was only a boy when they took you away.
My father brought us up to the bluffs
so we could watch you carried off.
I remember the look
on my father's face when he told us,
"That's Balon Greyjoy's last living son."
And those are the words I heard over again
when I saw what they were doing to you.
Those men' they said my father
knew what they were doing to me
Did he?
I don't know, my lord.
They... They never told me much.
My sister's men are loyal to her.
We don't need to hide from them.
Not all those are your sister's men.
Some of them are loyal to your father.
Hmm.
What is it?
I was just thinking how jealous I was
when my father told Yara
to take this place.
What did he tell you to do?
Raid fishing villages.
He didn't trust me. Thought I was a Stark.
I could never be a Stark.
Robb Stark always reminded me of that.
He lorded it over you?
Didn't have to.
All he had to do was be.
Be who he was born to be.
His life fit him better than his clothes.
How could someone like that
ever be a brother to me?
He's the King tn the North.
And me...
My father gave me a choice and I made it.
I could never be a Stark.
But ironborn that's what I was born to be.
I paid the iron price for Winterfell.
I murdered those boys.
The Stark boys?
Never found them.
Just some poor orphans
living with a farmer.
I let Dagmer slit their throats
and I let him burn the bodies,
so I could keep Winter-fell
and make my father proud.
Maybe it's not too late.
It is.
My real father lost his
head at King's Landing.
I made a choice,
and I chose wrong.
And now I've burned everything down.
Not everything, my lord.
She's up here.
- Yara.
- Shh!
Wait.
I brought him back. He...
He killed the others.
What? No, I didn't.
You can't'
No' Please. Stop!
No!
Put him back where he belongs.
Eat.
What are you doing?
I'm dying-
You can't die.
You need to live to take revenge.
I don't care about revenge.
You coward.
A little misfortune and you're giving up.
Misfor.
Misfortune?
You lost your hand.
My sword hand I was that hand.
You have a taste,
one taste of the real world
where people have
important things taken from them,
and you whine and cry and quit.
You sound like a bloody woman.
I know what you did for me.
You told them Tarth was full of sapphires.
It's called the Sapphire Isle
because of the blue of its water.
You knew that.
Why did you hem me?
You wanted to speak to me?
Yes, about Jaime.
What about mm?
I wanted to make sure we're doing
everything we can to get mm back.
When Catelyn Stark took Tyrion prisoner,
what did I do in response?
You started a war.
And if I would start
a war for that lecherous little stump,
what do you think I am doing
for my oldest son and heir?
Whatever you can.
Whatever I can.
You're still here.
Yes.
Why?
Did it ever occur to you that
I might be the one who deserves
your confidence and your trust,
not your sons?
Not Jaime or Tyrion, but me.
Years and years of lectures
on family and legacy...
The same lecture, really,
just with tiny, tedious variations.
Did it ever occur to you that your daughter
might be the only one
listening to them, living by them?
That she might have the most
to contribute to your legacy
that you love so much more
than your actual children?
All fight. Contribute.
The Tyrells are a problem.
The Tyrells helped us
defeat Stannis Baratheon.
The Tyrells saved your life,
your children's lives.
Margaery has her claws in Jeffrey.
She knows how to manipulate mm.
Good I wish you knew
how to manipulate him.
I don't distrust you
because you're a woman.
I distrust you because
you're not as smart as you think you are.
You've allowed that boy to ride roughshod
over you and everyone else in this city.
Perhaps you should try
stopping him from doing what he likes.
I will.
Do you like it Nana?
Another golden rose. How original.
I eat from plates stamped with roses.
I sleep in sheets embroidered with roses.
I have a golden rose
painted on my chamber pot,
as if that makes it smell any better.
Roses are boring, dear.
"Growing strong.“
Ha' The dullest words of any house.
"Winter is coming!" Now that's memorable.
"We do not sow." Strong Strong.
Those are houses you watch out for.
Direwolwes and krakens, fierce beasts.
But a golden rose growing strong,
that strikes fear in the heart.
Look, little loves.
A spider in the garden.
Run along now. Grow strong.
My lady.
I wanted to personally
welcome you to King's Landing.
The city has
been made brighter by your presence
The city is made brighter by my presence?
Is that your usual line:
Lord Varys? Are you here to seduce me?
A little obvious, perhaps.
Oh no please.
Seduce away It's been so long.
Though I rather think it's all for naught.
What happens when
the nonexistent bumps against the decrepit?
A question for the philosophers.
But you've come mincing
all this way for something.
- So?
- Might I sit?
No.
Come. I've heard you're such a clever man.
I'm curious why you've sought me out.
You've taken an interest in Sansa Stark
Havel?
Because I spoke to her once in this garden
and one of your little spies
came running to tell you?
Why shouldn't I? She's an interesting girl.
Is she?
No. Not particularly.
But she's had an interesting childhood.
She has. Sadly.
Well, forgive me for
wasting your time, then.
I thought we shared
certain hopes for her well-being.
Come, come.
You surrender rather easily.
Walk with me.
I know the walls have ears,
but apparently the shrubbery does, too
I choose my allies carefully, and
my enemies more carefully still.
Which is Sansa Stark?
Neither. A babe in the woods.
I admired her father.
Yes.
Ned Stark had many admirers,
and how marry stepped forward
when the executioner came for his head?
I could not help Lord Stark.
Perhaps I can help his daughter.
How?
You're not the only one
who has taken an interest in her.
That's hardly surprising.
She's a beautiful girl with a famous name.
Indeed. She'd make a lovely
match for the right suitor.
It almost feels
as if you're about to arrive at the point.
Littlefinger is not long for the capital.
A confidant of mine has told me that
when he goes Sansa Stark goes with him.
And why have you come
to me with this matter?
Littlefinger was born
with no lands, no wealth, no armies.
He has acquired the
first two. How long before he has the army?
Perhaps you'll laugh,
but I know him better than most,
and this is the truth.
Littlefinger is one of
the most dangerous men in Westeros.
If Robb Stark falls,
Sansa Stark is the key to the North.
And if he marries her,
he'll have the key in his pocket
Which seems such a shame.
Why should a man with such a low reputation
steal away such a lovely bride?
You must despise him.
You're working so hard to undermine him.
Actually, I rather enjoy him.
But he would see this country burn
if he could be king of the ashes.
You are a clever man, Lord Varys.
You are too kind.
I believe I have a possible solution.
One doesn't need to
be clever for that. It's obvious, isn't it?
I didn't mean to disturb you.
You haven't.
We'd like some privacy, please.
If you wouldn't mind
waiting back inside the keep.
Or if you'd be kind enough
to give me your names,
I'll ask the King to
speak with you himself.
What did you pray for?
I can't tell you.
Why not?
I'll tell you
what I prayed for in the Sept this morning
Let's see,
for my family's health and happiness,
for an end to the war, for a short winter.
Boring and traditional, I'm afraid.
And you?
I'm sorry, I just can't.
My cousin Alanna
was the most beautiful girl I'd ever seen.
When I was 12, I was all elbows and knees,
and Manna
looked like a goddess sent to torture me.
"Pig Face," she called me.
“Pig Face"? That's ridiculous.
It had something to do with my nose.
Whenever she passed me
in the halls, she'd oink.
So I prayed that
she'd catch a horrible skin disease.
A week after that,
she came down with porridge plague.
Porridge plague?
Oh: you don't have it in the North?
Your" skin starts to look like boiled oats,
and eventually,
your face slides off and you die in agony.
But that's awful.
You're...
I believed you!
Porridge plague. I'm an idiot.
Don't say that. No, you're not.
So what happened to Alanna?
Oh, she grew up to be
the most beautiful woman
and married a handsome
lord and they have darling children
and live in a castle by the sea.
It's all terribly frustrating.
I'm sure she's jealous of you now.
You'll be married here in the capital,
and shew have to come watch and
pretend to be happy that you're queen.
I want us to be friends, good friends.
That would make me very happy.
You must see Highgarden.
You'd love it there. I know you would.
We have a great
masquerade the night of the harvest moon.
You should see the
costumes. People work on them for months.
Uh. I don't think the Queen would
let me leave King's Landing.
The Queen Regent you mean.
Once I marry Joffrey. I'll be queen.
And if you were to marry Loras,
your place would
be at Highgarden, wouldn't it?
We would be sisters,
you and I. Would you like that?
His name was Bannen.
He was a good man, a good ranger.
He came to us from...
Where did he come from?
Down White Harbor way.
He came to us from White Harbor.
Never failed in his duty.
He kept ms vows the best he could.
He rode far. Fought fiercely.
We shall never see his like again.
And now his watch has ended.
Didn't think a broke foot could kill a man.
It wasn't his foot that killed him.
That bastard Craster starved him to death.
Craster's got his daughters to feed.
You on his side?
We can't just show up
and steal all his food.
We're brothers of
the Nights Watch not thieves
The day we leave.
Craster will tap a barrel of our wine,
and sit down to a feast of ham and potatoes
and laugh at us starving in the snow.
He's a bloody wildling.
Never knew Bannen could smell so good.
You have one son. Don't you, Mormont?
I had my 99th.
You ever meet a man with 99 sons?
And more daughters than I can count.
I'm glad for you.
Are you now?
Me, I'll be glad when
you and yours have gone.
As soon as our wounded are strong enough.
Ah!
They're as strong as they're gonna get.
Them that's dying, why don't you
out their throats and be done with it?
Or leave them if you've not the
stomach, and I'll sort them myself.
Whose throat you gonna out, old man?
Wait outside.
It's cold outside and
there's nothing to eat.
My wives gave you bread.
There's sawdust in the bread.
You don't like it,
you go out there and eat the snow.
I'd rather eat what you've got hidden away.
I told you to wait outside.
He's sitting there drinking our
wine, eating his fill while we die.
I gave you crows enough.
I've got to feed my women!
You admit you've got a hidden larder?
How else you make it through winter?
- Enough! Out!
- I am a godly man.
You're a stingy bastard!
Bastard?
Out with you, you little thief.
And you! And you!
Go sleep in the cold on empty bellies.
I'll chop the hands off
the next man who calls me bastard.
You are a bastard.
A daughter-fucking, wildling bastard.
The Gods will curse us for this.
By all the laws...
There are no laws beyond the Wall.
Show us where he hides the food,
or you'll get the same as him.
Unhand her.
- I shall have your head for this.
Quickly Quickly.
What's happening?
I'm not going out there.
No, we have to go. Now!
Follow me. I know the best way.
Come on.
Run fast, Piggy, and sleep well!
I'll be cutting your throat
one of these nights.
Can I take this hood off yet?
I do apologize little lady,
but it's better for you
if you don't see where we're going.
Halt!
- What is it?
- Blackstrap rum.
Ugh!
Not easy finding molasses in wartime.
I'd have some.
Let's go home.
What is this place?
Somewhere neither wolves
nor lions come prowling.
You look like a bunch of swineherds.
Some of us were swineherds.
And some of us
tanners and masons. That was before.
You're still swineherds
and tanners and masons.
You think carrying a crooked
spear makes you a soldier?
No.
Fighting in a war makes you a soldier.
Beric Dondarrion?
You've seen better days.
And I won't see them again.
Stark deserters. Baratheon deserters.
You lot aren't
fighting in a war, you're running from it.
Last I heard,
you were King Jeffrey's guard dog.
But here you are 1000 miles from
home. Which of us is running?
Untie these ropes and we'll find out.
What are you doing
leading a mob of peasants?
Ned Stark ordered me to execute your
brother in King Robert's name.
Ned Stark is dead
King Robert is dead.
My brother's alive.
You're fighting for ghosts.
That's what we are,
ghosts waiting for you in the dark.
You can't see us, but we see you.
No matter whose cloak
you wear, Lannister, Stark, Baratheon,
you prey on the weak,
the Brotherhood
Without Banners will hunt you down.
You found god? Is that it?
Aye.
I've been reborn
in the light of the one true god.
As have we all.
As would any man
who's seen the things we've seen.
If you mean to murder
me then get on with it.
You'll die soon enough, dog.
But it won't be murder, only justice.
And a kinder fate than you deserve.
Lions, you call yourselves.
At the Mummer's Ford,
girls of seven years were raped,
and babes still on the breast were out
in two while their mothers watched.
I wasn't at the Mummer's Ford.
Dump your dead children at some other door.
House Clegane was built upon dead children.
I saw them lay Prince Aegon and Princess
Rhaenys before the Iron Throne.
Do you take me for
my brother? ls being born Clegane a crime?
Murder is a crime.
I never touched the Targaryen babes.
I never saw them never smelled
them, never heard them bawling.
You want to cut my throat, get on with it!
But don't call me murderer
and pretend that you're not.
You murdered Mycah.
The butcher's boy. My friend.
He was 12 years old.
He was unarmed And you rode mm down
You slung him
over your horse like he was some deer.
Aye, he was a bleeder.
You don't deny killing this boy?
I was Jeffrey's sworn shield.
- The boy attacked the prince.
- That's a lie!
I hit Jeffrey. Mycah just ran away.
Then I should have killed you. Not
my place to question princes.
You stand accused of murder.
But no one here knows the truth
of the charge, so it is
not for us to judge you.
Only the Lord of Light may do that now.
I sentence you to trial by combat.
So, who will it be?
Should we find out
if your fire god really loves you: priest?
Or you, archer? What are you
worth with a sword in your hand?
Or is the little girl the bravest one here?
Aye.
She might be.
But it's me you'll fight.
The master says they are untested.
He says you would be wise
to blood them early.
There are many small cities between
here and there, cities ripe for sacking.
Should you take captives, the masters will
buy the healthy ones and for a good price.
And who knows?
In 10 years some of the boys you send them
may be Unsullied in their turn.
Thus, all shall prosper.
Is it done, then? They belong to me?
It is done.
She holds the whip.
You hold the whip.
This bitch has her army.
Unsullied!
Forward march!
Halt!
Tell the bitch her beast won't come.
A dragon is not a slave.
You speak Valyrian?
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of the House Targaryen,
of the blood of Old Valyria.
Valyrian is my mother tongue.
Unsullied!
Slay the masters,
slay the soldiers,
slay every man who holds a whip,
but harm no child.
Strike the chains off every slave you see!
I am your master!
Kill her! Kill her!
Kill her!
Dracarys.
Unsullied!
You have been slaves all your life.
Today you are free.
Any man who wishes to leave may leave,
and no one will harm him.
I give you my word.
Will you fight for me?
As free men?