Are you
sure about this?
No.
It's dangerous.
If we take Tywin's castle from him,
the lords of Westerns
will realize he's not invincible.
Take his home, take his
gold, take his power.
Why are you telling me?
You begged me not to send Theon
to negotiate with his father,
and I ignored your advice.
Now Winterfell is burnt to the ground,
the North is overrun with ironborn,
and Bran and Rickon are gone.
So, Casterly Rock...
I'm asking your advice.
We have enough men?
If Walder Frey cooperates.
If reinforcements arrive from King's
Landing before we take the castle,
we'll be caught between
Tywin's army and the sea.
We'll lose the war and
die the way Father died.
Or worse.
Show them how it feels
to lose what they love.
My honored guests,
be welcome within my walls and at my table.
I extend to you my hospitality
and protection in the light of the Seven.
We thank you for your hospitality, my lord.
I have come to make my apologies, my
lord, and to beg your forgiveness.
Don't beg my forgiveness, Your Grace.
It wasn't me you spurned. It was my girls.
One of them was supposed to be queen.
Now none of them are.
This is Arwyn, my daughter.
My daughter Walda, my daughter Denna,
my daughter Waldra.
My eldest granddaughters Ginia and Neila.
Serra and Sarra, granddaughters, twins.
You could have had either.
Could have had both, for all I care.
My granddaughter Marianne.
My granddaughter Freya.
My granddaughter...
Wertha.
Waldra.
Waldina.
I'm Merry.
Fine.
And herds my youngest daughter Shirei,
though she hasn't bled yet.
Clearly you don't have
the patience for all that.
My ladies.
All men should
keep their word, kings most of all.
I was pledged to
marry one of you and I broke that vow.
The fault is not with you.
Any man would be lucky
to have any one of you.
I did what I did not to slight
you, but because I loved another.
I know these words cannot set right
the wrong I have done
to you and your house.
I beg your forgiveness
and pledge to do all I can to make
amends so the Freys of the Crossing
and the Starks of Winterfell
may once again befriends.
Very good.
There she is.
Come closer. Let me have a look at you.
Still can't see you.
Old eyes.
Love.
That's what the Starks of
Winterfell call it, eh?
Very honorable. I call it a pretty face.
Mmm.
Very pretty.
Prettier than this lot, that's for sure.
Very shapely as well.
Oh, you try to hide her under that dress.
If you wanted to hide her,
you shouldn't have
brought her here in the first place.
I can always see
what's going on beneath a dress.
Been at this a longtime.
I bet when you take that dress off,
everything stays right where it is.
Doesn't drop an inch.
Your king says he betrayed me for love.
I say he betrayed
me for firm tits and a tight fit.
And I can respect that.
When I was your age, I'd
have broken 50 oaths
to gel into that without a second thought.
Well, I've enough room
in the hall for you lot.
We'll set up tents outside
with food and ale for the rest of your men.
Thank you, my lord.
Well, let's get ready.
The wine will flow red
and the music will play loud
and we'll put this mess behind us.
Where?
There.
There. It's a back gate.
My men use it
when they visit Yunkai's bed slaves.
Your men, but not you?
I have no interest in slaves.
A man cannot make love to property.
This is where we enter
the city. Very few guards. They know me.
They let me inside...
We're not gonna
sneak an army through a back gate.
I kill the guards.
I take your two best men
and lead them through the back
streets, which I know well,
and open the front gates.
Then comes the army.
Once the walls are breached,
the city will fall in hours.
Or perhaps you'll lead Grey
Worm and me to the slaughter,
cutting the head off our army.
The masters of Yunkai will pay you your fee
and you won't have to split it three ways
'cause you've already
slaughtered your partners.
You have a very suspicious mind.
In my experience,
only dishonest people think this way.
You command the Unsullied.
- What do you think?
You are a leader now.
Do you trust him?
I trust him.
You leave tonight.
Very good. We'll prepare.
Ser Jorah.
You can use an extra sword.
You're the Queensguard,
Ser Barristan. Your place is by the Queen.
If we are truly her loyal servants,
we'll do whatever needs to be done,
no matter the cost, no matter our pride.
We're west of Castle Black,
but the Nightfort's closest to us.
It was the first castle on the Wall.
The Watch abandoned it
during the reign of King Jaehaerys I.
Too big. Impossible to maintain.
Other than Castle Black itself,
the Nightfort's the perfect castle for us.
It's got a secret sally port,
the Black Gate, as old as the Wall itself.
No one's used it in centuries, most likely.
It leads through
the Wall right down into the Nightfort,
if one knows how to find it,
which, it just so happens, I do.
How do you know all that?
I read about it in a very old book.
You know all that
from staring at marks on paper?
Yes.
You're like a wizard.
Our father used to tell us
that no wildling ever looked
upon the Wall and lived.
Here we are.
Alive.
Remember what happens to children who run.
I'm your father and I'll do the talking.
The roads have gone right to hell.
Cracked three spokes this morning.
Need a hand?
Need about eight hands.
Oh!
Got to get this salt pork to the
Twins in time for the wedding.
Many thanks.
Don't! Don't kill him.
Dead rats don't squeak.
You're so dangerous, aren't you?
Saying scary things to little girls.
Killing little boys and old people.
A real hard man you are.
More than anyone you know.
You're wrong.
I know a killer.
- A real killer.
- That so?
You'd be like a kitten to him. He'd
kill you with his little finger.
That him?
- No.
- Good.
Don't kill him.
Please.
Please don't.
You're very kind. Someday
it'll get you killed.
Where are we?
The Gift, I think.
Brandon the Builder gave all this land
south of the Wall to the Night's Watch
for their sustenance and support.
Maester Luwin taught me that.
Doesn't seem to be supporting
anyone at the moment.
It's good land, and there's no war up here.
Why leave?
Wildlings.
Sorry.
But they come over
the Wall and raid, steal, carry off women.
Old Nan said they turn
your skull into a cup
and make you drink your own blood from it.
That's what Old Nan said.
There's a storm coming.
I don't see any.
It's as good a place to shelter as any.
We can drink some blood while we wait.
I don't need much.
Only one old man
and eight good horses.
What's one old man doing
with eight horses?
He breeds them for the Watch.
How's he keep folks from stealing them?
The Watch protects him.
Not today, they don't.
He's selling horses,
he's got some gold in there.
And proper steel.
Let's carve him up.
We just take the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
I keep telling you.
He's an old man. A spear through
the heart's a better way to die
than coughing up your
last with no one but your horses to hear.
The Watch might send
a few men looking for a horse thief.
They'll send a lot more
to hunt down murderers.
I hope so.
Killing crows in their castle is tough.
Killing them out
here in the open, that's what we do.
Spread out. Surround the hut and move in.
Ygritte!
Clear the barn!
No one's going to believe
you're a hog farmer if you eat them all.
Best part of the animal.
Don't worry. They're still there.
I know they're still there.
You check every five minutes
like you're afraid they're gonna move.
I'm not afraid.
Of course you are.
You're almost there
and you're afraid you won't make it.
The closer you gel, the
worse the fear gets.
No point in trying to
hide behind that face.
I know fear when I see it.
Seen it a lot.
I knew fear when I saw it in you.
You're afraid of fire.
When Beric's sword went up in flames,
you looked like a scared little girl.
And I know why, too.
I heard what your brother did to you.
Pressed your face to the fire like
you're a nice juicy mutton chop.
That give you some ideas?
Might do.
Go ahead, then. You might get away.
Might even make it there on your own.
They're just over the river.
The closest you've been to family
since llyn Payne snipped your daddy's neck.
Someday I'll put a sword through
your eye and out the back of your skull.
How are we going to get past the Wall?
My uncle said it's 700 feel high.
How did you get past it?
Got in a boat and rowed
past the Bay of Seals.
It would take us two months
to get to the Bay of Seals.
Some climb straight up the ice.
Even Hodor's not strong enough to
climb the Wall with me on his back.
Hodor.
Nineteen castles guard the Wall.
Only three are still manned.
- Hodor!
One of those abandoned
fortresses will give us a way through.
My uncle said the gates
were sealed with ice
and stone when the castles were deserted.
Well, we'll have to open them up again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
There's a rider out there.
- Just one?
There's more.
- Hodor!
It's just thunder, sweet giant.
Hodor.
I yield.
- I yield.
- Wildlings.
Where's Shaggydog and Summer?
Hunting.
- Hodor!
- Shh. Quiet, Hodor.
Make him shut up. If they hear us...
Hush, Hodor. No... No more Hodoring.
Hodor!
- Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
- You need to keep quiet.
- They're gonna hear us.
Hodor, be quiet.
- Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
Hodor! Hodor!
Hodor, be quiet!
What did you do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
What's that?
That's a horse dying.
Bring them over here.
That was
the last of them. The rest are dead.
I heard shouting up there.
Thunder.
I know the difference
between shouting and thunder.
Maybe it's ghosts.
That won't help you, grandpa.
Where you riding?
Doesn't matter now, does it?
No, it doesn't matter now.
Cut his throat,
or he'll tell the crows we're here.
You understand.
Let me stand at least.
Let me go with a bit of dignity.
Make the crow kill him.
You're one of us now. Prove it.
The wolves are out there.
I can't do it by choice.
I don't know how.
It happens in my dreams.
You're a warg, Bran. It's in your blood.
I can't.
You just did, with him.
A wolf is nothing compared to that.
She looks sharp.
Do it.
I told you. He's still one of them.
Go on, boy.
Go on!
He's a crow. He'll always be a crow.
And here's his crow wife guarding him.
He'll stab us in the back
first chance he gets.
- Kill him.
He's one of them.
No!
Do you hear me? Ahh!
You're not gonna die for one of them.
Do it.
They'll find us if you don't.
You were right the whole time.
When you hear
a songbird's whistle, you come.
I'm a great whistler. The
greatest in the land.
Daario Naharis.
That one was quick.
- There may be others.
- I doubt it.
The Yunkish prefer to let their
slaves do their fighting for them.
That's what you call a few guards?
Come on! What do you got, huh?
Lord Edmure,
I hope I'm not a disappointment to you.
You're a delight to me, my lady.
You may now cloak the bride and
bring her under your protection.
In the sight of the Seven,
I hereby seal these two souls,
binding them as one for eternity.
Look upon each other and say the words.
- Father, Smith...
- ... Warrior, Mother...
- ... Maiden, Crone, Stranger.
- I am hers...
- I am his...
- ... and she is mine...
- ... and he is mine...
from this day
until the end of my days.
Is that safe?
They're long gone.
You were right.
I can get inside
Summers mind whenever I want.
Of course you can.
North of the Wall there are wildlings
who can control all sons of animals.
But you did a lot more than that.
You got inside Hodor's mind.
They can't do that north of the Wall?
No one can do that. Anywhere.
When I was looking through Summer's eyes,
- I saw Jon.
Where?
He was with the wildlings.
They tried to kill him, but he got away.
He'll be heading back
to Castle Black, then.
That's where we should go.
For all we know,
Castle Black's already under attack.
If this many wildlings got through...
I already told you.
I'm not going north of the Wall.
Everything Jojen told me is true.
You saw what I did to Hodor.
I have to find the three-eyed raven.
Listen to me, little lord.
Don't worry.
I'm not asking you to come with me.
It won't be safe for Rickon.
Me? I'm coming with you.
No.
You and Osha and Shaggydog
head for the Last Hearth.
The Umbers are our bannermen.
They'll protect you.
I'm coming with you.
I'm your brother. I have to protect you.
Right now I have to protect you.
Robb's at war and I'm
going beyond the Wall.
If something happens to us,
you're the heir to Winterfell.
Would you know how to
find the Last Hearth?
You Southerners
build your big castles and you never move.
You're easy to find.
We're not Southerners.
And I don't want to leave you.
Shh!
Come here, little soldier.
You and me,
we're gonna have some adventures.
You don't have to do any of this.
Your family took me in
and was good to me without cause.
We'll be fine, you and me.
The Umbers are great warriors. Even I
heard about them growing up.
They'll teach you how to swing a sword.
I know how to swing a sword.
You're leaving now?
It's the middle of the night.
I learned to walk in darkness.
Say your good-byes, little man.
Keep this one safe.
He means the world to me.
We've been waiting a longtime.
Haven't we?
Well, I don't know, you tell me.
How long does it take to sack a city?
It was just as you said.
They did not believe until it was too late.
Their slave soldiers
threw down their spears and surrendered.
And Daario Naharis?
The city is yours, my queen.
They're good, aren't they?
They ought to be because they cost enough.
Look at the crowd there.
He complained about this marriage
the entire ride from Riverrun,
and now look at him.
The Gods love to reward a fool.
- Uncle.
- What?
He's my nephew. I love him.
And he's a damned fool.
Don't you drink, Lord Bolton?
Never do, my lady. Dulls the senses.
That's the point.
Didn't you marry one of these Frey girls?
Aye. Lord Walder
let me choose any of his granddaughters
and promised me
the girl's weight in silver as a dowry.
So I have a fat young bride.
I hope she makes you very happy.
Well, she's made me very rich.
Pardon, my lord,
my lady. I need to find a tree to piss on.
My mother's alone
with Roose Bolton. I should rescue her.
Your mother is less in need of rescue
than any woman I've ever met.
Be kind. She's finally
starting to like you.
And I like her.
But if she had her way,
I would be back in Volantis
playing my harp
and you would be sitting over there,
eating blackberries out
of Roslin Frey's hand.
Perhaps I've made a terrible mistake.
Striking your king is an act of treason.
No, don't.
Don't insult them.
Your Grace.
The septon has prayed his prayers,
some words were said,
and Lord Edmure
has wrapped my daughter in a cloak.
But they are not yet man and wife.
A sword needs a sheath.
And a wedding needs a bedding.
What does my sire say?
To bed! To bed! To bed!
If you think the time is right,
Lord Welder, by all means,
let us bed them.
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Go on.
Ho-ho!
Careful now, ladies.
Once you set that monster free,
there's no caging him again.
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Poor girl.
Every bride suffers the same.
I'm sure you endured yours with grace.
Oh, Ned forbade it.
He said it wouldn't be right if he broke
a man's jaw on our wedding night.
That is a very strange custom.
I suppose it does seem strange
from a foreigner's perspective.
It seems normal to you?
It's a tradition.
Without the bedding ceremony,
there's no real proof
the lord and lady
consummated their marriage.
No, but there
are other ways of providing proof.
Boy or girl?
I don't know.
But if it's a boy,
I know what we should name him.
Oh, do you?
It seems to me the father
should have some say in his son's naming.
Eddard.
Don't you want to
leach little Ned Stark how to ride horses?
I do.
Go on, line 'em up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Got salt pork for the feast.
The feast is over.
Doesn't sound like it's over.
If I tell you it's over, it's over.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell out of here.
Got pig's feet, too.
Are you soft in the head?
Turn this can around.
Your Grace.
I feel I've been remiss in my duties.
I've given you meat and wine and music,
but I haven't shown you
the hospitality you deserve.
My king has married
and I owe my new queen a wedding gift.
Robb!
Ohh!
- Ahh!
Ahh!
You ready to head home to Winterfell, eh?
Feast over yet, is it?
Aye, it's over.
Aim!
It's too late.
The King in the North arises.
Lord Walder!
Lord Walder, enough!
Let it end!
Please. He is my son.
My first son.
Let him go,
and I swear that we will forget this.
I swear it by the Old Gods and New.
We will take no vengeance.
You already swore me
one oath right here in my castle.
You swore by all the Gods
your son would marry my daughter!
Take me
for a hostage, but let Robb go.
Robb, gel up. Get up and walk out.
Please!
And why would I let him do that?
On my honor as a Tully,
on my honor as a Stark,
let him go, or I will
out your wife's throat.
I'll find another.
Mother.
The Lannisters send their regards.