Subtitles by explosiveskull
Morning, sunshine.
Although, we don't exactly
get any of that down here.
Where the hell am I?
Well, right now, I'd say
somewhere between...
Houston and Quintana River.
Who are you?
Well, I could ask you
the same thing.
It's been a long time since I saw
him this worked up over an inmate.
Inmate?
No, that doesn't make any...
It'll wear off.
Don't worry.
It's easy at first, I know.
It'll all come back.
How long have I been here?
About a day now.
What about you?
I stopped counting.
I never saw the point
if I'm not going anywhere.
Why? What did you do?
How much time you got?
What is this place?
It doesn't officially exist.
Which means neither do you.
Black site?
It's more like a burial ground.
Except there ain't no
ground down here.
You're 30,000 leagues under
the goddamn sea, my friend.
No, no, no, no...
So, whatever you've done it seems
like someone took great lengths
to make sure
you never see the light again.
No, no, no...
No, this can't happen.
I should not be here.
Yeah, but you are so, maybe
you ought to figure out why.
What's the last thing
you remember?
Eh, that's far enough.
Set the keys down.
And the gun.
- You're early.
- So are you.
Are you going to shoot me?
That depends, did you bring it?
Yeah.
Show me.
Only if you say please.
Standard issue.
If the occasion calls for it.
Whoa, how did you know?
Didn't I tell you?
It's one of my many talents.
Mm... Mm!
Oh, no, no.
- You first.
- You don't trust me?
- Pick up any tails?
- Do you really have to ask?
See?
It's safe.
Your turn.
Are you satisfied?
You tell me.
We still have to
talk some business.
Business can wait.
So, tell me Mr. Wheeler, are all
your partners this lucky?
Lucky? You never tried
the breakfast here.
So, what'd Drummond say?
He's on standby
until we make contact.
Our guy will turn up.
It's just a matter of time.
Unless he doesn't.
And then we lose the buyer.
Buyer won't matter
when we find the leak.
Hey, we're going to
get these guys, okay?
- But if anything goes wrong...
- I know, I know.
You don't have
to worry about me.
I am gonna go investigate
this breakfast
that you speak so highly of.
Bring you something back?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Can you come back in an hour?
Go back inside, go.
We'll have to make a run
for the pickup truck.
- I'll cover you.
- Scott, listen...
There's no time to talk, go.
Scott!
Get in, let's go!
Wait, wait, shit.
The drive.
What?
I gotta go back and get it.
Cover me!
Fuck!
Mel!
Fuck.
Go ahead.
- We're blown.
- Is the drive secure?
Negative.
But I've got the dongle.
They won't be able to access
anything without it.
One hundred and fifty miles east of
your location is a town called Milton.
There's a parking garage,
corner of 3rd and Roxy.
Meet me in three hours.
You keep your head down.
On the ground!
Down!
Easy.
There ya are.
He's clean, it's not here.
We tracked the pickup to
an alley three blocks from here.
Empty.
Phones no good either.
Must have swapped
the SIM after the call.
Prep him for evac.
Notify them that we're en route.
Where do you think
he stashed it?
That's what
we're gonna find out.
First Ballad and now Tom, looks
like your boy is cleaning up, Ed.
It's not his M.O.
I'd say these bodies
beg to differ.
I think you and I both know
there's more to it than that.
All I know is that right now
he's the only one
who knows the location
of those files.
And we're gonna do whatever
it takes to find them.
I don't doubt that,
Agent Ferris.
But perhaps you might want
to reconsider your strategy.
I know this man very well.
Let me talk with him.
You're here as a courtesy,
nothing more.
Your relationship with Wheeler
becomes relevant
only when I deem it as such.
So let's put the breaks
on this chit chat
and I'll let you know
when you're needed.
As you wish.
- Ferris.
- You Kingsley?
That's right. Your boys tell me
this reservation is top priority.
He's a former asset, so Langley
needs this contained.
Discretion is of
the upmost importance here.
Has he been prepped?
Sleep agent has been
administered.
We got about 12 hours.
And how long do you intend
to stay on my clock?
Until we get what we need.
You think those other men
are necessary?
Why? Is there a problem?
No. But if there was, my men
could sure as hell handle it.
Yeah, but they're watchdogs.
Lackeys at best.
So, forgive us if we don't
share your confidence.
This is Edward Rhodes
from Intelligence.
He's here just to oversee
the interrogation.
Look, it's quite simple.
You stay out of our way
and we'll stay out of yours.
Alright, let's do this.
Correct me if I'm wrong, this
was repurposed for the navy?
That's right.
After it was retired
from the fleet,
the government elected
not to scrap it.
We figured it be better
to retrofit it
and house all the Bin Laden's
around the world.
Former squid paid to steer.
They stick to their side,
we stick to ours,
everybody minds
their own business.
I've heard rumors about this thing.
I didn't think it actually existed.
It doesn't. As far as
the CIA is concerned...
we were never here.
I wasn't aware
of another pickup.
Last minute reservation
just came down
from Military Intelligence.
Just another John Doe,
nothing to worry about.
With all that nonsense
surrounding GTMO:
it's about time
the company men went mobile.
Like I always said, it ain't really
a black site if you can find it.
- You got enough men?
- Payloads a little light.
No need to overhaul.
But let me show you something.
Everything is controlled
electronically from this room.
Even the cells.
- Is that his room?
- Yes, it is.
I want to see it.
Look, they all start off tough,
say they could take it,
but sooner or later,
they all crack.
Ain't that right, Marco?
He withstood
it all once upon a time.
Water torture, sleep deprivation,
even erectile feeding.
Halls reinforced with steel.
Toilets,
they don't lead anywhere.
Look, I appreciate you trying to get a lay
of the land, but this ain't my first rodeo.
The man staying in this cell is a highly
decorated officer and a trained killer.
He's been taught to adapt,
improvise.
He so much as gets a hold
of a strand of floss,
you'd best believe
he'd find his way out of here.
Believe me, Agent Ferris,
there's no way he's getting out of here.
Nobody ever has,
and nobody ever will.
I'm just concerned
that he doesn't take
a whole bunch of us
with him when he goes.
This stuff takes time.
Yeah, babe, I know,
but this might be
the last chance that I get
to call for a while so...
Oh, shit, look I gotta go.
I'll call you
as soon as I can, okay?
Alright, love you, too, bye.
- Hey.
- How's your dad?
He's alright.
What's going on?
- Right now, suits are here.
- What? Already?
- Yeah.
- Shit.
Oh, God, who they bringing?
- They didn't say.
- Fuck.
Whoever it is, it's someone
important though.
Never seen Langley bring
so many men before.
Huh.
Ferris is running point.
Shit.
Fuck, why didn't you tell me?
Cass, relax.
Look, he probably hasn't had
a chance to look at it yet.
- You know, just busy...
- Yeah, right, it's been weeks.
Of course he has.
Okay, how do I look?
- Desperate.
- Ha, very funny.
- Okay. Come on.
- Let's go, come on.
Let me know when we hit
international waters.
In the meantime, I'd like to put one
of my guys in there til he wakes up.
Just an extra set of eyes. Don't
worry, she's still your ship.
- Where does this go?
- Bow access door, crew side.
Only two keys can unlock it.
It doesn't look they visit much.
Security measures.
Speaking of security measures...
Here come your two.
You're company?
That's right,
I'm Ryan, this is Taylor.
Ferris. How we looking below?
Interrogation room is already
prepped and set.
Good.
Mind if we go take a look?
Actually, sir,
we haven't been briefed yet.
And you won't be. All you need to
know is he's a high value target.
Of course, but,
typically protocol...
SOP went out the window the second this
man compromised national security.
All I need from you two
is your cooperation
and assistance
if and when it's needed.
Sound good?
- Yes, sir.
- Good, let's go.
I just wanted to say I'm looking
forward to working together, sir.
I've actually put in a request
with your unit for field ops.
Looking to make the jump.
Taylor.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Oh, that's right, yeah.
Well, I'm sure someone
will get back to you.
Hm.
This is the captain, I've got
the con, prepare to dive.
Wakey, wakey.
Subject's awake.
You got a name?
Marco.
Okay.
Okay, I'm Scott.
- How can I get out of here?
- You don't.
Well, unless you're
a fan of body bags.
Oh.
I see you're about to meet
Weddle and Dax.
Stand back and turn around.
Step back, hands on the wall.
I want to speak to
someone in charge.
Hands on the wall, now!
Look, who is someone in...
Hey, Dax.
Come on, Dax.
Take it easy,
it's his first day.
You wanna piece of this,
too, Marco?
Yeah, well, it's been a while
since I felt a woman's touch.
Show me your pecs, baby.
We're on the move.
Agent Ferris, please, let me
explain something to you.
Scott Wheeler was hand-picked
into my division for a reason.
Guys like him, they have an
infinite threshold for pain.
And they're not just
trained for it.
They're born with it.
That man was built to numb.
Now a little torture
isn't gonna go anywhere.
You know, I've been trying
to figure your angle here, Ed.
You pulled a lot of strings
to get on board
and somehow I just don't think
it's to tell me how to run my op.
I just don't wanna see a good
man get rolled up. That's all.
Then he shouldn't
have changed sides.
Allegedly changed sides.
They're here.
Kill the feed.
- Rankin, kill it.
- Copy that.
You wanna learn a thing or two?
Go inside there
and pay close attention.
Yes, sir.
My name is Patrick Ferris,
I'm a chief officer with SAD.
I'd like to start by making you aware
that you're an enemy combatant.
And therefore have not and will
not be granted any rights.
You know how this works
so I'll keep it simple.
I want the location of the drive along
with the names of those complicit
with your efforts to sell it.
Now, if you give me
everything you know,
then maybe we can talk a deal.
You got any ID on you?
- Excuse me?
- Do you have any ID?
There you go.
I don't have it.
Oh, come on.
We know your guys took it
from Agent Ballard.
- Who's your buyer?
- We never met him.
Drummond was hoping
that we can draw out the leak.
How much did they offer you?
You're not listening. Ballard
and I were assigned deep cover.
I was on my way to meet Drummond,
but someone got him first.
And maybe that someone was you.
"Agent Wheeler has begun to show
ambivalence towards his objective.
He has failed to check-in
on three occasions now.
I have suspicions that he is
already in contact with his buyer.
and have asked Agent Ballard
to investigate further."
Is that why you staged
an ambush and killed her?
She was on to you, wasn't she?
- Someone is setting me up.
- Right.
And you just happen to be
in possession
of the only other device that can
access what's on that drive.
Convenient don't you think?
Who tipped you off?
Drummond was the only one
who knew.
How do you know it wasn't
Drummond himself?
I know you're a smart guy,
but you need to drop the act.
I want the location
and the names.
I can't tell you
what I don't know.
Do you know that there's a spot
just below the retina
where the sensory nerves can channel
receptors directly to the brain?
See, we've been doing it
wrong all these years.
Going in through a vein
in the arm.
Forget sodium pentothal.
You want me
to tell you the truth?
You put a needle in his eye.
This won't go anywhere.
Who's your buyer?
Who's your buyer, Scott?
This is the last time
I'm going to ask you.
- Then stop asking.
- Welcome to hell.
Just do it.
You're wasting my time.
Godamnit. Ed!
Get in here!
You're starting to look
a little pale there, darling.
That's not exactly
how you get promoted, Cass.
I mean you're lucky Ferris
didn't see that.
I know, I just need some air.
I know that guy.
They brought him to the farm
when I was a recruit.
He's a legend.
So what?
So nothing.
Now he's a traitor?
That's the game, Cass.
Look, you can't
let it twist you.
Alright, and if it does,
you can't let him see it.
I know, I know.
Look, it's my first time
in there, too.
Okay?
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- I just need to sit.
- Okay.
Make him talk or my boys
start laying down plastic.
Rhodes.
What are you doing here?
We don't have a lot of time.
These guys don't trust you,
they don't trust me,
they don't trust anybody.
This guy Ferris,
he was trained to chase facts.
He's worse than a Doberman.
So you're gonna have to earn
some good faith right now.
What's the first thing
I taught you?
Don't get caught.
Yeah, right, but if you do,
you have to create the leverage
to keep you alive
long enough to make a move.
Right?
So do you have this dongle?
Where?
It's safe.
Scott, I can't help you
unless you give me something.
If I hand it over,
I will have nothing.
Let me worry about that, okay?
You just have to buy
enough time where I can
get you the heck out of here.
- I'll take your guys to it.
- You know that'll never fly.
We're on a submarine.
Look, just give me a location.
Scott, this is your only move.
And they're gonna
put the hounds on you
until you die or until
you make something up.
Whichever comes first.
This is it.
Hey, Ed, clocks ticking.
Okay.
They're assholes.
Fine, only you.
Nobody else.
I can live with that.
Great, you did the right thing.
Now you hang in there.
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
Where's the drive?
Well, he doesn't know,
but he said he'll
take us to the location
of the second component.
Second component?
What are you doing?
- That's not the objective.
- Well, it is now.
Bup, bup, bup, bup, bup...
Mr. Kingsley, you and your men
have 30 seconds
to make
a very important decision.
I can make you all
extremely wealthy,
I'll need your assistance,
immediately.
You now have 20 seconds.
You don't look surprised, Scott.
Let me guess,
the location thing
was bullshit, huh?
When did you know?
When you went after the only
thing Ferris didn't need.
Good catch.
You know, I was never one
for all this needle nonsense,
I've always preferred
the direct approach, okay, so...
Kingsley, times up.
We have an agreement.
Very good. I'll wire the money
as soon as we get topside.
We'll negotiate an exact amount
in a few moments.
Where is it?
Where is it, Scott?
Let me check my bucket,
do you mind?
Tell me where it is.
The missions over.
Your team's dead.
I don't wanna kill you.
You fucker.
Just tell me where it is.
What's gonna happen to you
when your buyers find out
you fucked up, huh?
You really wanna die over this?
Do you?
This isn't working.
Cut an inch off,
we'll leave him half.
You ready for round two?
God, I hope so.
Drop it!
I'm not the enemy here.
Interlock your hands
behind your head.
- Come on.
- Are you sure you want to do this?
Now!
Walk to me.
Let's go!
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Taylor.
It's Rhodes,
do you have sights on Wheeler?
Where's Ferris?
Ferris is dead.
He went rogue, he and his men
came here to assassinate Wheeler.
We were sent to keep him alive.
Do not listen to...
Do not listen to him.
Are you with Wheeler?
Ryan, are you with Wheeler?
Yes.
Well played, good move.
You need to turn him
over to us right now.
Who the hell are you?
I am your superior
and I'm giving you a command
right now to hand Wheeler over.
You stay you die.
I'm also the man
that can give you
the assignment you want
or you could be
answering phones for the rest
of your life in Somalia!
Now turn him over, now!
Taylor, I'm coming out unarmed
and we will discuss this.
You have nothing to worry about.
If you get a shot,
kill them both.
- Keep Wheeler alive, you copy?
- Done.
I'm coming out.
I'm unarmed.
Shit. They're gone,
they're gone, get out here.
They're gone. Lock down this boat,
we have to find them right away.
This is Kingsley.
We've got an escaped subject
moving through
the stern of the ship.
He is with Agent Ryan
and Taylor.
If you see them,
employ non-lethal force only.
- This is not a drill.
- You heard 'em, switch the mags.
Son of a bitch.
Rankin!
Rankin, I need eyes!
I need eyes on the monitor.
- If you see them let me know.
- Yeah, copy that.
We need to talk business
and we need to talk right now.
Go to the right,
go to the right.
Go, go through.
We're clear.
You did good out there.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
You know, I need you to tell me what
the fuck is going on right now.
Cass, come on,
let's turn him in, alright.
- This has nothing to do with us.
- It does now.
Look, I know you don't trust me.
Either we do this together
or I do it alone.
Hey.
Fuck.
I'm trying to be nice here.
Rhodes needs me.
He doesn't need you.
Step back.
Now you're gonna tell me
where I can find a com system.
Control room by the bow.
How many guards?
Two, maybe three.
Any weapons here?
Are you sure?
Come on, step back.
Your turn.
Drop the guns, please.
Yo, let me make one thing clear,
okay?
You're still in our custody.
You do anything to fuck this up
or jeopardize this,
one wrong move I swear to God
I'll fucking kill you.
Okay.
My men are doing a sweep.
- And guess what, we'll find them.
- Good, good.
Hypothetically,
okay, if Wheeler needed
to contact someone topside,
what exactly
would he have to do?
He would have to
get to the control room.
And if he did,
it wouldn't even help him.
- Why?
- At this depth, he's gotta surface or float the buoy.
But he can't do that
without the com.
You think Wheeler knows that?
No, he wouldn't.
But Ryan and Taylor, they would.
Alright, look, get a few men
and come with me.
- So this was the only post they had, huh?
- What?
I'm guessing the agency promised you
field agent after what, six months?
Come on, it's been
longer than that. Right?
Yeah, if it's
all the same to you
I think we can do without
the small talk, okay?
I just want to make sure
you know how to use that thing.
Believe me, you'll be
the first to know. Come on.
Let's go.
Wait.
Slowly.
- Looks like nobody's home.
- Rankin never leaves.
No, Kingsley could of pulled
them, aid with the search.
No, control room's
always occupied.
- Okay, listen, I'm going in.
- No, I'll go.
- Watch him.
- Cass.
I got it.
Just have my back.
Taylor's alone.
No sign of subject.
Men,
listen up, he'll be close by.
Just wait.
Tell them if they get the shot,
take her.
If you see her,
take the goddamn shot.
- Got another one.
- Is it Wheeler?
Can't tell from this position.
Tell her to come back.
Cass. Come back.
Come on.
It's Ryan.
Take them both.
Just take them both.
Down!
Squeeze it, hold it. Hold it.
Don't talk, don't talk.
Cass... Get out of there, now!
I'm sorry.
- Come on, let's go. Let's go.
- We gotta get Ellis.
It's too late!
We gotta get him!
Clear!
Clear.
Jesus.
Don't worry, there's not
many places they could go.
Oh, really?
What about that access door?
Without this, unlikely.
It was also unlikely they were
gonna shoot up there sub.
Sir...
We have a live one.
Oh, Jesus.
Sorry, kid, it's just business.
Fuck.
Here.
You let him fucking die!
- Hey, he was dead already.
- Bullshit!
He could've lived
and you know it!
I made a judgment call,
you had a chance, he didn't.
- He was dying.
- No, you just wanted to fucking even the odds!
Listen, I know he's your friend,
I'm sorry.
That's the job.
Now...
Is there any way to radio out?
Yeah, we have to make it to
the com, but it's sealed off.
Kingsley's the only one
with the key.
Unless we get the ship
to surface,
the only way we're getting any signal
is by releasing the com's buoy.
So lead me to the bow.
Did you not hear me? Without
Kingsley, it's impossible.
There has to be an actual crew
on the other side, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, then, if we cannot get to them,
we make them come to us.
And how exactly do you
plan on doing that?
- This is a really bad idea.
- Do you have a better one?
Auxiliary and lower
engine rooms are clear.
Whoa, whoa, wait, you're not
seriously considering this, are you?
These valves control all the
ventilation for those tanks.
We just need a trigger. Something
that will force their hand.
As long as we reach the valve before the
repair crew, we have a shot, that's it.
- Okay, great, and then what?
- Then, well, you be the hero.
- Well, I'm still taking you in.
- Whatever.
How much time to get
from here to that door?
Three, four minutes tops.
But it's less for them.
Come here,
I think I have an idea.
So, the safety tanks
are meant to be full,
but if we overclock
the negative tank,
I think we can create enough
pressure to just cause a leak.
In the old days,
it was just red wire, blue wire.
Come on, help me.
What the...
- It's time to go.
- Yeah, let's go.
Com, com, this
is engine control.
We have a problem here.
Engine room, repeat.
Let's go.
The negative tank
is spiking, captain.
A computer glitch?
It doesn't look like it, sir.
Sommer, this is the captain,
I need a...
Sir, the tank's water pressure
is mounting fast.
Can you close the vent valve?
Negative, someone's bypassed
the emergency line.
- What?
- We'll have to do it manually.
Kingsley, you there?
Kingsley? Kingsley?
What do you think
you're doing, captain?
You're breaking protocol.
Your men have
strict orders to stay away
from all the vessel equipment.
What the hell
is going on back there?
One of your men disengaged an
emergency line on the ballast tank.
Well, then fix it, damn it.
It's a goddamn water leak.
I'm sending someone over.
We have a problem!
Well, that can't be good.
Come on!
Control,
this is the engine room!
We have pump failure
on negative tank!
Get a damage team
down there, now.
Kingsley, your compartment is
flooding and it's filling up fast.
I'm sending men over. Whatever
they tell you to do, you do it.
- Fuck.
- Copy.
Crew's on its way. Redirect all
units to the bow access door.
Go, go, go, go, go.
You're lucky,
it could've been a live round.
Hey, come on, let's go!
Move, move!
- Get that door closed!
- Sir.
Engine control, this is chief of the
boat, requesting damage report.
Where's the tank?
We got at least a foot of water!
- Can you contain it?
- Sir, I think so!
Don't think, officer,
just do it.
Check those valves!
Start the drain pump!
Once this is under control,
take us to periscope depth.
Take an extra guy, get down to the tank
bay, and keep your eye on those squids.
Where's my guy?
You alright?
Kingsley, you have to start
listening to me, alright?
I know, Wheeler. I know the way he
thinks, I know the way he reacts.
If he figures out a way
off this thing, it's over.
He ain't getting
off of this ship.
We've stopped him twice now.
Where's he gonna go?
I don't know, it's your boat.
Looks like you're starting to get
a little flush there, Rhodes.
- You don't know my employer.
- Let me guess.
The Russians, the Chinese,
maybe the Koreans.
- Does it make a difference?
- No, it doesn't.
As long as the money clears.
Just find him.
Come on.
Ah, fuck.
Perfect.
You've been shot before.
Why, you surprised?
Look, I'm hoping that
you have a new plan.
I was kind of hoping you did.
Yeah, well, it's gonna be a little
difficult considering Rhodes seem to know
every single one
of your moves before you do.
Who is he?
Just someone I misjudged.
Yeah, no, it's more than that.
Look, I'm taking
a leap of faith with you.
You want me to trust you,
you have to trust me.
What's going on?
He recruited me.
I spent years reporting to him
until he was transferred
to Intelligence.
Last time I saw him he was
talking about retirement.
What's on those files?
It's an algorithm detailing how
we activate our sleeper agents.
If it falls into the hands
of the wrong people, it's over.
Com, we reached full pump
on negative tank!
Flooding is slowed, we got it!
Copy, Sommer, how we looking?
Water pressure's normal.
And tank defaults restored.
Radio those boys
and bring them back.
And set your course
for periscope depth.
Aye, captain, setting course
What do you want me
to do about the crew?
Send them packing.
Alright, copy that.
Looks like they stopped it.
What now?
They're still out there.
We need to level
the playing field.
How, there's only two of us?
It's time to change that.
I don't like what he saw
when that door doesn't open.
Okay?
I see you brought the rookie.
How the hell did you know that?
No one else wearing that cheap
perfume down here, sweetheart.
She's a friend.
Could use another.
Haven't you heard,
friends will get you killed?
I'm looking to get out of here. Would
be very nice to have an extra hand.
What does she think about that?
Well, that depends on what
you're really doing down here.
Never seen you on the manifest, you're
names not on any of the official logs.
Well, I guess the term
is ghost detainees.
That's right,
well, my question is why.
Let's just say I got a terminal
case of I know too much.
Your people can't kill me and they
can't exactly let me go either.
He's KSK.
German Special Forces.
Okay, so, say we do
make it to the com
and we get the sub back,
then what are you gonna do?
Say, "You're welcome."
How much longer do you wanna
wait this thing out?
Let's give 'em another sweep.
We still have a bit of time.
You know, I really think that we
should consider our second option.
No, no, it's too soon.
And at what point will it
be too fucking late, hmm?
Shit, come on.
Now would be good.
Darrows.
Darrows, do you hear me?
Kingsley, we're climbing.
No shit, we're climbing.
Darrows...
Captain Darrows,
what are you doing?
Kingsley, this charter
has encountered
it's fair share
of bent shit cans.
Now, I don't know what the hell
is going on back there,
but my command
supersedes your authority.
I'm also surfacing the vessel
at the nearest port
and waiting for further orders
from Langley.
You will do no such thing.
Stay your course, captain.
That'll be all, Kingsley.
Officer of the deck, open the
locker and let's arm ourselves.
I'm not taking any chances.
I need to get up there.
What exactly is that?
Taylor just accessed
the cell door.
Which one?
Son of a bitch,
he's grabbing Marco.
Who the fuck is Marco?
I believe we should
get you one of these.
I knew I liked you.
Take Dax, go check it out.
I'm heading to the front.
Hold on, Kingsley, hold on.
I think you should go with them and
you should let me handle Darrows.
I think we should throw
everything we have at Wheeler.
And, besides, Darrows may be
captain but I'm agency.
And I think I can persuade him.
To him you're just
a hired hand, right?
Yeah, fine.
Get the package ready.
You know what to do.
I think we really
have to move fast on this.
You can't let him off this boat.
You understand that, right?
I'm on it.
Weddle, you're with me.
Dax, take the two men
down to the crew cell block.
- Check it out.
- Got it.
Set rep every five minutes.
Flash bangs coming.
We're done fucking around, boys.
Come on, let's go!
Alright, they should be
closing in any minute.
But I think if we take positions
on the other end,
we can corner them
and get a drop from behind.
Actually, you know,
I got a better idea.
But she's not gonna like it.
Six-hundred and twenty-five
feet, captain.
- What's the closest port?
- Havana.
About 45 clicks southeast.
But we're gonna need clearance.
Who the hell are you?
Edward Rhodes, I'm with agency.
You're not authorized
to be in here, agent.
No, sir, I'm sorry.
I take full-responsibility.
I apologize but we have
an urgent matter below
and you and I need to talk,
captain.
- Well, there's a radio for that.
- I understand.
I couldn't risk it.
I believe Kingsley
has been compromised.
Now, you know broke protocol,
you know that.
But the situation
has since worsened
and, I could really
use your help, sir.
What in God's name
is going on back there?
Now you know I'm not supposed
to answer that question, sir.
Well, you better try.
Okay, one of the detainees on
board used to be one of ours.
He's extremely cunning,
incredibly lethal,
and he has information that is
vital to our national security.
Well, he managed to escape during
interrogation and he is wandering below.
I'm not sure,
but I think he got to Kingsley
and made some kind of deal
with him and his men.
Now, they can't truly escape
until you surface.
So I'm just asking for
a little time,
hopefully my men can
neutralize this situation.
I mean, please captain, can you just
maintain this depth for a short while?
Alright, Agent Rhodes.
But I'm gonna verify
a few things.
Thank you, sir.
Float the come buoy.
Aye, captain.
What the...
How 'bout that?
Psst.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I mean good call on the blood.
Dax, do you read?
Dax, do you copy!
Dax!
Taking fire, Taylor's down!
Taylor's down, incoming!
- We gotta get over there.
- Wait.
Do we have eyes on Wheeler?
Taking fire, advancing!
I got a visual,
he's down, he's hurt!
Say, hi, asshole.
Fuck you.
What about the prisoner?
No longer an issue.
Get 'em up to the mess hall.
Good work, men.
Should we
call it in to Rhodes?
No. I don't trust
that son of a bitch.
I need to talk to Wheeler first.
Copy that.
- Well, your story checks out.
- Yes, sir.
But we're still being ordered
to dock in Havana.
Extraction team
is already en route.
You just bought yourself
some time.
Thank you, captain, thank you.
You look nervous.
- You're not?
- I never saw the point.
And usually I shoot the other
guy before he shoots me.
Of course.
Okay, let's do this.
Wheeler...
I'm glad you could
finally join us.
I thought perhaps you and I could
talk before getting Agent Rhodes.
- He's not here?
- No, he is not.
Then this should be
over quickly.
I was gonna
cut you in on a deal,
I swear I was gonna
cut you in on a deal.
Where's Rhodes?
Fuck you.
He's somewhere upfront
playing bureaucrat.
How many of your guys
are with him?
One guy. That's it.
What do you want to do with him?
Don't, don't...
please don't kill me.
I'm not gonna kill you,
Kingsley.
I can imagine he has a few words
he'd like to say to you.
He's all yours.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I guess this is the part where I'm
supposed to tell you that I owe you one.
Pretty sure, yeah.
- Good luck.
- Try not to have too much fun.
Don't worry...
I know exactly
what to do with him.
- ETA 11 minutes, sir.
- Copy.
Echo one, we're 11 minutes out.
Requesting docking coordinates.
Copy that.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Chief of the boat,
make your depth 75 feet.
Aye, captain.
It's not looking good.
Uh-uh, keep them up.
- What the hell is this?
- Jesus Christ.
Captain,
my name is Cassie Taylor.
I'm an agent on board.
Whatever this guy's saying
is a complete lie.
- Unbelievable.
- He's operating without clearance.
He's killed half of our men,
including my partner.
You cannot trust him.
- Is that him?
- That's correct, captain.
We can prove everything.
All I need is a line out.
Just two minutes,
you can monitor the whole thing.
You gotta be joking.
Do all you company men
rehearse the same way?
He already got that deal.
And guess what?
It panned out.
Where's your guy?
Come on, Wheeler,
stop the charade.
You know you murdered
everyone on the boat.
Wheeler, look,
they set the course to dock.
Captain, you can take my gun.
We can wait until
the team arrive.
Captain,
this man is extremely lethal.
Things could get out of hand
really quickly.
I suggest you command your men to
make a move right now, captain.
Go on, take it.
Captain, think about it.
If anything
he was saying was true,
we wouldn't be willing
to hold out with you.
Captain, don't listen to them.
Alright, they're playing you.
This is exactly
what we train them to do.
Have your men move, now!
I think I've heard enough.
I don't give a good goddamn which
one of you is spinning the yarn.
So I think I'll let
Langley decide.
In the meantime, Agent Rhodes, I
think I'm gonna have to take that.
Sure, just take it.
Cut the chase, back off,
back off! Now, back off!
Everybody don't move! I'll put a
bullet in his head, I swear to God.
Okay, everybody stay calm.
We're all gonna stay alive.
Captain, this is
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna command your men
to alter the coordinates
to surface
before the port
as close to land as possible.
- Like hell I will.
- Okay, I understand.
Godamnit!
Issue the order right now
or I will shoot you
and I will shoot your men!
Issue the order!
Do it!
Take it up!
Command your men to drop their sidearms
to the floor and kick them over.
Tell them, now.
Sinclair, lower your side arm.
That's right, nice and easy.
Drop your sidearms.
Drop 'em now!
On the ground!
Drop 'em on the ground!
Back the fuck up, Scott!
I'll blow your fucking head off!
Kick your guns over here,
both of them.
Kick the fucking gun over here!
Very good.
Cass, drop your weapon.
- Go fuck yourself.
- Really?
Okay, well,
maybe he'll help you out.
- Fuck.
- Put the gun...
Put it down
on the fucking table.
Too bad, Wheeler. She would've
made an incredible partner.
She's loyal right to the end.
I know how to pick them.
Not exactly.
Agent Ballard!
Hi, Scott.
I saw you die.
You saw what
I wanted you to see.
Rhodes knew we were on it
from the word go.
That's why he cut me in.
Don't beat yourself up
about it, Scott.
We both did our job.
I just did mine
a little bit better.
Go. Put it down.
Hand it over.
- You get it?
- Not exactly.
But there's more than enough
to split three ways.
We need to cut our losses
and move now.
- No, I didn't agree to that.
- We don't have a choice.
The deal was they were gonna wire the
money once we gave them the second piece.
Now we don't have it. So it's
still a win, don't be greedy.
Greed is the reason we're here.
Let's take him with us.
I'll get him to talk.
It's too risky, just let it go.
Jesus Christ. You, you.
Answer that phone,
put it on speaker.
This is Captain Darrows.
Copy that.
Darrows, echo, zero, five.
We're about two mikes out,
do you copy?
Affirmative.
Coordinates are locked in.
I can see them now.
Good, as soon as you land
disengage your forward hatch
so my man can board.
We want this to be
easy sledding.
Understood, over.
Put it down.
Okay.
Tell him to unlock
the forward hatch.
Hey, amuse me,
was any of it real?
The sex wasn't bad.
I guess she'll never find out.
Please, you've only
been dead for two days.
Look,
it's nothing personal, Scott,
but it would take two lifetimes
to make this kinda cash
chasing guys
we both know
get replaced on a dime.
If you can't beat them,
join them.
Hm.
You're crazy.
Jesus.
We have to go, Mel.
You're gonna get caught. You
think offsetting the coordinates
by a couple
miles is gonna change anything?
Someone's bound to see you trying to
make it to shore. You'll be fugitives.
Really? Thanks.
Are you finished?
Good. You can kill her.
Wait! Wait.
I will tell you
where it is okay?
If you want the dongle,
let her go, it's yours.
Where is it?
In a safe deposit box, okay?
- He's lying, let's go.
- Yeah, well, what if he isn't?
Don't be a fool.
You made
a small fortune already.
No, we're talking about
millions here.
Hey, hey, hey, Ballard.
Watch yourself.
Give me the location, Scott.
- Give me your word she lives.
- God damn it, let's go!
You have my word.
Fuck this, you're dead!
Wheeler!
You pain in my ass, you!
Shoot her!
Goddamn it, Ballard, shoot her!
Shoot her, Ballard, shoot her!
Goddamn it!
Shoot her! Ballard!
You bitch! Bitch!
- Wheeler!
- Yeah, you gotta get to Ballard.
- Jesus Christ, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- We got to go, come on.
- Are you sure?
This way!
On the ground!
On the ground, now!
I'm deputy, don't shoot!
We have an escaped target!
She just ran out of here,
you need to find her!
- Hands behind your back!
- He's been shot, he needs help!
- They're ready for you.
- Okay, great, thank you.
Agent Taylor, sir.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Agent Taylor.
- Hi.
- Please, have a seat.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Anything you'd like to say
before we start?
- No, sir.
- Good.
We've looked over your report
and it seems to fall in line
with Agent Wheeler's statement.
Now, I'd be remiss
if I didn't say
his vindication was in part
due to your testimony.
Now, having said that...
this is one of the biggest fuck
ups to ever come across my desk.
The panel can't open an inquiry
because the Black Site doesn't exist.
And we can't label
the source of the leak
because that would mean
admitting to a failure
that we weren't prepared for.
I've got six dead agents,
three civilians,
and an oversight committee
breathing down my neck.
I knew Tom Drummond.
He was a good agent
and one smart son of a bitch.
But the second he got autonomy
to run that division
was the second that we had
to start answering for it.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
As for Agent Ballard...
We've been trying to track her movements
since she disappeared in Cuba.
Interpol tracked her to down
to some bodega in Caracas,
while another dead end led us
to a safe house in Peru.
Wherever she is,
she's being careful.
Now, if there's anything good
to come out of this,
it's the fact that
we were able to recover
a terabyte of data
from an encrypted server
that Rhodes was accessing.
This should help us locate
and identify his buyer.
How would you like to be part
of the team that takes him down?
Yes, of course, sir.
- Thank you.
- Good.
I trust you won't have any issue
with your new partner?
No.
Then that's all for now.
Thank you.
Oh, Agent Taylor, one
more thing before you go.
When our team went in to sweep the
site they took log of the detainees.
All of them have been
accounted for except one.
A German.
When they located his cell
they found Kingsley naked.
Tied to a toilet
with three of his guards.
Son of a bitch insisted
he was being coerced.
You know anything about that?
Can't say that I do.
- Mm-hm.
- Thank you.
- Did he call yet?
- No, not yet.
Hm.
Go.
Fuck off.
Yeah?
Consider us even, friend.
Stay out of trouble.
You too.
So, Special Agent Taylor.
Has a nice ring to it.
It does, doesn't it?
Tell me something,
where did you really
hide the dongle?
- Exactly where I said.
- In a safe deposit box?
So you actually
stopped at a bank?
I got an account and everything.
I hate to break it to you
but you know that spy stuff?
It's not so exciting.
Hmm.
- Really?
- I swear.
Most of the time
you stay in a shitty motel.
Shitty bed.
Hopefully, no shitty breakfast.
I forgot you got shot.
- Huh?
- How's he doing?
Subtitles by explosiveskull