And we're back.
♪ I said oh my,
I don't know why ♪
♪ I was just busy watching everyone go by ♪
♪ She got my number,
though I can't stand her ♪
♪ I can't help diggin her a hope I guess I wonder ♪
♪ And oh it's clear,
you want me dear ♪
Welcome students, new and old,
to another fall semester at Greendale.
It's time for clean slates
and fresh starts.
Celebrate your fresh start tonight
at the Fresh-Start Dance
in the cafeteria.
The same cafeteria where Britta Perry,
publicly professed her love to Jeff Winger
who then walked out on her.
Unforgettable.
Plus, free punch
and fresh start cookies
tonight, at the Fresh-Start Dance.
Look at us, living together,
driving to school together.
I know, we're like Batman and Shaft.
Batman actually had a guy.
His name was Robin.
He rode around with him.
Troy, Batman's friend
didn't have to be Robin,
he could have been Shaft, Dolemite,
Leroy Brown.
Don't let society limit your people.
"Batman and Shaft", wow.
You're reading Troy's Twitter's page where
- he posts everything Pierce says?
- Yeah, "Old white man says"? It's hilarious.
Hey.
Hello, Annie.
I like your hair.
Thank you, Abed.
- You're welcome.
- Oh, Jeffrey. Hello.
Hey! how was your summer?
I live with you.
- How was your summer?
- Great. How are you doing?
- Oh, okay.
- Hey.
- It's good to be back here.
- I know.
Okay.
So... are you guys ready
for whatever Anthropology is?
We should wait for Britta.
Do we know she's coming back?
She never returned any of my calls or e-mails.
Me neither.
It's not gonna be the same
without her.
Hey, did you guys see Toy Story 3?
- Yes.
- Oh, I loved Toy Story 3.
- It was amazing, I love...
- Hey!
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Hey, Toy Story...  Britta.
- How's it going?
Okay, yeah, yeah. I made an ass
of myself and Jeff at that dance.
I was caught up in a competition
with his turd of an ex-girlfriend,
and I wish I could erase
the entire night.
- And I owe you an apology.
- I accept.
Oh, sweetie, you don't owe us anything
and you don't have to hide from us.
You? I'm hiding from them.
It's like high school all over again.
Psycho Britta,
the walking freak show
for every Barbie
with a Cosmo subscription.
Look, I don't mean to be a tool, but you
embarrassed me that night too, so call it karma.
Wow, boy, I hope I'm not around
when you do mean to be a tool.
Let's just put this behind us
and just walk to class, okay?
- Yeah.
- You're Britta Perry?
- Yeah, what's it to you?
You're the coolest.
Right. Um...
At what exactly?
Being fearless, honest,
speaking from your heart.
- "Jeff Winger, I love you".
- Right.
- My heart may have overstated...
- Do you sign stuff?
- Now and again.
- Awesome.
I don't like where that's going.
I know, right?
Look...
uhm, remember the little talk we had?
The one about discretion?
Yes. Stop that.
Look, uhm, we agreed you and I kissing
was a mistake.
And, if anyone were to find out about it,
I would be tarred, feathered,
and put on one of those websites
people check when buying a house.
It's forgotten, Jeff.
Jeez, I'm not some love-struck teenybopper.
But you should know, we didn't just kiss,
we technically frenched.
I checked the make-out meter
in this month's issue of...
National Review.
I don't like where that's going.
Community 2x01 - Anthropology 101
Sync and corrected by vNaru
www. addic7ed. com
Señor Chang. Oh, wait,
I guess it's not señor anymore.
What should we call you?
Student Chang?
Two-credits-into-
a-music-major Chang?
Ok, how about not calling me anything?
Why are you guys in this class?
We chose it together.
The real question is,
why are you in it?
- Oh, you missed us?
- Oh!
Don't flatter yourself. Ok, have you
checked out the course description?
Ancient weaponry? Genital mutilation?
This subject's talking my Chang-uage.
Ugh.
I don't get it.
Well, Star-Burns has grown reliant
on his star-shaped sideburns,
but still craves identity beyond them,
so he added a hat.
No, what's up with Britta-mania?
Oh, that's even simpler.
In the eyes of the public, Britta put herself out there
and you walked away,
making her the underdog,
the GLT, the Aniston.
- That's ridiculous.
- Yeah.
Hey Jeff, do you have any hillbilly cousins?
I wish, why?
What about a wealthy uncle, or and old drinking buddy,
that may or may not have had a sex change?
Abed, why are you mining my life
for sitcom scenarios?
I guess I'm just excited about the new year,
looking for ways to improve things.
I'm hoping we can move away
from the soapy relationship-y stuff,
and into bigger fast-paced,
self-contained escapades.
What is it exactly that separates man
from animal?
Divorce?
Tools. Like this blowgun I used
to hunt monkeys
with the Korubo in the Amazon.
My name is Professor June Bauer,
and this semester I will guide you
to the very threshold of your humanity,
where you will lock eyes
with the shrieking, blood-drenched,
sister-raping beasts
from which we sprang.
You will also have to
make a diorama.
For your first assignment,
I would like you to form tribes
of no more than eight,
and if you can, mix up the races.
Or you'll be surprised
at how quickly things get awkward.
You know, now that Troy's off the streets
and living with me,
he's learning so much about the world.
Yeah. Tell me again
why Jewish people wear yarmulkes.
Half a hat, saves money.
Thank you.
"Half a hat"? That is so offensive.
I love Old White Man Says .
Hey, find an eighth dork
for your tribe of dorks?
Chang, I'm starting to think
you took Anthropology,
because you wanna be in our group,
but are too proud to ask.
What?
Keep dreaming, Winger.
Would somebody with
too much pride... do this?
Current balance: $23.20.
Consider yourself Chang'd.
Mac and cheese, please.
Sorry, looks like your food
just walked out on you.
Same way you did Britta.
Hey, can we talk?
Oh, now he wants to talk.
No, it's fine, I'll be right back.
Man, you got some real passionate fans.
Eh. It'll blow over.
Well, would you mind, uhm,
helping it blow over?
My stock is kind of plummeting
around here.
Oh, I don't mean to sound like a tool,
but maybe it's karma.
Britta I know you're excited
to finally be popular with women,
but don't get too high
on your own drama.
High on my own drama?
People's champion.
Sorry, man,
I gotta go where the heat is.
Jeff Winger, you're a jerk.
She's turned every woman
on campus against me.
Well, not every woman. Certainly not the one
that deserves to be with you.
Annie, all women deserve to be with me,
and vice versa.
Granted, but who doesn't eventually
settle down?
I don't, and I never will. And if I did...
If I did,
I could beat Britta
at her own game.
Oh, good.
Yeah, you better take a hike.
Do you know
where the cleanest bathroom is?
- Teacher's lounge.
- Thank you.
Don't be shy, come on up,
have a sip.
The yogi of India swear by
its restorative powers.
Okay, more of my urine for me.
Now, for your tribe's assignment.
This box contains
nine different tools,
all of them important
to humanity's survival.
One of them,
is the most important of all.
Your tribe's assignment for tomorrow
is to tell me which tool that is.
Questions?
I have a question.
But not for you.
It's for Britta.
Britta.
I love you.
Now I know this puts you
in an awkwardly powerful position,
but I have to know, right now,
in front of everyone.
Do you love me too?
More than anything in the world.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So it begins.
- Hmm.
The greatest relationship
ever known.
This is making me sick.
- I'm gonna love you forever.
- Good, I'm gonna love you forever.
- I don't believe you.
- Why, don't you want me to?
No, I do. Bring it.
Doesn't it make you wanna cry?
Something like that. Excuse me.
I downloaded a song
that makes me think of you.
Let's listen to it,
each using one ear bud.
Shirley, would you consider spinning off with me?
Just riffing, but we could open
a hair salon together.
I don't understand.
Is this you being meta?
I wanted to come out of the gate having adventures,
like paintball. This is boring.
Well, I think that's selfish, Abed.
If you were a friend to Jeff and Britta,
you would see their relationship
as an adventure.
I hadn't thought about it that way.
Oh! Look at how they walk.
Clearly, the most important tool to a tribe's survival is here.
The cross, representing Christianity.
It's an ax.
It's an ax?
Maybe the telescope. Look through
it backwards. Shrink your enemies.
I'll show you the tool that's
most important to our survival,
but fair warning, it's my penis.
Old White Man.
Sorry I'm late.
I was in my car loving Britta.
- I guess I just love you too much.
- Not half as much as me.
- Aww.
- Jeff, do you think you'll marry Britta?
- I'd like to see someone stop me.
- I just peed a little.
- Then here, propose.
- Oh.
I got it, I got it, got it.
Jeff Winger, will you marry me?
Yeah, of course.
No problem.
Perfect, I'll be right back.
Thank the Lord, you're getting married.
I was so worried about your souls,
ever since you had pre-marital sex
on the table.
Oh!
Awesome.
- You told Shirley?
- Well, there's no need for secrecy now.
It was during the paintball game.
Was there anything
you didn't win that day?
Oh, my God!
You slept with her
and then kissed me?
What?
♪ Now they're in so deep. ♪
♪ You know she's such a fool for him. ♪
♪ She has a ring around her finger, ♪
♪ and Abed hired an Irish singer. ♪
♪ Britta's marrying, Britta's marrying
Britta's marrying Jeffrey Winger ♪
- What the hell is this?
- A wedding, episode.
- Abed, there's no wedding.
- Cold feet?
Talk it over with your best man,
George Clooney.
- What's up?
- He's a George Clooney impersonator,
- but still razzle-dazzle, right?
- Abed?
Hmm?
- Jeff made out with Annie.
- What?
- When? Where?
- Yeah, where?
That's inappropriate.
I'm assuming on the mouth.
- It was after the Transfer Dance.
- Oh!
So I tell you that I love you, and then you go
outside and stick your tongue into a teenager?
What is wrong with you, Jeffrey?
Well Shirley, since you have clearly failed
to grasp the central insipid metaphor
of those Twilight books you devour,
let me explain it to you.
Men are monsters
who crave young flesh. The end.
At least we have the decency
to be ashamed of it and keep it a secret,
instead of publicly blurting I love you
to everyone who sleeps with us.
Oh, please, I never loved you.
Ah-ha!
I win, I win, I win. In your face.
So this was all a game?
Everything they do
is some sick competition.
Oh... like you hate competition.
How long did it take you to kiss Jeff
after I told him I loved him?
Oh, that's right.
First Vaughn, now Jeff.
I better not smile at that wall outlet
or you'll fry your tongue off!
Way to hog all the girls, Jeff.
You know, when there's three sprinkle doughnuts,
you don't eat one and then lick another.
Anyone object to us
being referred to as doughnuts? No one?
I'm sorry we can't all be
as honorable as you Troy.
And post Pierce quotes
all day on Twitter.
Wow, is that your lame attempt
to try and pass the hot seat to me?
- Nice try.
- Wait, I'm Old White Man Says?
No wonder he says
everything I'm thinking.
You bastard.
I'm just sharing what you say.
Yeah, well, what if I shared
all the stuff you say?
He thinks all dogs are boys
and all cats are girls.
There's no way to disprove that.
Have you ever seen a cat penis?
Where are you going?
By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you canceled.
Oh, good. Yeah Abed, cancel us.
And while you're at it,
why don't you take your cutesy
"I can't tell life from TV" gimmick with you?
You know, it's very "season one".
I can tell life from TV, Jeff.
TV makes sense, it has structure,
logic, rules, and likable leading men.
In life we have this.
We have you.
I'm on the clock for another hour if
you want me to do some Batman lines.
- Not sitting with your little group?
- The group is done.
Yeah, well,
missionary accomplished, right?
What does that mean?
Come on, I know you and Britta did it.
Isn't the whole reason
you got together with those people?
Because you wanted to bang
the blond?
Now I hear
that you Frenched the brunette.
What more could you have gotten
out of that group?
Good morning, class.
Let's dive in and hear the results
of your assignment.
Who wants to go first?
I don't know, Mr. Winger,
the last time I called on you,
I kind of got what the Maku-Maku
call "dirt-roaded."
Using it.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
It was a trick question.
The tool most important
to humanity's survival
wasn't any of the nine in the box.
Go on.
The most important tool is respect.
Ha! Gay.
And the reason I know
respect is a tool,
is because it is clearly
not a natural thing
and we forget to use it all the time.
And then we start competing with
each other, and exploiting each other,
and humiliating each other,
and controlling each other.
And we lose each other.
And without each other,
we'll go extinct.
And that's a fact.
Heh. A gay fact.
That's my answer, professor.
Hmm.
Well, that's one answer.
Here's the one I had in mind.
Combining all nine tools,
you get this,
a deadlier weapon
than any one item in the box.
So, I'm gonna use this to attack you,
and you use respect
to defend yourself.
Uh... Oh... Uh...
- Oh, my God.
- Jeffrey.
I respect you.
That's why you fail.
- Oh, my God.
- Jeffrey.
He's passing out.
Stay with us, buddy.
- Hello.
- Oh, thank God.
Hello Jeffrey.
What happened?
Professor Bauer got suspended,
and we got an automatic A on our assignment.
Did someone throw urine in my face?
Oh, sometimes I surprise myself under pressure.
Jeff, about the assignment,
we decided you had the right answer.
I think we need more respect
and a little less passion.
Which will be easy for me,
because I think you're kinda gross now.
Awesome.
Pierce, I'm gonna delete
that Twitter account.
Your friendship is more important
than 600,000 strangers.
Wow, wow, wow. Are you saying 600,000
people read what I say on Twitter?
Come on, we gotta cash in on that.
How about Old White Man Says,
the TV Show?
- No.
- Who would watch that?
Speaking of bad development
strategy, I owe you all an apology.
I was trying so hard
to make our first week a great one,
that I didn't realize there was something great
in front of us the whole time.
An old woman drinking her own pee.
- You're Right.
- That's true.
Guys?
I got a confession to make.
I took Anthropology because
I wanna be a part of your study group.
Now I gotta do the honest thing
and just ask.
Is there any room in this pocket
for a little spare Chang?
Uh... look, we've been through a lot today.
- Give us a little time to think it over.
- Totally, totally, man.
Just think about it.
Take your time and let me know.
- Bye.
- See you, Chang.
Bye.
Aww. Poor guy.
We'll let him in eventually.
Says who?
Look, we have the strength
to survive anything.
What's the worst that can happen
with Chang?
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah, Good point.
I told you they hate you.
No, they said
they just needed more time.
Time? They destroyed your life.
How much time
before we take revenge?
But they're my friends.
I'm your only friend.
No.
No!
♪ Kingdom: Animalia.
Chordata ♪
♪ The class is... Mammalia ♪
♪ 'Cuz boobies we gotta ♪
♪ Order is Primate.
Hominidae ♪
♪ The genus is... Homo ♪
♪ But you know you're into me, ♪
♪ 'Cause I am in the species
known as Sapien. ♪
♪ Dogs used to eat me,
but now they bring the paper in. ♪
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to get me away from you. ♪
♪ Damn, damn. ♪
♪ There's nothing that a
hundred men or more could ever do. ♪
♪ Sapien. ♪
♪ I bless the rains down in Africa. ♪
♪ Oh, bless the rains ♪
♪ I bless the rains down in Africa ♪
♪ Africa ♪