City college has a
space simulator.
We know. Close the door.
As I was saying...
On Monday, city college
will be unveiling,
the City College Cosmic Pioneer...
their very own orbital
launch simulator.
Pretty soon,
they will have an astronaut
on their brochure,
and we will still be bragging
about our foosball table.
What do you think happens
to enrollment then?
I don't know about you, gentlemen,
but I love my campus,
and I don't want to watch it
become a city college parking lot.
Well, what can we do?
We can launch our
own space simulator.
Before they simulate
their launch on Monday,
we simulate a launch this weekend.
We make Greendale,
not city college,
the first community college
to pretend to put a man in space.
Do we even have a simulator?
We can get one.
In 1980, the county museum
had a state-of-the-art
space mission simulator
sponsored by Kentucky
Fried Chicken
called the "Kentucky Fried Chicken
leven herbs & space experience".
Gentlemen...
Greendale's future!
Oh!
Actually, that photo's
from the past.
Here's one more current.
It's seen better days.
I admit... it could
use a good wash.
And I've got just the crew
to wash it.
Can we stop walking in slo-mo now?
20 more yards.
You guys are walking in slo-mo?
Community 2x04 - Basic Rocket Science
Sync by vNaru - Corrected by Kerensky
www. Addic7ed. com
I think you know the reason
this group has been
chosen for this job...
to atone.
For the obscene
entry you submitted
in the Greendale
school-flag contest.
That's right... I know
that this isn't a symbol
for the crossroads of ideas.
I now know it's a butt.
Yeah, keep snickering.
Pack yourselves with peanuts
and really be satisfied.
But guess what?
This won.
This is now our
school flag forever.
Proud of yourselves?
How do you know it was our design?
We submitted it anonymously.
Whoops.
One of you actually came forward.
What?
Now, somewhere beneath this dirt
is Greendale's newest pride.
And my hope is that
while you scrub it,
you will find the school
pride in your hearts.
After we clean it,
can we go inside?
No. That is a job for
some upstanding students
who are training right now
in the simulator simulator.
Great job on this.
Hard to believe I'm not
really not really in space.
I expect this craft
to be squeaky clean
in time for the pretend launch
in front of the press at 3:00.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to make this
into a butt flag.
Man, I remember this
thing from High School.
During field trips,
we used to sneak inside and get...
to praying.
Oh, that's nice.
We should take a coffee break.
Let's all get coffee, okay?
Where are Troy and Abed?
I'm pretty sure they made
their way into that thing
five seconds after the Dean left.
What?
It's more beautiful
than I ever imagined.
- You've never been in it?
- My dad never let me.
He always had grudge against
fast-food restaurants.
They almost wiped out
his falafel stand.
But I memorized every
detail of this old girl
on the Internet.
Guys, we can't be in here.
Then get out.
Wow, it's pretty well preserved
for something that
survived the '80s...
And apparently a local transient
who liked to collect doll heads.
The '80s.
Our teen years, right, everybody?
I feel like I'm
underdressed for this.
I'm gonna get something
from the dorm.
Guys, seriously,
I have to ask that we
all step out of here.
Or what, you're gonna tattle on us
like you did with the flag?
I didn't tattle about the flag,
but you shouldn't have
made it in the first place.
If you love Greendale so much,
why don't you marry it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm a little claustrophobic,
that's all.
It's no big deal, as long
as I'm standing near a door.
In close situations,
I get a little nuts,
and I don't know,
you know, what's...
- no, no, no!
- Hey, hey!
No!
- Hello?
- Oh!
Greetings.
I am Systematic Android Network
Diode Energy Rocket System.
But you may call me "Sanders".
Sanders. Sanders,
this is Pierce Hawthorne.
Can I get this door open, please?
Hey, look for the handle.
There's got to be a
handle on the door.
You don't know that.
It was the '80s.
Everybody who made
this was on cocaine.
We can't be in here.
Just as Kentucky fried chicken's
secret process seals
in the flavor,
I'm sealing the cabin's air
so you don't explode
on your journey.
- What?
- What does that mean?
Please find a seat,
strap yourself in,
and wait for mission control.
Okay, we got to find a
handle on this door!
Guys, guys, can we just
take a mental step backwards
and realize we are
simply in a winnebago
and we'll be fine.
Oh, God!
Please find a seat,
strap yourself in,
and wait for mission control.
I'm not strapping
myself into a coffin.
We got to get out of here!
I hope you found a seat.
I want you to be safe.
Did you just threaten me?
Pierce, you're talking
to an atari cartridge.
Sit down!
This is part of the
simulation, right?
I don't think this
is a simulation.
I think we're being towed.
- Come on!
- Hello?
Hey, guys, forget it.
Whosever towing us can't hear us.
You know, this is
classic Greendale.
That place deserves an anus flag.
Can anyone get a phone signal?
- No.
Mine's working,
but it's the black guy
with the wrong number again.
Pierce, I keep telling
you that that is an iPod
and you are listening to
Wesley Snipe's audiobook.
Well, he sure hates
the government.
This is a long shot.
But maybe if I do this,
it will solve everything.
Damn it!
This is all my fault.
- Very much so.
- Oh!
Hey, when you go fishing,
sometimes you catch a boot.
Where... Re... You...
Tel... Where... You are!
Hello?
Where are you hoodlums?
Bring my spaceship back!
Uh, we are...
40 light years outside
of the buttermilk nebula,
although it is possible...
Yeah. It's a sticker.
Hey, terrible Dean.
This thing is being
towed with us in it.
Oh. Oh. Okay, wait.
So handicap spots
count on saturdays?
Assuming we don't wind
up in a compactor,
when we get back,
I'm going to step on you.
Okay, as much as I might
enjoy that, Jeffrey,
if you don't get back here
in time for the launch,
City College wins,
and Greendale becomes just
another school on my resume
that no one can call,
because it doesn't exist.
Now, tell me where you are!
In a moving canister
with no phone and no GPS,
because the only
window is sealed shut.
Hel... hello?
Jeffrey!
It isn't sealed shut.
Hmm?
The window isn't sealed shut.
It slides open when you
complete the simulation.
Well, can you talk
them through it?
Abed, if they can
open that window,
they can tell us where they are,
and we can find them.
I was supposed to
be on that thing.
I know how she works.
Hey. That's why they need
you to bring her home.
I'll get us some coffee.
- Troy.
- Abed?
You can get that window open
by doing the simulation.
Look at the panel on your right
- ... and tell me your recipe.
- Original.
- How many pieces?
- 6
- Flavor heading?
- Tasty.
We need to get it up to delicious.
That makes sense.
Excellent work, Captain.
Now keep your herbs
and spices balanced
while the crew helps
you with teamwork.
Guys, we can get the window open
if you man your terminals,
and we complete the simulation.
Yeah. I got a better idea.
- Oh!
- Jeffrey!
We're all dying.
We're all gonna die!
My readings indicate the
need for cooperation.
I hate to pull rank on you,
but I need you to man
your station now, Jeff.
I hate to pull reality on you,
but you got your rank, Captain,
by sitting in the chair
with the largest knobs!
My readings indicate Pierce...
- What?
- Pierce...
My readings indicate
you're going to die alone.
Why's he saying that?
Why's he...
why's he saying that to me?
Uh, he... he's getting worse.
Almost there.
Stop talking, old man.
You can't make me stop, Pierce,
because Troy is killing
your life force.
- I knew it!
- Oh!
I knew it!
Abed!
Kentucky one...
Do you read me?
Kentucky one, Kentucky one,
do you read me?
Kentucky one, copy.
Kentucky. Come in, Kentucky.
I've worked out a way for
them to reroute the power
from the auxiliary battery.
Reroute to what?
Everybody...
Here is the situation.
This is Greendale.
This is the maximum
distance from Greendale
we can drive to haul
them back up here in time
for the simulated launch.
And these are city impound lots...
Any of which might
be their destination.
What are these other circles?
What other circles?
Looks like you circled
public restrooms
and truck stops. Yeah.
There's another one. - Okay.
That is a different
side of the map,
and that is...
for a different project.
Why do they have star ratings?
- Let's get to work, people!
- Got it.
Talk to me, Buddy. Come on!
Uh, bro, we stopped moving.
Pierce has got space madness,
or he's just old or something.
They're locking him
up in the back.
- Argh!
- Run, Jeff!
You can't do this to me!
We just did!
Guys, please!
You're becoming animals!
Oh, shut up!
We wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for you.
That's not true!
We weren't supposed to be
in here when it happened!
When what happened?
When we got towed?
How did you know we
were gonna get towed?
I set it up.
I called City College
about transferring,
and the Dean told me
that he would get me in
if I helped sabotage
Greendale's launch.
I was supposed to make
sure nobody was around
so that they could steal it.
And then you guys were late,
and then...
Wait, wait. You're transferring?
Why?
You guys thought that
butthole flag was so funny.
I mean, I respect you all enough
to let you hate yourselves,
but I respect myself too much
to let you hate my school.
Eh. I'm not buying it.
Yeah.
Let's kill her.
Wait! City College was behind this?
We have to get back in
time for that launch.
- Why?
- We earned the right
to pick on Greendale
every day by going there.
Our school may be a toilet,
but it's our toilet.
- Nobody craps in it but us.
- Yeah.
- Now, that was inspiring.
- Seriously?
Captain.
Get to your stations.
Okay.
- Thrusters.
- Full.
- Turbo shield.
- On.
- Navigation.
- Three.
- Chicken.
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Suppertime.
Hold it...
Congratulations, crew.
You've worked together.
Now feast your eyes on the
wonders of the cosmos.
Greendale. Greendale.
Everybody be quiet.
Everybody quiet down.
Quiet down.
Say again.
Stand by for location.
What do you see, gang?
We are in...
Coldwater.
Here...
Right next to the truck
stop with three thumbs.
Those aren't thumbs.
Greendale. Do you copy, Greendale?
I'm sorry, Jeff.
I'm afraid...
You're out of town.
I guess somebody'll
come get us eventually.
I really miss Greendale.
How many schools would let
you make a butt flag...
Then actually fly it?
How many schools would
let you get a degree
in theoretical phys ed?
Annie...
We owe you an apology.
Nobody should have to choose
between their friends
and their school.
Thanks.
But you shouldn't have
tattled about the flag.
I tattled.
I told the Dean it was our design.
And I told him it was a butt too.
- What?
- Why, Jeffrey?
He kept not seeing it.
I mean, it was driving me crazy.
It says "e pluribus anus".
I told you we should
have put cheeks on it.
There's a time and
place for subtlety,
and that time was
before Scary movie.
Hey, guys?
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Well, you... you sound good.
Yeah, you know, in a weird way,
being in a smaller
place like this,
I was able to work
through some things.
I think I'm ready to come out.
I'll kill you!
I will kill you, Sanders!
- Congratulations...
- Come on, man, come on.
Let go!
No!
Get off my mommy! I'm her man!
Pierce, stop! Stop it! Calm down!
Who's feeling skinny?
Dean? The press is here.
- Oh...
- I tried to buy us some time
with these double-icious
sandwiches,
but they thought I was doing
product integration for KFC.
This hawaiian bread
is so good, though.
Time to face the music.
Craig.
Stephen.
I'm surprised to see you here.
You don't think I'd miss your
moment of triumph, do you?
Greendale beating City College
into simulated space?
Unless...
You're having trouble
locating your ship.
You.
You were behind this?
The next time you
provoke City College,
you will lose more
than a winnebago.
Greendale. Come in, greendale.
Go ahead, Kentucky.
You can call off the rescue.
We're coming to save you.
Come on, you family-sized
bucket of bolts.
Abed, construction on spring road.
I see it. Left on apple valley.
Annie, left on apple.
Hold tight!
- Hi.
- Get off of me.
They'll never make it back, Craig.
That thing might as well be
on a simulation of the moon.
Oh, you know wha...
Ah, yes!
Hey, look out!
- Whoo!
- What just happened?
Ladies and gentlemen,
returning from their
maiden simulation,
the fabulous Greendale
greenstronauts!
Well, Annie...
I suppose you're not City
College material after all.
Thank you.
- Annie!
- Good job.
That's good!
Just to say... could
you hold on one second?
Great job up there, Captain.
Really?
You think I could be a
real astronaut someday?
Well, if NASA ever needs someone
to keep an arrow inside
of a moving rectangle,
I know who I'd recommend.
Abed...
Want to ta a seat in
the Captain's chair?
I think you've earned it.
No, thanks.
I can't imagine anything
that could have been cooler
than what I've done today.
Okay, that was cooler.
In the future...
Mission control, headed for base.
Target acquired.
Mission control,
I've got a bogie on my 6.
Yeah, I'm on your 6.
Evasive maneuvers.
Still on your 6.
I took evasive maneuvers.
You can't be on my 6.
Then I'm on your 12.
That means I'm your 6.
Good.