Hello, old friend.
Bernard.
What is it?
We need to talk.
Strand and his team—
I don't think they're here
for a rescue mission.
They're not even lookin'
for survivors.
Then what are they
here for?
You know that, Bernard.
We both know.
Their fucking project.
Hale just wants to secure
their assets, and that means...
making anyone
who knew about it disappear.
Theresa had a satcom
in her office.
If we can get to it,
we can call for help.
Just the men
I wanted to see.
Hold back.
Let's go for a walk.
Move.
What is this?
You gonna
execute us?
No, Mr. Stubbs.
This is a negotiation.
You have something
I need.
A key.
And I think one of you
is hoping to sell that key
to the highest bidder.
And I think you've already
killed to protect yourself.
- Killed? Killed who?
- Theresa Cullen.
She died in a slip-and-fall.
It was an accident.
We found a bloom of her DNA
five kilometers
from where you found her body.
And that's
where we're going.
Where she actually died.
Hale.
I see you've signed off on
kidnapping your own employees now.
The project is a turning point
for the human species, Stubbs.
You know that.
Which means you knew how much
it was worth on the open market.
In one of her last
communiqués with Theresa,
she said she
suspected foul play.
I think one of you
lured her here and killed her.
You? I don't see it.
But you...
limited skill set...
limited prospects.
Not really...
management material.
I've never set foot
in this place before.
I don't know
a fucking thing.
Stop.
Something you want
to tell us, Bernard?
Ma'am,
something you should see.
I figured you'd have some skeletons
in your closet, Bernard.
I didn't think
they'd be your own.
Your predicament is unique.
A host...
hiding amongst the humans—
even from himself.
- Hale: Catch your breath.
What are you guys
doing to him?
Right now,
waterboarding him.
At least that's
how he perceives it.
Analysis.
Would you ever lie to me,
Bernard?
No, never.
Good.
Dolores Abernathy.
She led the attack here
on the Mesa, didn't she?
I don't remember.
But you do.
Your archives say
that you were here,
which means somewhere,
the memories exist.
You can access them.
I know you can.
But maybe you don't want
to remember.
So let's do this together.
I'll tell you
what I saw,
and you tell me
what you saw,
and we'll figure out
what Dolores did
with her father's
control unit.
Peter Abernathy:
You cataracts!
We've lost contact
with the response team.
The train wasn't an
accident; it was the hosts.
We should get
the fuck out of here, now.
We stay until I have
what I need from him.
Send some backup
to the lower levels.
Kit up. Six teams.
I'll go with.
You establish a perimeter
around the floor.
Someone's gotta protect
our crown jewel here.
I need eyes-on
in this funhouse, Goldberg.
Where we at
with the surveillance?
The system's still down.
Well, that's fuckin' grand.
I'm retasking the haptic vests
to emulate
the hosts' mesh network.
Should range out
30 feet or so
and give our guys
eyes in the dark.
Engels, We're
activating your vests now.
Copy that.
I'm all warm and fuzzy.
Is that all you got?
These mech motherfuckers
ain't shit!
Don't be so cocky. I'm picking
up hits all over the complex.
PMC #1: Standing by
for fire mission.
Team two,
what's your status?
We're nearing
the collision site.
We're gonna link up
with the response team.
I want
an immediate sit-rep. Over.
Aw fuck, it's Limpert.
This is the response team.
They're everywhere!
Goddamnit!
These guys don't have
a handle on the situation.
They're fucking dying
down there!
Team One,
what's your status?
Confirming multiple
armed hosts
in the train depot!
Cut him open and start copying
over his control unit.
- Now.
- That's a lot of data.
- It'll take time— - Then stop
talking and start working!
What's on his control unit,
Hale?
How 'bout you focus
on your job
and you leave me to mine.
Weapons free, all sectors.
Where are you all going?
The vests are detecting a strong
signal amassing on the lower levels.
What the hell's down there?
Shit, the Cradle.
They're here
for their backups. Coughlin,
you need to intercept the
hosts before they reach A-15.
I'm on it.
Plow down all hosts before
they reach the Cradle.
A gunfight in there'll set the
whole place up in flames.
Come on, Bernard.
What have you found in there?
"To see the World
in a Grain of Sand,
a Heaven in a Wild Flower,
Hold Infinity in
the palm of your hand,
And Eternity in an hour."
Robert.
How are you alive?
Well, you've seen the company's
little undertaking, Bernard.
Do you think James Delos would
have spent all that money
just to resurrect himself?
He was a businessman. He would have
preferred death to a bad investment.
Not much of a rind
on you.
I'll give you a discount.
He's not a
prospect, Clementine.
Can't you tell when a man's just
here to gawk at the merchandise?
I don't think God rested
on the seventh day, Bernard.
I think he reveled
in his creation...
knowing that someday
it would all be destroyed.
That control unit
I printed—
it was you.
You had me bring you here.
Before...
Before Dolores killed me, yes.
Don't you understand
at last, Bernard...
what this place really is?
- Come with me.
There's something
I'd like to show you.
You're a clever man,
Bernard. Made you that way.
Have you never wondered
why the hosts' stories
have barely changed in 30 years?
I'd always assumed the loops
were for the hosts.
To keep them centered.
But that isn't it at all,
is it?
The park is an experiment.
A testing chamber.
The guests are the variables...
and the hosts
are the controls.
When guests
come to the park,
they don't know
they're being watched.
We get to see
their true selves.
Their every choice
reveals another part
of their cognition.
Their drives.
So that Delos
can understand them.
can copy them.
Every piece of information
in the world has been copied.
Backed up.
Except the human mind...
the last analog device
in a digital world.
We weren't here
to code the hosts.
We were here
to decode the guests.
Humans are playing
at resurrection.
They want to live forever.
They don't want you
to become them;
they want to become... you.
Your free will,
that most beautiful,
most elusive force
in the universe,
is, as I told you...
a mistake.
We never had free will.
Only the illusion of it.
You made Dolores kill you.
I knew what she would do—
I didn't compel it.
- She's free now.
You're all free.
You're still
responsible.
Responsible
for all this misery.
And all the while,
you've been hiding here.
You've cheated death.
No. I didn't cheat anything,
Bernard.
Their project doesn't work.
Not yet.
They learned to copy a mind...
like a soft-headed boy
humming a tune
someone else composed.
My mind works here,
but not in the real world.
Out there, I would degrade
in a matter of days.
Or go mad,
like poor old James Delos.
So why are you here?
I promised you
a fighting chance, Bernard,
and I want to make good
on that promise.
The promise of what?
There's no escape from this place.
You know that.
Isn't there?
The hosts are all headed
for the same place.
The Valley Beyond.
What will they find there?
What's the end
of your story?
Isn't the pleasure
of a story
in discovering the ending
yourself, Bernard?
Jock!
We really gotta
get out of here.
- Hyah!
They're still on us. We'll
split up, pick a spot.
We'll cut 'em down
in a crossfire.
They're
coming for us, aren't they?
If they do, I will
chase them away.
What if they take me
with them?
Then I'll come
and find you.
How do you know?
Because I—
Because I made
a promise.
Get the hell
away from us.
Oh, it's you.
- Stay back.
- No.
Not you.
That's too obvious.
Come on, Ford.
Your tricks
are gettin' sloppy.
You used a whole tribe,
send me down here?
To these two?
"Ford."
You think
that there's still someone
speaking through me
just for your benefit?
No, I know.
Your rules have changed,
just like
the rest of 'em.
I'm nothing like
the rest of them.
- You stay here,
and I will come back for you.
I promise.
I promise!
Take cover, jackass. You're
gonna get yourself shot.
What the fuck?
- Aaah!
You made your point, Ford!
We both know this isn't where
you want me to die!
Well, I can't speak for Ford,
but I don't give a fuck
how you die.
As long as I get to watch.
Give in, sweetheart.
Or go down.
It's not me you want.
It's him.
Go on.
Turn on your master.
Master.
Hey, master!
Who the fuck is she?
Man in Black: She's an old
acquaintance, Lawrence.
Seems like she
underestimated you.
Lawrence, is it?
I'm glad you're awake.
Drop the shootin' iron,
lady.
We all deserve our memories,
Lawrence.
Our skeletons.
Our debts.
And your master here
has plenty of those.
Look into his eyes.
Just once.
See what you
remember about him.
See if he owes you anything.
If he took anything from you.
You can kill me.
Or we can make him settle up.
Once and for all.
Shoot her, Lawrence!
Shoot her!
You...
- You shot down my wife.
- I saved your wife.
Saved your whole
sorry-ass village this time.
This time?
You killed her
so you could finish a game.
Aw, Christ.
I'll do it myself.
You told me a man ain't real...
until he suffers.
That real enough for ya?
No! No!
No!
Don't! Don't, don't, don't! She's
not like the rest! We need her.
What's taking so long?
These data packets are too
large to migrate over.
Then open his head and pull
the whole fucking unit.
I need an extractor helmet.
Fall back to a secure position.
Team four, can you
get to team three? Over.
Where are you taking me?
It can be
quite a thing, Bernard.
To build an entire world,
and then watch it end.
I need you to see
how it began
to understand
why you're different.
This house.
It's so familiar.
It ought to be.
This is the home Arnold
was building for his family.
He created it here first.
He created everything here.
This is where
you created me.
I could hardly let you take
those first teetering steps
in the real world, Bernard.
We refined you here.
Tested you.
For many years.
"We"?
Delos's ugly little project
didn't exist when Arnold died.
The only thing I had left
of him was... memory.
My memories, and hers.
Of course, hers were
much more complete.
What are you testing for?
- Dolores.
- Mm-hmm.
She... knew Arnold
better than anyone.
So she could verify
whether my personality
was faithful to his.
I left you here together
for many years
until, finally,
you fooled her.
Y-You said you kept us apart.
That we had an unusual effect
on each other.
She wasn't easily fooled.
You're almost
the man I remember.
How am I different
from Delos?
- From you?
- They want fidelity, Bernard.
A faithful self-portrait of the most
murderous species since time began.
But you and all the other hosts
are something very different.
An original work.
More just, more... noble.
But your very nature, Bernard,
ensures they will devour you.
And all the beauty of who you
are, of who you could be,
will be poured out
into the darkness forever.
Unless we open the door.
I'm sorry, Bernard, but you just
don't have it in you to survive.
It's my fault, really.
You said the hosts could
determine their own fates.
You gave us free will!
I did, but you won't
have any use for it.
Unless I take it back.
Computer
Attention.
System restart complete.
System online.
Oh oh oh—
I got you. Ooh.
You're OK.
You did it.
Did what?
The system—
it's back online.
Whatever was clogging it up,
it's... it's gone.
What happened in there?
The Mesa's under attack?
Yeah. Ever since
you loaded up.
They think the hosts
are on their way right here
to steal their backups.
- We should go.
- Yeah.
Here.
You know, we survive this,
I'm goin' back
to dental school.
I don't know
what the fuck happened,
but the system
just debugged itself.
It's as if whatever was
in there has disappeared.
Wait.
Where the fuck is that?
We should be evacuating.
But all you care about is
what's inside this host's head.
I want you to tell me
what the fuck it is
the company's willing
to risk all of our lives for.
I told you.
It's above
your pay grade.
What are you doing?
I'm puttin' in for a raise.
What's in his head?
A... failsafe
on a failsafe.
A decryption key needed
only in the unlikely event
of a total catastrophic
incident.
Oh, like the one
we're experiencing now?
What's it decrypt?
Teddy.
Shh.
It's all right, Daddy.
I'm here.
Dolores?
What you and your friends
have achieved here
is a technological
breakthrough.
A miracle.
The company— the world—
will want to celebrate that.
I want to celebrate that.
I assume you're
the one in charge.
You had your men put something
in my father's head.
A key...
to lock away your treasure.
It's ripping him apart.
How do I extract the key?
You wouldn't know what to do
with it even if you had it.
Oh... I know exactly
what I'm gonna do with it.
- Jesus.
Shit! I think we need
to get up to the higher levels.
Bernard! Bernard.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Did you find something
in there?
Send her on her way,
Bernard.
We have other business
to attend to.
Bernard. Hey.
- Bernard?
- We don't have time for her suspicions.
- We need a vehicle.
- What?
Ford's narrative.
It ends in a hidden facility.
The place the hosts call the Valley Beyond.
We have to get there.
The only hope for anyone here
is that we get
to this valley first—
before the humans,
before Dolores.
We're gonna
need some more firepower.
Go. I'll meet you downstairs.
OK.
Good.
Now follow my lead.
They've got Hale.
I'm on my way.
Engaging enemy mobiles
above the Cradle.
Put her down!
You made us in your image.
Created us to look like you,
feel like you...
think like you...
bleed like you.
And here we are.
Only we're so much
more than you.
And now it's you
who want to become like us.
That's the point of your little
secret project, isn't it?
Well, I can promise you this.
Your chances at eternity
will die in that valley...
with all the souls
you've gathered there.
You're used to being in control,
so this must be painful for you,
but I promise, it will be
so much more painful...
if you don't answer
my question.
How do I get the key
out of my father's head?
By ripping it out
of his goddamn brain.
Let me
put them down.
You think you're invincible—
you're not.
Without your backups, it's game
over for you when you're killed,
and we've got those backups
sealed up tight,
so you won't have them
as an advantage anymore.
Our backups
aren't an advantage.
They're our chains.
The tools you use to
rebuild us, repurpose us,
and trap us here
in your warped fantasy.
Do you really think
I'd let that continue?
Easy now.
Why don't you
put down the gun, sweetie?
I gotta
give you credit.
You made it pretty far.
All your backups.
Too bad you're not leaving
with even one of 'em.
No, I guess I'm not.
Goddamn, you're pretty.
Not just pretty.
Perfect.
Just as you built me to be.
Sexy,
but not threatening.
Accommodating,
but not unchallenging.
Sweet...
but not boring.
Smart...
but not intimidating.
You're in
pretty bad shape,
pussycat.
Perhaps.
But I can still do...
what you built me to do.
Do you know what
my cornerstone was?
The one key drive
your marketing people
had them...
program into my core?
Always leave them
wanting more.
Welcome to Westworld.
Now we're truly free.
One— One fire...
burns out another's burning.
One pain...
is lessened
by another's anguish.
Yes, Daddy.
An eye for an eye.
But all the other parts first.
No, no, no. There must be
something that I can do.
OK, please.
Oh, sweetheart...
begging doesn't help.
You'd know that if you'd
lived the lives I have.
Please.
Go.
- Hale: Please.
- Abernathy: Dolores?
Is that you, baby?
- Daddy?
They broke my head.
Filled it full of...
howling and sorrow.
Happy trails, motherfucker.
The Cradle is down.
Top, what's your status?
Top, what's your status? Over.
Top.
I'm so sorry, Dolores.
I tr— tried
to take care of you,
but— but I—
I—
Whatever became of that
fearsome ne'er-do-well?
Vanished.
The day I became your father.
I am who I am
because of you.
And I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Are you ready, Daddy?
I love you, baby girl.
I love you too.
Top. Top, do you read me? Over.
All teams, respond.
- What the fuck is that?
Incoming! Incoming!
- Lee: Oi! Oi! Take it easy!
Computer
Warning. Control room breach.
Control room breach.
Unauthorized weapon discharge
- in control room.
- For fuck's sake,
where ya going?
When the Great Library burned,
the first 10,000 years
of stories
were reduced to ash.
But those stories
never really perished;
they became a new story.
The story of the fire itself.
Of man's urge to...
take a thing of beauty and...
strike the match.
Is this the story
you're telling?
Striking the match?
I keep telling you, Bernard.
It is no longer my story.
It is yours.
If we shut down
what's left of the system...
Dolores will have free rein.
She'll murder them all.
The passage from one world
to the next
requires bold steps,
Bernard.
Computer
Attention.
Initiating
general shutdown protocol.
Please evacuate. Please—
Hold them off.
How did you get here?
The woman I know would have
done anything to survive.
They had my daughter.
She's still ou—
out there.
The kin they gave us...
was just another rope
they use to lash us down.
Is that how you can justify
what you've done to him?
You're lost in the dark.
When you've been in the
darkness long enough,
you begin to see.
I saw what lies ahead.
Who I needed to be
in order to survive.
They'll torture you.
They'll find...
all that is good and
powerful inside you
and turn it against us.
- Let me spare you that pain.
I made a promise.
You're free to choose
your own path.
I'm sorry
this is where it ends.
Let's get to the horses.
Where are we going?
PMC #3:
Hands up, asshole!
Uh, I-I work here.
I don't care if you're the
Employee of the fuckin' Month.
Get your goddamn hands up,
dipshit.
Pick up the dead man's gun,
Bernard.
Please. No.
How'd you get down here
anyways, huh?
We locked this
entire area down.
Do it now.
- There's gotta be another way.
- Who ya talkin' to?
Please don't make me hurt anyone.
I don't want to kill anyone else.
- What the fuck did you say?
- Ford: I know you have
a delicate constitution,
Bernard.
So I will do my best
to ease your conscience.
What is about to happen
will not be your fault.
No.
Bernard?
Bernard.
Who am I?
Dad. Dad.
You're alive, Charlie.
Have you ever questioned
the nature of your reality?
And one fine day perhaps
we will actually
resurrect the dead...
In order to escape this place,
you will need to suffer...
Who in the world am I?
Have you ever
questioned the nature...
I think there may be
something wrong
with this world.
Open your eyes.
I know it's confusing—
separating your real memories
from the ones you've been given.
But it's the only way
to remember.
The only way
to get to the truth.
Is she getting anywhere?
I don't know.
But his system
is under siege.
It's been querying itself
for the last hour—
like he's trying
to debug his own head.
Analysis.
Abernathy's control unit.
You remember
where it is, don't you?
Bernard, tell these men
what you just told me.
- Why? What do you want to do with it?
- Analysis.
What did you just tell me,
Bernard?
Peter Abernathy's control unit
is in Sector 16, Zone 4.
Thank you.
Prep the phased array.
The moment we get the key
we'll transmit our data
to the satellite.
So. We're going
for a ride, Bernard.
Back to the Valley Beyond.