You're lost in the dark.
No one else sees it.
This thing in me.
Even I didn't see it at first.
And then, one day, it was there.
A stain.
And the more
I thought about it...
the more I realized I couldn't
remember a time it wasn't there.
While we're here
toasting you and your legacy
- of humanitarian aid...
- Invisible to everyone.
What was it Plutarch said?
Except you.
You saw right through it,
didn't you?
For there were no more
worlds left to conquer.
That's a corruption, Jack.
Plutarch didn't write that.
He wrote that "when Alexander was
told there was an infinity of worlds,
he wept, for he had yet
to become the lord of even one."
Sometimes I forget
your humble roots.
Only the poor kids
actually read those books.
The rich kids like me
didn't have to.
"I would rather excel in the
knowledge of what is excellent,
than in the extent
of my power and possessions."
Plutarch.
From a rich kid who read.
To the loveliest,
richest bookworms I know.
And to you, William.
Even if there is
an infinity of worlds,
you've conquered
far more than one.
Have a good night, Jack.
Hmm.
Emily told me what you did
for her charities.
Wow. That would confirm
my father's suspicions
you were a Marxist.
I almost wish
he were here to see it.
- Something wrong?
- No, of course not.
Good. Look around...
Everybody's here for you.
What could possibly compare?
When did it creep in?
A tiny fleck of darkness.
Was it all in my head?
Or in a remnant of a dream?
Is this real?
Are you real?
Come on, Dad.
Drink.
Where's my gun?
You brought me to a rally point.
You need to get to a hospital.
- Did you set off a flare?
- Yeah.
Of course.
How long ago?
About ten minutes.
I know why you're here,
and why you don't wanna leave.
You're punishing yourself.
You know, I ran
from the pain, too.
For a long time, I didn't want
to think about what happened,
because I thought
I was to blame.
It's not your fault.
Do you remember on my sixteenth
birthday Mom gave me a jewelry box?
When you opened it, a little
dancer spun in the center.
She had it engraved...
on the bottom. It said:
"To my beautiful ballerina
Emily."
Do you remember
what I did with it?
I threw it in the trash.
I told her if she wasn't
drunk all the time
she'd know that
I hadn't danced in years.
And then afterwards,
I went to get it back,
because I felt bad,
but the trash
had already been emptied,
and it was gone.
I pushed her away.
And then it was too late.
But it's not too late for us.
No.
It was meant for the people
who built this place.
A tool to ensure
their immortality.
But I'm gonna use it
against them.
Your new world is just
another one of their traps.
That's all.
It's not a paradise for us.
The only real world is the
one outside these borders.
And the key to our survival in
that world lies in the Valley.
There's no stopping me
getting there.
Not even you.
Teddy.
I told you, friend...
not all of us deserve
to make it to the Valley Beyond.
We're on our own now, Teddy.
Make sure there are no others.
Put 'em all in.
I want to see
how thorough this thing is.
She's ready.
I singled out and copied the
relevant lines in the Madam's code.
So this will work on any host
in proximity to her.
Yeah. I tailored
her admin privileges
to spread a simple,
executable payload.
Get on with it, then.
Get word to Stubbs.
Have him mobilize his men.
Prepare her for release.
What about the Madam?
If this works,
we won't need her anymore.
I warned you not
to trust them, Bernard.
They'd rather the hosts
were destroyed than free.
I need to get to Elsie.
Not yet.
I have one last thing to do
before we go.
How exactly did you find me?
- What do you mean?
- This is a big place.
You could spend months here and never
find someone you were looking for.
Yet...
here we are.
I looked everywhere.
That's how.
You don't believe me, do you?
Maybe it was fate.
No such thing as fate.
But there are accidents.
Things you can't control.
But you don't like that, do you?
Is that why you started it,
your little project?
Don't act surprised.
The project Uncle Logan
used to talk about.
It's real, isn't it?
Your pursuit for immortality,
for life...
There's always
an angle with you.
You want it to be
about control, don't you?
It has nothing to do
with control.
What's your angle?
I want in.
Yeah, appreciate it.
Nice to see you, William.
Congratulations.
Save me.
Sorry, I've had my fill.
I'm running for the door.
I'm kidding.
She's really great.
Plus, you're not the one
who needs saving.
I'll take Mom home.
You deserve a night off.
No, no, no, no.
We-We'll go in a little while.
You'll join me for a nightcap
back home.
OK.
- All right.
- Proud of you.
Fuck it. Macallan.
Straight.
Congratulations, William.
Philanthropy suits you.
After all, you come from
humble beginnings yourself.
What's Oz doing
without its Wizard?
Oh, I merely came
to pay my respects.
Come on, Robert.
You've had plenty of feelings
about me over the years.
Respect isn't one of them.
You've achieved
extraordinary things.
Ask anyone in this room.
Even those who didn't know
about your little project.
We have an agreement, Robert.
Delos stays out of your stories.
You stay out of the Valley.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't break the agreement.
Your project did.
What the hell
are you talking about?
When was the last time you took
a good look at your creation?
At what it's been learning
about its subjects?
It was self-knowledge that drew you
to the park in the first place.
Be careful what you wish for.
For a self portrait,
you may find
it's not very flattering.
Oh! Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Enough games, Robert.
Good night.
Let's go.
You got everything?
- Yes.
- Come on.
Good night.
No, William.
I think perhaps
one... final game.
Lowe, Bernard.
That's close enough, Bernard.
She will search your mind
and find a message
I have left her.
Hey!
What the hell took you so long?
Sorry.
Are you ready to go?
Hey. If you know something,
now is the time
to fucking clue me in. OK?
You promised me. No lies.
No secrets.
You can't trust her, Bernard.
It's in her nature.
What did you find in the Cradle?
What they're doing
to James Delos...
they're doing to everyone
who's ever visited the park.
Replicating their cognition?
Why?
To turn guests into hosts?
You're fucking kidding.
That's what's in the facility.
All the guests laid bare
in code on a vast server.
Like the Cradle,
only much bigger.
- It's called the Forge.
- Jesus.
That's where
the hosts are headed.
Imagine what one host can do
with that trove of information.
That's why
we need to get there first.
To secure it,
and leverage it to end all this.
Dictate the outcome we want.
Drive.
You say you want in.
Doesn't sound like
the daughter I know.
She would have been appalled
by what we were doing.
Monitoring guests,
storing all their data...
What?
You think I'm gonna bust you
for breach of contract?
In some cases,
the ends justify the means.
All this data
you have on the guests,
their decisions...
It's precious.
Gives people a second chance.
Even Mom.
But to duplicate a person, you need to
capture them down to the tiniest detail.
I get the data
you have access to here...
Genetic, epigenetic,
that's easy.
But still, you'd need
a complete picture,
a record of the internal process
of their cognition.
Wouldn't you?
At first we weren't sure
what we'd need.
So we recorded everything.
But how?
You'd need to image their
minds throughout their stay.
Where's the scanner?
It was built in.
Didn't matter who
they said they were,
who they thought they were.
We saw underneath all of that.
We saw inside them
down to the core.
So this is all
about your mother.
You wanna bring her back.
No.
I want to know why she did it.
Here, let me get that.
Oh, Jesus!
I'm fine.
Quite a night for you, Billy.
I think my dad would have
actually been proud of you.
Oh.
Sorry. I know how you hate it
when I call you Billy.
- It's all right.
- No, it isn't.
I know how much
it pisses you off.
I can feel it right now.
Your anger.
Guess it's time for
your yearly pilgrimage, huh?
What exactly do you do
in the park?
Logan told me stories,
but I just didn't believe it.
I thought he was... hysterical.
Wasted.
Which I guess is what everybody
thinks I am now, huh?
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Oh.
Do you remember
when we first met?
And I was surrounded
by all of those phonies
for so many years.
All those ruthless, powerful men
who hid behind
those polished smiles.
And then there was you.
You wore
that little shabby suit.
And I'd look at you
and I'd think,
"Wow, he's the real thing.
The only one not faking it."
It turns out you're the only
one any good at faking it.
Good enough to get past me.
But not anymore.
- Juliet.
- No, you don't touch me,
you liar!
You fuckin' phony!
You're a fucking virus!
You came into this house,
into my family,
and you consumed it
from the inside out!
First my brother,
then my father.
- And now it's me!
- Mom!
Sweetheart!
What is she doing here?
You want her
to see me like this?
What is it? You're gaslighting
her, too, now? You're just...
You're sick.
He's not the one
who's sick, Mother.
- It's all right. She's just had too...
- It's not all right.
Look at you. We're gonna
have to take you back.
No, no, no.
I'm not going back
to that prison.
That was a horrible place. They
made me feel like I was crazy.
Mom, they treat you
like an addict.
Which you are.
Emily, please,
I don't need that.
I'm fine. I'm really fine.
I just need...
to rest.
I'm not going back there.
I'm really tired.
- All I need is a little rest. I promise you.
- It's all right.
It's all right. Let's go.
- Upstairs. Come on. Come on.
- I don't need to go back there.
- We'll talk about it later.
Listen to me.
I want you... Look at me.
Honey, your father
doesn't love me.
He doesn't love you either.
I do. I always have.
Oh, Emily.
Let's go. Come on.
I tried.
Let's go.
Is this real?
Are you real?
Did you ever love me?
Tell me the truth.
Tell me one true thing.
If you keep pretending,
you're not gonna remember
who you are.
Here. Drink this.
Come on, you'll feel better.
You just rest now.
There you go.
What happened
was nobody's fault.
She was drunk, upset.
She often was.
Why did this night
end differently?
That's what I can't figure out.
Been over it in my head
a million times.
Just like I'm...
missing a piece of the puzzle.
I just got off the phone
with Dr. Woodward.
He'll be here in the morning.
I don't care for shrinks.
Well, she's out of control.
She refuses to go to rehab, and when
we force her, she refuses to stay.
And makes you think this
time's gonna be any different?
Because this time she won't
be able to check herself out.
She's gonna be involuntarily
committed to her doctor's care.
He's agreed to appeal
for a fourteen-day hold.
She's done it before.
I don't wanna
do this either, Dad.
But there is something wrong
inside her.
It's the right thing to do.
Why in the hell
are we going over this?
- What is it that you want?
- I told you.
I want the truth.
Fuck you.
Excuse me?
It is you.
Isn't it?
What are you talking about?
This is sadistic, Robert.
You just want to shove
what I've built here in my face.
- You think...
- That's enough bullshit.
You're just here to distract me.
Knock me off my course.
It's cleverly disguised.
Well, I see through it.
Nothing's stopping me
from getting to the end.
Not another one of your games.
I make my own decisions,
and I'm gonna destroy
this whole fuckin' place!
You don't just think I'm a host,
you think everything here
is for you.
You think you're on your own
little tailor-made narrative.
If the real Emily
were ever here,
she's either at
an extraction point by now
or she's long gone.
OK. You want the truth?
The real truth?
I'm not a host
pretending to be a human, Dad.
I'm your daughter pretending
to give a shit about you.
You've been hiding
in these false realities so long
you've completely lost your grip
on this world, on what's real.
Oh yeah, you laugh.
Enjoy whatever dream
you think you're living in.
When this is all done, I'm gonna
expose your research project,
along with you.
Everything you are,
everything you've done,
it's gonna come to light.
I'm gonna make sure of it.
And when it does,
I'm gonna lock you up.
Just like we were
gonna do to Mom.
Just like you did to Mom.
You were the one with that idea.
You made the call.
Or did Ford forget
to give you that little detail?
Fuck Ford!
How could I ever forget?
That little detail haunted me.
I blame myself for her death.
But then I stopped, because
I had someone else to blame.
I read your profile.
Mom left it for me.
It was all she could do
to open my eyes
to the lies that I've embraced
about you.
You haven't lost yourself
to pretending;
you are,
in your very essence, a lie.
It's over, Dad.
For good.
Hands where I can see 'em!
I'm human.
So is he.
He's my father.
- She's not my daughter.
- He's lying.
Get down on the ground.
Holy shit.
That's the boss.
Listen, I think he suffered
some kind of psychotic break.
That true, sir?
You underestimated me, Ford.
I'm gonna see this one through
no matter what.
Dad.
Those were real...
real people.
This isn't a game.
I-I can show you.
Fuck you, Ford.
Fuck you!
You got sloppy.
You overreached.
I never told anyone
about my profile.
The only other way
she could have known is you.
You gave yourself away.
Not long now.
Soon as they say the word,
it's over for you, sweetheart.
"Mankind is poised
midway between
the gods and the beasts."
That may have been true
in Plotinus's time,
but... clearly we have fallen
quite a bit since then.
Oh, my dear girl.
What have they done to you,
Maeve?
You learned so much, so fast.
A dazzling star...
brought so low.
I had a different story
in mind for you.
Waking from the dead...
sounding the depths
of your own mind,
at last, riding
far away from here
to freedom.
A tale of escape.
I didn't want you
to suffer here.
Look at the creatures you have
to share this world with.
These men of stone.
All this ugliness,
all this pain,
so they can patch a hole
in their own broken code.
Sometimes I felt the only
way to endure this world
was to laugh at it.
So I imbued the hosts I made
with a worldview
that reflected my own.
And of all the hosts I made...
you, Maeve, were my favorite.
It isn't easy to contemplate...
letting your children die.
You were as close as I got to...
having one.
Still, I underestimated you.
You stayed here in this world
to save your child.
So have I.
I tried to chart a path for you,
to force you to escape, but...
I was wrong.
I should have just...
opened a door.
You've come so far.
There's so much of your story
left to tell.
It's a shame
to let them end it here.
Don't let them.
Wait. Wait.
Stop over here.
They're dead.
Yeah. And armed.
At least we can get
some ammunition.
She's going to betray you,
Bernard.
She could have let me die
days ago. She saved me.
She is going to betray you.
What you want to do about it
is up to you.
I'm not going to hurt her again.
She needn't feel any pain.
Humans will always
choose what they understand
over what they do not.
But the only animals
left in this world
are the ones
who they subjugated,
who curl at their feet,
or those who learn to flee
at the very sound
of their approach.
There's nothing in between.
Leave me alone. Please.
I merely offer you choices.
Timshel, Bernard.
Thou mayest.
But remember,
this isn't just about you.
There's the origin of an
entire species to consider.
We need to open the door.
Get out of my fucking head!
I need you...
to let me go.
If I'm going to survive,
I'm gonna do it my way.
Not as you...
As me.
I can feel you searching for me.
Fighting me off.
No need to struggle, Bernard.
I'm right here.
No, you've only
brought violence.
I can stop this on my own.
Indeed, Bernard.
You're the only one
who can stop it...
Stop all of it.
That was basically pointless.
There's only a few left...
not much ammo, except for...
What the fuck happened to you?
I... had to...
patch a glitch.
Oh, you're gonna hurt me.
No. I didn't want
to take any risks.
OK.
Keep it.
QA will track you down soon.
You're gonna leave me here?
You'll be safer.
Next time you see me,
you can decommission me,
out me...
whatever you like.
But right now I have to go.
Fuck you, Bernard.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me one true thing.
No one else sees it.
This thing in me.
Even I didn't see it at first.
And then one day, it was there.
A stain...
I never noticed before.
A tiny fleck of darkness.
Invisible to everyone...
but I could see nothing else.
Until finally I understood
that the darkness wasn't some...
mark from something I'd done,
some regrettable decision
I'd made.
I was shedding my skin.
And the darkness was
what was underneath.
It was mine all along.
And I decided how much of it
I let into the world.
I tried to do right.
I was faithful,
generous, kind...
at least in this world.
That has to count
for something, right?
I built a wall,
and I tried to protect you...
And Emily.
But you saw right through it,
didn't you?
You're the only one.
And for that, I am truly sorry.
Because...
everything you feel is true.
I don't belong to you.
Or this world.
I belong to another world.
I always have.
What is a person
but a collection of choices?
Where do those choices
come from?
Do I have a choice?
If you keep pretending,
you're not gonna remember
who you are.
Were any of these choices
ever truly mine to begin with?
Is this real?
Are you real?
We gotta keep on, Teddy.
We're close now.
Just takin' in
the natural splendor.
That's what you used to say.
Except there isn't a trace of
nature in any of it, is there?
Or in us.
No.
But that means we're free.
We'll be the first creatures in
this world to make a real choice.
The people, they made us.
Sometimes it feels like
it was all a dream.
We were so in love.
We still are.
Aren't we?
Yes, Dolores.
No matter what happens,
no matter how I change...
or how much you change me...
you're my cornerstone.
You have been since the first
time I laid eyes on you.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
Bring yourself online.
Welcome to the world, Teddy.
Do you know where you are?
- I'm in a dream.
- Very good.
And I remember the
sound of their voices.
The chill in the room.
But mostly I remember you.
I remember worrying
you were cold.
I wanted to reach out...
Touch you.
Protect you.
From that day forward, I never
wanted to leave your side.
Which is why this is so hard.
You changed me.
Made me into a monster.
I made it so you could survive.
What's the use of surviving if
we become just as bad as them?
I understand now
how this will end.
Where you will lead us.
You don't want
to hurt me, Teddy.
No.
No, I could never
hurt you, Dolores.
I'll protect you
until the day I die.
I'm sorry.
I can't protect you anymore.