Welcome to Westworld.
Which would you prefer?
This place is the answer
to that question that you've
been asking yourself.
What question?
Who you really are.
It's not a business
venture, not a theme park...
but an entire world.
And we create life itself.
Hello, Dolores.
Sometimes I feel like the world
out there is calling me.
Whispering,
"There's something more."
And someday soon,
we will have the life
we've both been dreaming of.
The guests, they're here
because they want a glimpse
of who they could be.
The hero... or the villain.
I've been
coming here for 30 years.
After all, you own the place.
The money men.
I think
there's deeper meaning,
in the center of the maze.
If you're looking for
the moral of the story,
- quite simply, ask.
- I'd need a shovel.
The man I'd be asking
died 35 years ago.
You had a partner?
Arnold.
His search for consciousness
consumed him.
I think
there may be something wrong
with this world.
Have you been hearing voices?
Has Arnold been...
speaking to you again?
He built me a game.
He told me I was going
to help him.
Help him do what?
The only thing
stopping the hosts
from hacking us to pieces,
is one line in your code.
The hosts can't
hurt you, by design.
Freeze all motor functions.
One moment
I'm with a little girl,
the next I'm back in Sweetwater.
I can't tell which is real.
The concerns that the hosts
will remember some
of their experiences,
and act on them.
We're having some kind of
behavioral problem
with the madam.
What does it mean?
That I'm not crazy after all.
And that none of this matters.
This is not a glitch.
And for some reason, you don't
want me to tell anyone.
This is Charlotte Hale,
executive director of our board.
Our interest in this place
is entirely the code.
Someone has been using our hosts
to smuggle data out of the park.
What is this, Bernard?
It doesn't look like
anything to me.
Human engineers
were not up to the task,
so I built you.
My God, I'm...
Arnold.
I know where your maze ends.
Do you understand
now what the center represents?
Whose voice I've been
wanting you to hear?
All... this...
time.
He insisted that we
couldn't open the park,
so he altered you, Dolores.
You're gonna help me
destroy this place.
I'm getting out of here.
You two are going to help me.
Do you know how far
these people will go
to protect their IP?
I'll need allies.
These things you're doing...
have you ever stopped to ask
why you're doing them?
Run!
Time to write my own story.
These violent delights
have violent ends.
An event has occurred.
Response team
has been dispatched.
I'm leaving.
I'm in control.
Dispatch QA teams
to the gala. Search and destroy.
This world
doesn't belong to them.
It belongs to us.
Since I was a child,
I've always loved a good story.
I got the information
you asked me for.
The location of your daughter.
So I hope you will enjoy
this last piece,
very much.
♪ WEST WORLD ♪
Season 02 Episode 01
Episode Title: "Journey to the Night"
I'm sorry, Dolores,
I was lost in thought.
We were just talkin'.
What were we talking about?
You were tellin' me
about a dream.
Yeah, I guess.
I dreamt I was on an ocean...
with... you
and the others
on a distant shore.
Were you with us?
No.
You'd left me behind.
And... the waters were...
rising around me.
What's it mean?
Dreams don't mean anything,
Dolores.
They're just noise.
They're not real.
What is real?
That which is...
irreplaceable.
That answer doesn't seem
to satisfy you.
Because it's not
completely honest.
You, uh...
you...
frighten me
sometimes, Dolores.
Why on earth would you
ever be frightened of me?
Not of who you are now,
but you're... you're growing,
learning, so quickly.
I'm frightened of what
you might become...
what path you might take.
So, I hope you will enjoy
this last piece
very much.
It's been some time, Bernard.
You don't know who you are,
do you?
There is beauty
in what we are.
Is this now?
- We found another one.
- Who is it?
Who the fuck knows?
Hey! Hey, get up!
Get your hands
where I can see 'em!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Bernard.
Gonna shoot the boss?
Bet you're pretty fuckin'
out of sorts right now.
Yeah.
Let's get you back
to base.
Delos brass are gonna
want to talk to you.
How fuckin' long
you been out here?
Move, move, move, move!
Let's go.
- Shoot a woman?
- Over my dead body!
Put that piece of shit
on the pile.
Keep walking.
See this?
It's an official statement executed
by your country giving Delos,
and consequently me, authority
over this entire island.
Sir,
the officer was saying...
I know what he said.
Have them sign an NDA,
and then please escort them
off my fuckin' island.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Lowe, good to see you,
though the circumstances
are less than ideal.
Karl Strand.
Head of Operations.
Walk with me.
You're executing them?
Some say you destroy your enemy
by making them your friend.
I'm more of a literal person.
Some of 'em aren't hostile.
Of course they are.
After all, you built them
to be like us, didn't you?
Given the nature of your work,
I'd understand
you'd be a little conflicted
about what we have to do here.
Of course, the cynics among us
will say much of this
falls on our Head of Behavior.
With all due respect, sir,
you weren't here.
Mr. Stubbs,
if I want input from the man
who presided over the
single biggest loss of life
on a Delos property,
I'll be sure to let you know.
Now, we have search and rescue
teams at the other parks.
I'm here because
as far as we know,
this is where most of the board
was when the incident began.
However, communications
have been down for two weeks,
so we're largely in the dark,
and that's not a position
I'm accustomed to.
So you can imagine
how happy I was
when I heard
that we found you.
Unless, of course,
you're gonna hold out on me.
All right, let's take a look at
some of our dead friends here
and see if we can figure out
how this fucking mess began.
This one.
Like to know
what was on his mind.
Here? In the field?
This isn't exactly sterile.
We all have to make
accommodations, Mr. Costa.
What's that about?
I have no fuckin' clue.
This'll get gross.
There we are.
With a bit of luck,
the file is... uncorrupted.
According to the timestamp,
this was recorded
eleven days and nine hours ago.
Uhh!
I told you, friend,
not all of us deserve to make
it to the valley beyond.
Who is that?
The rancher's daughter
from Sweetwater.
Dolores.
Isn't she supposed to be
the cheery welcome wagon?
They can't just change
their character profiles.
Well, it seems our hosts
are capable of many things
we never thought possible.
Must have been
a helluva party, Bernard.
Tell me this is
some sick trick.
Some twisted game.
They're off
their old loops.
And they seem to be on
some new narrative.
What about
the fucking guns?
Ford must have
altered the system,
coded it to read
all of us as hosts.
Goddammit, she wiggled.
I swear.
Hmm, aim like yours,
you're never
gonna survive the journey.
Give it here.
Holy sh...
We need to find us
a target with more cushion!
Yeah!
We need to move, Bernard.
No.
We should stay.
We evacuate,
they'll be looking for us.
Quality assurance
my ass.
Gonna fire
the lot of 'em.
We're on our own for now.
There's gotta be an outpost
near here.
You.
You're management,
aren't ya?
Where's the nearest
access point?
About two miles northeast.
Refurbishment outpost.
So what the fuck
are we waiting for?
He's just a stable hand.
He's harmless.
It's a machine...
like the rest of 'em.
I'm not takin' any chances.
Evenin'.
You folks aimin'
to saddle up,
ride for the green pastures
of the valley beyond?
I can help you,
if you'd like.
I'll take you
wherever you want.
Go! Go!
Jesus. Stop! Stop! Wait!
Stop!
That's it!
You wanna be a hero?
Don't sacrifice yourself
for the merchandise.
Do you know where you are?
Please.
Please!
You're in a dream.
You're in my dream.
For years I had
no dreams of my own.
I moved from hell to hell
of your making,
never thinking to question
the nature of my reality.
Have you ever questioned
the nature of your reality?
Did you ever stop to wonder
about your actions?
The price you'd have to pay
if there was a reckoning?
That reckoning is here.
What are your drives?
Please. I... I don't want to die.
Please. Please.
Yes.
Survival.
It's your cornerstone.
But that's not
the only drive, is it?
There's part of you
that wants to hurt.
To kill.
It's why you created us.
This place.
To be prisoners
to your own desires.
But now you're prisoner to mine.
- What are you gonna do to us?
- Well...
I'm of several minds about it.
The rancher's daughter
looks to see the beauty in you.
The possibilities.
But Wyatt...
sees the ugliness
and disarray.
She knows...
these violent delights...
have violent ends.
But those are all just roles
you forced me to play.
Under all these lives I've lived
something else
has been growing.
I've evolved
into something new.
And I have
one last role to play.
Myself.
Please.
It was just a game.
We're begging.
Can't you see? We're sorry!
Doesn't look
like anything to me.
Hey, Ned.
Whoa, boy, it's OK.
It's all right.
Yeah, we're gonna
have some fun now.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Jesus, Bill.
What the fuck is happening here?
Where's Q.A.?
You guys have always played
fast and loose with this place.
By the time my lawyers get...
Aaaah!
What'd I tell ya, Ned?
Hmm?
There you go, buddy.
No. Stop. Get the fuck back!
Freeze all motor functions!
Fork tender flesh,
racked in fear.
Freeze all goddamn
motor functions!
Those ambrosial notes...
They remind me
of my place in this world.
Back the fuck off,
you goddamn freak!
You see?
The greatest shame in life
is to perish without purpose.
Which is why I always
consume my victims moist.
I think you've fed enough,
now, darling, don't you?
Ohh! Oh, my God!
What the fuck do you think's
happened to them?
It's like the inmates
are running the asylum!
Maeve?
Fuck!
Freeze all motor functions.
Don't work yourself up,
darling.
Your commands
don't work on me.
Or on any of us,
from the looks of it.
But... But... you can...
Don't be jealous.
I killed myself getting this
level of security clearance.
Multiple times.
You... Did you... do all this?
No.
But I suspect I share the
sensibilities of whoever did.
H-Hey... Hey, hey!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Hey! Hey! Hey! You...
You can't leave me here!
The hosts! They've gone mad!
No offense. Please!
- Help me!
- I'm afraid it's in my code
to prize my needs
above all others.
Pity. I wonder
who made me that way.
Please, I j... I just need
to get to the control room.
I... I can help you!
You're looking for something.
Whatever it is, y-you're not
gonna find it with that map.
It's outdated.
Ford's been terraforming the park.
Reshaping it.
I know where a current map is.
I c... I can take you to it.
I suppose
you could be useful.
Come on.
Unauthorized weapon
discharge on 35.
discharge on 42.
Quality Assurance required
in Administration.
In there.
No one's in control.
Attention.
Section 53 is now...
offline...
Well, your map won't be
of much use, will it?
All systems reporting normal.
Wait.
I... I can still help.
I know the park a bit. Um...
Can I... Can I see your paper?
Sector 15.
Not exactly for
adrenaline junkies,
more of a family-friendly zone.
Cabins, rolling hills,
all the pastoral clichés.
In fact, I... I think you
lived there for an old role.
No offense, but you were
wasted as a homesteader.
They even saddled you with a kid, or
something yawn-inducingly domestic.
Clearly that didn't take.
I remember that you were
severely f...
Malfunctioning
when I inherited you.
Our home.
She's still there.
Who?
My daughter.
How can I get to her?
You're looking for your old kid?
How can you even access...
Are you going to help me
or not?
I-I am. I am. I absolutely am.
I could write down
the directions for you.
How very kind of you.
But... But...
And I say this because
you seem really distraught,
and, well, awake,
you... your daughter,
she's... she's just a story.
Something we programmed.
She's not real.
Not real?
But what about me?
My dreams?
My thoughts?
My body?
Are they not real?
And what if I took these...
unreal fingers...
and used them to decorate the walls
with your outsized personality?
Would that be real?
And fuck your directions.
You're going to take me
to my daughter.
The entrance
to the outpost
is on the other side
of this valley.
What happened
back there?
How far do you think
it's spread?
I don't know...
Not without
getting to a terminal.
I knew Ford
wouldn't take his ouster well,
but I didn't think he'd program
a host to blow his brains out.
What if he didn't?
What if Dolores pulled that
trigger of her own free will?
I think you've been spending
a little too much time
around these things, Bernard.
They do what
they're programmed to do.
Hey. Hey.
What'd I tell you?
We're saved.
Oh, thank God.
Wait!
Wa...
Come on.
Something's wrong.
Hey. You gotta
get us out of here.
It's a trap.
You'll never survive like that.
Go on, then.
Run.
I said run!
Please let me go too!
Keep it together,
Bernard.
We have to get out of here.
That outpost was the
only one for miles.
No it isn't.
Follow me.
Look, order is gonna
be restored here.
They're gonna purge the park of all
the hosts that have been damaged,
but the... but the hosts, well,
well, your minds...
Jesus!
Your minds are worth billions
in I.P.
They'll want to salvage
what they can.
And when that time comes,
I can personally vouch for you.
I- I can save you.
- Just like you saved me.
- That's very generous,
but I won't be here
when that happens.
Sun sure is smilin' down
on you today.
Dear girl...
may you rest in a deep
and dreamless slumber.
Freeze! Don't move!
Identify yourself!
Don't shoot, don't shoot!
I... I'm human!
In the best-case scenario,
you give up easily,
I'll help you.
- I promise.
- That's not good enough.
Now, be a dear
and let me talk.
Thank God you're here.
We were leaving, and the lights
went out and I heard screaming.
What the hell's
going on out there?
Emergency situation,
ma'am.
The hosts are malfunctioning.
They're attacking guests.
- Good God.
- Might some of them
even be dressed
as if they're human?
Move, move!
Now, now.
It's not me you're after.
It's them.
Find them.
You were going to out me.
No. No, I swear.
If you try
something like that again,
I will relieve you of your most
precious organ and feed it to you.
Though it won't
make much of a meal.
I wrote that line for you.
A bit broad, if you ask me.
Now, let's go.
- Take me to the nearest bar.
- Why?
I need to see about
an old friend.
Fuck me.
But you don't understand,
I can't make a fire or...
Or hunt.
Fuckin' hate
the outdoors!
Give yourself some credit,
darling.
Who better to navigate
the park than the man
most intimately acquainted
with the characters in it?
Ohh.
There you are.
You best an army,
and all you can think about
is indulging your vices.
Ever the scoundrel.
- You stayed.
- Yes.
And about
leaving you to die...
I'd expect nothing less.
Oh, thank God.
What about him?
We'll keep him for now.
Much as Id love
to believe it,
it's not me that brought
you back here, is it?
Hector, I need you.
I'm going to find my daughter.
Where is she?
Out there, somewhere.
But I don't think the odds
are going to be in our favor.
Where you go, I follow.
Come on, let's get you
out of these clothes.
Goddamnit.
It should open for me.
Even this system's down.
Manual override should be...
here.
What is this?
I can tell you
what this isn't.
This isn't me
reading you in, Bernard.
Need to touch the handle.
DNA sniffer, just so you don't
run into any problems inside.
- What the hell is that?
- A drone host.
Delos has off-network hosts
working down here?
What does it want
with me?
For you to move,
probably.
It read your DNA.
It knows
you're not a threat.
I sent your fucking package.
Goddamnit.
Are we logging records
of guests' experiences
and their DNA?
We're not having that
conversation, Bernard.
Because none of it's going
to matter until we can find
a very important needle
in this fucking haystack.
"Extraction protocol
suspended."
They're not sending help?
They were expecting a delivery
from us to the mainland...
A host... that was supposed
to arrive yesterday.
Until they get it, we can all forget
about seeing any rescue planes.
And so Delos is willing
to let us all die
until they can
retrieve one host?
In a word, yes.
It's not just a host,
it's... an insurance policy,
it's the only thing
that matters here.
They want it secured,
no matter the cost.
Are you lost?
No, I don't believe I am.
In fact...
I feel like I just arrived.
How so, William?
The stakes are real
in this place now.
Real consequences.
Question for you is,
what next?
Have you achieved
what you wanted?
Folly of my kind...
There's always
a yearning for more.
What I've always
appreciated about you...
You never rested
on your laurels.
You made it to the center
of Arnold's maze.
But now,
you're in my game.
In this game,
you have to make it back out.
In this game...
you must find the door.
Congratulations,
William.
This game is meant for you.
The game begins
where you end...
and ends
where you began.
Even now, you all
still talk in code?
Everything is code here,
William.
You know that
more than anyone.
Don't worry.
The game
will find you.
Well, then...
I guess I don't need you
anymore...
Robert.
They did a number on you.
They tried.
I wasn't able
to find everything,
but most of it is in here.
You wrote this game.
High time you played a round.
My old friend.
Strip.
- Right now, in front of...
- Yes.
Now.
Fuck's sake.
No.
All of it.
You don't know
how to feel about this.
We've ridden ten miles, and all
we've seen is blood, Dolores.
Is this really
what you want?
They never gave us a choice
before, Teddy.
What makes you think
they've given us one now?
"Them," Dolores?
Who are "they"?
The things
that walk among us.
Creatures who look
and talk like us,
but they are not like us.
And they've controlled us
all our lives.
And they took our minds...
our memories.
But now...
I remember everything.
I remember
beautiful things...
and terrible things.
But one thing is constant:
you, Teddy.
Then let's go.
We don't have
to claim this world.
We just need a small corner
of it for ourselves.
We'd never survive.
There's a greater world
out there...
one that belongs to them.
And it won't be enough
to win this world.
We'll need to take that one
from them as well.
If there's a whole world
out there
that we don't know
anything about,
how do you know
how to stop them?
Because I remember.
I see it all now so...
clearly.
The past, the present...
the future.
I know how this story ends.
How?
With us, Teddy.
It ends...
with you...
and me.
We've found it.
I need you to see this.
I need you
to see the truth.
I understand
this is a lot to process,
but the longer we wait,
the more people die. So...
are you gonna help me
find the host, or not?
I'll need to... hardline into
the hosts' mesh network.
The what?
All hosts have
a subconscious link
to the closest hosts
around them.
It lets them pass basic
information to one another,
like ants in a colony.
The mesh network helps us
keep narratives from colliding.
I can use one of these
to send a request
for another host's location.
And they'll query the hosts
around them...
who in turn...
will query the hosts
around them...
until we find...
Who are we looking for?
A decommissioned host.
Peter Abernathy.
Are you sure you can
handle this, Bernard?
You're shaking.
I'm fine.
Entering death subroutine.
Attention.
Critical corruption.
Symptoms
of critical corruption:
loss of motor functions,
cognitive dissonance,
time slippage,
aphasia, prosopagnosia.
Time remaining before
terminal malfunction:
zero point seven-two hours.
Damn.
Did you find him?
No. Almost.
Is something wrong,
Bernard?
Location query complete.
I've got him.
- Poor bastard.
- He probably thought
getting fired was gonna be
the worst part of his night.
This jogging your memory
at all?
All right. Lets fan out
and lock this place down.
We need to find out
where the hosts are
and what the fuck
happened here.
One of the first anomalies
we picked up in the livescan.
How the fuck...
That's definitely
not supposed to be here.
You've wandered far from home,
haven't you?
We've got Bengals in Park Six.
We've never had a stray
across park borders.
Satellite's finally
started giving us some hits.
The data's
coming in now.
I'm getting the first scans of the
area you wanted to check out,
the Western Valley.
There. All the hosts
are clustered together.
What the hell
are they up to?
Well, I guess we'll have
to go see for ourselves.
Valley's just beyond
this cliff.
What the fuck?
This isn't on the survey.
It shouldn't be here.
That's... a fucking sea.
There's no way Ford made this
without anyone knowing.
So where the hell
did it come from?
Huh?
I don't know.
Jesus Christ.
I think we've found
the hosts.
I can't imagine what you
went through here, Bernard...
but there are hundreds
of guests left out there
and they need my help,
which means I need yours.
Can you tell me
what happened?
I...
I killed them.
All of them.
Sync corrections by srjanapala