All the banks and trains around here,
and you choose to rob us?
I... I... I need
to get to the train.
They've broken my father.
He's wildly unstable...
bouncing between old roles.
It looks like an immensely
complex encryption key.
Drive!
Whatever's in there,
they want to get it out of here.
Take this dog out back,
put him down with the rest.
Get out of here.
What is this place?
It's complicated.
Oh!
We have to go!
We have to get out of here
right now!
Shh!
♪ WEST WORLD ♪
Season 02 Episode 05
Episode Title: "Akane No Mai"
Maling for you, sir.
Go ahead.
Dredging's almost
at fifty percent.
Should have the rest of them
skimmed up by end of day.
We also started draining
the valley.
You want all personal effects,
or just skin and bones?
Everything.
Down to the last Stetson.
Fly the whole pile over.
We'll crack 'em open to see if
we can't reprogram these things
- to behave by our rules again.
- Copy that.
Sir, I have two teams out
looking for Abernathy.
Good.
When you find him,
bring him to me personally.
- So, what have we got?
- It's not good.
We're pulling what we can off the
recovered host control units.
But what's really unsettling
is... what's in
about a third of them.
- And what's that?
- Nothing.
- They've been wiped?
- More like they're virgin.
Like they never held data
to begin with.
No user prints
or anything.
And that's not
the worst of it.
Have a look.
We've put the fires out,
but there's nothing
we can recover from the Cradle.
The hosts' backups
have all been destroyed.
So we've effectively lost a third
of our IP in a single sweep.
Well, that's quite a story
you gave them...
and one hell of an ending.
How did all
these disparate threads
come together to create
this nightmare?
If we figure that out,
we'll know how the story turns.
What the hell's that?
Looks like a dead man to me.
You know the old saying
about knives and gunfights?
Does the saying have a footnote
about fucking lassos, then?
All right,
that's enough.
Lay down your sword.
Tell your associates
to set us free.
We mean no harm.
See, darling?
Everything under control.
Beautiful way
to watch the sunrise.
Glistening off the intestines
of the recently mutilated.
Oh, Jesus. Ohh.
Judging by their weapons,
I'd say local police.
And given that
he's got one now...
Captured by samurai cop-killers.
Fuck me!
Can't you...
say something to them?
I'm from Honk Kong,
asshole.
This is just the tip
of Shogun World's prick.
An experience
expressly designed
for the guests
who find Westworld too tame.
We based this park
on Japan's Edo period
for the true aficionado
of artful gore.
This world will end badly,
but I'll make sure
your end is worse!
You understand them?
You all do. Look,
she's a Madam...
Consciously fluent
in dozens of languages,
including Japanese.
But you all have
those com skills
buried somewhere
in your code.
The point is,
the fact that
these psychos
didn't flip to English
as soon as I opened my mouth
means that the same
malfunctioning shitshow
that's playing out in Westworld
has found its way here.
That's also why your vocal
voodoo didn't work on them...
You spoke
the wrong language.
This all feels
a little too familiar.
Is that a...
a butterfly?
A mariposa.
I'll be damned.
It's us.
Yes, fine,
I may have cribbed
a little bit from Westworld.
Well, you trying writing
300 stories in three weeks.
W-W-We're human shields now?
Welcome to Shogun World.
Shit!
Can you watch it?
Behind you!
Hell of a homecoming.
Sweetwater was never
home to begin with, Teddy.
You and I were born long before
this place even existed.
But it's the place I
return to again and again.
No matter how far I strayed,
somethin' always...
carried me back.
Somethin' like that?
Looks like she's taken some
hits the past few days.
But who hasn't?
Make a thorough inspection
from the engine
to the last axle.
Fix what's broke,
strip her for speed.
Teddy.
With me.
What do we need
the train for, Dolores?
They've taken my daddy.
So we're gonna get him back.
Well, it ain't doin' any good
sittin' in that bottle.
Sorry, Maeve.
Didn't get much sleep
last night.
Sometimes...
sometimes
they're real bad.
Clementine?
You're new.
Not much of a rind on you.
That's enough.
Rejoin the others.
It's like I
told you, Teddy...
this place was never home.
Let's ride.
There's someplace I want to see.
When I asked for
a civilized conversation,
I meant the quickest way
out of here, not all this.
Just try and rein it
in a bit, will you?
The narrative bones of this
place are just like Westworld.
Hospitality is the foreplay
to a new quest.
But in this world,
if you don't hear them out,
you've dishonored them...
Sometimes homicidally so.
Fine. We'll listen.
But then we go
and find my daughter.
And for the record,
it's not just the narrative
bones that are identical.
You've plagiarized
our stories, our identities...
It's not plagiarism.
It's supply and demand.
But if you're asking
can you trust Akane,
the real question is:
can you trust yourself?
You know who
I don't trust?
Him.
Say the word
and I'll skin him like a rabbit.
What's the matter with you?
He's not supposed to be here.
Who knows how seeing
your own doppel-bot
is gonna fuck with
your cognition?
Heightened aggression
and suspicion.
Feedback loops.
That.
Yet another reason to get out
of here tout fuckin' suite.
Our quest, I presume?
I recognize this one.
It's called
"Army of Blood."
Madam Akane,
a mere geisha,
has no choice
but to give up Sakura.
That's not
supposed to happen.
Looks like someone
had a choice after all.
Snow Lake is her cornerstone,
but it also has an access point
back to the tunnels.
It's our way out.
So you're not so useless
after all.
Did you have something
to do with this?
Both of you.
Look.
Oy!
Shit! Ninjas!
Oh, fucking hell!
Ohh!
Aah!
Ahh!
We got three.
The rest vanished with Sakura.
This is insane.
Ninjas never show up
in this story.
Oh, fuck!
The Shogun's army
never comes into town.
You three, with me.
I don't need
to know the language
to know a puckered asshole
of a man when I see one.
You and I spent
a lot of time here.
Watchin' the herd...
talkin' about
makin' a life together.
Someday.
I guess I just wanted to
see it one last time.
What if someday
was right now?
What are you talkin' about,
Teddy?
There's a fight comin',
Dolores.
And it's gonna be one
that's gonna change us
in ways we can't even
begin to predict.
And I'm still waking up to...
what I really am.
And if that means I'm free,
then we both are.
Free to walk away.
Now, you can't tell me that somewhere
out there in all that beauty...
there isn't a spot for us.
I ever tell you about the
year we almost lost the herd?
Bluetongue.
Quarantined the cows
that had it, but...
it kept spreading
all the same.
Daddy finally figured out that it
wasn't spreading from cow to cow,
it was the flies
that carried it.
He worried over it
all night.
How do you stop
a sickness like that?
One with wings.
Say it was you.
What would you do, Teddy?
I'd give 'em shelter.
House the weakest in a barn, out
of the air, away from the flies...
until it passed.
You're a kind man.
Daddy burned 'em.
The weak and the infected.
Made a pyre
that went on for days.
And it stank, but...
the flies hate smoke.
The herd lived.
I'll think about
what you said.
I'd like to take this moment to
appeal to your sense of survival.
If the Shogun
is awake enough
to play fast and loose with
his ninjas and his army,
then the odds of us surviving here have
dropped to approximately fuck-all.
But I say we ditch Akane
and make a run for Snow Lake.
Why should we all get killed
over a literal sex machine?
P-P-Present company excluded,
of course.
That machine's name
is Sakura.
You can't keep doing this to us,
giving us people to love and
then getting upset when we do.
- But it's just fucking code.
- You're wrong.
I'm coded to care about
nobody but myself,
and yet here I am, willing to
risk my life for someone else.
Well, so much for
your so-called daughter.
You want to go it alone,
be my guest.
But mention my daughter
one more time
and I will snap you
like a matchstick.
Like you did that ninja?
He took one look at you
and self-impaled.
How did you do that?
I don't know.
That was no voice command.
I think I'm finding
a new voice.
Our transportation is ready.
Goddamnit.
What have they done
to the place?
Is that...?
The fucking cavalry.
Great. So
much for our rescuers.
I'm gonna take
a fuckin' moment.
Don't stop
on my account.
If you've quite finished.
It's time to sell this ruse.
How many of them
are there?
Between the camp
and the town?
Hundreds.
Literally hundreds.
So Maeve's gonna
freeze all those assholes
and we're gonna make off
with that geisha?
We're gonna die.
Did you just
make that up right now?
Damn convincing.
Not to the daimyos.
It's like they had no idea
what I was saying.
Shit.
That's cortical fluid.
The Shogun's not awake.
He's broken.
No fucking wonder the
daimyos didn't hear you.
We've gone completely
off the rails here,
and this loon is driving
the fucking train.
Train'll be ready
by morning.
To go where?
Exactly where we thought.
I caught up with the men
who took your father.
Couldn't get him back,
but I got this one.
Took a while, but
he gave up their destination.
- Tell them.
- It's the Mesa.
We're goin' home, Teddy.
Load everything up
on the train.
We'll leave at first light.
Let's find a spot for the night.
What you asked today,
about walking away,
making it on our own.
Would you want me to say yes
even if I was only
going to disappoint you?
I'm not some stranger,
Dolores...
coming from outside,
looking for a pretty lie.
I've known you
my whole life.
Where we go...
we go eyes open...
together.
You're right.
Some things are
too precious to lose...
even to be free.
There's something
I need to show you.
For days now...
I've been questioning
my feelings for you.
How much is real,
how much is just some story
I was made to believe.
But tonight I know.
It was all true.
They built us
to perform for them
and for each other.
That's over.
I saw you tonight, Dolores.
And you saw me.
I did see you, Teddy.
These past few days...
I've seen you so clearly.
Ohh.
And I've seen
you're not gonna make it.
Wh... What is this,
Dolores?
This is what
I don't want you to become.
There's a swarm descending.
Just like the bluetongue
when I was a girl.
And if we're gonna survive...
some of us will have to burn.
Hold him.
Dolores! Dolores!
I wish there was
another way, Teddy.
But where we're about to go, it's
no place for a man like you.
I'm so sorry.
You sure you want this?
With changes this extreme,
without a full reset, it's...
I can't guarantee that
he'll hold together.
To grow...
we all need to suffer.
Arigato, Maeve.
Jesus.
What do we do now?
I told you
I found a new voice.
Now we use it.
Sync corrections by srjanapala