♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Who was it?
Somebody's about to
get their asses kicked!
When I find out who did this...
PC Principal is on the
warpath! Run for your lives!
Again?
Oh, Jesus. Now what?
Who was it, huh?
Somebody better fess up right now!
I'm gonna find out who did this!
Broflovski!
Was it you?
Was what me, sir?
I just saw a copy of
the school newspaper
in which a student
used the word "retarded"
to refer to our cafeteria lunch policy.
The word retarded does
not belong in our school!
Who is in charge of the school paper?
'Cause I'm about to
break their fucking legs!
Uh, he's in charge of the school paper.
You gonna break his legs, PC Principal?
All right, uh, I-I guess we
haven't formally met before.
Uh, the reason I need
to talk with you, Jason,
is because of a very important...
It's Jimmy, actually. My
name is Jimmy, PC Principal.
All right, Jim, thank you.
I want to talk to you today
about the use of the "R" word
in your school paper.
You see, the "R" word is very bad.
Says who?
Says me, all right?
And I know a thing or two about the
rights of people with disabilities.
When you use the "R" word to describe
the school's lunch policy,
it can hurt people's hearts.
Can you understand that at all?
That was an Op-Ed piece in the
paper written by a first grader
who found the school lunch
policy to be ridiculous,
and he thought "r-retarded" to
be the best word to describe it.
As the editor of the paper,
I didn't think it was right
to censor the words the student used.
Okay, well, from now on,
I'm gonna need to approve
the school paper before
you hand it out, okay?
No.
What'd you say?
You're new here, so you don't understand
how seriously I take my job
as editor of the school paper.
I don't allow ads, and
I don't allow anything
that might t-t-taint the truth
behind what people are thinking.
I don't want people
to be afraid of words
if it stops them from having a dialogue.
Look, I don't want to get angry, okay?
Why? Are you uncomfortable
around people with disabilities?
That's okay. Lots of people are.
No, I'm not! I am
very not uncomfortable.
All right, look... Unless
I can approve your paper,
it is not being distributed
on campus. You got that?
I can't hand out the
school paper in school?
Not unless it is approved
by me. Do you understand?
Yep. Got it.
Don't forget to read the school paper,
now delivered directly to your door!
Super School News!
What is that, bro?
S-S-S-S-Suck my
dick, PC Principal!
Who does this kid think
he is, challenging me?
I said one microaggression to him, okay?
One little microaggression,
but that doesn't mean
I have an unconscious bias
towards people with disabilities!
No way, bro. That's whack!
But why would a person
with a disability not see
that what I'm trying to do
is actually protect them?
Sometimes victims of
oppression are so marginalized
that they begin to sympathize
with their oppressors.
Yeah, bro.
You're right.
This kid just needs to be
shown he's being an Uncle Able.
I can also count on my PC
frat brothers to have my back.
Let's go, PC!
PC! Whoo!
Wow.
Wow, this is so great.
Have you ever read the
elementary-school newspaper, Linda?
There's no ads, no sponsored content,
no links to click on,
just news stories
about what's happening.
Did you know that the
police in ShiTpaTown
beat up homeless to clear them out?
Do you know how long its been
since I was able to just
sit back and read the news?
I got so used to getting
news off the Internet,
but I feel like I'm always
trying to chase the news, somehow.
It's like I'm in a black void
trying to reach the news story.
But then the next thing I know,
I'm reading and ad for GEICO,
so I click out of that and
try to read the news story,
but it's not a news
story, it's a slide show,
and I'm looking at the worst
celebrity plastic-surgery jobs ever.
So, of course, I want
to see the next slide
of plastic surgery gone
wrong, so I hit the arrow.
But then the arrow wasn't
the arrow for the next slide,
it was to take me for
an ad for face cream.
Aah!
I wanted to get a news story,
but I'm reading about face cream,
and I try to click out of it,
but the ad is following me.
It's... It's following
me all over the screen!
No!
So, I click on the "close" button,
but it wasn't a "close" button,
it was another slide show.
And I just want to know what's happening
in the Middle East, but instead,
I'm looking at the top 10
scariest movies of all time.
And that's not the arrow for the
next slide, it's for another ad!
Aah!
But this... This is just news.
And I don't get lost
in all the bullshit.
Linda.
Linda!
All right, Jim, I know you've
been trying to get your head around
some of the social issues
we discussed yesterday.
I'm sure you're feeling confused
and a little unsure of yourself.
I'm not confused at all,
actually, PC Principal.
Okay, well, no, you are confused...
I'm pretty sure you're the one
that's confused, but go ahead.
'Cause you don't grasp
the severity of this.
And that's why I've brought in
another young person with disabilities
to share his feelings.
Thanks for coming in
to talk to us, Nathan.
I like apples and bananas.
Me, too, bro. Me, too.
Nathan, could you
tell Jimmy how you feel
when people use the word "retarded?"
It hurts my feelings because I feel bad.
Are you serious right now?
You feel bad. Right.
You feel like that's
a no-no word, right?
That word makes my heart piss its pants.
Okay, wow. That's pretty heavy.
Pretty heavy, huh, Jim?
Do you want to ask him
what he means by that,
or are you just pandering
because you're uncomfortable
around disabled people?
I am not uncomfortable!
I simply care about a
horrible, outdated word
that is exclusive,
ignores individuality,
and equates intellectual
disability with being...
And it... and it...
Spot! I need a spotter!
Spot me! Somebody spot me, bro!
And it's... it's part of
a derogatory hate speech
which fosters isolation and loneliness,
and being part of a
voice to stop the "R" word
is not only right, but
extremely important!
I'm afraid of bears.
Hey, Nathan. Hold up.
What were you doing in there?
What do you mean, Jimmy? Are you mad?
Come on, Nathan.
You and I both know you use the
word retarded 400 times a day.
Oh, Jimmy.
So righteous, aren't you?
So blind to everything that's going on.
What are you talking about?
You really think all the
changes happening to this town
are just coincidence?
This goes so much deeper than
you can possibly imagine, Jim.
Everyone's about to learn the truth,
and then... there's a war coming.
A war, Jim.
And I'm just gonna make sure
I'm on the right side of it.
Come on, boys. Let's get back to class.
I like to smell trees!
An elementary school
newspaper is making big waves
as more and more people say
no to news on the Internet.
I read Super School News
'cause it don't try and fool me,
and its news reports aren't
paid for by ad companies.
We just feel like this is actual news,
and instead of clicking on
links, we're reading stories.
I had to get away from the ads.
I felt that the ads
were... evolving, somehow.
They started knowing what I
liked, what I was afraid of.
I tried ad blockers, but
it seemed like every time
I tried to block the ads,
they just got smarter.
I'm never going back
from Super School News.
The young editor of the paper claims
that since most people now watch
news reports on the Internet,
they're easily distracted
or even fooled by ads,
which are finding more
and more clever ways...
- Ooh, brutal celebrity mug shots.
- To disguise them...
Oh, it got me.
Ad got me, Sharon.
We now return live to the
2015 Presidential Debates.
Our next question is
for you, Mrs. Clinton.
Many voters believe that
Syrian refugees should not
be allowed into our country
for security reasons.
What do you think?
Keeping our country safe has
become more and more difficult,
but I believe there
are several things...
No! You shut the hell up!
You've got a dumpy butt and seven chins.
Syrian refugees are all terrorists!
I know that our government needs
to take a harder look at all...
Yeah, well, it's pretty
hard to look at you.
We can all agree on that.
She looks like a donkey
took a shit on her face.
Yeah, good one, Caitlyn.
See, what I know is
that there's only one way
to deal with Syrian
refugees, and that is...
Fuck them all to death!
Thank you!
That was hilarious when
you called her a pizza face.
It's like a Papa John's pimple party.
Oh, that was classic, Caitlyn.
You're the best running mate ever.
Hello, Mr. Garrison.
Oh, my God.
Principal Victoria?
Congratulations on the polls.
We need to talk.
Celebrate diversity! Whoo!
Let's go, PC!
All right, everyone. Listen up.
Tonight's a very special
night for the PCs.
We're honored to be throwing this
event for people with disabilities.
I, for one, am sick of
how these amazing kids
are marginalized in today's society,
but tonight is about
learning and healing.
So, let's get to it! PC!
Hey, guys. I'm Brad.
I'm PC Arizona State.
Nice to meet you, Brad. Where do you...
Uh, excuse me a second. Hello, ladies.
Thanks for coming to our event.
- Hi!
We're just tired of the way people
with disabilities get treated.
Can I get you some alcohol?
Yeah, you know, it just
bugs me when people refer
to persons with
disabilities as handicapped.
When I hear that word,
I want to fucking punch
them in the fucking face.
That's so cool of you. Wow.
Yeah, to be marginalizing
persons with disabilities
by asking them what their handicap is
is a microaggression no better
than asking a person of color
if they went to college.
Wow. You're really progressive.
No other way to be.
So, uh, listen, I think you're
really pretty and interesting,
and I'd kind of like
to take you upstairs
and totally crush your pussy.
Would that be acceptable to you?
Oh. Well, I-I guess it would.
No, I'm sorry. I need
affirmative consent.
I'll need you to say, "Yes,
you may take me upstairs
and crush my pussy at this time."
McKenzie, you got consent forms?
Oh, yeah. Right here, bro.
Rise and shine, guys.
If you scored last night,
I need your consent forms.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Whoa, Barker,
did you perform cunnilingus?
There's a different release form, bro.
Yeah, uh, s-sorry. It's right here.
Nice.
Bro!
Oh, dude! Bro!
What, bro?
Dude, I scored with this female,
and after consenting to
putting her mouth on my penis,
- she wanted me to walk her home.
- Yeah?
And when I got to her house,
she had me meet her
father, who is Filipino.
So, I asked him if
he could tell me about
the cultural and social dynamics
of being a Filipino American.
- Naturally.
- So, he said some stuff,
and then a newspaper
lands on his doorstep,
'cause I guess her dad subscribes
to this school newspaper,
and he picked it up, and I
saw the headline said this!
What the fuck is this, bro?
Bro, that little kid wrote
that our tolerant views
and fight for social justice is
just a way for us to crush puss!
But that's not true!
I know, bro! We're
being totally victimized!
That little fucking dude!
Hello. You're the boy responsible
for the South Park Super School News?
That's right.
We would like to give you $26 million.
Contracts and the first check.
We'd love to be in business with you.
What is this for?
I represent an
organization called GEICO:
It's an insurance company.
We think Super School
News would be a great way
for us to reach new customers.
Sorry, Charlie, but I don't
allow ads in my newspaper.
We've heard all about that,
so we thought you could just do some...
news stories about car insurance.
Just state the facts
because the truth is everyone
can save by switching to GEICO:
That's called "sponsored content."
I know the difference
between the news and ads.
You think I'm stupid?
Everyone's doing it, Jim.
You're sort of the last holdout.
$26 million just to
write some news stories
that get people thinking
about their insurance coverage?
S-S-S-Stick
it up your ass.
Hm.
Well, they said you'd be tough.
Do you really think you can stop ads?
Yes.
You can try to block
ads, but they get smarter.
The more we try to shut them
out, the more clever they get.
There's a war coming, kid,
and I'm gonna make sure
I'm on the right side of it.
Officer Barbrady?
Come with me if you want to live!
Come on! Come with me
if you want to live!
I'm serious!
Do you want to explain to
me what pussy crushing is?
What?
Your little meetings you go to at
night to discuss social justice...
It's just a way to
pick up on young women?
Sharon, most of the guys in my PC club
are right out of college, all right?
You know how college kids are.
Who wrote this?
I don't want you going
over there anymore.
I don't cheat on you, Sharon.
I'm happy.
Look at what's happened to our town.
We have ShiTpaTown,
boutique restaurants, and artisan shops.
We have a fucking Whole
Foods, and that was all me!
Diverse people are moving here.
Everyone's being aware of how they talk.
This is paradise, Sharon!
Is it?
All I know is that you've changed.
Ever since you joined this PC thing,
you just bully people
and wait for people to
say anything improper
so that you can jump down their throats
for whatever words he or she used.
"He or she" is an agenderphobic
microaggression, Sharon.
You are a bigot.
The average human can no
longer tell the difference
between the news and an ad.
You seem to have some mental ability
that allows you to know the difference.
Does this have to do with me calling
the school principal a pussy crusher?
The PC people are
simply being manipulated,
unwittingly setting the table
for the new enemy of humanity.
You mean ISIS or ninjas?
Something much worse.
Have you ever felt like
an ad had... intelligence?
That it somehow knew what you wanted
even before you knew you wanted it?
What if I were to tell you
that ads have become smarter than us
and now they're manipulating
everything we do?
I'd say that sounds pretty retarded.
It was our own fault.
Mankind became tired of ads,
so we kept inventing ways
to make things ad-free.
We even created ad blockers.
That's when the ads had to adapt.
They had to disguise themselves
as news in order to survive.
Sponsored content?
If you really can tell the difference,
then you could be the key
to saving our species, Jimmy.
We'd like to run a test on you.
Sponsored content.
Test 17-B. Ready.
Begin.
That's the news.
That's an ad.
That's the news. That's
an ad. That's an ad.
That's the ne... Oh, wait.
That's an ad for cat food. My bad.
Jesus Christ. He's off the charts.
Increase the intensity.
That's the news. That's an ad.
News. Ad. Ad. Ad.
Ad. Ad. News. News.
Ad. Ad. Slide show. Ad.
That's a perfect score.
You are a very special child, Jimmy.
I prefer "handicapped," actually.
We have another child
here who is special, too.
Do you know Leslie?
All right. That's good.
Everyone get inside.
Everything past here is safe space.
No reporters, no harassment.
We're gonna figure this shit out.
All I know is that I don't
speak up for minorities
so that I can crush pussy.
Me, neither, dude.
I want social justice, and
now I'm being made fun of.
Yeah, bro.
They're taking our incredibly
tolerant views and distorting them.
PC people are under
attack. That's what this is.
Hey, yeah.
Bro, we're the victims now.
Like, we're being marginalized.
Like, that makes us pretty cool.
Yeah, I'll bet now we
can get a lot more puss.
No, Topher! It's not
about puss, all right?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
We're being labeled as meat heads
who just want to crush puss
by an intolerant newspaper.
Yeah fuck that dude, bro.
Yeah, and, like, if
you're gonna belittle
and make fun of PC people like that,
then who's to say he won't do it to
other marginalized groups like us?
I mean, this kid could
be the next Hitler.
And if you guys could stop
Hitler, what would you do?
I'd rip that dude apart and then go home
and totally smash some puss, bro.
- Yeah!
- Hell, yeah!
- Hell, yeah, dude!
- No!
You look familiar. Don't
you go to my school?
Yes. Uh, I'm Jimmy,
Editor in Chief of Super School News.
I'm Leslie.
Nice to finally talk to you.
Did they bring you in and
give you a bunch of tests, too?
Yes, the did. Do you know who they are?
I think they're ex-newsmen...
You know, the men in suits who
used to be in charge of the news.
I thought I recognized them.
They told me I was special.
Are you special, too?
I prefer handicapped.
I like that.
Principal Victoria, if
everything you've said is true,
then why doesn't anyone know about it?
There are people who know,
but they have to stay very hidden.
I'm just having a hard
time swallowing all this.
And between me and this one over here,
we can swallow just about anything.
God, you're such an asshole.
Mr. Garrison, I wasn't fired.
I was replaced.
This goes much higher than anyone knows.
I came to this town
really thinking I
could make a difference.
I've been called a bigot towards
persons with disabilities.
I've been called a... pussy crusher
because of the behavior of a very
few individuals in my PC frat.
Jimmy Valmer is off
the school newspaper.
I want you to take over.
Oh, boy!
And I will be reviewing
your paper to make sure
nobody is ever attacked
the way I was again.
I think this will be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Jimmy almost made me lose confidence,
but I know who I am.
I know what I am.
Dude! Bro!
Oh, bro.
I went online to read a news story
about immigrants being
discriminated against.
- Yeah.
- Well, and so I clicked on the headline,
but it turned out to
be an ad for Reddi-wip,
so then I clicked on the "X"
button to make it go away,
but then it was a link to another ad,
and when I tried to cancel that,
another window came up, and it was this.
Dude, what the fuck bro?
What does this mean, dude?
Bro, what the fuck, bro?
Do you like our school, Jimmy?
Uh, yes, Leslie. I like
our school very much.
I like our school, too.
I like the kids who go there.
Uh-huh.
I'm starting to wonder
something about you, Leslie.
I'm starting to wonder about you.
I mean, you seem like a nice kid,
but don't you feel like
you could be happier?
- Holy shit.
- What?
Can you excuse me for a moment?
Okay.
Well, Jimmy? What do you think?
Does she know she's an ad?
He can spot them.
Does she kn-know she's an ad?
What the hell is going on, bro?
Bro?
Bro, what the hell is going on, bro?
If we're going back, remember...
We don't know who we can trust.
If they want to mess with my town,
I'll fuck every last one of them.
Let's do this!
Buckle up, buckaroos!