♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Morning, Randy.
Morning, Ger.
Just another day in paradise, huh?
Yeah, look at all these new restaurants
the Whole Foods has brought in.
Let's try out that one there.
Hi. Two of us, please.
Yeah, sorry, guys. We got
about a 30-minute wait.
Oh, uh, excuse me.
Yes, sir. Give me a second.
I'll have a table right away.
Whoa. What'd you say to him?
I just told him who I am.
Who are you?
I'm a Yelp reviewer.
I usually keep it on the down-low
so they don't kiss my ass too much.
Right over here, sir.
All right, guys, welcome to Vernacular.
Thanks.
Uh, did they mention to
you that I am a Yelper?
Yes, we've been alerted, sir.
Great.
Could you have them turn the
lights up a little, please?
Oh, look at it, Gerald... All
the new families moving in.
Our little town is all grown up.
Where's that other taco
plate? We need it now!
I'm a little overwhelmed.
I know, but we put everything into
moving here and starting this business,
and we have to be impressive.
David, you must help
your mama however you can.
We're not going back
to that miserable place.
I don't want to go back, either.
- Okay, done.
- Great!
We really have to impress this
customer. He's a local food critic.
Another one?
Mmm. Hmm. Mm-hmm.
Okay, here you go, amigo...
Another taco plate and the taquitos.
Oh, thank you.
And did I mention I am
a food critic for Yelp?
Yes, you mentioned that several times.
Okay, I just didn't want
you caught off guard.
I was thinking of giving
this place five stars.
Really?
Yeah, but I'm kind of teetering
on five stars or one star.
Oh, no, no. No one star,
please. What can we do to...
I mean, I could probably be
persuaded with some free desserts.
Let me get that for you.
Great. And could you
turn down the music a bit?
- This pagan shit hurts my ears.
- Of course.
Oh, hey. Hey, busboy.
Busboy! Busboy! Por favor!
- Busboy!
- My name is David.
- Excuse me?
- I said my name is David.
Uh, it's actually
pronounced "Day-vid," okay?
Well, I'm "Da-veed."
It's David, dude. Look it up.
What's going on?
Do not argue, son. We need him.
There you are... A few free desserts.
Oh, excuse me. More customers.
- Hi. Two of us for lunch, please.
- Yes. Right away.
Oh, and, uh, I just wanted to mention
that my wife and I are Yelp reviewers,
so, uh, your best table, please.
Oh, geez. You guys, too, huh?
Okay, um, I'll get you set
up right over here, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Hmm. This place seems nice.
I guess we'll see.
I guess we'll see, won't we?
Oh, God. Now everyone
thinks they're a food critic.
Did you get them? Did you get
them? Did you get them? Huh?
Here you go.
Whoa.
Crispy risotto bites from Olive Garden.
How do you do it, Eric?
I'm a restaurant critic,
Butters. I get whatever I want.
Geez.
So, the cafeteria's back that way,
and most of the classrooms
are this way down the...
Ew! What's the busboy doing here?
- David is new to our school.
- Oh, cool.
Are you gonna clean
the tables here, too?
How do you get to school? Do you
ride your tiny bicicleta? Huh?
Shut up.
Look, amigo, I'm sorry I only gave
your parents' restaurant two stars,
- but it could've been worse.
- Why'd you only give them two stars?
I'm sorry, but the food
totally messed my stomach up.
The morning after I ate
it, I went to the bathroom,
and my poop was all solid...
Like, no water at all.
It's not supposed to have water, you...
It was like this one, solid piece
that I had to push out my asshole.
It was like being raped from the inside.
Your parents' restaurant just
wasn't up to my standards, "Day-vid."
- "Da-veed."
- "Day-vid."
"Da-veed."
"Day-vid."Day-vid."
I can update this to a one-star
review in two seconds, dude.
Oh, God, I love being
a restaurant critic.
And yet, there was more.
For in this crisp time
when autumn begins to fade,
the chef brines chicken in habañero
and even adds habañero
powder to the crust.
But the heat is restrained.
You experience the fruity, delicious
flavor of this without any spicy pain.
I don't need anymore pain.
Hell, does anyone?
Gerald, we're going to the park.
You want to come along?
Sorry, honey. This review for
Applebee's has turned into a 50-pager.
Then I have a polish on Ruby Tuesday's.
Why don't you take a
break from Yelping, Gerald?
You seem a little overwhelmed.
I am overwhelmed.
Sometimes, I don't know
what I've gotten myself into.
But now everyone relies
on my Yelp reviews,
and I-I don't want to let anyone down.
Well, there's chicken in
the fridge if you get hungry.
Thanks, but I-I got Yelp a new
place in Shi Tpa Town tonight.
God, I'm so damn tired.
Okay, have fun.
Ha. "Fun," she says.
In finality, I would say my
experience at Applebee's was sublime
and my treatment near that
of a gladiator most decorated.
But the street parking
wasn't that great.
Two-and-a-half
stars.
Yes.
Come on, Liza. I'll
introduce you to the girls.
Well, aren't you eating lunch, Eric?
I am a food critic, Butters, okay?
I can't just eat cafeteria food.
Okay, here you are, sir!
There's orange peel chicken,
some city beef, and a city egg roll!
Are you joking?
Well, you are a little late.
Like, I don't know,
maybe only-one-star late.
Oh, no. No one star, please.
You Yelpers are killing me.
Okay, you no pay. You no pay. Please.
Sounds good. Now get
the fuck out of here.
Yes, yes!
I'll get the fuck out! Thank you!
Wow. Well, you're
pretty important, Eric.
He's not important at all.
Yeah, no.
No, no, you're right,
Kyle. I'm not important.
Oh, hey, David, I was just wondering.
Um, how do you get to school?
Do you ride your tiny bicicleta? Eh?
- Stop it.
- What?
I just want to hear him say,
"Si, me ride me tiny
bicicleta to school."
Si, me ride me tiny bicicleta to school.
That's awesome.
I'm gonna go out to recess.
Will you bus this for me, David? Thanks.
Ah, don't. Dude... Dude, don't.
Sir, it's midnight.
Go home. Get some sleep.
There's no time to sleep when
the city's counting on me.
More Yelp reviews, sir?
I had a bad experience at Red Lobster,
and if the people don't know
about it, they could, too.
Folks deserve to know
where to eat, Mitch.
But does anyone even thank you for it?
I don't need them to.
I know they need me, and that's enough.
God bless you, sir.
I know.
Welcome to Whistlin' Willy's.
Y'all enjoying your pizza?
Look here, my good man. We've
been waiting over 15 minutes
for you to sing "Happy
Birthday" to our son.
Unfortunately for you,
we are both restaurant
critics, and so is our son.
One star.
Excuse me! Emergency!
Over here! Emergency!
I would like a table inside the area
with all the little plastic balls, please.
And make it snappy. I am
a food critic for Yelp.
That does it! I've had enough!
All you Yelp reviewers
get the hell out of here!
I don't care what
happens to my business!
I ain't kissing your asses no more!
Go on.
Every Yelper, get the fuck out of here!
Careful now, Bill. You
don't want a one-star review.
You're not a food critic, Dennis!
You're a fucking mechanic!
Now get the fuck out! Go on!
All you Yelping sons of bitches
get the fuck out of here!
You're gonna regret
this, Whistlin' Willy.
You can't treat Yelpers this way.
You get the... Get the fuck out!
Ow!
Well, good for you.
You, too, you son of a bitch.
Whoa! Hey!
It's over! It's over!
You see paper? It's over!
Whistlin' Willy! He
stand up to the Yelpers!
We don't have to kiss
their asses anymore!
Look! Everybody doing the same!
It's over! It's over!
Hey, Skeeter, you hear the news?
It's a miracle.
It's a miracle!
What the fuck.
Uh, dude, somebody
spilled shit on the floor.
Hey, David, somebody
spilled something here.
Could you clean this up, por favor?
David?
Over here. There's
some shit on the floor.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's going on, man?
You haven't heard?
Nobody gives a fuck what
Yelp reviewers think anymore.
What are you talking about?
I'm the most influential
critic in this town.
Okay, David, forget the
spill. Just give me one little,
"My name is David. Me ride
me bicicleta to school."
My name is "Da-veed."
Ha!
Okay, I'm... I'm updating my review.
I'm about to do it.
You better say, "I ride
me bicicleta to school!"
One star.
No... no stars?
No stars?
You can't just treat
me like I'm nothing.
I still know I'm worth something.
Come on, guys.
Oh, yeah. Y-you guys stay at school.
That's cool. Y-you guys stay here.
Oh, hey, Eric.
It's all over, Butters.
Everything I've worked
so hard to achieve.
All these hack wannabe food critics
have made my profession a joke.
Aw, I'm sorry, bud.
All these people trying to be like me,
and they don't even write about
poop consistency the next day.
Well, Eric, you should be proud
that people want to be like you.
I mean, you really started something.
I guess.
Well if these people look up to you,
maybe... maybe you can sort
of set the record straight
and show them the way
it's supposed to be done.
You're right, Butters.
Maybe I can actually use
all these people somehow
to make real food
critics respected again.
Harrison Yates, what's gotten into you?
That's it, Maggie. I'm hanging it up.
If people are gonna be trying
all the new restaurants in town,
they'll have to do
it without my reviews.
What are you talking about?
You said that protecting people
from bad dining experiences
was what kept you going.
The restaurants put up
signs saying I can't come in.
I don't know why they singled me out,
but it's like people don't need me.
Well, I'll be damned.
What is it?
Somebody's put a note in the mailbox
asking me to come and talk to them.
They do need me.
I need to get going.
You want me to come along?
No. They're just asking for me.
I guess maybe I do
have a town to protect.
Oh, are you having a party, sweetheart?
Not a party, mom.
I've invited all the poser
food critics over for a meeting.
Oh, how fun.
It's not fun. It's serious.
These people think
they can do what I do,
but they need to be made
to understand the reality.
When the Yelpers get here,
I need you to get lost, okay?
Okay, that's them, that's
them. Go! Get lost, mom!
Hello! Hi!
My name is...
I'm here for the meeting.
Is this the right place?
Fuck.
Mom!
I'm going, honey.
Mom, there's like a billion people here!
Oh, yes, sweetie. I think quite
a few people are Yelp reviewers.
Oh, this many people have nothing
better to do than write reviews on Yelp?
I guess so, honey. Do
you need more lemonade?
Mom, there's a fucking
billion people here.
Uh, thank you all for coming.
My name is Eric, and as you know,
us Yelpers are being scrutinized.
Can't you speak a little louder?
Yes, us Yelp critics
are being scrutinized!
That's right! Yeah!
Now, you see the problem is that
when there's too many reviewers,
people no longer know who
is the real food critic.
It's great that you
all want to be critics,
but we all know who the real
food analyst of the town is.
That's right!
Yeah!
Ha. Oh, thanks.
Okay, so, as long as
there is one clear leader,
then the rest of you can just follow.
And with this many people
all following one captain,
we can fight to get our power back!
Poweeeer back!
So now rise up, and
fight for your leader!
Fight together, and show the restaurants
that our food critic does matter!
Yeah, let's go!
All right, follow me!
This way, everyone!
Another local business is
closing its doors tonight
after being taken
down by Yelp reviewers.
Whistlin' Willy's, a
child favorite in town,
was destroyed and its
owner stripped and beheaded.
The following video is graphic.
No, please! No, no, no, no, no!
Aww!
We all loved Whistlin' Willy's.
It didn't do well with Yelpers.
You assholes destroyed
the best place in town
because they wouldn't kiss your asses!
Oh, come on, admit it. The food sucked.
Nobody went for the fucking food!
Look, I'm sorry guys,
but Whistlin' Willy failed
to recognize the influence
someone like me has on their business.
Now I just have one
question for you, David.
Do you ride
your teeny, tiny bicicleta to school?
Sí. Me ride mi teeny
bicicleta to school.
You're done.
Yeah, I'm done!
I'm now the leader of
thousands of people!
They all hang on my every word,
and I'm gonna use my power to finally
get what this town really needs.
I found the waitstaff
at Red Lobster to be rude
and barely even acknowledging who I was
or what I meant to this city.
Gerald, I'm taking Ike to clown
school. You care to join us?
I can't, honey.
I'm now the leader of
thousands of people.
They all hang on my every word.
And I'm going to use my power
to finally get what
this town really needs.
For the fifth day in a row,
historic Shi Tpa Town is
under siege by Yelp reviewers.
The restaurants are still
refusing to be intimidated,
and the Yelp reviewers are...
And the Yelp reviewers are
preparing for all-out war.
The angry Yelp reviewers are
demanding special treatment
at all city restaurants.
They claim that as local food critics,
they deserve respect and that
all who oppose them will suffer.
The online restaurant
critics are getting ready
to bring businesses to their knees,
and some are already
closing their doors.
One local restaurant
worker actually called out
the Yelp critics' leader!
I guess you win, huh, big shot?
If you really are any
kind of important anybody,
then get your bullshit food-critic ass
to the south of town and face me,
because you aren't a food
critic, and you aren't important!
And unless you're chicken,
I'll see you south of town.
- Where you going, sir?
- You heard him.
Little Mexican kid called me out.
He wants to fight me, that's fine.
You need backup, sir?
No. He's just calling me out.
God bless you, sir...
I know!
David! Dude, wait!
Dude, you don't wanna do this.
You don't know what
Cartman's capable of.
Where I come from, we
settle things with our fists.
But this isn't Mexico.
I'm not from Mexico, dude!
I'm from Idaho!
I'm gonna show this prick
how we do things in Boise.
Oh, hello, David!
All right, you've got your army.
You've got your followers.
If you're such a great leader,
then just tell the city
what you want, fat ass!
Don't call me fat, son.
I'm doing this because they've...
What I want is to be able to lead these fine
people with the respect and the dignity...
I didn't ask to be the
leader. I was appointed!
You see, I'm extremely important to
this town, and I'm not going to be...
My journey as this town's food...
You've made these people feel unwanted,
and now they look to me for answers.
Now here I stand, vulnerable, afraid,
and yet willing to do
what the people of this...
And so we said to hell with it!
And we took the challenge to
go from the town's food critics
to the town's spiritual leaders.
What do we want?
People would say, "Oh,
you're just a food blogger.
You're just a tiny voice in the crowd."
Well, now my voice is
heard, and I will...
Wanted special privileges,
but these people think
I should have them.
Right, guys?
Maybe I don't deserve special treatment,
but how else can I be the
elite food critic they want?
Every person here thinks
this is about them.
I think I know what to do.
Yeah. Me, too.
And for all your service
to this community,
we want to once and for all declare you
our most elite food critic.
To distinguish you, we present
to you the golden badge.
Wearing this badge means you will always
get the special treatment that you deserve.
Thank you, Mayor.
It's a big responsibility,
but I suppose I have to accept.
I will do my best to serve this town.
We know you will.
Okay, bring in the next one.
Mr. Davis, you have
proven yourself a leader.
And for all your service
to this community,
we want to once and for all declare you
our most elite food critic.
To distinguish you, we
present the golden badge.
Wow!
Wearing this badge
means you will always get
the special treatment you deserve.
All right, we got all the restaurants
to agree to let the Yelpers in
and to make them feel special.
How did you do it, son?
Ah, yes. The steak, please.
I'm the, uh, Yelp elite.
All right, we got a Yelper.
Give it that special attention.
You got it!
♪ So you're one of
Yelper's special blessed ♪
♪ You demand a
restaurant's very best ♪
♪ Well, they're gonna
treat you special ♪
♪ I'm telling you, chum ♪
♪ Now get yourself ready
for some boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ That's called a Yelper special! ♪
♪ Say, what's that
on your pretzel? ♪
♪ Your online critiques
are real useful to some ♪
♪ Now have a good time
eating boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Someone farted on your salad ♪
♪ But your decor
critiques are valid ♪
♪ You think you're special,
like you're A number one ♪
♪ Well, there's a whole lot of
special in boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ How about some feces
with your flounder? ♪
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ You like that queefy
quarter-pounder? ♪
What's that spice that
feels tangy on my tongue?
Oh, that's a yuzu pepper...
along with some boogers and cum.
Here you are, sir.
Thank you, David. That's good service.
I will bring you food
every day, my friend.
Hmm, is that a jalapeño cream sauce?
Yes. My father made it just for you.
Hmm. It's tart, but savory.
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Bein' a food critic's easy! ♪
♪ Oh, you feel a little queasy? ♪
♪ Do you need a diagnosis?
Well, the doctor's got one ♪
Your stomach seems to be
filled with boogers and cum.
♪ Boogers and cum! ♪
♪ Piss in your potatoes! ♪
♪ Some guy shit on your tomatoes! ♪
♪ All right, fancy food
critic, looks like you've won ♪
♪ Now please enjoy all the ♪
♪ Bo-o-o-o-gers ♪
♪ and cuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuum! ♪