♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample Parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
So, these guys made fun of your
weight and made you feel ashamed?
Yes, I was just trying to do my job
as a food critic, and
they all ganged up on me
and said I was fat.
All right, why don't you
take me back to what happened.
I was in the locker room...
And I was in my underwear,
and these kids walked by.
Then I looked in the mirror, and
I thought I looked kind of ripped,
and so I asked one of the kids if he
would take a picture of m-me, and he did.
And I looked at the picture,
and I looked pretty ripped,
so later at home, I put the
picture up on my Yelp account,
And I typed in, "Don't I look ripped?"
And I thought people
would be stoked on me.
Then this morning, I saw
the comments on Twitter,
and some people c-called me
names and said I wasn't ripped,
and they said I was fat,
and I didn't have muscles.
Internet m-m-made
fu-fun of me and...
Well, Eric, maybe you shouldn't
have put a picture of you
in your underwear up on social media...
Hey! You got a fucking problem, Mackey?
N-no, P.C. Principal!
Because body shaming is fucking serious,
and I'm not gonna allow
that shit in my school!
Nobody should have to
feel that kind of shame.
Okay, sir, looks like
your total is $37.83.
All right.
Okay, and would you like
to add a dollar donation
to help hungry kids around the world?
Oh, uh, no, th-that's okay.
- Sorry?
- I'm... I'm good.
I'm sorry, you don't want to
give the dollar to hungry kids?
- Not today, thank you.
- Okay, no problem.
Window's gonna come up and ask
if you're helping the hungry kids.
- Just hit "No, I'm not."
- Oh, come on.
Try hitting it again.
It's the box below the one that says,
"Sure, I'd love to help however I can."
Ah, darn thing. Sorry.
Most people give the dollar.
I can do this manually.
Look, I give money to
charity a lot, okay?
Oh, sure you do.
I do! I just don't want to
every time I shop for food.
That's completely understandable.
"Have customer speak
on the"... Oh, okay.
If you can just speak into
the voice decoder and say,
"I'm not giving anything
to the hungry kids."
I'm not giving anything
to the hungry kids.
Okay, that's got it.
So, with the ice cream,
the vodka, pizza pockets,
and nothing for hungry
kids, that's $37.83.
Oh, don't forget your change.
Look, if I gave money every time I
went grocery shopping, I would be...
Thanks for shopping, sir. Next, please.
Dick.
Come on in, Kyle. Have
a seat right there.
You probably heard that Eric here has
been dealing with some body shaming.
Uh-huh.
Well, Eric and I have been talking,
and we've decided it's probably best
for him to get off of social media.
Yeah, probably.
So, what we're looking
for is a student volunteer.
Somebody who can put the things Eric
wants up on the Internet for him,
and also filter through all the comments
and make it more of a safe space for him.
Wait, what?
I said you were perfect
because you're really good
at getting all your
schoolwork done on time,
s-s-so you'd probably
do a really good job.
You want me to run Cartman's
Twitter and Yelp account
and only give him the good comments?
- That's right.
- No.
Kyle, you know what
body shaming is, right?
How much it can hurt someone's life?
All you have to do is
check out all the comments,
type out just the positive ones,
and give that to Eric on paper.
If he doesn't like what
people say on Twitter,
he can get off.
Okay, Kyle, well maybe you'd
like two weeks detention instead.
Give me... Give me detention.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah, I'll take the detention.
That's two weeks detention for
you, bud. I'll see you at 4:00.
And when we said someone
should probably help Eric
by filtering out any negative comments,
he mentioned you by name.
Is this a joke?
I'm not a joke!
Nothing funny about this, Testaberger.
- This is a big problem in our country.
- I'm not doing it.
And that's two weeks detention
for you. Congratulations.
And so any comments
that seem inappropriate
or hurtful in any
way, you need to delete
and not include in your
daily report to Eric.
I wanted someone smart and hardworking!
- Do I gotta?
- You want detention?
Well, if I get detention,
I'll get grounded.
Then you start today.
Butters, it's your job to make
sure Eric has a safe space.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Oh, no, my... my fault.
Isn't it great having a Whole Foods?
This is where I come
for lunch every day.
Got to eat healthy to stay fit.
Oh, shit. It's that guy.
And how are you today, sir?
Great.
Uh, listen, before you ring me up,
I just want to let you know
I'm not gonna be giving
extra money to charity,
so can we... can we just skip that part?
Oh, no problem, sir.
They've updated the system so
it's a lot more streamlined now.
Find everything you need today?
Yeah, thanks.
There we go, and that's...
Okay, and would you like to give
a dollar to hungry kids today?
- No, I said no before.
- Oh, that's right.
Okay, there's a picture
of a little hungry boy.
Will you just press on his belly?
Owww! Owwwww!
Okay, that's got it.
So, with the no help for
hungry kids, that's $18.87.
Out of $20...
Your change is right there.
Just pull out the sandwich
out of the little girl's mouth.
This is not streamlined.
It's just the new change dispenser, sir.
I... I-I can't...
Yeah, she's a hungry
one. You got to pull hard.
The sandwich isn't coming out.
Try putting your foot on her face.
Ugh.
Have a nice day, sir!
I was having a nice day.
Eric, hold up.
There you are. You have
my social-media comments?
Yeah. Yeah, right here.
I just finished this morning.
Mm-hmm. Oh, that's nice. Oh, great.
This is all the Twitter comments?
Yeah, and people commenting
on your Yelp page starts here.
Okay, nice. Oh ni...
Oh, very enthusiastic. This is so great!
Oh, Kyle!
You thought me having
someone edit my social media
would make me look stupid?
You should see all the
comments I'm getting.
People are actually
really stoked on me now.
It's a pretty brutal job sifting
through all that darkness.
All right, everyone, listen up.
In order to better understand the
negative affects of body shaming we have...
Hey, Leslie, put a fucking sock in it!
We have a guest speaker today
who will challenge our
perceptions of physical beauty.
So, please welcome action
star and hero Steven Seagal.
You got a problem with me?
I'm your worst nightmare.
I have no fear of death.
More important, I don't fear life.
I'm a big action-movie star,
and people are pretty stoked on me.
And then I put a picture of
myself up on the Internet,
and I had my shirt off, and I said,
"Do you think I'm ripped?"
and some people commented
saying I didn't look
ripped, that I was fat,
and they called me Steven SeBoomBoom,
and so then I put another
picture on the Internet,
and I thought people
would be stoked on me,
but they said I looked like a fat turd,
and they said I wasn't buff.
Body shaming isn't cool,
And if p-people shame
you on the Internet,
You have to make sure that you stay...
You stay strong,
And tell everyone you're proud
of how you look. Like this.
♪ What you find, ahh ♪
♪ What you feel now ♪
Hey, Seagal.
Listen, that was a really
amazing talk you gave to the kids.
Thank you.
I can see that you're
in a lot of pain, bro.
I've got someone who I think can help.
So, I want you to do for Mr. Seagal
The same thing that you're
doing for Eric Cartman.
But P.C. Principal, I
really don't have time.
This man took the time
to come to your school
And help spread body-shaming awareness!
I think you can give him
a little of your time!
Yes, sir.
Find everything you needed today?
Yes.
Okay, looks like your
total comes to $37.98.
Would you like to give a
dollar to help feed hungry kids?
Yes, I would like to give a dollar.
You want to give a dollar?
Yes, I will.
Oh, wow! Okay!
So, that's $10 for the beer,
$4.20 in chocolate-covered peanuts,
$26 in filet mignons,
And $1 for hungry kids around the world.
On amount of donation, it
will say $10, $20, or $50.
Can you just press the $1 box?
Attention shoppers!
Somebody just joined
the one-dollar club!
Giving one whole dollar to
help feed hungry children!
Here's your T-shirt!
Oh, won't the kids be thrilled
when they get their piece
of that big, impressive dollar!
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellooow ♪
♪ He ended world hunger ♪
Oh God, that's terrible. Jesus.
Yeah, no, I'm telling you, Tracy,
It's the greatest thing ever.
I'm getting all my Twitter and
Instagram comments on paper,
And the nasty mean stuff
all gets edited out.
Oh, my God. Ugh.
Yeah! And the coolest thing?
Ever since I started using this service,
All my followers are actually
way more stoked on me!
So cool, right?
Butters!
What the hell is this?
The last report you gave
me has a comment that says,
"This picture of you
burned my eyes, fatso."
I'm sorry, Eric. I-I guess
it slipped through the cracks.
I'm overloaded with all the new people.
What new people?
I've got Demi Lovato
to take care of now,
And Lena Dunham just put
a picture of her asshole
On Twitter and wants only
the positive comments.
Dude, fuck Demi Lovato.
She's fucking hot.
She's not being fat shamed.
Am so! But I don't care.
People just have to accept
my body the way it is.
Butters, I want this fixed
by tonight. You got that?
Okay, Eric.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
This is a place where hope is scarce.
These people are hungry.
Little Jo Jo here might not eat today.
But does that mean
it's okay for cashiers
To ask us for money while
we're in the checkout line?
It isn't right, and it isn't fair.
Just 2 dollars a day adds up
to 62 goddamn dollars a month
If you go to Whole
Foods as much as I do.
Nobody should have to feel
the shame, the humiliation,
Of being asked to add money
onto their grocery bill.
Help now. Let's make grocery
stores a safe space for all.
Together, we can make a difference.
Because charity shaming hurts everyone.
You know, if there's one
thing I really respect,
It's plus-sized models
who challenge the idea
Of what makes a woman beautiful.
These ladies are gonna be
part of a big ad campaign
For plus-sized lingerie,
and we want make sure
They're protected from
any harassing comments.
Do I have to, sir?
Hey, they're gonna be
putting themselves out there,
And all I'm asking you to do
is go through their social media
And delete the two or three
comments that are mean.
P.C. Principal, I don't
think you quite realize
How much negative stuff
I have to sift through.
I know it's a lot, but
I just really need you
To help these plus-sized models.
And Vin Diesel.
Vin Diesel, too?
Look, bro, You've done an
amazing job with Eric Cartman.
You have really turned his life around,
And other people deserve
to be as happy as he is.
♪ Everyone likes me
and thinks I'm great ♪
♪ In my safe spaaace ♪
♪ My safe space ♪
♪ People don't judge me
and haters don't hate ♪
♪ In my safe space ♪
♪ Your safe space ♪
♪ Bully-proof windows,
troll-safe doors ♪
♪ Nothing but kindness in here ♪
♪ You might call me a pussy ♪
♪ But I won't hear
you in my safe space ♪
♪ My safe space ♪
♪ Bully-proof windows ♪
♪ If you do not like
me, you are not allowed ♪
♪ In my safe space ♪
♪ My safe space ♪
♪ Look and you will see
there's a very select crowd ♪
♪ In your safe space ♪
♪ My safe space ♪
♪ People that support
me mixed in with ♪
♪ More people that support
me and say nice things ♪
♪ Rainbows all around me ♪
♪ There is no shame
in my safe space ♪
♪ My safe space ♪
♪ Bully-proof windows ♪
♪ I am going to tear
down your safe space ♪
♪ Brick by brick, I
shall smash it with glee ♪
What? Who is that?
♪ You cannot stop me
from getting inside ♪
♪ I am cold and I am
hard and my name... ♪
♪ Is Reality ♪
Oh, no, not Reality! Somebody stop him!
I'll take care of him, Demi!
Pew, pew! Pew, pew, pew!
♪ You can't ruin
our lives, Reality ♪
♪ Our safe space will keep you out ♪
Drat!
♪ We can face almost anything ♪
♪ But Reality, we can do without ♪
Noooo!
♪ Bully-proof windows ♪
♪ Troll-safe doors ♪
♪ My safe spaaaaaace ♪
That was nice.
All right, thanks! Have a great day.
Good afternoon, sir.
Oh, hello.
You might know Steven Seagal.
You want to play with me?
And this is Vin Diesel.
Oh, hello, gentlemen!
It'd be... a really bad idea for
you to charity shame me today.
These guys are here to
protect my safe space.
That's great!
♪ This little piggy went to market ♪
♪ This little piggy stayed home ♪
♪ This little piggy was
in "Fast and the Furious" ♪
♪ And this little piggy
goes direct to cable ♪
And this little piggy just bought
$53 in beer and frozen pizzas!
Would you like to make a dollar
donation to hungry kids today?
♪ Amazing grace ♪
Look around you. What do you see?
People who are slim, skinny.
But not everyone can have
nice bodies like them.
Just imagine it... Putting
your pictures up on Twitter
Just to have some people write
comments about your weight.
It happens. All too often.
But it doesn't stop there.
People also can be shamed for
other traits viewed as negative.
Mike here was shamed for
not being a good recycler.
And so, together, we have
created "Shameless America."
So no one is ever labeled...
Tubby.
Bad with tools.
Dyke.
Butter, butter dirty line-cutter.
Let's work together to create
a completely shameless America.
Because shaming hurts everyone.
"Hey, Demi Lovato, I
bet your vagina has a"...
Oh... oh, God...
Oh, that's ter... horrible!
Geez. Delete.
Delete that, too.
"I'd like to stick my wiener in
those fat rolls of"... Oh God!
Delete. "You aren't
fat, but my dick is."
Oh, God.
Ha ha! Aaaah!
So, you're the one
trying to destroy me, eh?
What?
You little shit! Keep me out, will you?
I don't know you, sir!
You can't stop me!
I'm going to kill you!
Butters! What are you doing!
W-well, the man! The
man is gonna get me!
And some chocolate-covered almonds...
Vanderpump sangria mix...
Yeah, I'm... I'm a little tired
because I'm actually hosting a
huge fundraiser for my
charity organization.
That I'm sort of the head of.
That's great, sir.
Ice-cream sandwiches...
Yeah, we're gonna raise a lot of money.
Celebrities are coming.
Demi Lovato has given
$100,000 for the event.
Wonderful. Rotisserie chicken...
Oh yep, got to have
that Frank's Hot Sauce.
I just thought, you
know, a fundraiser dinner
Was sort of the appropriate
place to ask for donations.
That's great, sir.
Okay, your total's $37.85.
And would you like to give a dollar
to help put a hamster through college?
What? Did you not
hear anything I said?
I'm... I'm doing all this stuff!
Not a problem, sir.
If you could just press the "No" button,
And tell the little hamster
he's not going to college.
Just look him right in the eye, sir,
And say, "Not today, buddy."
Actually, my big fundraising gala
Is helping put hamsters
through college, too.
Oh, really? Wow!
Did you hear that,
Banjo? You've got support!
Well you have a nice day sir,
And thank you so much
for being so generous.
You're welcome.
Hey Kyle, you want to see
What people on the Internet
said about my dick pic?
Everyone's pretty stoked on it.
There's more than two
people on the Internet!
The man! The man, the
man, the man, the man!
The man! He's gonna get me!
He follows me everywhere!
Did you see the man?
Butters, what are you doing?
He's gonna get me!
Dude, Butters, you're seeing things!
Sifting through all the horrible stuff
People say on the Internet
is making you lose it.
The world is darkness!
The man is coming!
Dude, Butters!
And what color is the little
ball the kittens are playing with?
Run for your lives, you little...
The man is coming!
Butters, listen to my voice.
The man is gonna get me if I don't stop.
Then stop, dude.
Butters, all this isn't worth it.
Just take the detention, dude.
Yaaaah!
All right, everyone, thanks for coming
To help raise money to stop shaming
and put hamsters through college.
What'd he say?
And now a woman who knows
about shaming firsthand,
Supermodel Gigi Hadid.
All right, everyone enjoying themselves?
How's that filet mignon?
Good! Really nice! Great!
You know, we're all here for
a really important reason.
Because everyone should have
a safe space wherever they go...
- Randy! Randy, we've got a problem.
- What?
Reality's here. He's
trying to crash the party.
Reality? Who let him in? Shit!
Our hope is that with your donation...
Ooh, nice wine, huh?
What do you think of that?
You know what I think
of your pretty flowers?
There you go! How do you like that?
All right, buddy, let's go.
I shit on all of you!
Seagal!
Fuck you fuck you fuck
you fuck you fuck you!
Give me that, you stupid bitch.
What a lovely charity event.
I suppose you're all feeling
Pretty good about yourselves, hmmm?
What have you done?
You've raised $300 by spending $500,000
On Filet Mignon and crystal glasses.
Look at you. Vin Dipshit
You say fat shaming is wrong,
So in response you show off your abs.
You're the one fat shaming, idiot!
What's the matter with you people?
You're sad that people are mean?
Well, I'm sorry, the world isn't
one big liberal-arts college campus!
We eat too much. We take our
spoiled lives for granted.
Feel a little bad about it sometimes.
No, you want to put all
your shit up on the Internet
And have every single
person say, "Hooray for you!"
Fuck you. You're all pricks.
And I've got news for you.
While you've been sitting
here trying to feel good,
the little boy who sucked all
your shit is about to die from it!
What?
Oh, my God.
What have we done?
Jesus. I-I didn't even think...
I guess... I asked too much of one kid.
Listen, everybody...
I think there's a way to try
and make this right for everyone.
To date, Shameless America
has raised over $40,000.
With that money, we are
putting more and more iPads
Into these people's hands.
With iPads, these people can
finally help more Americans
Get rid of negativity
on their social media.
Oh, thanks, Jo Jo.
I'm shame-free now, and you can be too.
For just $1 a day, one of
these beautiful children
Will protect you from trolls and
make your Internet a safe space.
We won't rest until America
is completely shameless.
The world can be brutal.
But Shameless America is
going to continue to take steps
to make sure everyone
has a safe space forever.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Uh-huh.