♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Attention all units in the
vicinity of South Park Elementary.
We have a code red.
Principal calling
for help during school assembly.
All officers needed at once.
The school?
Oh, geez Louise!
We need to get to the gym.
Half go this way, half
go around the side.
Barbrady, you go around back.
On 3.
1... 2...
There she is, officers, right there.
I told you to stop chatting with
your friends, didn't I, Leslie?
You see, officers,
apparently, Leslie thinks
That talking to her
friends is more important
Than learning about diversity
in third-world countries.
It's that one.
That's her, right there. You
remove her from my school.
Aah! Nobody move! What's happening?
- Get her out of here!
- Oh, they've got me!
Aah!
This town is outraged, Officer Barbrady.
People are tired of the police not
being held accountable for their actions.
Mayor, I didn't know if there
was a gunman or a bomb...
You shot an unarmed
6-year-old Latino child.
I'm sorry.
You are fired.
No, Mayor, please.
This is all I know.
I used to be the only policeman
in this town, remember?
Bob, I-I used to chase away
the sixth graders for you.
You're from another time, Barbrady,
And the last thing that needs to go.
Your gun and your badge.
And your sunglasses.
No. Please. Not my sunglasses.
You're done, Barbrady.
The town doesn't want you here.
Where should I go?
You should have thought of
that before you shot a Mexican.
Latino American.
Latino American. Shit.
You should go away.
You don't belong anywhere in a
town as progressive as this one.
Hey, quiet down over
there. I'm trying to sleep.
God damn it. You people
all get out of here!
What makes you in charge?
'Cause this is my fucking house!
Hey, beat it, man, or
I'll make you my bitch!
Aah!
Yeah, we've got a bunch
of drug-addict vagrants
Trespassing in our yard,
and we need assistance.
Oh, is that so?
Well, we'd like to come help you,
But we don't want to get fired.
What are you talking about?
There's homeless people here,
and they're scaring my kids.
You need to come do
something about this.
I see.
And are any of these homeless
people of a minority persuasion?
Why does that matter?
Oh, it matters.
See, used to be we could beat
up minorities, and nobody cared.
It's the reason a lot
of us joined the force.
Hey, Mitch, you want to go down
and arrest some homeless people,
But not be able to
beat up any minorities?
No, thank you.
Yeah, no, I think we're good.
In fact, we're thinking of maybe turning
the whole department into a hula school.
What do you think?
God damn it!
What are they doing?
They're not coming!
But they have to!
Karen brought in one of their
syringes, for Christ's sake!
Well, it's just too bad.
The cops won't come,
So there's nobody to
scare the homeless away.
Hey, sweetheart.
I've, uh... I've been
let go from the force.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, old girl.
Might be a little tough
to afford your medication,
but I'll find a way.
You know me.
I like to help.
I like to be needed.
You guys! Oh, my God, you guys!
You guys, they're gay!
They're totally gay.
- Who?
- Kenny and Token.
What?
Kenny and Token, dude. They're
so gay. Butters told me.
- You're lying.
- No, dude.
In those old, abandoned
buildings around Kenny's house,
Kenny and Token turned it
into a big ninja clubhouse,
And they dress up and play ninja
in it, trying to scare people away.
How is that gay?
It's the gayest thing ever, dude!
Ninjas are fucking dumb!
Dude, come on! We got to go see this!
Over this way!
Wah! Wah, wah!
Hoo-ah, wah, wah!
We will defend our ninja honor.
Wo-chew,
wo-chew!
Intruders! Defend the base!
Hey, guys, did you come
to see our ninja fortress?
Oh, my God.
They're so gay, you guys.
You and Kenny built all this?
Yeah, with Clyde and David, too.
You guys should come and check it out.
Uh, no. We're good, thanks.
Oh, my God, dude. It's a sausage party.
It's pretty cool, dude.
People are really scared of us.
Yeah, I'm sure they are.
Hey, excuse me, man.
Do you know where...
Aah! Aahhhh!
Oh, my God!
Go, go, go!
That's pretty cool.
Well, the way I heard it was
that the girl in the school
Wasn't even doing anything,
just talking too loud,
And someone ends up getting shot.
Hey! What do you want?
It's okay. I'm off-duty.
Just came for a nice Pinot.
Yeah? Well, go somewhere else, copper.
ShiTpaTown is for people
who care about each other.
We don't take kindly to folks
who impose their authority
on the underprivileged.
Now, look, not all cops are
racist, trigger-happy assholes.
Really?
I'll bet you don't even know
what "farm-to-table" means.
Yeah! All right!
Wow.
We've only had a Whole
Foods for a month,
And already, we don't need cops.
So cool.
It is a great honor to see
that you all want to be ninjas.
Joining our club is very serious.
You must promise to
uphold the warrior's code.
Totally, dude. Ninjas are sweet.
Together, we must strive to
make our fortress super badass
And keep all intruders out.
To that end, let us
proceed to our training.
Dude, can I talk to you for a minute?
Listen, I don't think we should
let Kyle be a ninja, okay?
He said ninjas were gay.
He's probably gonna try
to turn it around on me,
But that's 'cause
Kyle knows I heard him.
You're talking to Kyle right now.
Yeah, cool.
It's me... Butters.
You're the one who said ninjas were gay.
Why do you want to make this a problem?
I'm... I'm just Butters, man. I
have problems with lots of things.
Hey, Eric, you want to
try sparring with me?
Yes I do, Butters.
Ooh! Ow!
Intruders!
Yeah, it's right up here.
We can shoot up in these
abandoned buildings.
Aah! Aah! Aah. Aah!
The town of South Park is
holding a large protest tonight
Outside of their police department.
The townspeople say the protest
is meant to begin a dialogue
About the relationship
between law enforcement
And the citizens they
are supposed to protect.
♪ Fuck the police ♪
♪ Comin' straight
from the underground ♪
♪ A young nigga got it
bad 'cause I'm Brown ♪
♪ And not the other
color, so police think ♪
♪ They have the authority
to kill a minority ♪
♪ Fuck that shit,
'cause I ain't the one ♪
♪ For a punk motherfuck
with a badge and a gun ♪
♪ To be beaten on
and thrown in jail ♪
♪ We can go toe-to-toe
in the middle of a cell ♪
♪ Fuck the police ♪
Fuck Fuck
♪ Pulling out a silly
club, so you stand ♪
♪ With a fake-ass badge
and a gun in your hand ♪
♪ But take off the gun
so you can see what's up ♪
♪ And we'll go at it, punk,
and I'mma fuck you up ♪
♪ Ice Cube will swarm ♪
♪ On any motherfuck
in a blue uniform ♪
♪ Just 'cause I'm from the CPT ♪
♪ Punk police are
afraid of me, huh ♪
♪ A young nigga on the warpath ♪
♪ And when I'm finished,
it's gonna be a bloodbath ♪
♪ Of cops, dying in L.A. ♪
♪ Yo, Dre, I got something to say ♪
♪ Fuck the police ♪
Aahhhh!
Are your children being lured
into terrorist organizations?
A shocking report shows that some
kids in the town of South Park
Are swearing loyalty
to a murderous regime.
Yeah, we're pretty badass,
And, um, this is, like, our fortress,
And you can see it's pretty cool.
And what about this way
of life is attractive to you?
Well, it's just
cool 'cause we're tough,
And we fight and stuff. And we can...
Yeah, yeah, yeah! And it's
like we can do whatever we want,
And people are scared
of us. It's totally rad.
Then why did you say it was gay before?
Oh, my God! I never said it was gay!
Wait, he said this was gay?
That is a total lie!
Why would I say something homophobic
about the way Tweek and Craig make love?
He's a lying, backstabbing Jew!
I'm Stan.
No doubt the growing number of
kids swearing loyalty to ISIS
Could be problematic
for the progressive town.
Here you go, old girl.
We'll just have to make do.
Ew!
Spare a dollar?
No, I don't. I'm sorry. Thank you.
God damn it. Ew.
Mayor, I didn't bust my ass
to gentrify this part of town
to have it overrun with homeless people.
Why are they all suddenly coming here?
Mayor, what are you
going to do about this?
My wife and I can barely eat or shop.
When a town like ours
has a homeless problem,
It must look at the root
of what's causing it.
- It's ISIS!
- What?
There's these troubled kids who've
turned their backs on America.
They've taken over SodoSoPa,
forced all the homeless out.
Why would kids in our town
want to be a part of that?
They're just bad kids,
rotten on the inside,
probably with shitty parents.
Son, I've always tried to be a fair dad.
I-I don't want to make
you angry, but why?
Well dad, I just r-r-really
like being a part of something.
I feel like it's character-building,
and it's lots of fun.
Fun?
But what do you... believe in?
What do we believe in?
We believe in something
greater than ourselves,
and that by following
our strict warrior code,
We believe that our
faiths and our traditions
Are a way to a greater path...
the p-p-path of the warrior.
And as long as we stay united in honor,
We can defeat all our enemies.
Waghgh waaaaghghhhg!
Wow. The fellas were right.
People are really freaked out by ninjas.
Okay, we've just got
to be really apologetic
And tell them we didn't mean it, okay?
Geez. This is so embarrassing.
What if they won't help
us with the homeless?
I'm pretty sure the police will help out if
it's because ISIS is taking over the town.
Officers, there's kids in
town who have joined ISIS:
We don't know who they are, but they...
What? What's that, you say?
The town is in danger, all right?
We don't know what these
kids are capable of.
Geez. I'm sorry.
We've got to work on our Kaholo Koloa
And get the lomilomi chicken
ready for the big Ho'olaule'a,
Which leaves us, oh,
Not enough time to deal with ISIS:
All right, look, there's homeless people
All over our gentrified
food-and-arts district.
If you don't stop these
twisted kids, then...
Hey, who was it that
said fuck the police?
Was that Ice Cube? Tupac?
Oh, right. That was you guys.
Sorry, but I guess you'll
have to find somebody else
to do all the difficult, dirty shit
you don't want to do yourselves.
I got to be ready for the luau.
I might even kiss a dude.
So, then, after you told me, we
both went over to Kyle and Stan,
where they were playing
basketball, remember?
Yeah.
And we said Kenny and
Token were playing ninja,
And Kyle said that ninjas were gay.
And I said, "Ninjas are
gay?" But it was a question.
You remember?
I thought you said it first.
No, no, no, no. See, now, Kyle's
got everyone remembering it wrong
because he doesn't want to
get kicked out of the group.
That's what Jews do when
they're caught in a lie.
You cannot trust a
Jewish ninja, Butters.
You guys, you guys!
What?
- Actual ninjas want to talk to us.
- What?
Kenny and I both just got the
same e-mail from people overseas.
Whoa, dude!
How'd they find out who we were?
They're fucking ninjas, dude!
So, you are the brave children
who have committed to our cause.
We have heard of what you are doing,
And we are very impressed.
Cool. Thanks, dude.
What you are doing is very important,
And we would like to
help you however we can.
We are going to be
wiring you some money.
Whoa! Cool!
This is the greatest
thing ever, you guys!
Uh, excuse me, could I just set
the record straight on something?
Of course.
Should Jews be trusted?
I mean, if one of us is a Jew,
Do you see that as
being at all problematic?
Extremely.
Yes!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
What did I tell you guys? Thank you!
Hey, Barbrady.
Officer Barbrady?
Wha... who?
Hey, buddy.
What do you want?
How would you like to
be a policeman again?
I'm no good as a policeman.
I'm a bumbling, old fool.
That is not true. Who said that?
Look, Barbrady, the fact
is, the town needs you.
They need me? To do what?
We need you to shoot some kids.
No! Shoot kids?
I don't want to shoot kids!
These are really bad kids... terrorists.
This is totally different from before.
Oh!
Are any of them minorities?
A couple of them we think, yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Look, look, look! Barbrady! Barbrady!
We were wrong about you.
I was wrong about you.
You protected this town back
before anybody else ever did.
You used to do it all on your own.
We need you to do that again.
You're the only cop this
town needs, Barbrady.
Go shoot those kids.
Guys, I know
this is hard for all of us,
But to truly be ninjas,
we must face hard facts.
Last night, I spoke in private
with our ninja leader overseas.
We talked a long time about
Jews and the Hebrew faith.
He told me a lot I didn't know,
And I was able to tell him
some things he did not know.
But after talking with that guy,
It is abundantly clear to me
that Jews cannot be ninjas.
I went to Kyle's house
to talk to him about it,
And I found this.
It was then that Kyle confessed to me
About how he had brainwashed
Butters and Stan into thinking
I had used a homophobic slur
to refer to our organization.
And he almost got away with it.
That's when Kyle tried to kill me.
Luckily, I was the faster ninja.
Kyle knew I would never call ninjas gay.
When I take the gag off,
He's going to try and tell
you that I'm lying now.
Do not believe him. Kyle is a liar.
I'm right here.
Who... Who's this?
That's Clyde.
And I am Token.
Why do I do these things, you ask?
Black rage.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God.
This chicken tastes like
shit. What'd you do to it?
Okay... Okay, Dad, it's
not organic chicken.
I'm not comfortable
shopping at Whole Foods
With all the homeless people there.
But don't worry, that's
all about to change.
Soon we'll all have
ShiTpaTown to enjoy again.
Where's Stan?
He's playing ninjas
over at Kenny's house.
Ninjas? That's gay.
He's playing ninjas at Kenny's house?
- Yeah.
- You mean SodoSoPa?
Wait a minute...
Ninjas...
Scary...
Gay...
Gay.
Scary. Gay.
Randy what are you doing?
Scary.
Gay.
Gay!
Staaaan!
Oh, I get the
misunderstanding now!
No, see, I told Clyde that
Kyle said ninjas were gay,
But Clyde thought I was Kyle,
So then he was saying that
I said ninjas were gay.
Meaning I as in Kyle.
Nobody ever gave
a shit, you fat turd.
All those in favor of Cartman
being kicked out of our ninjas club?
Hai!
No! You can't kick me out!
I have to be a ninja.
They hate Jews. I was
made for this, you guys!
Please!
What should we do with him?
Freeze!
Oh, shit!
Please! I don't want to shoot you!
Cool. Don't.
I understand you're
feeling angry at this town.
I'm getting pretty angry, too!
But we can't give up on it.
Please, boys...
Don't make this end violently.
They're just stupid ninjas!
Aah!
Aaaah!
What were you thinking?
Boys innocently playing ninja,
and you pull your gun on them?
David Rodriguez was lucky to live.
Everybody told me they were terrorists!
We thought they were!
But if it turns out they
aren't, as a policeman,
You have to figure that out!
But... You said you needed
me to kill some kids!
Oh, he's gonna lay this on us now.
I said "kill some kids,"
But I said it as a question, remember?
I said, "Kill some kids?"
I'm sorry, but we just can't
cover your ass on this one.
There's going to be
an investigation and...
You just don't have what it takes
To be a policeman in today's times.
Do you even know what
"farm to table" means?
Let's go, people. You can't stay here.
You are being relocated.
Hey, you can't kick us out of here, man.
Oh, no? I'm a cop.
Thank you, officers.
We've got a deal, right?
Yes.
All right, you. Come on.
Aah!
Please! You can't take
me back to SodoSoPa!
ISIS is there!
No, those were just ninjas.
Ninjas?
Oh, that's so gay.
I told you guys.
What did I tell you?
I said ninjas are fucking gay,
But you didn't want to listen.
Nooo.
Officer Barbrady?
Yes?
We've been watching you.
And what we see
Is a man who truly wants
to protect his town.
You do?
You've been in this town
longer than almost anyone.
Have you noticed... changes lately?
Yeah, a lot of changes.
They aren't a coincidence, officer.
They are all part of a plan
To take down your beloved
town and everyone in it.
What?
What do you know about
a little girl named...
Leslie?