♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
All right, everyone, listen up.
I don't know about you,
but I, for one,
am sick and tired of hate speech
that serves
to marginalize others.
Ahh.
You know, if there's one thing
that makes me sick,
it's when a race thinks
they're superior
and don't know how
to check their privilege.
An African American flips
a turtle over on its back.
A transgender
Filipino comes
and sees the helpless turtle
baking in the sun.
What color is
the Filipino's father?
I didn't think
you were human.
Aah!
Yeah, everybody's pretty
freaked out over here, baby.
Everyone is on edge
and feeling really nervous.
That sounds terrible.
Be careful, Butters.
I will, honey.
Butters, get to
the bathroom. Now.
All right, Kyle,
what's this about?
Jimmy's dead.
What?
I know the whole story.
PC Principal killed him
and tried to kill Leslie,
but she got away.
Mrph rmh rmphm?
PC Principal is part
of a huge network of radicals
who kill everyone that doesn't
follow their PC ideology.
How do you know all this?
Because Leslie's with me.
I'm keeping her safe.
♪ Kyle's got a girlfriend ♪
It gets worse.
Someone in our town helped
these people come here.
That person
faked the Bill Cosby joke
to get
Principal Victoria fired.
Who would use a Cosby joke
to push their own agenda?
I think it's obvious —
Stan's dad.
Kyle...
Stan, your dad is
one of them.
He had to be the one
that let them in!
You're letting paranoia and
suspicion get the better of you.
There's no way to know
who we can trust.
So, what do we do now?
There's only one thing
we can do.
We have to get guns.
Guns?
It's the only way for us
to be safe.
Kyle, even if we thought
it could help protect us,
how are we all going to
get our hands on guns?
All right, cool.
We got guns.
So, now what?
Mrph rmhmhm rm!
I already feel
a lot safer!
You guys lay low
and watch your backs.
I'm gonna go
keep Leslie protected.
Hey.
Don't fall too hard,
partner.
Do I look sweet,
Butters?
Yeah.
What?
Can you pass
the garlic bread, Randy?
Why wouldn't I be able
to pass the garlic bread?
Dad, where were you
last night?
What? When?
Where was I what?
Out. With friends.
Doing things.
Well, I'm full.
I'm gonna go work in the garage
for a little bit.
Work on what?
On stuff
that do things.
Um, oh, I'm gonna take
some of this with me.
I'm still hungry.
Thought you just said
you were full.
Jesus!
What am I, on trial
or something?
God damn!
You guys are really
acting strange.
All right.
We're good.
Nobody suspects a thing.
Take a look at this.
We've got everything
from PC Principal's hard drive.
He was on to the gentrification
around the world,
and he was convinced
that whatever was responsible
wasn't human.
Not human?
Then what?
I don't care
if they're aliens or vampires.
We need to
round 'em up fast
and fuck them
till they're dead.
You don't want
to fuck a vampire.
You'll get hepatitis.
Oh, girlfriend,
I am well beyond that.
Oh, my God.
Don't you see what this means?
If something not human
is gentrifying the entire world,
soon no human will be able
to afford it.
They're trying to price
our species out of existence.
Well, how do you like
my new apartment?
What happened to you,
Nathan?
I always thought
you were a nice kid.
Now you've got a gun?
Oh, everyone's getting
one of these now, Jim.
Nobody knows who to trust.
Yeah? Well,
guns are never the answer.
Don't you kind of wish
you'd had one
back when Leslie betrayed you
and nearly beat you to death?
Oh. I guess it would have been
a decent answer then.
T-T-T-Touché.
You see, I've got
expensive tastes, Jimmy.
I like good food,
organic pressed juices,
and I've got a thing
for high-class prostitutes.
Have you been introduced
to my current girlfriend?
My name is Classi
with an "I,"
and a little dick
hanging off the "C"
that bends around
and fucks the "L"
out of the
"A"-"S"-"S."
Nice to meet you,
Classi.
All I had to do
was work for the ads,
and I got
everything I wanted —
My own loft with all of
ShiTpaTown right at my doorstep.
All it took was some PC, and the
whole thing was set in motion.
Oh, great.
So, now ads are using PC
for their own gains?
That's a new low.
What is PC but a verbal form
of gentrification?
Spruce everything up,
get rid of all the ugliness
in order to create
a false sense of paradise.
Only one thing can actually live
in that world — ads.
I know I've set it before,
but man, do I hate ads.
Eric Cartman, I told you
to go get ready for bed!
Yeah, I just want to finish
this movie.
No, Eric,
this is a school night.
Mom,
I'm into this movie.
I'm not going to bed
right now. Chillax.
You most certainly are.
Right now, mister!
I will go to bed
when this movie is over, Mom.
Eric!
Where did you get that?
Turn off the light
and go back to bed.
I'm staying up.
Eric, you march right up
to your room, and you —
I don't think so, Mom.
Eric, you get
your butt to bed!
No means no,
Bill Cosby!
I told you to go upstairs
right now!
Whoa, Mom,
what the hell?
I'm not going to
tell you again, Eric.
It is time
for night-night!
Mom, put down the gun.
I am your mother, and you will
do what I tell you!
Okay, I am going!
Well, then you go
right now, mister!
I am going to bed Mom!
Chillax.
All right, then! No comic books!
Just straight to sleep!
I love you, sweetie!
Okay. I love you too, Mom.
Night-night.
Wow, he — he listened.
There has to be
something —
some clue as to what
we're dealing with.
The news stories
PC Principal researched
are all so contradictory,
as if whatever
these things are
have control
over the news somehow.
That sounds
like vampires to me.
We have to find out who had me
fired with the Cosby joke.
It's the key to knowing
what we're dealing with.
Principal Victoria?
Mr. Garrison?
Caitlyn Jenner?
Stan, what the hell
are you doing in here?
Tell me
what's going on, Dad.
Nothing.
We're just hanging out,
talking about Coldplay,
all right?
No! I want to know what the hell
is going on right now!
What are you doing
with that?
Kyle said
I couldn't trust you.
What are you
planning, Dad?
Stan, it isn't
what you think.
Then what is it?
Look, I need to show you
something, okay?
You need
to see this, son.
Ooh! Psych! Now put
the fucking gun down, bitch!
I'm gonna go tell Mom!
Oh, yeah?
You go tell her.
I'll tell you had a gun.
You'll be
in more trouble than me!
Stan, I am your dad.
Put the gun down
and sit over there.
Mom!
Shit!
Took a lot to hunt you down,
PC Principal.
You mind telling me why you're
going around the world
shooting up revitalized
arts and foods districts?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Try me!
I don't know what they are,
but they used me
and others like me
to try and change the planet.
You don't know
what who are?
Sir, the President is
on the phone.
Wants to talk to you
about PC Principal.
Yes, Mr. President.
I see, sir.
Yes, I understand.
We're to release him
immediately —
No questions asked.
And we're not supposed to
believe anything he tells us.
Huh.
Ain't that a peach?
He's being set free now,
Mr. President.
Can I tell
the commander why?
This is a matter
of national security.
I understand, sir.
Thank you.
God Bless you.
God Bless you,
too, sir.
And may God Bless
the United States of America.
You okay?
Yeah, just
feeling butterflies,
and my hands
are freezing.
Here.
Thank you, Kyle.
Don't worry, Leslie.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
I'm warning you — You're on
the wrong side of this.
We're just trying
to get answers.
You pulled a gun
on our son, Randy!
He pulled one
on me first, Sharon!
Because you wouldn't
talk to me, Dad!
Stanley, let your mother and I
deal with this.
I told you
to leave him alone!
God,
I hate this family!
Why are you always
taking Stan's side?
Whoa! Whoa! Shelly!
Put down the gun,
Shelly!
You're always acting like Stan
can't do anything wrong!
She doesn't always
take my side!
You shut up or I swear to God
I'll use this.
Shelly,
put it down now.
You don't even try
to know me, Dad!
I want to, Shelly!
I just sometimes feel
like you hate me!
I feel like
you hate me, Randy!
I don't hate you!
I love you!
I need to be a better husband,
a better father!
We all need to be better
to each other!
Okay, maybe I need
to stop being so angry!
I love you guys.
We love you,
too, Dad.
We just want to know
what's going on with you.
All right,
I'll tell you everything.
Wow. These things
are amazing.
All right,
Mrs. Farnickle, enjoy.
And remember — If the safety's
on, you're good as gone.
Okay, and next customer,
please.
Ah, going for
the big one, huh?
You must be feeling
extra jumpy!
you don't know
the half of it.
Well, this thing should make you
feel more at ease.
You know, you ought to
check out the gun show.
The gun show?
Yeah, it's gonna have
everything,
and with guns being so popular,
practically everyone in town is
gonna be in attendance.
The entire town
in one location?
Oh, my God.
The principal has become
our biggest problem.
We need a news headline
that will draw him back to town.
Oh, you're going to
sponsor my content
some more, baby?
I'm all ears.
I've got to get to
the Super School News.
Hey, Classi, do you think
you could get me my crutches?
Naw.
I don't think
Nathan would like that.
You seem like
a reasonable person.
Do you really want to live
in a world controlled by ads?
I mean come on, Classy.
No, it's Classi.
With an "I."
The little dick
that hangs off the "C"
fucks the "L"
out of the ass.
Cla-ass-I.
Sorry. My bad.
Look, I'm a news reporter,
Claaassi,
and in a world where ads
control the news,
there's no way to be sure
anyone's ever hearing the truth.
Truth about what?
We can't just hide, Kyle.
We have to let people know
PC is the enemy
before it's too late.
Leslie, we don't know
who is on their side.
We have stay safe.
The principal is
going to try
and make up
some crazy story.
That's what PC people do.
You have to get
in front of everyone
and tell them
what you've learned!
I... gave up
giving speeches.
But why?
I came to you
because I had heard
how good you were
at getting messages across.
That and because...
I thought you were cute.
I'm sure I'd have no problem
giving a speech
if you could be
by my side.
well, I can't go with you,
you know. It's too dangerous.
Not if we go somewhere
that's completely safe
from any violence.
Where?
The gun show.
Gun show?
There'll be so many guns
that nothing bad can happen.
Someone purposely had
Principal Victoria replaced
with the new principal?
Yes, they wanted
to use his PC
as a means to start
gentrification in our town.
That's why we thought
PC Principal was behind it,
but now we know they were just
using his PC abilities
to service
their own needs.
When the pussy crusher story
came out in Super School News,
it started to make PC Principal
question himself.
He started digging for answers.
They didn't like that.
So, they tried to distract
and mislead him with this.
Sorry. Wait. That's an ad
for McDonald's. Hold on.
With this —
Ugh, there's that ad again.
God, these things
are annoying.
Anyways,
whatever these beings are,
they try to keep anyone
from knowing the truth from —
Ugh, I don't want to see
a slide show.
PC Principal said something
was trying to divert
and distract his
subconscious mind with this.
Wait, that's Leslie.
Oh, my God.
It's Kyle.
Kyle?
Kyle's been protecting Leslie.
They're together.
He's been making everyone
feel paranoid
and saying
you're the enemy, Dad.
Well, then,
it's time to go ask Kyle
why he sold out
his own kind.
How will we get him
to talk?
We're going to kill him
with kindness.
But instead of kindness,
we're going to use guns.
Yeah!
Come on! Let's go!
Shelly,
you take care of Grandpa!
Okay!
No, no, no.
Don't shoot Grandpa.
Just literally
take care of him.
Buckle up, buckaroos!
Here it is, Jimmy,
hot off the presses.
What is that?
The newest edition
of Super School News,
hitting the streets
tomorrow.
"Tragedy at Gun Show."
What happened
at the gun show?
Not what's happened,
what's going to happen.
The final sweeping
underneath the rug.
By this time tomorrow,
nobody will be
asking questions ever again.
The ads will have won,
and I will be the man.
I think the ads
are playin' yo ass.
Shut up, Classi!
Oh, hell, no!
What?
Oh, hell no, your Down syndrome
ass just slapped me.
I'mma break
yo dick off!
Hang on, Classi.
I'm sorry.
I will bust
yo fucking ass!
yo fucking nose!
I ain't no
mimsy-ass ho!
I'm a classy bitch,
and I do not...
want ads...
controlling my news!
Classi, thank you!
You need my help?
You gots it.
I need your phone
to call Officer Barbrady,
and we have to get to
that gun show fast!
Quick, to
the Classi-mobile!
Welcome back
to the South Park Gun Show.
We've had
over 2,000 gorgeous guns
come through
this arena today.
It's been whittled down
to seven,
the winners
from each group.
David,
take us down the line.
First, we have
the beautiful Yorkshire.33mm
with proud owner
Steven Stotch.
An absolutely gorgeous gun,
David.
The playful and lovely
Australian semi-automatic,
owned by Father Maxi.
And there's the Mayor
with her delightful
Rhodesian Ridgeback
shotgun/rifle mix.
That's a favorite
of the crowd here.
Always a favorite
at these shows.
That's a nice gun
right there.
The judge now asking to see
that Yorkshire.33mm up close.
And there it is —
Just a beautiful gun in motion.
Everybody loves it.
Looks like the judge
wants to take another look
at that
shotgun/rifle mix.
And next up will be the —
Nobody move!
Everyone just stay
where you are!
And it looks like the gun show
is under attack, David.
Yes, six armed gunmen
have entered the arena,
one of which is carrying
an absolutely gorgeous
little Pekingese
Glock 17.
Listen to me, everyone!
There are beings
who are purposely
gentrifying the Earth
so that humans
can no longer afford it.
We've been looking
for Kyle Broflovski.
Somebody's hiding him.
Don't listen to them!
The real conspiracy here
are the PC extremists
who have
no problem killing
whoever doesn't think
like they do!
You son of a bitch,
Stan.
How could you have sided
with the enemy?
Fuck you, Kyle.
You're the enemy.
You've both got it wrong.
Jimmy?
Officer Barbrady?
Classi?
Randy?
Kyle, I know
you probably thought
Leslie was
a kind, caring girl,
but the truth is
she's just an ad.
An ad?
They've
become sentient!
They've taken
human form.
You can't tell what's human
and what's an ad anymore.
Oh, geez.
Are you serious?
How am I supposed to
fuck an ad to death?
Ugh, flippin' ads.
They're such
a pain in the ass.
You told me
Jimmy was dead.
So, now we know who got
Principle Victoria fired.
Nobody move, m'kay!
Everyone just
stay where you are!
Mackey?
Yes, I wanted
Principle Victoria fired,
but I didn't want
any of this!
You got me fired? Why?
18 years of answering to you —
18 years!
You always telling me
what to do.
If you had problems with me,
why didn't you just talk to me?
You never listened!
Nobody listens to me!
They just expect me
to listen to them!
Maybe we should
have realized
that sometimes a counselor
needs counseling!
I don't know.
Maybe I got manipulated
by these ads,
too, somehow,
but I should have been
a better person!
We all could be better people —
all of us!
We all played a part.
Maybe from now on people in this
town need to communicate more!
Care about each other!
If we're going to defeat
our enemies,
that's what it's going to
take — all of us, together!
If only we'd had these
before, huh?
Every time you block us,
we get smarter.
Every time you try to stop us,
we are more.
If one plan fails,
we will plan another.
You will never
be rid of ads.
Hey, Leslie!
Your species took PC and
twisted it for evil purposes.
That pisses me off!
You're expelled.
Yes, dude!
Well, I guess there's just
one last thing to take care of.
Why did it have to be
like this?
Why couldn't we try to live
on this planet together?
Maybe we're not perfect beings,
but we built a better town!
We didn't need you
to do that!
And we'll keep on trying
to make it better!
Randy, you're yelling
at a Whole Foods.
Go on! Get out of here!
We know!
Others will know!
It isn't going to be so easy,
not anymore.
All right everyone, listen up.
I don't know about you,
but I, for one,
am sick and tired
of all the hate speech
and microaggressions
against our species.
We have a new enemy out there —
an almost invisible foe
that is so bigoted,
so racially biased,
they actually think
we should all die.
They are trying
to attract our youth,
using tactics that are
underhanded and unfair.
But no matter how hard
they hit us,
we cannot let them take
from us our PC.
And so, I have been asked
to stay on as your principal.
A lot of changes will happen
in the coming months.
The bottom line is
that the only thing
that distinguishes
those who want to kill us
from those who don't is
that we have the burning desire
for social justice.
We are at war,
but the only way to win this war
is to be as understanding,
non-biased,
and politically correct
as possible.
This is gonna be
really hard.
There's only one thing
we can do.
We have to get guns.
Guns?
It's the only way for us
to be safe.
Kyle, even if we thought
it could help protect us,
how are we all going to
get our hands on guns?
All right, cool. We got guns.
So, now what?
www. tvsubtitles. net