Now, last week
we were all reminded
that intolerance still exists
in our country.
It took a very special
young student
to light up social media.
We've invited him
to the White House today
to show our appreciation.
Because never have there been
more tolerant, more moving words
than Kyle Broflovski's speech
about his hero, Caitlyn Jenner.
Come on up here, Kyle.
You see? There!
This is why it's happening.
Everyone's preaching
openness and acceptance,
and so now millions
of Goddamn immigrants
are coming over the border,
and nobody seems to care!
But what are you gonna do?
In today's world,
it's like you can't even say
anything negative
about illegal immigrants.
Whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Did somebody over here say
"illegal immigrants"?
Because the correct term
is "undocumented immigrants,"
all right, bro?
It's like nobody cares!
And they just keep coming,
crossing the border
with their dirty families,
playing their stupid music.
I mean, look at 'em!
I'll bet not one of them
is here legally.
All right, guy!
Hey, buddy.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey, what's going on, friend?
Hey, buddy,
another Moosehead, eh?
We should have put up
a Goddamn wall.
But wait.
There's still more.
Because this country
was built on dreamers.
And, Kyle, we want to make
your dreams come true.
And so here is your hero,
Caitlyn Jenner.
I just want to say
thank you, Kyle,
for your beautiful words
of support.
Now, Kyle, we got another
little surprise for you.
We told you we were
flying you back home,
but the truth is,
you're getting a ride back
all the way with your hero.
How do you like that?
Buckle up, buckaroo.
Okay, children,
let's take our seats.
As you've probably noticed,
our government has decided
to let anyone who wants to
cross the border
and screw up our country.
I know you're all as pissed off
as I am,
so why don't we begin
today's lesson
on why the once-great
empire of Rome fell to shit.
Huh? Who can tell me
why Rome fell to shit?
No, somebody who matters.
All right, fine.
In the yellow shirt.
The Roman Empire, buddy,
was facing several issues, guy,
as it reached
a new millennium, friend...
Oh, speak in English!
You see, what happened
is that these immigrants
called the Goths were welcomed
into Roman territories
because some people
felt bad for them.
And then the Goths
suddenly decided
they were being oppressed,
you see?
And so, then...
What the hell are you doing?
It's 8:00 A.M., guy.
That's it!
Why don't you Canucks
go back where you came from?
You really think you can refer
to an undocumented immigrant
as a "Canuck"?
P.C. Principal, they got up
in the middle of my lecture
and started playing music.
So did you forget
that at 8:00 and 11:00,
all Canadians face east
and play Chuck Mangione,
or did you not care to find out
about their religious customs?
They... They don't
even speak English.
Then you need to be teaching
in both languages from now on.
Mackey, sign the faculty up for
Canadian-language night classes.
What?
Yes, P.C. Principal!
R-right away! M'kay.
You're on thin ice, Garrison.
Get in line,
or you'll be out of a job, bro.
What are they doing now?
Well, they're all eating
together and praying,
and they're putting syrup
on their mac and cheese.
Ugh! So weird.
There's just so many of them.
You guys, I think this whole
thing is a conspiracy.
- What do you mean?
- Think about what happened.
America had pretty secure
borders for years.
Kyle gives a big speech
about tolerance and acceptance
that goes viral.
A bunch of Canadians
cross the border illegally.
Kyle's brother is Canadian.
What if Kyle knowingly
gave that speech
to get all the illegals in?
I'm sitting right here.
And he's sitting right here.
You really think just my speech
brought on a wave
of illegal immigration?
You did kind of
go overboard, dude.
What?
It's just, I know you like
giving speeches and stuff,
but not everything
is black and white.
Yeah, I mean, it's fine you want
to go preach about Caitlyn Jenner,
but you can't just make
blanket statements
about letting anyone do
whatever they want.
I didn't even
want to give that speech!
Yeah, yeah.
This is interesting.
Have you guys read Genesis 34?
- Unh-unh.
- Well, it's intriguing,
because in Genesis 34,
the Jews actually did
something similar
to what Kyle's doing now.
I'm not responsible for this.
Illegal immigration
has been happening forever.
But it's happening
a lot more now,
after you decide to give
a big speech
about Caitlyn Jenner
because you want to bring down
the cultural fabric of America
'cause you're a Jew.
You guys, immigrants,
either legal or illegal,
are always gonna find ways
to cross into richer countries
- if they're not living...
- Oh, boy.
- Here we go again.
- Yeah, I'm out.
Yeah, sorry. I can't listen
to another one either.
Happy evening, friends.
My name is Mr. Stkrdknmibalz
,
and we are going
to learn Canadian.
With a lot of practice,
you're going to find
that speaking Canadian
isn't so difficult,
and in fact, our alphabet
and yours are fairly similar.
So why don't we begin
singing it together?
♪ E, F, Guy
♪ L, M, N, O, Buddy
♪ T, U, Friend
♪ W, X, Eh, and Pbht!
♪ These are Canadian ABCs
♪ Susie likes hairy balls
♪ What do ya think of these?
All right, now everyone.
♪ E, F, Guy
♪ L, M, N, O, Buddy
♪ Where has my country gone?
♪ It was a land of opportunity
that we held dear ♪
♪ But now all these other
assholes are comin' here ♪
♪ And where's my country gone?
♪ It was just here
like two seconds ago ♪
♪ 'Cause when they said that
this was the land of the free ♪
♪ I'm pretty sure
that they were referring to me ♪
♪ And my country's gone!
♪ It got upset,
and now it's wandered away ♪
♪ It took 43 presidents
to make us stand tall ♪
♪ And just one black guy
to unravel it all ♪
♪ Country gone!
♪ Please tell it
that we need her back home ♪
♪ There's a great big hole
in the liberty bucket ♪
♪ 'Cause someone forgot to tell
the foreigners to suck it ♪
♪ And now they're all
hanging out on my lawn ♪
♪ And now they're ruining
my song ♪
♪ Making it sound
like Chuck Mangione ♪
♪ Where my country gone?
Seems like everyone's afraid
to speak the truth around here.
Well, I'm throwing my hat in
and saying
I'll figure this thing out.
Now, I might not understand
politics or immigration policies
or the law
or basic ideological concepts.
But damn it, I understand
there's a bunch
of Canadians here,
and I'm gonna do something
about it!
Whoohoo!
All right, everyone, listen up.
In order
for better understanding,
we have asked students
of Canadian origin
to introduce you
to their culture and...
Hey, Leslie,
shut your mouth!
To introduce you
to their culture and customs.
So let's give them
our undivided attention
as they take us
on a whirlwind journey
through their diverse history.
We are the Hopewell and Abenaki,
first settlers
of Canadian soil, guy.
We are French and British
explorers,
seeking furs and goods.
Yeah, and I'm Dan Rather,
and I got news for you...
Nobody wants you here!
Sorry. Not sorry.
It's time for someone
to say it like is
and make our country
great again.
Garrison,
what do you think you're...
And I'm also not afraid
to stand up to P.C. Principal.
You, sir, have a pizza face,
and you suck your mom's dick.
That's it, Garrison.
You are fired
from South Park Elementary.
Oh, see?
And now I'm fired.
That's the cold, hard truth
of immigration.
Well, there's only
one immigration policy
that I believe in,
and that's
'em all to death!
I'm just saying what everyone's
thinking here, kids.
Sorry. Not sorry.
Dude, the Canadians
are pissed off.
Can you really blame them?
What made Mr. Garrison
do that?
Guys, what if this was all
exactly what Kyle planned?
Get the Canadians here,
make them feel persecuted,
and then what?
Uprisings, rebellion.
Next thing you know,
they're sending us to camps
and using us as livestock.
You really think
Kyle would do that?
That doesn't matter.
We have to think of a way
to smooth this over fast.
Yeah, we're gonna need a
symbolic union. A what?
You know, what's that story
about the two sides
that were fighting,
and then a guy from one side
got with a girl
from the other side,
and their love sort of
brought the groups together?
"Lion King 2"?
Yes, "Lion King 2."
I mean, if we can get one of us
to go out with one of them,
probably have sex,
then it could be a symbol
of us all getting along.
Yeah, it's kind of like
when a princess of one country
marries the prince of another.
Oh, come on.
This is stupid.
You guys,
when two groups of people
don't understand each other,
you can't just try and diffuse
- the tensions with...
- Is he seriously...
Is he seriously
giving a speech right now?
This is gonna have to happen
pretty fast,
so whoever's gonna do it needs
to ask a Canadian girl out soon.
- 1, 2, 3, not it.
- Not it.
- No, no! Not it!
Oh, shit!
Support is growing
for a Colorado man
who claims the way to deal
with illegal immigrants
is to them all to death.
We go live to Minnesota.
Tom, the political activist
is going around the country
to get support for his agenda.
And, Mr. Garrison,
you believe
the immigration problem
is easy to solve.
Yes.
them all to death.
Let's make this country
great again.
And when you say,
"them all to death,"
what are you actually
suggesting be done?
I'm suggesting
we round them all up,
pull down their pants,
and them
until their spirits
leave their bodies.
And then after we've
every last one of them to death,
we build a big wall.
And if anyone
comes over the wall,
we them to death, too!
And then
we to death all...
Uh, Dan? Dan?
We are getting word that
a wall has already been built.
Is that right? Yes?
CNN is confirming that Canada
has built a wall to keep us out.
What do you mean
they built a wall?
They can't build a wall!
Oh them to death!
Hey, there!
Beautiful day, isn't it?
What the hell is this?
Oh, this?
This is a wall.
Sorry, buddy.
Nobody allowed in.
Can they do that?
Look, we came to speak
with your government
about the...
Yeah, no, sorry!
Everything past here is ours.
You can't... You can't go
past... past here.
We're Americans!
We don't even
want to be over there!
What do you think
we're gonna do?
Well, you know,
we just don't want you
raping our women and stuff.
That is ridiculous!
All right, smart-ass,
that's just about enough...
Look, there's just some really
cool shit back here,
and we don't feel like
sharing it.
Cool shit like what?
Don't worry about it.
No. What's back there?
Let me see!
It's all right, Garrison.
No, Goddamn it!
Let me see!
What about that one
in the glasses?
She's kind of hot.
She's not hot.
She looks like a messed-up
cucumber with wieners on it!
All right.
How about the lanky one there?
Ooh, ooh!
What about the one in the hat?
She kind of looks like
Alanis Morissette, huh?
Alanis Morissette is like
80 years old or something!
Geez!
Okay, B-Butters, relax.
Well, I don't want
a Canadian girlfriend, Eric!
Okay, you just want a race war?
No!
The one in the white shoes
isn't that ugly.
Okay, go the one
in the white shoes.
Okay.
Hi. My name is Butters.
What's yours?
I'm Charlotte.
Oh, Charlotte,
I've never done this before.
You think Scar's up there?
He wasn't my father,
but he's still part of me.
Oh, no, Simba.
We have barely begun.
We'll run away together
and... and...
And start a pride
all of our own.
Tom, the scene at the Canadian
border is electric
as several political leaders
try and strategize
how to deal with being shut
out of Canada.
If the Canadian government
wants to put up a wall,
they have every right.
And yet, we must ask why they
thought this to be necessary.
No, them,
and you.
I want to see if they have
really cool back there.
What we need is a...
No, you've got a gaping gash,
and you've got vinegary balls.
The Canadians can't do this!
Don't they realize that hundreds
of thousands of their people
are over here illegally?
Oh, you guys didn't put up
a wall?
And you keep your
Goddamn mouth shut, smart ass!
I'll deal with you.
I get things done,
and I'm getting back there!
Here you go.
Thanks, Butters.
I'm sore-y I didn't know
what ice cream was.
What's sore-y?
Well, that's what Canadians say
to express remorse.
Oh.
H-Hey, that's neato.
Hang on, Charlotte, one sec.
What do you want?
Have you given her
the old Hot Cosby yet?
No. We saw a movie,
and now we're going to the park.
Butters,
we don't have time for that.
I told you, you have to cut
to the chase with a Hot Cosby.
If I'm gonna be with this girl,
I don't want her
someday thinking
it was all super rushed.
Nobody cares
about 40 years from now
when she suddenly changes
her mind, Butters.
Time is of the essence!
We're all gonna die!
Everything all right?
Yeah, just some
work-related stuff.
So, hey, I wanted to see
if you wanted come over
to my house for dinner tomorrow.
Oh, boy.
Yes, I'd love to.
Here we go.
Oh, God.
Okay, that's... that's good.
Watch the balls.
Okay, all right,
give me the helmet.
We'll see what they've got
behind that Goddamn wall.
You know what I am, friends?
I'm a doer.
Yeah!
Yeah! That's right!
Canada says we can't go
into their country,
I'm going into their country!
And when I do,
I am every last
Canadian so hard!
All right, let's do this.
Aw, he's dead.
So, young man, I understand
that you and my daughter
have started a romance.
Well, uh...
Well, yes, sir.
And I suppose you have a thing
for Canadian girls, huh?
Is that it?
You've got maple fever?
Eh, Daddy!
I'm sorry, Charlotte,
but I get suspicious.
It's bad enough we have
to live in America.
Now all the boys
with maple fever
are gonna want to have
at our daughter.
That's enough, Donald.
Wait.
You don't want to be here?
Why would we want to be here?
Well, you know,
'cause everything is great here,
and we have cool stuff.
Canada has everything.
It's the greatest country
on Earth.
But... so,
then why did you leave?
There were several candidates
during the Canadian elections.
One of them was this brash
asshole who just spoke his mind.
He didn't really offer
any solutions.
He just said outrageous things.
We thought it was funny.
Nobody really thought
he'd ever be president.
It was a joke.
But we just let the joke go on
for too long.
He kept gaining momentum,
and by the time
we were all ready to say,
"Okay, let's get serious now.
Who should really be president?"
He was already being sworn
into office.
We weren't paying attention.
We weren't paying attention!
Geez.
How bad can a president be?
If certain people want to leave
this country, then let them!
You tell those pussy homos
they can suck my balls!
But, Mr. President...
And tell
the prime minister of China
that he can suck my balls!
Oh, and Johnson...
Mr. President?
Suck my balls.
I'm sore-y
about my papa.
He can be really emotional
sometimes.
You don't got
to be sore-y.
It's me
who should be sore-y.
I think everyone has
the wrong idea
about your people, Charlotte.
It's okay.
We just have to give them time.
I wasn't supposed to have time.
I was supposed to give you
a Hot Cosby
so our species could coexist.
But now I realize you guys
don't even want to be here.
Oh.
So do you want to be here?
Now?
There's really nowhere
I'd rather be.
If it's okay with you...
I'd like to try
a nice Slow Cosby instead.
In Canada,
we call a Slow Cosby "love."
Oh, look!
A shooting star.
In Canada,
we say that's good luck.
So do we.
Hello?
Oh, God!
Hey!
Where is everyone, guy?
Geez.
♪ Safety dance
♪ We can dance if we want to
What?
♪ We can leave...
Hey!
How did a U.S. citizen
get past my wall?
I came here to find out
where my country gone.
Where your country gone?
Where my country gone!
No, where my country gone,
bitch!
Nobody talks to me
like that, buddy!
like that, fwiend!
- Ergh! Yeah?
- Stupid... unh!
- Little asshole!
- This is why I built that wall!
You think you can...
There you go!
I came here to do one thing!
Hey, what the...
Aah!
Hey, that pokes, buddy!
Oh, my God, guy.
Please! Please, I can't...
Oh! No, please!
No! No!
No!
Oh, look at them, Thomas.
I think
they really like each other.
Yes, I have to admit,
it seems they're actually
falling in Slow Cosby.
I'll get it.
Hey did you hear the news,
buddy?
Canadian President
has been to death.
Yes! Yes!
What?
Are you sure?
What is it, Donald?
Canadian President
got to death, darling.
Oh, my goodness!
Should we go back
to Canada, then?
Yes, I guess, let's go back.
- See ya!
- Bye!
It's been real, guy!
See ya, guy!
Charlotte!
I'll Skype you when I'm home,
my love!
Ah, I should've done
the Hot Cosby.
You did it, Garrison!
Thank you, Garrison!
Friends, I think I've proven
that my policies work
to get things done.
I know what my true calling is,
and I am going to keep this
going all the way to Washington.
Hold on! Wait!
It wasn't me!
I wasn't the one
who brought the Canadians here.
It was something just like this.
Don't you see?
If there's anything
we've learned,
it's that we have to stop
this kind
of sensationalistic politics
before the same thing
happens to us,
because if we let this
kind of...
this...
Dude.
Unbelievable.
All right, my friends,
I have to say goodbye now
because I'm off to Washington
with my running mate.
Buckle up, buckaroo!
Because I'm off to Washington
with my running mate!
Buckle up, buckaroo!