♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
All right, guys.
Now let's go back and
talk about infinitives.
Remember... Those are verbs
combined with the word "to."
Oh, my fucking God.
Now, usually, an
infinitive acts like a noun,
as in "I want to go out to eat,"
or "I hope to be chosen today."
What?
- I'm so bored, dude.
- Now, usually, it isn't common
to split "to" and the
verb, but sometimes you can.
Knock it off!
Is there a problem, guys?
Go get my pen, fat ass!
I'm am not your slave, Kyle.
Go get my pen!
Attention, students.
Kyle Broflovski, report to
the principal's office, please.
PC Principal wants to see you, Kyle!
Kyle Broflovski to the
principal's office. M'kay?
God damn it.
Have fun, dude.
Oh, Kyle, uh, thank you for coming.
Where's PC Principal?
I think he's finally lost it, Kyle.
He and his PC buddies
are on a hunger strike.
They're calling for
people's resignations!
Kyle, PC Principal had problems
with Jimmy and with Leslie,
and now they're missing. M'kay?
Nobody knows where they are.
That's what happens.
You go against PC, and
you just end up missing.
M'kay.
What are you talking about?
PC Principal had
issues with them, m'kay?
And he had issues with you, Kyle.
Whatever's going on...
it's pretty damn scary.
For years, mankind has tried
to rid the world of ads.
For our ancestors, ads
couldn't be avoided.
But everyone knew what
was an ad and what wasn't.
After many years,
mankind invented cable,
a way to pay for television
so there would be no ads.
But somehow, the ads still found a way.
And so mankind invented TiVo,
a way to skip past commercials.
Finally, it appeared
to be the end of ads.
And everywhere, people rejoiced.
The ads were stopped. Or so it seemed...
With the rise of the Internet,
suddenly the ads had an
en-entirely new way to attack us...
Pop-ups.
The top scientific minds
were brought together
to find a way to stop
the ads once and for all.
They invented the ad blocker.
Suddenly, there were no
ads on phones, on computers.
And everywhere, people rejoiced.
But the ads adapted.
They became s-smarter.
They disguised themselves as news.
All around the world,
people read news stories
completely unaware
they were reading ads.
And now, the ads have taken the
next step in their evolution.
They have taken human form.
Ads are among us.
They could be your
friend, your g-gardener.
The ads are trying to wipe us out.
The question is how?
So, um... South Park kind of sucks now.
You guys want to bail?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
It's just, you know, used to
be nice and laid back here,
but now it's all "ngh," you know?
Like... Like now
everybody's all, "ngh-ngh."
Let's bail. You want to bail, Stan?
No, I don't.
What's going on, Randy?
Nothing! I just... You know,
we don't have to live here.
We could live anywhere!
Last month, all you could talk about
was how great this town had become.
What changed your mind?
We can't afford it.
We can't afford it?
All these fancy new
restaurants and shops
and everyone wants to live here.
A bowl of City Beef costs 10
bucks now, for Christ's sake.
And there's nowhere to
shop but stupid Whole Foods.
Well, we'll just have to
stop going to those places.
I had to take out a second
mortgage on the house.
You what?
I had to Sharon! It isn't my fault!
It's the man! Don't you see?
The man is pricing us
out of our own town.
It's just my luck.
I talk to a nice girl,
seem to hit it off,
and she turns out to just be an ad.
Well, that's what an ad does.
She was designed to
entice and manipulate.
This is such a fantastic
story for the school newspaper.
Why don't we just run it so
that everybody knows the truth?
Jimmy, we're newsmen like you.
For decades, we used
our soft, buttery voices
to inform the people
about what's happening.
Then we watched as our entire
industry was taken over by the ads.
Some of our colleagues were
manipulated into doing the ads' bidding.
The man who came to your house
with a gun was one of them.
Our own Kevin Jarvis has more.
Thanks, Tom. Jimmy, the
man who tried to kill you
was a Brian Bouyant
of WXNR: Fort Collins.
When he saw there was
no money in news anymore,
he sided with the ads
even though he knew
it meant the destruction of our species.
- Back to you, Tom.
- Thanks, Kevin.
The only hope for the truth
to get out there, Jimmy,
is for you see through
this ad's deception
and to find out what they're planning.
Your Super School News
was a threat to them,
but unless you get this
little bitch to talk,
we may never know why.
Dude, Kyle!
Will you look at this?
"Principal sends two favorite
students on a Disney Cruise.
This week students Jimmy
Valmer and Leslie Meyers
are being treated to an
all-expenses-paid vacation
for their outstanding
school"... What the hell is this?
It doesn't make any sense, dude.
PC Principal is using the school
paper to cover something up.
Yeah, I... I don't want to get involved.
You don't want to get involved?
Dude, what's wrong with you?
I've already learned you
can't win against PC Principal.
You should know, of all people,
since he's converted your dad.
What's that supposed to mean?
Fellas, we found out
what happened to Jimmy!
He got to go on a vacation
for being an exemplary student.
That is not what happened.
Something is very wrong here.
We all have to stand up
to PC Principal together.
Yeah, and wasn't Jimmy the one
in charge of the school newspaper?
So who's putting this out?
I like the school paper.
I like to type with my hands.
Who told you that the principal
sent Jimmy on a Disney Cruise?
Uhhhhh...
Uh, don't remember.
You have quotes in here from Jimmy.
Did you talk to him?
Uhhhhh...
Uhhhhh... I like the school paper.
Come on. We'll get
to the bottom of this.
Did I do good, computer?
I think the sponsored
content fooled them.
I hope I made you happy.
Can you see me, computer?
Do you know what I'm thinking right now?
Ahh, thanks, computer.
We have to make sure
nobody recognizes us.
There's no telling who works for who.
Here, Caitlyn, I got you
this fake mustache to put on.
I'm not putting on a
mustache. I'll look silly.
Oh, that... That's where you
draw the line, huh, Caitlyn?
Don't be an asshole.
No, you're right. That's nuts.
A woman wearing a mustache...
That's just ridiculous, huh, Cait...
All right, all right. I'll put it on.
No, no, please, Cait.
Don't put on a fake
mustache. That's crazy.
You don't want people
thinking you're a weirdo.
I mean, geez.
You're such an asshole.
What the hell is this?
What have they done to my town?
Keep your voice down!
Since when do we have
a flippin' Whole Foods?
Everything's changed.
Hi, there. You got a
minute for gay rights?
Gay rights? Geez, you
already got all those.
What the hell do you want to do now?
All right. Your total is $126.39.
And would you like to give a
dollar to help hungry children
get iPads to protect your
Internet safe space today?
I will.
What the Sam hell is going on?
Why would anyone think that
I'm on the principal's side?
I hate the principal.
I think he's a dick.
So, you don't know anything about the
principal that might be newsworthy?
Super School News-worthy?
Just that he hated me and
called me a blabbermouth.
I don't think I'm a blabbermouth.
I just like talking to people.
Leslie, what kind of plans do you have?
Do you have any plans?
What kind of plans?
Just, you know, plans.
Like, what are you
hoping to... accomplish?
I don't know. What are your plans?
Well, I want to pursue careers
in both news reporting and comedy.
Really? That's... different.
Yeah, you're pretty
different yourself, Leslie.
How so?
I'm starting to think that
maybe all ads aren't so bad.
Jimmy, you're thinking with your dick.
- I am not thinking with my dick.
- Yes, you are.
- No, I just think that she's a...
- Put your dick away.
She's an emotional,
interesting, caring girl.
Jim. Jimmy. That's your dick talking.
Believe me. I know how you feel.
Ads promise us things.
Ads are perfect.
But make no mistake... All ads lie.
And all ads deceive.
There... Leslie's
Instagram and her Twitter.
Last entry was 10 days ago.
What about Jimmy's?
Jimmy never used that stuff, remember?
He said he hated using the Internet.
How do you hate the Internet?
That's like hating titties.
What are you doing now?
I'm just looking for any news articles
or anything about PC Principal.
Where did you say PC Principal was from?
I think it was Vermont.
Maybe there's something
from the news in Vermont
that can give us a clue about...
God damn it. What the hell is this?
That's an ad for skiing in Vermont.
That looks fun!
Dude! Dude, look at this.
How PC culture is changing Vermont
from a state of intolerance to a...
Dude, there it is again!
It's that goddamn guitar!
This ad is fucking following me!
- Just click out of it.
- I'm trying!
God damn it. Get over here!
That's a pretty sweet-looking guitar.
It is pretty cool,
dude. It tunes itself.
How does it do that?
It's this company that does all
kinds of high-tech instruments.
See, look, I'll show you.
Oh, that's sweet. Send me
the link to this so I can...
Oh, dude, that new
"Frankenstein" movie's out.
I totally want to see that.
That movie's gonna suck, dude.
Hit the arrow. I want to
see where it's playing.
Oh, sorry. Wrong arrow button.
Wow! What kind of ice cream is that?
Yeah, yeah. So... So,
Clyde says to Token,
"Why don't you open a bank
account with your mouth
so I can deposit my dick in it?"
So then what did Token say?
Token was all like...
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, whoa, whoa.
What the hell are we doing?
Eating ice cream, dipshit.
But what about Jimmy? We were, like,
totally trying to find
out what happened to him.
Whoa.
What the hell just happened?
We got distracted!
We got to get back to that computer!
Now, this here is a dry Riesling.
You're gonna experience
vanilla after tones
and a nutty finish.
You mean like someone put
their balls in the glass?
Nah, like chestnuts, damn it.
I just can't keep up
with this town no more.
Everything's gettin' all nice and fancy.
I swear I'm gonna need
to get a second mortgage
on the ranch just to
pay my daily expenses.
Don't you get it?
That's just what they want.
Nobody cares about the
people who lived here before.
They want us to move
'cause then they want
to knock our houses down
and build more lofts and villas.
All right, Randy, you
should probably lay off
the ol' vine Chatuenuf de Pape.
You'll all see.
Pretty soon, everyone
who used to live here
is gonna have to move,
and we'll all be shopping
at the Safeway again.
♪ Where has my town gone? ♪
♪ Where has my... ♪
Oof!
You like apples?
How you like them apples?
Hey, it's Caitlyn Jenner!
Check his ass!
Principal Victoria?
- He's one of them.
- One of what?
Caitlyn.
Okay, Leslie, let's try
a different approach.
Let's say you wanted to
destroy an entire species.
How would you go about it?
Why would I want to
destroy an entire species?
You have the wrong idea about me, Jimmy.
The person trying to change things
and make everything terrible
is the new principal.
And what is the new Principal
trying to do, Leslie?
He's trying to make sure people like
you and me aren't allowed to exist.
I know that you're trying to help.
I know that the newsmen in
there are trying to help, too.
But now I'm going to tell you
something very important, Jimmy.
♪ Like a rock! ♪
♪ I drive a Chevy, I'm a cowboy,
and I drive it like a rock! ♪
What the hell is that?
Tom, it looks like a pop-up ad.
How did an ad get in here?
Let's go to David at the network hub.
No answers here, Tom.
We're trying to correct the problem.
You have to get me out of here, Jimmy.
- They're going to kill me.
- What?
Listen to me carefully,
and don't look at the glass.
I feel something for you
I have never felt before.
I think it's trust.
The men in there are sick with hatred,
and as soon as they realize
I have no information,
they are going to burn me.
I've seen them do it to others.
Please, you have to help me, Jimmy.
Don't let them hurt me.
Please don't abandon me.
When the lights go back on,
just look at me and smile.
David, any word on the
pop-up ad situation?
Tom, we've just about got it fixed.
Should be ready now.
And that's really it, Jimmy.
I want to help all of you however I can.
So, then Token tells Clyde
that if his mouth was a bank,
Clyde's mom would have already
deposited her dick in it,
which is hilarious because
Clyde's mom is dead!
Wait, wait, wait, whoa, whoa.
What the hell are we doing?
We're trying on shoes and
eating chicken nuggets, stupid.
What do you think?
No. That's not what we set out to do.
We were... We were
on Cartman's computer,
looking up news stories
about PC Principal.
Didn't we finish doing that?
No, we didn't.
It's like someone's trying
to distract us because
they're worried what we'll
uncover about PC people.
Yeah, like one of us is
purposely trying to keep us
from digging too deep
because they're afraid.
Why are you looking at me?
Why isn't anyone looking at me?
Hey, fuck you.
Wake up, dickhead.
Garrison, what the
hell is wrong with you?
I'll tell you what's wrong with me.
There's enemies to humanity out there,
wanting to put an end to all of us,
and there's assholes
like you helping them out!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Whose idea was it to revitalize
the shitty part of town
into an arts-and-foods
district called ShiTpaTown?
All right, it was kind of my idea.
Son of a bitch.
What, to take one area
of town that was crappy
and gentrify it for the
local people to enjoy?
I thought we could keep it contained!
It doesn't contain.
What's happened to South
Park is happening everywhere.
30 miles south of here
in the town of Fairplay,
they've changed an area north
of downtown into NODOFOPA:
A run-down area south of
the capital in Cheyenne,
Wyoming, is now historic SOCACHEYWO:
Channel Street in mid-Chicago
is being revitalized into Chimichanga.
Oh, my God.
LODO, SOBRO, RIVMO: All
happening at the same time.
And it isn't just in the U.S.
In Cairo, the area northwest
of the third pyramid is NoWE3Pi.
Three miles north of
Auschwitz is NoMoAuchie.
It goes on and on!
What does it mean?
In our town, it all started
when PC Principal arrived.
He's part of a much larger conspiracy,
and you're his lackey.
Not me.
If PC Principal has been using us,
I'll take the bastard down myself.
It's day two of the hunger strike
started by the college-aged
fraternity brothers
who are demanding that
all of South Park's
community leaders step down.
The PC frat brothers say
they've gone now two days
without eating any pussy
and will continue to do
so until people resign.
Who is that reporter? Do we... know him?
Tom, that's Bill Keegan, WCFO.
Thanks, Brian. He's working
for the ads, obviously.
Sellout douchebag.
That's right, Tom.
He was always a douchebag
at the conventions.
Thanks, Rick. Stay dry.
Leslie, come on.
Jimmy, you're gonna help me?
Yeah, I'm gonna help
you. I mean, come on.
Jimmy!
Oh, Jesus, he let her out!
PC Principal is our enemy, not her.
His dick is compromised. Stay back!
It is not my dick.
I'm thinking rationally and with logic.
I am taking her out of here.
Well, then, I'm sorry I
have to do this, Jimmy.
Officer Barbrady, we need
you to shoot these kids.
What?
The ad has gotten to him.
There's no time to argue.
I'm not shooting any more kids!
Do you want to save your town?
Officer Barbrady, we have to stop
PC Principal before it's too late!
Barbrady, shoot them in their heads!
No! I'm not shooting any more people...
Not for you, not for anybody!
You're making the worst
mistake of your life, officer.
Maybe so.
All I know is I'm done shooting people.
Aah!
Oh, sorry. Geez.
Damn it!
Think about it, you guys.
From the moment PC Principal took over,
Kyle's been different.
Haven't you noticed?
Yeah.
He's distracting us either because
he's too afraid or because he...
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing!
Stan's calling you a traitor.
What?
Kyle, I think it's pretty obvious you
don't want us investigating PC Principal.
- And why do you think that, Stan, huh?
- I don't know.
Because if anyone has a reason for us
to not mess with PC Principal, it's you!
Let's not forget that Stan's dad
is PC Principal's little bitch!
That's a good point!
I am loving this right now.
My dad's stupid, not a bitch.
This is about you being scared, Kyle!
It is you, isn't it?
That's why you're trying
to shift blame on me.
That's very Cartman of you, Stan.
Oh, that's low.
Don't you dare call me a Cartman!
No, that's good.
Just keep on distracting everybody.
It seems to be working, Cartman.
Fuck you, Kyle!
Fight!
Time to take this asshole down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Guys, whoa!
We can't just go walking in there.
Why not?
This is a safe space.
We're not allowed past this.
When you breach a college safe space,
you're crossing the most
sacred human boundary there is.
Oh, give me a break.
No, no, no, no, no.
Look, this is very real
and very important in PC culture.
Every human has a right to a safe space.
It cannot be entered.
Yeah, it can. Watch.
Wow, how did you...
Whoa!
Burning the midnight oil, huh, Nathan?
- Jimmy!
- You son of a bitch.
What have done to the Super School News?
I was just holding down the
fort while you were away, Jim.
Writing headlines sponsored
by PC Principal and the ads?
How much did they pay you?
Please, Jimmy. I'm just
trying to survive here.
Everyone's gonna know the truth, Nathan.
We're getting a new edition of
the school paper out by morning.
Everyone's going to
know all about the ads.
Deal with him.
Leslie, I thought we were b-besties.
Hey there, big man.
Editor of the school paper, huh?
You still don't even
know half the story.
It's clear.
Where is everybody?
I thought the news said
they're on a hunger strike.
This doesn't make sense.
Someone's always here.
Take a look at this!
What the hell?
It looks like he was researching this.
You see this news story?
If this is true, then PC
Principal was trying to help.
Click on that. What is that?
No, click out of that. What is this?
So, then... So, then, Caitlyn says,
"Look, bitch, you're
married to Bill Clinton.
If anyone should be
afraid of AIDS: it's you."
That stupid bitch had it coming.
Oh, God, I love you, Cait.
We are so gonna win the primaries.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
What... What were we doing again?
Leslie?
You're trying to find out
what's going on, right?
But your friend is standing in your way?
How do you know that...
I can show you what's going
on, Kyle, but you have trust me.
What's the last four digits of your soc?
2692.