♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Nobody is safe. Nobody can hide
from these monsters.
Internet trolls are truly
predators of society.
As parents,
we find it hard to believe
our children are doing
these things online.
And that is why I've been asked
to come and speak to you
about the student
who has been trolling
your school message boards.
This troll is known only
as Skankhunt42.
we believe it probable he's
one of the boy students here,
since his favorite target
seems to be women.
Here, you can see
Heidi Turner's mother
Photoshopped with a penis
in her mouth
after she defended
her daughter's right
to sit out the national anthem.
Since then, this child has been
trolling all over the Internet,
visiting message boards
and social media
and filling it
with vile comments
and hate-filled garbage.
But trolling is on the rise
with teenagers,
and we all need to come together
to stop it.
We need every parent to look for
the signs in their own child.
In order for us to find
these secretive monsters,
we need all parents
to ask themselves
"could my child be a troll?"
My God, what children
are capable of now.
What kind of hate would have to
be in that's child's heart?
Well, you never know.
Could be someone who just...
kind of thinks it's funny
to stir the pot
and watch everyone freak out.
Uh, you know, maybe the fact
that it's so not funny
makes it somehow funny...
to kids.
Gosh, I-I certainly
don't understand it.
Dude,
what's going on?
You didn't hear?
Hear what?
What happened?
Heidi Turner — she...
she quit Twitter.
Oh, no.
Yesterday after school.
She wrote one last tweet
that said, "Goodbye forever,"
and then just got off for good.
She'll get back on.
No, dude, she threw her phone
in the river.
She's — She's gone.
All right, students,
I know we're all dealing
with the loss of a good friend.
We have to accept the fact
that Heidi won't
be on social media anymore.
I know we're all gonna miss her.
M'kay?
We're gonna miss
seeing what she's up to,
miss seeing those silly pictures
she'd post
of her and her friends.
M'kay?
But this is what can happen
when someone gets bullied online
to the point they just can't
go on anymore.
I know that some of you
are feeling anger, m'kay,
some of you are feeling
a little guilt,
and asking how something
like this can happen.
But the best thing
we can do for Heidi
is come together
as friends and as students.
M'kay?
So now why don't we all
get on Twitter, m'kay,
and just tweet
some of the things
we loved about Heidi, m'kay?
M'kay.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
Oh, that's a good one, Sarah.
Uh-huh.
That's — that's a pretty poem.
Nice, Butters.
Oh, Heidi would have
loved this so much.
This is so special.
M'kay?
Okay,
can we all agree now
that whoever is doing this
needs to stop?
Totally, you guys.
This has gone far enough.
The girls are really
pissed off at us.
So tonight,
whoever is doing this
isn't going
to do it again.
'Cause if he does,
we're gonna have to do
something about it.
You hear that,
guys?
It better not happen
again tonight.
I am so seriously.
Ike, can I talk to you?
Come on.
Pull up a chair.
You know,
we had a big parent meeting
at the school tonight.
And, uh, apparently,
there's someone
trolling
the school message boards
and putting penises
in people's mouths.
And whoever it was
then got a big reaction from it,
so he's now putting penises
in people's mouths
all over the Internet and...
he's actually getting
pretty famous.
So, Annie Jerkins' mother
started an online campaign
to stop Internet trolling
with a picture of her
and her daughter,
and you know what happened?
She got a dick
in her mouth.
Okay, okay, I know
it's just guy humor stuff.
You know,
we can laugh about it here,
but it is serious,
too.
Well, love you, pal.
Get to sleep.
It's a school night.
Oh, hey!
Did you talk to him?
Yeah, yeah. We talked.
It was good.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, well, I better go
and get some of my work done.
Oh, right,
right, yeah.
Yeah, don't wait up.
I'll be a while with these
stupid case profiles.
All right.
Night, Gerald.
Night, sweetie.
♪ We're gonna play you a song ♪
♪ A little bit
of rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ We're gettin' down today ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Get down tonight ♪
♪ Smokin' ♪
♪ I feel all right, mama ♪
♪ I'm not jokin', yeah ♪
♪ Gettin' off today ♪
♪ We'll pick you up
and take you away ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Get down tonight ♪
♪ But all right ♪
You should have seen
what he said about my mother
on her Instagram!
Pages and pages
of disgusting things!
This is an attack
on all of us.
It's time to make
the boys suffer.
It has to be swift
and serious.
We have to make a statement
that girls in South Park
aren't going to be treated
like afterthoughts anymore!
Yeah! Yeah!
This has gone on too long,
and it's time to do something!
Yeah! Yeah!
What do you think
they're talking about?
They're talking about how
they're gonna get us!
What do you think?
That's how the world works now!
You get blamed
for the group you belong to,
even if you didn't
do nothing!
What are we gonna do
about him?
The girls want
to see Cartman punished,
so we have to prove
it's him!
We're never gonna prove that,
and you know it.
We have
to make him stop.
He's not gonna stop!
He's loving all this!
He wants the girls
to hurt us!
- Then let's end it.
- What do you mean?
Cartman is the cause
of all our problems, always.
We all know
what has to be done.
It's not like we haven't
talked about it before,
fantasized
about how we'd do it.
Yeah, but not like
we'd actually do it.
Clyde's right.
Stan,
you can't be thinking —
What else do we do, Kyle?
You know better than anybody
what a monster he is.
He pushed everyone
too far.
It's him or us.
Are we seriously
talking about doing this?
How would we ever
get away with it?
We do it out in the woods.
I know how to get him to go.
'Sup, dudes?
After school,
we're gonna go to my uncle's
cabin in the woods.
We're gonna have a slumber party
and play "Counterstrike"
all night
with no one around
to bother us.
Are you serious?
All night broship
"Counterstrike" party?
That's fuckin' sweet!
Does your uncle's cabin
have good Wi-Fi?
Yeah, but don't tell anyone
where you're going.
We don't want adults to know
'cause there's gonna be
a ton of junk food.
Bros!
Dude, that's so awesome!
This is gonna be
the best night ever!
'Member TIE fighters?
Oh, 'member Jawas?
'Member?
Hey, 'member
"Jurassic Park"?
Ooh, you loved
"Jurassic Park"!
'Member Jeff Goldblum?
Oh, I 'member Jeff Goldblum.
He was fantastic.
I love Jeff Goldblum.
'Member?
Mmm...
I can't do this anymore!
I can't take it!
Oh, uh, hi, Scott.
Nobody ever pays attention
to me! Nobody cares!
I just want to end it all!
Scott, come on.
We've talked about this.
You don't want
to quit Twitter.
Why not? Everyone would be
happier if I did!
Who'd be happier?
Everyone!
What about
your parents, huh?
How do you think they'd feel
if you quit Twitter?
I don't think
they'd even notice!
Of course they'd notice.
They'd be sad, m'kay?
They'd be sad.
You've got so much
ahead of you, Scott,
so many posts and tweets
still ahead of you.
You haven't started to see what
social media has to offer you.
You can't — You can't just
end it all, not now.
You're right. I guess
I don't want to quit Twitter.
There you go, m'kay?
But now
you come back here
anytime you're having bad
thoughts, m'kay?
Okay, thanks.
Twitter would be better off
without me! I'm quitting!
Okay, okay,
now, Scott —
What's the point?
Better to just end it all now!
M'kay.
This is gonna be so awesome,
just hanging with the bros,
playing "Counterstrike"
all night alone in the woods.
You pumped, Token?
Yeah,
I'm really excited.
I'm totally gonna do
massive pownage.
Whoever's on my team'll
be stoked.
My laptop's so fast,
it doesn't lag at all.
I can jump around
like a pownage powerhouse.
I'm sure you will.
You guys all seem
kind of, like, bummed out.
Is everything cool?
Everything's fine,
Cartman.
We'll just get there sooner if
maybe we don't talk much.
Okay, cool.
We're going a long a way
to play "Counterstrike."
Guess it's sweet,
though.
There won't be any adults
to screw it up for us.
How much further now?
We're almost there.
This place has
sweet Wi-Fi, right?
Gonna be so awesome.
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
Someone keeps trolling
our campaign site.
He just keeps leaving
horrible comments,
and now he's attacking me
personally.
Aw, don't let him
get to you.
Don't let him —
He took a picture I posted
and put a dick
in my mouth!
Who does that?
Someone who probably
still lives with his mother
and hates himself.
He obviously has
nothing better to do.
Just let the him wallow
in his own misery.
♪ I was lying on the grass
of Sunday morning of last week ♪
♪ Indulging in my self-defeat ♪
Get out of the street,
idiot!
Sorry. My bad.
You've got
to be an idiot
to want to vote
for that piece of garbage!
You're brain dead!
You're voting
for the terrorists!
Are you kidding me?
He's an idiot!
You're voting
for the terrorists!
No worries.
♪ If you steal my sunshine ♪
♪ Making sure
I'm not in too deep ♪
'Member the cantina?
Oh, I 'member!
'Member
the star destroyers?
Yeah, I loved
star destroyers!
'Member?
I have a coupon
for that, too.
And those are six for $4
with this coupon.
Sorry.
No, please.
It's no problem at all.
♪ If you steal my sunshine ♪
♪ My sunshine ♪
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna quit Twitter.
I mean it this time.
Oh, Scott, uh, it —
it's sort of after hours, m'kay?
They all laugh at me.
They won't be laughing
when I do it!
I'll show them!
All right, Scott.
Come on inside.
Oh, dude, is this it?
This is cool.
So isolated.
Check it out.
There's a shovel
next to a hole
dug in the ground.
Dude, is this where
we're gonna play?
I call dibs on this side.
What's the Wi-Fi called?
Is there a password?
I don't see it. I don't see it
coming up on my laptop.
I don't know, I think
maybe the Wi-Fi's not working.
Where's the box? You got to
unplug it and plug it back in.
You guys?
You guys... there's...
no Wi-Fi.
The girls are gonna
do something drastic to us.
We have to take matters
into our own hands.
What are you —
What are you guys talking about?
You brought this
on yourself, Cartman.
We're sorry.
Oh, my God.
You guys are gonna
break all my stuff
so I can't get online.
Just put your stuff on the table
and step back.
Please! Please, don't break
my stuff, you guys!
This is like two Christmases
and a birthday worth of stuff!
You guys can't do this!
Please!
Let's just
get it over with.
No, don't take them from me!
Don't break my stuff!
I'm not Skankhunt!
I'm not!
You guys — you guys,
you don't have to do this.
You don't have to do this.
We can still
just play "Counterstrike"
and forget everything.
Oh, my God.
There's no Wi-Fi.
We can use my phone
to make a hot spot!
We can still
play "Counterstrike"!
It will be sweet!
You guys come on, please!
Please, you can't!
I can't listen to this.
Please, Clyde!
Clyde, you're my friend!
Please, you — you know how much
I need my stuff!
Let's just
get it over with!
No, please, if I can't
get online, I won't have a life!
Oh, God! No!
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
What have we done?
What we had to do.
Ugh!
Oh, God damn it.
You have got to be kidding me.
This is Counselor Mackey.
What's going on, Scott?
I swear to God,
I'm gonna do it this time.
Okay, Scott,
just try and calm down.
You don't want
to quit Twitter.
Why does it matter?
People would be happier
if I just did it!
That's not true.
No one would be happier.
This fuckin' kid.
Oh, my God.
Everybody thinks
you're a great kid, Scott.
I talked to my dad.
He said I don't have
the guts to do it.
Well, if I quit Twitter,
he'd be sorry!
Okay, um, how about this —
just, um, promise me
you won't quit Twitter tonight,
and we can — we can talk
all day tomorrow, okay?
M'kay?
I don't know if I'll make it
through the night!
Oh, for fuck's sake.
I just feel like
I'm at the edge of a cliff,
you know,
and being chased by hate,
and the only way out
is to jump.
Uh-huh.
M'kay.
Yeah, go on with that.
I keep thinking about what
the kids at school would do
when they find out I left
all my social media,
like they would finally see
all the damage they've done.
God damn it.
Just do it already.
♪ ... take you away ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Get down tonight ♪
♪ Well, all right! ♪
Another Internet troll
is wreaking havoc
on message boards,
this time attacking
a Danish website
for women with breast cancer.
I made the news.
The troll, who goes
by the name Skankhunt42...
Yes!
caused the website
to temporarily shut down.
Danish Olympic gold medalist
Fireja Ollengaurd,
who started the website,
spoke out about the incident.
I am not shocked.
I am not sad.
I am not giving
this pitiful person
the satisfaction
of being anything.
This little troll
can have his fun.
I'm going to be
the bigger person.
I am going to show
that people of Denmark
are not so easily broken down.
Hmm.
Game on, whore.
Game on.
What's going on?
You didn't hear?
Hear what?
The troll,
Skankhunt, Kyle —
he was all over
the Internet last night.
No.
That's impossible.
It wasn't him, Kyle!
We took Cartman out
for no reason.
We can't undo
what we've done.
Oh, my God.
The time has come.
We said
if the trolling didn't stop,
there would be
severe consequences.
Get the word out
to every girl in school.
It goes down tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
I don't know if I can
go through with this.
We all have to be
on board, Wendy.
Every girl in school
or it means nothing.
Don't forget
what you said, Wendy.
For too long, girls here have
taken the back seat.
Things have to change.
Now they'll have to listen.
Noooooooooooooooooo!
M'kay?
Oh, that's nice. That's nice.
Oh, that's a good one, Sarah.
Uh-huh.
That — That's —
That's a pretty poem.
Nice, Butters.
Oh, Heidi would have
loved this so much.
This is so special.
M'kay?