♪ I'm goin' down to south park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces everywhere
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ goin' down to south park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking day or night
♪ people spouting,
"howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ heading on up to south park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Troll hunter:
long ago in the dim and frozen
lands of scandinavia,
There were creatures who wreaked
havoc on humanity — the troll.
They dwelled in rocks, in caves,
isolated from civilization.
The creatures were ugly, fat,
and slow-witted.
But some could also look
and behave like human beings.
These were the most dangerous.
Now the creatures have returned.
This time,
1,000 miles across the sea.
Today the monsters believe
they can go undetected,
Free to attack and then retreat
to the darkness.
But in denmark, we have dealt
with the trolls before.
And now,
we shall deal with them again.
Dad, can I talk to you?
Sure, kyle.
All the girls at school
are really mad.
It's like
one guy gets online
And says terrible things
about girls,
And it reflects badly
on all of us.
Uh-huh.
Everyone's sad,
everyone's depressed,
And nobody knows
how to move forward.
Good.
I guess
what I'm saying is
I'm starting to feel a lot
of guilt just for being a boy.
How do I not feel that?
Sorry, kyle,
I have to meet someone.
Talk to your mother.
I love you.
It's been
a rough few weeks, baby.
The girls are still mad
About being trolled
on the school message board,
Parents are all freaking out
about the election,
And let me tell you,
you're glad not to be living
In this country
right now.
Butters, I'm sorry,
But I told you not to skype me
anymore, right?
But, charlotte, I love you.
I need you.
You can't break up with me.
I have to stand
with my girlfriends.
Oh, my god.
I can't believe they got to you.
Those slinky snakes
in the grass!
Who?
You know who!
The girls at my school!
They all broke up
with their boyfriends,
And now they got you
to go along with them!
This is a time when women and
girls have to stand together.
So then it's true!
You're all snakes in the
grass — every last one of you!
Oh, charlotte?
Are you there?
Honey?
I don't know
why you're harassing me.
I don't even
own a computer.
My name is dick.
Are you with the nsa
or homeland security?
No. I'm a colleague.
A colleague?
You probably know me
as dildo shwaggins.
Dildo shwaggins
from pussystormers. Org?
We need to talk.
You're just a troll?
Oh, thank god!
We're on the same team,
skankhunt.
Wait. That means I went
protocol zero for nothing.
Oh, shit!
What's protocol zero?
Everything's gone.
I destroyed my computers,
my phone.
Why couldn't you just say,
"I know who you are.
I'm a troll, too."
Why'd you have to be
so fucking cryptic?
Us trolls have to be careful.
You know that.
Look, I'm not
really a troll, okay?
I just started
as a yelp reviewer
And got sick of how stupid
everyone's comments sounded.
I just like messing with people
'cause it was funny.
I got carried away.
These are really dangerous
times, skankhunt.
There are things happening
in the world,
And trolls
have to come together.
For what?
Someone is trying
to wipe us out.
Our way of life
is in danger.
It's not a way of life.
I was just doing it
for the lols.
That's not true.
I've studied your work.
You're one of the best trolls
I've ever seen.
No, no, I'm done
with this crap.
I thought my wife
was gonna find out.
That was too spooky.
Gerald,
we need each other!
The danish are planning
something horrible against us!
I'm not one of you,
okay?
I just need to stop.
Guys, I've been
thinking this over a lot,
And we need
to be more active
In showing the girls
we respect them.
There's a big
girls' volleyball game tonight,
And we should all go
and show our support.
You really think
that's gonna make a difference?
I do. We need to show the girls
that all boys
Aren't the same, and that we are
willing to change.
Oh, why don't you
shut the fuck up, kyle?
All I've been hearing about
the past few weeks
Is how this is our problem,
how boys need to change.
Well, I'm getting
pretty sick of it!
Everyone else
seems to be able to be proud
Of who they are,
but not us.
And then we got uncle kyle here
telling us the girls are right.
Butters.
This is a war
on all of us!
You want to listen
to uncle kyle? Go ahead!
Pretty soon they'll be
locking us all up.
And don't think you're safe,
either, tweek and craig.
Just 'cause you're gay
doesn't mean
You aren't looked down upon
for being boys.
The world wants us all
to feel shame
Just 'cause we were all born
with wieners!
Butters,
you need to calm down.
No! We tried doing it
your way, kyle.
We tried doing what the girls
wanted us to do,
And where
did it get us?
Nowhere.
Right! It turned us against
one of our own,
That's what it did!
What happened to eric cartman is
the girls' fault, not ours!
That's true.
I'm done feeling guilt.
I'm a boy, dag nab it.
And you know what,
I'm proud of my little wiener!
Mark my words —
The moment is coming
when you all need to decide.
Are you with your kind,
or are you with uncle kyle?
Gerald, you've been
sitting at the table
For three hours now.
You okay?
I'm great. Totally good just
sitting and... Doing nothing.
Is there a problem
with that?
Is there a problem with wanting
to sit and just be?
Is that illegal now?
Not at all, gerald.
I'm sorry.
I'm totally happy.
I'm... Happy.
I don't need to do anything
to make me happy.
Fuck!
Well, I know you said
your computer was broken, so...
I went ahead
and got you something.
Here,
it's your own ipad.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
No, no, I-I-I'm good.
Get that away from me.
You don't like it?
No, sorry, I love it.
I'm just... Swearing off
electronics for a little bit.
Or maybe I could just get on
a couple of message boards.
No! I'm good!
I don't need it!
Gerald,
what's going on?
Nothing, sheila.
I'm fine.
I'm just trying
to make some changes,
And less electronics
is part of it.
I'm sorry, honey.
Everything is okay. I promise.
Okay, gerald.
I'll make us some lunch.
Oh, uh, did that guy outside
talk to you?
What guy outside?
What the fuck?
go away! Go!
Go! Go away! Go! Go!
Goddamn it!
Welcome,
students and parents,
To tonight's match-up
between the south park cows
And the buena vista demons.
Dude,
this is awesome!
Do you see how many of the boys
I got to come tonight?
Yeah, this is
a pretty sweet turnout.
This is exactly
what we needed.
Thank god
people listened to me.
And now, please sit, stand,
Or kneel
for the national anthem.
Holy crap, dude.
Look at butters.
Oh, no!
Son a bitch!
Ah!
Gerald.
Hey, come on in.
You're not alone, bud.
We're all facing
the same struggles
And trying to do something
about it.
Anyway, please continue,
richard.
Well, like I was saying,
I've been addicted
To memberberries
for about two months now.
It's okay, man.
You're not alone.
It's just, you know,
Membering is so much more fun
than thinking.
I want so bad to go back
when things were good —
When I was a kid, you know?
Like, the '80s and the '90s,
and things made sense, you know?
And that's how we got here to
this very memberberry election.
What is this?
What have been your struggles
with memberberries, gerald?
I-I don't even know
what a member—
Memberberry #1:
Member the degobah system?
Memberberry #2:
Oh, I loved degobah!
That's where yoda lived!
Memberberry #3:
Member yoda?
Oh, I member!
Michael, are there memberberries
in your pocket?
Oh-ho!
Member corellian corvettes?
I member
corellian corvettes!
Nope.
Anyway, gerald,
what has your experience been?
I don't even know
what memberberries are.
Gerald, come on.
The first step towards healing
Is admitting
you've got a problem.
Yeah?
Well, you've got a fat pussy,
And you should go
and fucking kill yourself!
Sorry.
I think I'm in the wrong place.
Make no mistake.
I want to be very upset.
However, as a community,
we have all decided
That people have the right
to protest the national anthem.
They took
their wieners out!
Correct.
But they did so peacefully
And without malice
towards others.
This was
an attack on us.
This is exactly why
we sat out the national anthem
In the first place!
I want you to understand
something, ladies.
I am in a pc pretzel here
Because if I say
they can't protest
Even though you protested,
And the only difference is
their protest
Included physical gestures,
then I'm body-shaming!
So, you're just gonna
let boys take their wieners out
Whenever they want?
That's what happens when
you sit out the national anthem.
We walk together in peace!
We walk together in pride!
We are not going to feel
ashamed for who we are!
We are not going to feel guilt
for the way we were born!
Wieners out!
Don't let anyone tell you
you're somehow less
Because you're a boy!
Don't let anyone tell you
to not think with your wiener,
As if your wiener is
a bad thing!
Yeah!
That's right!
What makes us different
makes us beautiful!
No more shame!
No more doubt!
No more bigotry!
Wieners out!
Don't be an uncle kyle!
Be proud of who you are!
You are either with us
or against us!
It's really that simple!
damn it! Get out of here!
Stop that!
You don't have to work
tonight?
Nope!
Nothing!
Wow. I don't remember
the last time you were able
To actually get in bed
at the same time as me.
Got all caught up
with my work!
Hey, I'm not complaining.
It feels good to have you here.
I'm going on a run!
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
yeah.
Screw you, skank.
You fat, little bitch!
Go —
go kill yourself, whore!
Yeah, fuck you, bitch!
Fuck you! Yeahhaha haha!
Fuck you, bitch! Hahaha!
Gerald?
aah!
oh, sorry, hon!
Sorry!
Everything all right,
guys?
Everything's fine, kyle.
Go back to bed.
One night, y-you say all
our computer stuff is broken,
And you —
you hide everything!
And then you show up
with all this new equipment
And now this!
Please!
Tell me
what's going on!
Nothing is going on.
You hissed at me!
You went
Okay, okay. I-I'm going to tell
you the truth, sheila.
I watch porn
on the internet.
Sorry.
I'll try to stop.
But I know
you watch porn.
You told me
you watch porn,
And I told you
I don't care, gerald.
Oh, yeah!
But, uh...
It's, uh...
But this is different.
Why? Because it's not...
Normal porn?
Right.
Like something
really embarrassing?
It's really embarrassing.
Tell me.
It's... Porn.
It's... Piss... Porn.
Piss porn.
Piss porn?
Like people
peeing on each other?
See?
It's so embarrassing.
No wonder I hid it,
right?
Phew.
I'm sorry.
It's good to get it out
in the open, though.
Do you want me
to pee on you?
No!
You only like watching
other women pee?
Oh, no, no. It's —
it's not like that.
Because
they're pretty?
You have to
watch it on a video
Because I'm overweight
and old?
No!
I-I-I want you to.
I just couldn't ask.
You do? Promise?
Yes?
Am I doing it right,
gerald?
Yep.
So hot, honey.
Ugh. Warm. Ugh.
Hi, cartman.
Hey, kyle.
I'm so sorry.
What we did to you.
This internet troll
has everyone going crazy.
We shouldn't have assumed
it was you.
We shouldn't have...
Broke all your stuff.
Cool.
That's cool.
No.
I know it's not cool.
I know you're figuring out
how to get back at us.
I saw a vagina, kyle.
What?
I'm not holding a grudge.
I'm happier now.
I have purpose.
You saw whose vagina?
My girlfriend's.
She stood six feet away
and flashed it really fast.
But in that instant,
you know what I saw?
I saw that humankind
could colonize mars.
I saw the potential
of our species
To terraform other planets
and reach the infinite.
Yeah, right, okay.
I'm being serious, cartman.
Butters needs
to be taken down a notch,
And you're
the best at that.
Eric! Hey, I got us
chocolate milks!
Of course you did,
'cause you're amazing.
And look
what I made you.
The pink and blue one?
That's what
my baby wanted.
Yay!
Put it on me!
Oh, sorry.
Heidi, you know kyle.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, kyle.
The show's on
at 5:00 tonight
If you want to watch
at your house or my house.
Oh, either way, we totally can.
I just —
I guess kyle had something
to talk to us about first.
Go ahead, kyle.
Uh...
The school's
in trouble and, um...
O-our friends are —
He said something about us
working together
To help
take down butters?
Why?
What's going on, boo?
I'm not sure, boo.
Could you start
from the beginning, kyle?
Heidi's amazing
at figuring things out.
It wasn't supposed to be
like this.
I just thought it was funny
making people get riled up.
It was just stupid, harmless
locker-room humor...
Until I made that lady
kill herself.
you can't deny
who you are, skankhunt.
don't call me that here!
Why can't you just
go away?
Because
we're all in danger!
Didn't you see the video
I sent you?
No!
Don't you get it?
I went protocol zero!
I broke my phone!
I deleted
all my e-mail accounts
So that nobody
can trace me ever again!
They will be able to.
Everyone.
You need to see this video,
skankhunt.
The whole world
is about to change.
You want to know
what's really going on?
I'll tell you
what's going on.
Even though women have made
great gains in the last century,
There's still a part of men
who aren't comfortable
With women having power.
It really
just comes down to that.
And then you have social media,
which allows men to
Anonymously say horrific things
like "women aren't funny,"
Even though heidi's, like,
the funniest person I ever met.
Pssh, shut up.
No, it's true.
Get over yourself.
I don't even try
to be funny.
I know. You don't have to
because you're awesome.
Cartman, will you just help me
mess with butters
To stop his little agro club
from getting any bigger?
Like, mess with
butters how?
What do you mean,
"mess with butters?"
You know what I mean.
Come on!
We need
the old cartman back.
Oh, I see.
You have a problem with heidi.
What?
You're threatened by her
Because she actually has
interesting things to say
And she's
funnier than you.
That's not true at all.
Oh, she's not
funnier than you?
Or is she just not funny
because she's a girl?
Babe, stop. I don't think
he meant anything by it.
Sorry, babe. It just
really ruffles my feathers.
Look, kyle,
I think it's great
You're trying to patch things up
with everyone,
But the truth is,
eric and I are
Just kind of
out of it now.
We're just
We gave up social media
and all the ugliness
That goes along with it,
and we're in a better place.
Humans.
On mars.
I'm warning you,
skankhunt,
This video is really gonna
rock your world.
can you please call me gerald?
It's a very obscure news story
from the bbc in England.
Hardly anyone's
even seen it over here.
This is why we all have to
come together, skank.
since the dawn of the internet,
Message boards and chat rooms
have lit up with people
Who incite and insult
for no apparent reason.
They're called "trolls."
And a controversial company
in denmark
Is working to make them
a thing of the past.
The days of trolls
hiding behind nicknames
And message boards are over,
the danish claim,
As a new website,
trolltrace. Com,
Will soon be up and running.
In less than a month,
the servers will become active.
Anyone can take
any troll comment
And send it
through the danish servers
Where a real name and a physical
address will be attached.
Every message, every comment
ever made by trolls
Will retroactively be given
a tag with the author's name,
Location,
and full internet history.
Fuck.
I told you.
And this is the man
who has masterminded it all.
What this
will allow people to do
Is trace back harmful
and hateful postings or e-mails.
You see, the troll hides behind
a protective layer,
If you will, that
internet anonymity provides.
We intend to strip them
of that protection
So that everyone will know
who they are.
And what about people
who will use this
To spy on others
who aren't trolls?
Uh, what do you mean?
Once your servers
become active,
Anyone could trace
anything on the internet
Back to
whoever wrote it.
How do you stop that
from happening?
Oh, oh. Right.
This service is only for tracing
the identity of trolls.
Thank you.
Komme oot troll.
Komme oot und dee.
I google translated
the last part.
He says "come out, troll.
Come out and die."
This can't be happening.
By next week, everything
everyone has ever done online
Is gonna be available
to the public.
Then it's over.
I-I'm dead.
You're not dead,
skankhunt.
There's still hope.
Everyone! Can I have
your attention please?
I know the past few weeks
have been very difficult...
For all of us.
I know, now more than ever,
that something has to change.
I thought a lot about this
the past few days.
I've seen a lot of things I
never thought I would ever see.
These are all complex issues
we're having to face.
And now I know
that after you break it down,
There's really
only one answer.
Good for you,
uncle kyle!
Fellow trolls, let me
introduce you to... Skankhunt42.
I'm not necessarily
skankhunt42.
It's okay, skank.
You're with
your kind.
Am I doing it right,
gerald?
Yep.
So hot, honey.
Ugh. Warm. Ugh.