♪ I'm goin' down to South
Park, gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting, "howdy, neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm! Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Hello, everyone, and welcome back.
We are live at South
Park Elementary school,
where the local girls volleyball team
is about to take on
the Jefferson Sabers.
And, Jim, it is a packed.
Sell-out crowd tonight... The
first time in team history.
Everyone turning out to
see what's gonna happen.
That's right, Mike. All eyes tonight are
of course on 4th grader Nichole Daniels.
Will she sit or stand
for the national anthem?
This week, with athletes
all over the country
sitting down for the national anthem,
the question on everyone's mind is,
what is this little girl gonna do?
She's not gonna sit down. Why would she?
Screw that. I got a hundred
bucks riding on this.
Come on, Nichole! Sit it out!
Now please rise for the national anthem.
This is it!
The national anthem starts.
Nichole Daniels seems to be waiting.
So far, no sign of... Oh, and
Heidi Turner is sitting down!
Mike, this is totally unexpected.
All eyes were on
Nichole when Heidi Turner
comes out of nowhere
and sits down for...
And there goes Meagan Ridley!
The crowd is going wild.
What a turn of events.
Let's check in with Dave.
Ed and Mike, I've just looked
at the girls' Twitter accounts,
and it appears they are
sitting out the national anthem
to protest all the harassment and
trolling they receive on the Internet!
Complete surprise, Dave.
Nobody saw this coming.
Three girls now sitting down, and...
And finally there goes Nichole.
- Wow!
- Yeah, 100 bucks!
And now as the anthem draws
to a close, this thing is over.
The final result...
Four athletes sitting out
on the national anthem,
three of them not even black.
A shocker here in South Park.
Thanks for joining us.
Oh, my God, that was great!
Uh, play ball.
All right, ladies, first
of all, I want to say
that I completely respect your
decision to protest our national anthem.
I thought it was sweet.
I believe you shed some light
on some very important issues
regarding gender equality.
What are you doing about Eric Cartman?
Ladies, I understand you're upset about
the trolling you've
received on the Internet.
But there is no evidence that
Eric Cartman is skankhunt42.
It is him. It's completely obvious,
and nobody's doing anything about it.
Well, he claims that he's been working
at changing himself and
the world around him.
Send in Mr. Cartman.
You wanted to see me, PC Principal?
Mr. Cartman, I'm gonna
ask you one more time.
Are you or are you not the
Internet troll skankhunt42?
It's skank-hunt42, and no, I am not.
He's lying. Make him show you his phone.
Unfortunately, that'd be a
breach of my civil rights.
But I can assure you, nobody respected
you girls' poignant
protests more than I did.
Fellow Senators, our nation
is divided like never before.
While people everywhere fight
for their voices to be heard,
perhaps it is time for us to consider
that our national anthem
needs to be changed.
Americans need an anthem
that inspires and excites,
an anthem that has
something for everyone,
while still paying tribute
to what it once was.
I believe there's
only one person capable
of achieving this...
J.J. Abrams.
Oh, J.J. Abrams!
He saved "Star Wars,"
and now we will ask
him to save our country.
Mr. Abrams?
Mr. Abrams, we need to speak with you.
Look there.
Mr. Abrams, I speak on behalf
of Americans everywhere.
We've come to ask you to
reboot the national anthem.
Please, Mr. Abrams,
we know you've been
asked to reboot a lot.
We know you're tired.
What do you say, sir?
We all want something new,
but that makes us remember
the things we loved.
We want to member.
We need your memberberries!
One light means yes.
Two lights means no.
Fellow students, as you
know, an Internet troll
by the name of skankhunt42 has
been harassing women and girls
by making degrading comments
on our school message board.
The girls are very upset,
and many male students believe
that it's just because girls
don't have a sense of humor.
I beg to disagree.
Girls rule. Women are
funny. Get over it.
Just the other day in the hallway,
I heard two male students saying how
the new "Ghostbusters" sucked balls.
I was shocked and appalled.
It is time for us all
to realize and accept
that girls are cool and women are funny.
Wendy? Wendy, could you
come up here, please?
Come on up, Wendy.
Wendy Testaburger, guys.
Wendy, go ahead. Be funny.
Say something funny,
Wendy. We can't wait.
I'm not funny.
Hey, girls are funny
Wendy, okay? Get over it.
Just do women's comedy
stuff... You know, talk about
how fat you are and how you
want to have sex with guys
and then say "my vagina!" a lot.
I don't feel like being funny right now.
And that's just the kind of sexist bull
crap that's gonna keep you in the kitchen.
Sit your ass down.
This isn't a joke, you
guys. Girls are funny.
Bebe, why don't you come up here.
Come on, Bebe.
No!
No?
Come on, talk about having sex with guys
and say "vagina!" and stuff like that.
Go ahead.
Girls rule. Women are funny.
Bebe, get over yourself, seriously.
Get the mic out of my face!
Huh. Oh, my God, that
wasn't really all that funny.
That's weird. Um...
Let's see. Red, you got
any zingers for the crowd?
No? How about you, Nelly?
Yeah, I got one. You're a fat fuck.
'Kay, that wasn't really
funny. It was just angry.
You see, what the problem is,
is that when a little troll
is allowed to say anything
he wants anonymously,
then he speaks for all you boys.
'Kay, that's good. Now, just try
and say it a little bit funnier now.
Go ahead and get on
our school message board
and see what he's saying about us.
Then see if you guys think it's funny.
Okay, and then... and then...
And then just go "my vagina!"
And as our country seems
to be more and more divided,
the only hope is that J.J.
Abrams' new national anthem
will appeal to everyone and bring back
those nostalgic memberberries
we know and love.
Oh, great.
Everything's getting a reboot now.
Hello, sir. I'm with the Gallup poll.
We're trying to get a read on how people
will be voting in the
upcoming presidential election.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Great. And will you be
voting for the Giant Douche
or the Turd Sandwich?
Well, this is usually a
Giant Douche household,
but we are going firmly
with the Turd Sandwich.
- Oh, the Turd Sandwich, huh?
- That's right.
You can put my wife and I
both down for Turd Sandwich.
Well, good luck with that.
So far, Giant Douche
is leading in the polls.
What?
What the hell is wrong with people?
They really think that a Giant Douche
should be president? It's insane!
Why'd you say I'd be voting
for the Turd Sandwich, Randy?
You haven't even talked to me about it.
You can't possibly be thinking
about voting for the douche.
What's wrong with you?
I just don't understand
why every four years,
you people freak out over whether to vote
for a Giant Douche or a Turd Sandwich.
Because we're Americans.
'Cause this is America.
Why are we doing this again?
Why are we back to Giant
Douche and Turd Sandwich?
Cynical...
Cynical man!
You just think everything
and everyone is dumb, huh?
- 'Cause you're a
kneel-ist? - It's ni-hi-list.
See? You're such a nihilist.
The newest Gallup poll results are in,
and they show Giant Douche
to be leading Turd Sandwich
by nearly 10%.
Turd sandwich has said
there is no need to panic.
Polls are of course a useful tool,
but they can often be misleading.
Our campaign is holding strong.
- Mrs. Sandwich, over here!
- Uh, Mrs. Sandwich.
- Mrs. Sandwich!
- Question, Mrs. Sandwich!
Yes, Arthur.
Well, Mrs. Sandwich, do you believe
that your opponent will gain
any momentum from this poll?
I'm sure that like me,
Giant Douche realizes
that polls are never the final answer.
♪ Sell to me, baby ♪
Yeah!
Suck that poll, you dumb bitch!
Up 10%. Can you believe that shit?
Oh, Caitlyn, I think we're
really gonna win this thing.
Think about it.
In a couple of months,
I will be president
of the United States.
Caitlyn, can I ask you something?
Uh, when we actually
get into the White House,
like, um, what are we gonna do?
What do you mean?
Well I mean, like, you know, once
we're president and vice president,
like, what do we do then?
How the fuck should I know?
Cait, you... you heard
about the poll, right?
We're probably gonna win.
Don't tell me you don't have a plan!
What plan? I thought you had a plan!
I don't have any fucking plan!
That's why I have you!
I'm gonna be the president,
and you're gonna be in charge
of all foreign and domestic policies!
I thought you were gonna do that part.
Are you telling me that we're
about to be voted into office,
and we have no idea what
the fuck we're gonna do?
Oh, geez!
I think they called it
"German collective guilt," right?
Where even the Germans
who just did nothing
while Hitler rose to power were...
were maybe somehow also responsible?
Mm-hmm. M'kay. M'kay.
But I can't control what Cartman does,
so why should I feel shame
for what Cartman does?
Well, J.J. Abrams is rebooting
the national anthem, Kyle,
so everything's gonna be fine, m'kay?
I don't think the answer to
all this is memberberries.
You don't like mem... memberberries?
Never mind. I'm just
gonna stay out of it.
'Member Chewbacca?
Yeah, a-a-and
'member AT-ATs?
'Member?
Hey, hey!
'Member "Ghostbusters"?
Oh, I 'member.
'Member Slimer?
- Oh, I loved Slimer.
- 'Member?
How could someone think
these things are bad?
- 'Member Storm Troopers?
- 'Member?
The Commander In Chief Forum,
with a Giant Douche and a Turd Sandwich.
Back now with the
Commander In Chief Forum.
I am joined by the Republican
nominee... a Giant Douche.
Thanks, Matt.
Mr. Douche, some say
you don't actually have
a viable plan in place if you
were to be elected president.
Oh, well, well, who said that?
The Turd Sandwich?
In your campaign, you said that you will
deal with our country's
immigrants and enemies
by personally "Fucking
them all to death."
How do you plan to
actually achieve that?
Well, Matt, I don't think I said
I would fuck them all to death.
Okay, well, let's roll the tape on that.
Oh, sure, okay.
Well, there's only
one immigration policy
that I believe in, and
that's fuck them all to death!
Fuck them all to death. Let's
make this country great again.
Fuck them all to death!
And then I'm gonna take all
the drug pushers in our country,
and I'm gonna fuck them!
And you know those people in
Syria? I'm gonna fuck them.
That's why I will make sure
that every terrorist on Earth
is fucking dead!
The leaders of North
Korea, I'll fuck them all!
Yeah! Yeah!
Criminals in our jails... Fucking dead!
A day after...
Yeah! Those ads that
are trying to kill us?
I'll fuck anyone in the
advertising business,
and they'll all die, too!
So, by our estimates, it's
roughly 7.6 million people
you have promised to fuck to
death in your first year of office.
Uh-huh. Okay.
And... And you think that's achievable?
I do. I do, Matt. Uh, I mean...
I'm not gonna just
get elected, you know,
and... and look like a jackass.
Oh, geez...
All right, kids.
Today, we have a very special treat.
One of the older students has written
an original children's story
and is gonna read it to you.
Come on over, Eric.
Hi, guys!
Are you all ready to hear a story?
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
This was a book I created
all with my imagination.
It's called "Little Red Riding Kyle:
the Story of a Little
Gay Boy and His Adventure
with Four Hilarious Women."
"One day, Little Red Riding Kyle
was walking through the forest,
thinking about guys.
He was on his way to visit his grandma,
who was a little black boy named Token.
Get over it.
But, then, a big, bad wolf,
who was a hilarious woman
named Janet, walked
into the house and said,
'I have a large vagina!'
and traded place...
What the hell are you doing?
Rebooting fairy tales to try and ease
the friction caused by Internet trolls.
You really think you're fooling
anyone with this fake persona?
Everyone knows you're
acting this way by day
so you can be horrible to
people on the Internet at night!
Why would I do that, Kyle?
I don't really care! Just
don't drag me into it!
What is wrong with people, huh?
How can they vote
against a Turd Sandwich
more than a Giant Douche?
It's senseless!
Randy, you got to calm down.
How can anyone be calm
in a time like this?
People actually think a
turd is worse than a douche!
Look, maybe you need some supplements
to help calm your nerves.
Have you heard of memberberries?
Memberberries?
It's a new super fruit that
helps you mellow out and relax.
'Member "The Fugitive"?
- 'Member "Bambi"?
- 'Member "Alien Nation"?
The guys at work told me about them.
Been taking them about six months now.
I'm telling you, they
really take the edge off.
- 'Member explorers?
- The little kids in a spaceship?
- 'Member Stormtroopers?
- 'Member?
Oh, they're adorable.
'Member the Millennium Falcon?
Come on, people, I need answers!
Real solutions!
You're my advisers, for Christ's
sake! How do we do this?
Maybe if you swam in a pool in Florida,
you could contract the Zika virus.
Then, you fuck all the people you can
and hope they eventually die.
That would take way too long!
And there's no guarantee
every pool in Florida has Zika!
Could you use nuclear weapons,
then fuck all the bodies after the fact?
What the hell do I do?
If I win, I won't be able
to do what I promised.
But every day, I keep
going up in the polls.
Why did the Democrats have
to elect such a Turd Sandwich?
Maybe you should just quit.
If I quit, I look like a total jackass.
If I win the election...
I look like a total jackass.
I have to keep running,
but I have to make sure she wins.
You guys see what skankhunt42
did on the school server now?
He Photoshopped a picture
of Heidi Turner's mom
with a dick in her mouth!
I want to see.
Look! There's Wendy's mom
with a dick in her mouth, too?
God damn it!
Do you guys even care how
this makes the girls feel?
- We didn't do it.
- We all know who did.
And if we don't do something, then the
girls will eventually retaliate against us.
Help! Help me!
Eric, what happened?
A bunch of the girls...
They cornered me in the gym!
They said all boys needed to pay!
They kicked me, and they hit me,
and then they held me down and
drew this vagina on my face!
They said it was to send a message!
That's a vagina?
Yeah, see? Here's the top of the
vagina, and there's the balls.
It's starting, you guys!
None of us are safe anymore!
I didn't know vaginas had balls.
Yeah, no, they do.
Vaginas totally have balls, right?
You're just trying to
start a war, aren't you?
What do you mean?
If vaginas don't have
balls, what do they have?
It's not gonna work, Cartman!
I'm not gonna let you divide boys
and girls in this school anymore!
When this whole thing comes to a head,
you're gonna be all on your own.
Hello, sir. How are you today?
I'm calling from the
campaign for president,
just seeing if, uh,
I can get your support
for Hillary Clinton today?
Yes, I know she's a Turd
Sandwich, but, you know,
if... if you look past
that, you know, she...
She really has a lot to offer.
Well, I hear you, but, you
know, sometimes in life,
you just got to suck a turd, you know?
Hello?
Damn it! This is impossible!
Are you having any success, Caitlyn?
I've tried to get people on board,
but she's just such a Turd Sandwich.
You're just gonna have
to do something awful
to throw the election.
Every time I do something awful,
people just get more stoked on me!
It's impossible to
piss people off anymore!
This is breaking news!
The moment has arrived.
It is here.
J.J. Abrams says he has
finished the new national anthem.
Turn it up.
The anthem is sure to
be fresh and exciting,
while recapturing the
moments we all knew and loved.
Democratic nominee Turd Sandwich says
she will be in attendance
to show her support
for the rebooted anthem.
Oh, geez.
Let's all hope that this new
anthem puts our differences aside
and unites this nation once again.
That's it, Cait.
That's what I have to do.
I'm gonna sit out the national anthem
on live television.
Then everyone will have to
vote for that Turd Sandwich.
'Member Spock?
Yeah! 'Member tricorders?
- I 'member!
- 'Member that?
- Yeah!
- 'Member?
Oh, and 'member Bionic Man?
Oh I 'member.
I loved Bionic Man.
- Mmm.
- 'Member?
'Member Chewbacca again?
Oh, I love to 'member Chewbacca!
'Member?
'Member that?
Hey, 'member when there
weren't so many Mexicans?
Oh! I 'member.
Wait, what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
'Member when marriage was
just between a man and a woman.
- I 'member!
- Ooh, I 'member!
- Oh, yeah!
- Yeah, I 'member that.
- Wait.
- 'Member feeling safe?
'Member no ISIS?
'Member Reagan?
Ooh! I 'member!
- Ooh, 'member?
What the fuck going on
with these memberberries?
Yeah?
Hey, Broship. Got a minute?
What are you doing here?
You were right, Kyle, okay?
I drew the vagina on my face.
I tried to fool people,
but you keenly noticed
my one tiny error in that
girls don't have balls.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Kyle, you have to try and
appreciate what I'm doing.
I know that a war is coming
between us and the girls.
I knew it the moment they
sat out the national anthem.
They sat it out because you
were harassing them online!
Suppose for one second
that I'm not skankhunt42
and that I really have been
doing what I've been doing
to try and stop the damage he has done.
Why would you care?
Because I'm scared, Kyle.
Don't know if you've noticed,
but race wars are back,
and now if we get gender wars, too?
If we could just prove
who the troll was,
then the girls wouldn't be
wanting a war, would they?
Yeah, but you can't track
down an Internet troll.
It's too bad.
Just know this, Cartman...
I'm going to prove
who skankhunk42 is, whatever it takes.
Everyone is going to know,
and skankhunt is gonna pay
for everything he's ever said.
Hello, everyone.
We are live at tonight's game
between the 49ers and the Panthers.
But of course what everyone
is really here for...
The unveiling of the
new national anthem,
rebooted by J.J. Abrams.
And, Mike, this new anthem
is said to have everything
the old one had, but some
new surprises, as well.
You'd have to be an absolute
asshole not to stand and support it.
This is such a big night for America
that both the presidential
candidates are here.
There you can see the Turd Sandwich
waving to all four
people excited by her,
and there is the Giant
Douche doing the same.
When I sit down to
not support this thing,
I'm sure to lose this election.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Here it is!
And the anthem begins. Let's
hope this fixes America.
For our national anthem,
we now ask you all
in solidarity to please rise,
or sit,
or take a knee
in order to honor America.
- Wait. Uh, wait, what? Wait?
♪ O say can you... ♪
Oh! And J.J. Abrams has absolutely
shattered expectations, Mike!
Now, whether people are
standing, sitting, or kneeling,
they are all honoring America.
J.J. Abrams is a
wizard, Tom... A wizard!
More people sitting now as
Abrams has made it irrelevant.
Who saw this coming?
And there's the rest of the anthem,
all the parts we remembered and loved.
J.J. Abrams has fixed America.
No! This was supposed to... oh!
Oh, geez!
Hey, Kyle. You okay, son?
Yeah, dad. Just thinking.
Well, I'll be in my
office if you want to talk.
Sync and corrections by Subban!