Okay, we'll get an estimate on
adding grass to the soccer field.
Good meeting.
Oh, Jeff, what time's dinner?
Uh, dinner?
Jeff, you didn't invite Shirley?
Well, it's Tuesday.
Shirley always goes to Elijah's
karate practice on Tuesdays.
It's okay. Part of making sacrifices
for my loved ones is not expecting
my loved ones to make sacrifices.
Aw.
- I can do tomorrow.
- I can't.
- I'm free on Fridays and Mondays...
- We're not moving it!
When Shirley can have dinner,
we'll have another dinner,
because it's just dinner.
And there's no need
to manipulate each other.
You know that's what you do.
You know you're doing
it now with that face.
You don't like my face?
Aw.
Hello, Save Greendale Committee.
This is David and Bixel.
They're app designers.
They'd like to beta test their latest
social-networking app on our campus,
which could be
good for us.
Look what Facebook did
for Harvard, right?
Hey, guys. Bixel
and I would like
to introduce you to a little app
called MeowMeowBeenz.
Ooh.
MeowMeowBeenz let's you
say how much you like,
who you like, when you like, all from
a standard non-boost mobile phone.
Let's see how it works.
Bixel, what did you think of the
way the Dean introduced us?
I thought he did great.
That's why I'm giving
him five MeowMeowBeenz.
Aw.
Well, Bixel, I'm sorry, but I
thought his intro was just okay.
That's why I'm gonna give him
two out of five
MeowMeowBeenz.
My MeowMeowBeenz.
With MeowMeowBeenz,
students can rate teachers.
Teachers can rate students.
Everyone and anyone
can rate each other.
MeowMeowBeenz.
You know...
I could...
I fought for this country,
and I know you don't get to pick and
choose the parts you fight for,
but I know...
I should go
number two soon.
♪ Give me some rope ♪
♪ Tie me to dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope ♪
♪ To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said
it can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the
reasons I should stay ♪
♪ One by one, they
all just fade away ♪
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Hurry up! I'm late for
Human Rights class.
I'm sorry.
Why is Starburns carrying
Garrett's books?
It's like toast bossing
crackers around.
I mean, I guess.
Garrett's got three MeowMeowBeenz.
Starburns is a Two.
Are you telling me people are
actually using this stupid app?
- It's addictively effective.
- No, it's effectively stupid.
There already was a rating system
in place called "cool people get more,"
and it was working fine.
MeowMeowBeenz takes everything
subjective and unspoken
about human interaction and reduces
it to explicit, objective numbers.
I've never felt more alive.
As long as you're
happy, I'm unsettled.
Hey, guys.
- What happened to you? - I sat on a
toilet so long, my feet fell asleep,
then I noticed limping was
getting MeowMeowBeenz,
so I just kind of
started committing.
- Did you understand a
word he said? - Mm-hmm.
Hey, here you go.
Here you go.
Nobody is gonna down-vote
a guy on his birthday.
Wait. Are you using
MeowMeowBeenz?
If you can't kill it, join it.
When you get older, you're
gonna see the warning signs.
Mark Zuckerberg is Fidel
Castro in flip-flops.
MeowMeowBeenz is gonna make
East Berlin look like Woodstock.
You take my word for that.
Do you own stock in Trivial
Pursuit's Baby Boom Edition?
Britta. Please tell me
you're not using this app.
Uh, I liked the idea at first,
giving a voice to the unheard,
but then Annie just told me that the
rating system is exponentially weighted.
As your ratings go up, your
ratings of other people
- become more important.
- No.
It just means the more others like you,
the more likeable you can make others.
- It makes sense to me.
- You know who else it made sense to?
Say "Hitler" one more time,
and I'm giving you a two.
- Jeff, are you not registered?
- The longer you wait,
the harder it's gonna be
to get your number up.
Annie!
Listen to yourself.
You're learning its language.
You're letting a video game play you.
- I got to set these people straight.
- Hey, hey, uh...
Students of Greendale!
We don't have to
worship a calculator!
There is no formula
for people!
Oh.
You're punishing me
for being alive!
That's the general
idea, baby.
You're gonna think I'm joking,
but you were getting through
to me more with
mustard on your lip.
- Oh, shut up.
- He's not kidding, Britta.
I thought I was
imagining it.
When you had mustard on your lip,
I was more open to your opinion.
Maybe it dilutes or distracts
from your excessive intensity.
from your stupid butt.
Hmm.
How you doing, Rog?
Hey, Charlotte. I see
what you did there.
Vicki, I love this.
Shirley's a Five.
- How?
- She's nice to people, Jeff.
You know Shirley.
Oh, Vicki, thank you.
Did you just give me
four MeowMeowBeenz?
Um...
I love my four from Vicki.
No!
Stop it!
I didn't mean it.
Yeah.
I do know Shirley.
Oh!
We should be
having brownies.
I'm going to help Shirley.
Not a bad idea for you, Britta.
She could make you a Two again.
Screw your Twos, and
screw MeowMeowBeenz.
I know that's
your One talking.
- What are you doing?
- Registering for MeowMeowBeenz.
I'm gonna become a Five and expose
this thing for the sham it is.
Oh, now you're
speaking my language.
That's unintentional,
trust me.
Mm.
Just make sure you
know the real reason
you're doing something, or
you'll fail before you start.
- That's actually a good point.
- It is? Why?
Oh, come on!
So I'm like, "That's two cups,"
and she's like, "What?"
I'm like, "Two cups,
balls back, tops off."
All right, Trent, Mulch, Dave,
Herpie, Clutch, Dirt Mouth,
Rope, Tingles, Cat
Woman, Steve.
All right, keep it floppy.
Haul it, ball it, never call it.
- Girls are objects.
- Yeah!
Two MeowMeowBeenz.
Congratulations.
Abed was just explaining
that the Fives get to choose
- what setting the air
conditioning is on. - Yep.
Is it me, or are more
people wearing gray.
I feel like I'm in a commercial, and
someone's about to hand me a Starburst.
Threes and Twos tend to
wear neutral colors.
Looking like you want to move
up can get you moved down.
- Abed, hey. Come here.
- Hi.
Those are other Threes.
We talk about how we're
glad we're not Twos.
Small talk, guys.
I make small talk now.
Hello, Jeffrey.
I see you decided to join
MeowMeowBeenz.
Oh, it's a great
tool for living.
- You look great.
- You know what you're doing.
I'm watching you, okay?
- Mm, mm.
Yeah, you'll be watching
my hinder, mama,
and choking on its billowing
plume of highly rated dust.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
Fours and above only.
These are snacks
for the Fives.
Yeah? You're a two.
Leonard, would you rather a
Three serve the Fives food?
No.
It is no secret that
the Threes and Twos
are growing suspicious
of the Fours and Fives.
All I know is that
it's my birthday.
What if we give these people
something to believe in again?
- Koogler? - Hey. I know what
you guys think of me, okay?
"Hey, it's Koogler."
You know. "He's cool."
"He likes to get laid.
He's not that old."
But I'm a Five because I know what
the Twos and the Threes need.
What do we all need?
Entertainment.
A talent show.
An event where Threes and
Twos can rise and fall.
It helps people believe
in the system.
Give my spot to someone else.
I don't want to be a Five.
I was happy as a Three.
I'm miserable.
Oh, dear Abed.
So humble.
You people are monsters.
Well, if there's
nothing else, then...
Speak.
Headline items... A few Twos
broke into a supply closet
and stole a box
of peanut butter.
The futurization of the campus
decor is almost complete.
And a few hours ago, Jeff
Winger became a Four.
That's nice.
You there, girl.
How many MeowMeowBeenz?
Two!
Two? Are you lost, Two?
Yes. Are you lost, Two?
I'll escort her to
the common area.
You're a Four?
I don't recognize you.
He's new Beenz.
Bye-bye, new Beenz.
Threes and Twos must leave
building one after 7:00.
Building one after
7:00 is Fours only.
- What are you doing here?
- How goes the revolution?
I can't break a Four.
It's impossible to get any higher
without half the Fives in your corner.
- They got this thing locked up.
- Yeah, but they're nervous.
They're hosting a talent show to
prove that anyone can be a Five.
If you enter it, you'll be center
stage with all eyes on you,
and you can tell everyone
this isn't democracy.
This is tyranny.
I'm sorry. Can you
put some mustard...
I shouldn't have to put mustard on
my face for this to make sense.
You know we have to
take this system down.
You know...
I once loved a Two.
Matthew...
He was my everything.
But numbers change.
I'll keep your
secret, new Beenz.
It says you're next.
Now, Jeffrey, I beg you
not to take this risk.
You know what they say. Fives
have lives, Fours have chores,
Threes have fleas,
Twos have blues,
and Ones don't get a rhyme
because they're garbage.
Craig, I got this.
No! No, please!
Not the Outlands!
Please!
Boo on you!
The Fives have spoken!
And you...
uh...
are not very good and...
What? No! Please!
I'm just not very good at
public speaking and...
Last chance, Jeffrey.
Showtime.
My name is Jeff Winger.
I recently became a Four.
Funny thing is,
when I was a Two,
I didn't actually
have any less.
But I did have a lot
of crazy friends.
Hey, my name's Tommy Talouca.
I'm from hallway "C."
I'm a Two!
I got to get to the cafeteria
before they run out of apples!
What is with
Twos and apples?
You're given three
kinds of fruit.
Mix it up.
Then you become a Four.
And you get that, uh...
that Four walk.
You know what I'm
talking about? It's like this.
It's like one of these.
And they got a little trail
of Twos behind them,
and they're like "Hey, is
there an apple up there?"
Oh, shit.
Wow. What else
is going on?
- He's killing it.
- Shh!
There came a time
when I has to a
"aks" myself,
did I even want
to be a Three?
Or did I just hate
myself for being a Two?
I don't know.
All I know is...
I sure do love
them apples!
Oh, the Koog "approogs."
That's a five!
Yeah!
Review. Review
meow meow meow meow meow!
meow meow meow meow meow.
Down here, guys.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Can I get a picture?
I want my future kids
to know this happened.
I admire your
optimism, Garrett.
- What the hell?
- I don't want to hear it.
I got this far because I need
to take Shirley down.
- What about everyone else?
- Look around you, Britta.
Everyone wanted this.
Fives only, ma'am.
Oh, great. Come on.
You... you think this
system's gonna last forever?
I'm gonna free people's minds.
I'm a Psych major.
Words are my weapons.
I'm a security guard.
Weapons are my weapons.
Welcome, Fives,
to the inaugural
fancy future dance.
I'm glad you don't think making Jeff a
Five was a mistake like everybody else.
I believe in taking risks.
Yeah! Jeff's really cool.
Couldn't help but
notice that Shirley
didn't clap with the rest of you
after my performance.
Is she always
so different?
If you talk to me, I can't
concentrate on the dance moves.
You don't believe the
rumors, do you, Koogler,
that Jeff manipulated
his way to the top?
Shirley, I can hear
what you're saying.
You're trying to manipulate someone
into thinking I'm manipulative.
I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
No one ever knows what
you're talking about
because you never
say what you mean.
Do you want to have
this conversation,
or do you want to just keep flexing your
veiny arms and throwing out apples?
Tranquility is advancement.
A happy Three is
a future Four.
Twos and Threes, you're accepting
a life you don't have to live!
Stand up for yourselves!
Really?
Ugh, fine.
- Give me that.
- Hey!
You're all alive!
You are all alive!
Look at the mustard on my
face, but listen to my words.
You're one of the angriest,
most vindictive...
You're the angry one, because the
rules got changed on you, Winger.
You can't just be cool
and be in charge now.
No, you have to gossip
and give out food
- and make people feel guilty.
- Okay, yeah.
I bust my ass making a world full
of selfish idiots remember my name!
Fine. Call it hard work, but don't tell
me the system measures who's nice.
Actually, it kind of does.
Security, banish them to the
Outlands with the rest of the Ones!
- Oh, no!
- Ow!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- No! No!
Ladies and gentlemen, please put your
tray tables in their party positions...
So sayeth Captain Koogler.
Actually, keep the tray tables
where they are, Koogler.
The rule of the Fives is over!
Long live the review-lution!
- No!
- That comes down?
- Okay, okay, all right, all right.
- Whoa!
- Happy?
- Are you happy?
Look, I knew you couldn't
go to that stupid dinner.
- That's why I didn't invite you.
- It's nice to be invited anyway.
- Sure, if you're a control freak.
- Oh, and you clearly hate control.
No.
I love it.
I guess it's easy to pretend
that you don't when you got it.
You'd think we'd
be better friends
because we're both such big
fans of the same thing.
You there! Ones!
You are permitted back indoors by
decree of Britta, the mother of Ones.
And do I hear correctly
that as a Five,
you felt you could park
in handicap spots?
Well, you see, that's just
part of the Koogler style.
It's human crap style.
Rate him!
Okay, well, that's low.
All Fives must be cleansed of their
Five filth and reduced to oneness.
Jeff. Hey, Shirley.
I'm not a Five anymore. I'm a one like
everyone else. I'm like everyone else.
Who's next?
- All right, time to pull the plug.
- Mm.
Oh, great mother of Ones,
mustard-faced savior,
there is still a Five hiding among
us that has not been cleansed.
Nonsense.
All Fives were reduced to oneness in the
great purge of about two minutes ago.
This Five cheats.
It never registered,
yet was given a five
from outside the system.
Behold...
The MeowMeowBeenz app.
Its beta test
ended days ago.
It's now available in
the app store... 99 cents.
Five stars.
This five lied to us,
used us, judged us,
yet exempts itself
from judgment.
And I'm pretty sure it's selling
our information to spammers
because I am getting
a lot more email,
and trust me, my penis
needs no enlargement.
So how do you cleanse a
Five that's unregistered?
Delete it.
By the way, guys,
it's a Saturday.
Um, you're all in
school for nothing.
Go home and get some sleep.
No!
No. Wait. No, don't go!
Where are you going?
No.
Attention, Greendale.
I'd like to propose we
basically forget everything
that happened over
the last few days.
And I don't anticipate a
lot of pushback on that.
I think we're all
pretty embarrassed.
- Hey, there.
- Oh, hey.
So I was thinking about checking
out this new restaurant tonight.
Oh, that's sweet, but
I can't tonight.
Not even takeout?
- We could eat in the study room.
- Oh, I think I have time for that.
Jeffrey.
What?
I'm not gonna take it off.
I still got two days
left on the rental.
Every once in a while,
a film comes along
that takes a serious look
at higher education.
This is not one of them.
Gentlemen...
Assume the party.
This summer...
fun has a new name.
- Koogler?
- Koogler!
- Koogler.
Koogler!
Koogler! Koogler!
Hope you don't mind
if I play through.
Hammer Road Pictures invited
you to meet the man...
the myth...
I'm photocopying
my rear end.
the Koogler.
Koogler.
I guess I have what you might
call an aversion to education.
Do you even have
a career plan?
Yeah, uh, does
getting laid count?
No!
Mitchell D. Hurwitz
is Koogler...
Rated "R."
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther