Jeff, we've known each
other a long time, right?
You've come to respect me.
- Sure.
- Well, get ready to stop.
Please help me seduce Britta now that
you've finished doing it with her.
- Please, please...
- Do you even really like Britta?
It seems like you like her
because she doesn't like you.
Have you met the women
that do like me, Jeff?
Neither have I, but trust
me, they're bad people.
Fine.
To get near Britta,
think like Britta.
Grab one of those free papers for hippies
on the quad, go to the calendar page,
and find a cause so tragic...
Are you writing this down?
Okay, we have confirmation
that all the bones
have been removed
from the football field.
And we agree that teachers should get a
10-minute head start at the job fair.
Any other items?
It's Friday night.
What's everybody doing?
Oh, there's a benefit show
at the Forefront Theater
in Riverside for starving
children with cleft palates.
- Aw.
- I'm gonna crash the premiere
of the Kickpuncher reboot
dressed like classic Kickpuncher.
They shouldn't
have redesigned that costume.
Keep your heads in the
sand if you want.
Professor Duncan, I didn't know
that cause interested you.
Well, it's starving children
with cleft palates, Britta.
What part would you have
me be disinterested in?
- Forefront Theater?
- Mm-hmm.
What time? I'm going.
- I'm going too.
- Me too.
Kids with cleft palates should
have extra food, not less.
I'm in.
I have...
dinner plans.
Yeah, make sure it's a hearty meal.
- Oh, boo.
- Help me out here.
Um, well, uh...
Pfft, are you really the one
that needs help here, Winger?
Yeah, should we write a check
to the Jeff Foundation?
- Okay. Maybe I'll go too.
- Well, it's the least you can do.
Yeah, feels good to help.
God bless you.
Cool, so 7:30?
♪ Give me some rope ♪
♪ Tie me to dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope ♪
♪ To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said
it can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the
reasons I should stay ♪
♪ One by one, they
all just fade away ♪
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Did you get it?
I don't think I got it.
Well, the ants were people. The
Queen Ant was an oil company.
Okay, so it was about our
marginalized perceptions
as drones being born into
a corporate hive-mind?
- Yeah.
- Mm.
- Wow. McDonald's?
- Oh, I was just thinking about that.
- Mm.
- Mm-hmm, hungry.
Hello?
Okay, Alessandra, I can't talk
right now. I just got out of a show.
Okay, hold on.
Well?
Look, if you're gonna
just yell at me, why...
Why are you doing this?
This is not happening
to you, okay?
It's happening to us!
Well, you called me!
Well, then let me be
the one to do this!
Uh, my mother used to tell a story
about how she killed a chicken.
Hong Kong, 1964.
- So you like the theatre, Ian?
- Oh, are you kidding?
I spent half my days at
university in wigs and tights.
You don't do that without
befriending some actors.
Hm.
Oh, my God, Michael. I know
Michael from my anarchist days.
God, he's gonna smell
the sellout on me.
Hey. How's it goin'?
- Oh, my God.
- What's going on?
- I don't like this "my-kale" guy.
I don't think he likes himself,
or he'd pronounce it "Michael."
Isn't she great? She's
everything I love about America.
Bold, opinionated,
just past her peak,
and starting to realize that
she has to settle for less.
And the moment she needs
a shoulder to cry on,
bam.
- Huh?
- The Duncan handkerchief.
Well, I'm out.
Have fun circling my former lover,
waiting for her to cry.
I tried to make that sound good,
but that's what you're doin'.
Eh.
Uh, you're all heroes tonight
for making a difference,
but I want to introduce
one of my heroes.
- Britta Perry.
- Oh.
She is the bravest,
most passionate activist
I have ever had the
honor of imitating.
So, hey, buy her a drink.
- Anything you wanna add, Britta?
- Oh. Wow, um, I'm not a hero.
I'm a high school dropout and a
bartender, so don't listen to me.
Or anyone.
Just listen to yourself,
and make sure you tell
yourself the truth.
Well, it was... it was
great seeing you, so...
I might stay for one drink.
- Why?
- I like to drink.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah. I have a serious problem.
That had better be true.
Cool. Cool, cool, cool.
I am Kickpuncher.
You are in violation
of future law.
Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew!
Pew! Pew!
Oh. Damn it, come on.
- What are you doing?
- What?
What... what are you doing?
Making a costume
for a movie premiere.
Annie banned glue guns
from the apartment
after an incident so hilarious
that even describing it
would narratively eclipse
what's happening here.
- What's happening here?
- You and me bonding.
Check it out.
Tell me the truth: If you were
a post-apocalyptic survivor...
I would raise goats, hoard cinnamon,
and travel only at night.
But, please, I have
some work to do here.
Just one thing. Watch this.
Initiate ballistic foam.
Oops.
- What the hell?
- Sorry.
You just destroyed
five hours of work!
- I'll clean it up.
- No, you don't touch it!
I know this is bad timing, but I should
go if I'm gonna make the movie, so...
- What are you doing?
- Oh. Something nobody ever does.
Teaching you consequences.
- But I have to go.
- But you can't.
Huh, isn't that crazy? You ever been
grounded? You ever been punished?
Do you have any idea what it feels
like to be refused something?
I know what it feels like when
people try to control me.
- You should know it never
goes their way. - Ooh.
And what "kicky-punch"
movie is that from?
The ones you've seen
or the one I'm gonna watch you miss?
I said I was sorry.
I'm sorry I punched my landlord,
but I'm not gettin' my deposit back.
That's an example of you being
punished for choosing to hurt someone.
I wrecked your
papers by accident.
You chose to spray
this crap on purpose
because you didn't
care what happened.
You know, let me tell you something.
For five years, I have watched people
walk around on
your eggshells.
"Oh, Abed. He's so
imaginative, so magical.
"Everybody hide
their hamburgers!
"If Abed sees a hamburger,
we'll all travel in time.
"Let's eat cookies and ice cream and dress
in pajamas in the middle of the day."
I watched my
third wife die!
You think I'm spoiled?
And you think I'm spoiled because it's
never occurred to anyone to do this?
You're not the Marco
Polo of bullying me.
You're just another tourist taking
pictures of a great, big wall.
Oh, you're gonna
make me cry.
When's the last time someone
physically limited you?
Oh, just now. You physically
ruined my drawings.
Drawings of what?
You're an artist?
I destroyed
something valuable?
Looked like you were
doodling chickens.
- He is a duck!
- Uh-oh.
Hey!
You're not allowed
in there.
Well, I just did a one-man show for a
little audience that would beg to disagree.
Audience? In there?
We haven't had a single
person or performance
in that theater since
the 1997 fire.
24 people died.
So what have you
guys been up to?
Well, this. Raising money. Organizing.
Trying to make a difference.
I'm impressed, and
embarrassed. I sold out.
- We sold out.
- You did not sell out.
I'm going to community
college to start a career.
We're in real estate. We own the
building we're standing in.
Wow. You guys did sell out!
I know!
- I should introduce myself
to her friends. - I knew it!
You don't have a
drinking problem!
You have feelings for Britta,
you disgusting monster!
Fine. Yes. Something about
everybody liking her turns me on.
It's a problem I have. I hated Reese's
pieces before E.T. ate them, sorry.
- You're a bad friend!
- That's not fair!
Wait, that's really not fair.
You're a terrible friend.
She was mine first. And it's not
like she belongs to anybody.
Oh, here we go. "Love isn't a game,"
say the guys that always win.
And now, you're going
to go pull a Dane Cook
in one of those three movies he was in
about Dane Cook getting laid by accident.
Only it's not a Dane
Cook movie, Jeff,
because this time,
someone's watching: Me.
Your friend, British Jason Biggs.
If you never call me Dane Cook
again, I'll stand down...
- for an hour.
- Okay. An hour.
Are your duck
drawings a secret?
Is that why you do 'em
when nobody's around?
Not that it's any
of your business,
but I am a cartoonist
in my spare time.
My cartoon's about a duck.
I was drawing him.
Does the duck have a name?
Does he have powers?
I'm not pitching to you.
- You're afraid I won't like it.
- Sure.
I've been a cab driver,
a soldier, a cop,
but what terrifies me the most is the
opinion of a manchild in cardboard pants.
Kickpuncher was a cop
before he became a cyborg.
So you were a cop before
you became... this.
And what were you before this?
Were you normal? Or do you act like this
because somebody stuffed you in a locker?
- Is that the idea?
- Other way around.
- What else do you want to know about me?
- What makes you stop talking.
- Letting me go.
- After you miss your movie.
Because you want
me to suffer.
For destroying your
duck cartoons?
The ones you're
ashamed of?
Uh, which one were
you laughing at?
No, no, no, no, no!
Stop that!
You're ghosts!
We're ghosts?
The janitor out there
told me you died in 1997.
Janitor?
Hey!
Those guys in there told me that
you're the one that died in a fire
- and you're a ghost!
- And you just believed 'em?
You just believed a
bunch of ghosts?
Have you guys seen that billboard on
Water Street for Consensual Perfume?
The one with the man chasing
the woman through the grass
and it says, "Proven
in its field"?
Yeah, proven in its field and in
labs on the eyeballs of rabbits.
We should make it say that!
Who's got the spray paint?
No, guys, I'm serious!
Doug and Janet,
you're on lookout.
Michael works the ladder. I
will banksy that mother!
Come on, guys, we gotta
start taking risks again.
Well, that's convenient for
the one with nothing to lose.
Oh, so the person with the least
wealth has the least valid argument?
That's convenient.
Britta, how many people have you
fed this year besides yourself?
- Oh, Janet...
- No, look.
I've spent enough
time feeling bad.
Fight the power!
- Would you like to go...
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Oh, my God.
These are really good.
It helps me to see why
you were so upset.
Did I ruin anything as
good as what's in here?
Ah, just practice
drawings.
I have to practice drawing the
duck from different angles.
It's hard when his back's
turned 3/4 because of the beak.
Well...
- I'm a real jerk for wrecking it.
- Ah, you didn't do it on purpose.
- That doesn't excuse my behavior.
- No, I appreciate that.
It's a good apology.
You're a good kid.
All right. Well...
I can see from the clock that
if I hit all the green lights...
I'm sorry, I can't let you go.
That'd undercut the larger lesson.
Yes, the lesson being that
you're very talented.
But I have this thing.
I can't walk into a movie...
You're not going
to the movie.
Yes, I am.
- You need this.
- Let me go!
This is you learning.
You're a bad person
and a bad cartoonist.
You go ahead.
Hurt my feelings.
Oh! You have feelings, huh?
Have you considered putting
them into your work?
Your cartoons are
monuments to joylessness,
nervously assembled jokes based on
nothing from your life or anyone's life!
You're furious at me for being creative
because you want to be able to create.
You have all this rage and
shame and loneliness,
which I don't even know how
to feel much less understand,
and you decide to put
what on paper? A duck.
Jim the Duck. You think I'm crazy. You
think there's something wrong with me.
- Jim the Duck?
- Publishers are interested!
Oh! Yeah, well,
publishers are stupid.
Either that or you're misinterpreting
what was probably a form letter.
- You shut up.
- Now you shut up.
Oh, are we yelling? Are we yelling
right now? Yelling! I'm yelling!
Yelling! I'm yelling,
I'm yelling, I'm yelling!
And you're not talented!
You made me miss my movie!
You made me miss my movie.
In the words of your hacky
duck, "What the hell?"
Do you like music?
Everyone likes music.
What are you, a fish?
I have... Ooh, I-I tell you
what we could listen to.
Do you know Rimples
and Splikket?
They were the British
Laurel and Hardy.
Most of their stuff is timeless,
but you do need to know
that the prime minister
went to Oxford,
not Cambridge, as
the sketch implies.
- Are they speaking English?
- Okay. '80s German techno it is.
Do you have any friends?
I'm sorry?
I've been defining myself with reactions
to and from other people my whole life.
Now I feel worthless just because I'm
worthless in relation to my friends,
which means they're
not my friends.
Who are your friends?
Well, there's my neighbor, Pat.
I try to stay on his good side.
I owe him money.
- Uh, Jeff. I'd call you a friend.
- Well, in fact, I'd call you a...
Oh, that's right.
You and Jeff have actually known
each other longer than anybody, huh?
I always forget that. I guess 'cause you
guys don't really act like friends.
Yeah, I guess not so much.
Where are we going?
Well, I think you
should go home
because you're having
an existential crisis,
and the best lesson you
could take away from it
is that you are someone, even
when you're by yourself.
I think you're right.
Thank you.
And please don't take offense at this,
but thank you for not hitting on me.
I was just vulnerable enough
to do something really stupid.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. Nothing.
It's nothing. It's the...
the stupid steering wheel
is on the wrong
side of the car.
- What are you doing here?
- I want to show you something.
What's this?
It's a script I wrote
about a cop on the edge.
Troy thought it
was hilarious.
I didn't have the heart to
tell him it wasn't a comedy.
Why are you giving
this to me?
I know all the tricks and
tropes of filmmaking,
but what I'm missing is what I think
the critics call "substance,"
- which is you more than me.
- You want to be film partners?
"It's time for Justice.
Police Justice."
Wait, the character's
name is "Police Justice"?
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah, I think
I may be able to help.
I'm sorry for the
stuff I said.
Me too.
Sit down.
You drink scotch?
- No.
- You're gonna.
Hey, handsome.
This stool taken?
- Struck out, huh?
- If that makes you feel better.
Or maybe I just realized that I
was spending the whole night
getting to third base
with the wrong person.
You're a good friend,
and I don't say that often enough.
That's really nice.
But you can't
have sex with me.
How about we have
these drinks
and then not have sex,
with anyone, together?
Sounds good.
Cheers.
So a 9-millimeter's actually
better than a 10-millimeter?
Millimeter don't make no difference.
Bullets just kinda kill you.
"Bullets just kinda kill you."
Are you quoting something?
Can I use that?
- Yeah. - You left your handkerchief
at my place last night.
- Ah!
- We had a boys' night.
A bottle of booze, an
argument about sports cars.
And I cut my hand trying
to prove that I can whittle.
Me too.
- Oh, hey. How was your night?
- Great.
I had a monumental
evening...
by myself.
- Oh!
- Oh... Almost feel left out.
Well, we've had our
share of focus lately.
Mm-hmm. Speak
for yourself.
Uh-oh.
I'm fine. I just, um...
Do you guys believe
in ghosts?
And if you do,
do you believe what those ghosts
tell you about other ghosts?
Chang, you cannot
be on the committee
if you're going to
be actively insane.
I'm not insane. I swear.
I just, um...
had a weird experience
at the theater last night.
- You were there?
- Yeah, you were there?
What do you mean?
Of course I was.
Huh, I guess we just
didn't see you.
Well, the ants were people.
The Queen Ant was
an oil company.
What if I don't exist?
Oh, I got this.
I had a very similar
night last night.
Go home, light some
candles, and take a bath.
Okay, coolsies.
Hey! I was thinking
off-campus lunch.
What's that Tex-Mex
place you mentioned?
Salsa Von Taco's?
Read my mind!
Oh. Oh!
- No, no.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
- Nah.
- Oh, okay. Yeah.
- Oh.
- No, wha... Let's...
- No.
- No, no, no.
- Well... O-okay.
- Ah...
- You... you just...
- Eh...
- Ah. Oh, okay.
- Ah...
- I...
- Wha...
I-I just don't like
being left behind!
My father got drunk in pubs and
left me in my room with nothing!
- So did mine!
- Oh, why would he do that?
Why do they do that?
- Why?
- Why do they do that?
I-I won't go to
that Tex-Mex place.
Oh, that's all I
wanted you to say.
- Hmm?
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther