Save Greendale Committee, please
welcome our newest member,
math teacher Ben Chang.
Okay, let's get serious.
I've compiled a short list of the
most immediate Greendale emergencies.
Is deforestation on the list?
I, for one, am glad
that this is happening.
What this school needs
is a band of heroes,
champions willing to rise up and "get
all those potatoes out of the gym."
We're like House Vagadosh in the HBO
original series Bloodlines of Conquest.
Bloodlines of Conquest.
That's my show right there.
- That is a good show.
- They really get the incest right.
What the hell is
Bloodlines of Conquest?
It's a medieval fantasy series.
It's based on these great books that
nobody seems to read. It's great.
It's got betrayal, boobs,
espionage, dragons.
Oh, wait, dragons? Is that a spoiler?
I just started season one.
I don't start watching shows
until they're so popular
that watching them is
no longer a statement.
So because you're three seasons behind,
we have to live in a fantasy world
where there's no such
thing as dragons?
Do we also have to pretend that
Lord Stevarios is still alive?
Thanks, Abed.
How about I just buy all the
Bloodlines of Conquest books,
read ahead, and spoil
the whole series for you?
That's insane. That's something
an insane person would do.
Knuckleheads, focus.
Item one,
the Greendale student
census is out of date.
Britta, Abed, why don't you
partner up on that one?
Give you a chance
to squash this beef.
Next, the midterm
dance is tonight.
Who wants to be on the
decorating committee?
- Mm.
- No.
- Fine, I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- I will be on that committee.
- Me too.
Are you guys volunteering because
you think I'll do all the work?
- I wouldn't.
- No. Not at all.
I don't care enough
to lie, so no.
I will reward that honesty by
giving you something easy.
A bulletin board fell down in the
cafeteria a couple months ago.
Think you can get
it hung back up?
- I'll give it a drive-by.
- Great.
We have now completed
our first task,
"Have a Productive Meeting!"
For every task that we complete,
a star goes on the task wall!
♪ Give me some rope ♪
♪ Tie me to dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope ♪
♪ To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said it can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the
reasons I should stay ♪
♪ One by one, they
all just fade away ♪
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Brince Ironstone's
daughter is his mother!
Hi there.
- What can I do for you? - Can you
get me a drill, a couple of screws,
- and a bulletin board?
- No, I cannot.
Okay, I tried. Bye.
You wanna hang a
bulletin board,
you need to get a work order
from the head janitor.
They get more
powerful than you?
Hello, I'm taking
the school census.
Please fill out this form, but
don't talk to me. I can't hear.
Are you deaf? But
you read lips?
Barbagarbagarba garbabarbabarba?
That was gibberish.
You're good.
I wish I knew sign language.
Are you going to have another
intense burst of compatibility
with a girl we
never see again?
I can't hear you.
The midterm dance
will need a visual theme,
like "let's blow off
steam," and it's trains.
- I have an idea. - Chang,
your last idea was to murder.
- Edison. The bulletin
board's a no-go. - Really?
So you did your best,
and this task just...
- eludes you? - I have a lifetime
of experience with red tape.
I know when to walk away.
- Yeah, you do.
- Hey, Edison.
The system is lazy. I have integrity,
too much to deal with any of it.
- I'll do it myself. - And I
would love to watch you try.
Okay.
I am on bulletin board duty.
You guys are in
charge of the dance.
Oh, Professor Pushpin!
Jerry, Carlo, Crazy Schmidt.
I'm Annie.
- You learned our names.
- I did.
Crazy Schmidt, how are C.J.'s
clarinet lessons going?
Whoa.
Well, she's having a little trouble
with his left finger lifts,
but she's getting there.
Annie, do you want that
bulletin board hung up?
Let me put in a
work order for you.
There you go.
That should happen in three
to six business months.
Any way we could
bump that up a little,
so it's somewhere above...
"Lower flag for Reagan's death?"
You gotta talk to a custodian
for that, we're janitors.
There's a difference?
We were just starting
to like you.
Had enough?
I'm just getting started.
What was your stumbling
block, being nice?
Look, I admire your idealism,
but my guess is that you
will be crying uncle
before that board
ever goes up.
Game on, baby.
Come on, come on, come on.
What? God.
This isn't over!
Here we go. You wanted to get dirty.
This is where it starts.
Deputy Custodian Lapari,
Annie Edison from the
Save Greendale Committee,
- how's your daughter's soccer...
- I'm sorry, this is a closed function.
We do not discuss business
at custodial mixers.
But your daughter, soccer.
Daughter, soccer.
Yes, thanks for coming.
Hey, get a load of
that wood burnt sign.
Did Mr. Whitney in woodshop
make that for you guys?
Yes, that is a Whitney original.
Oh! You know, I noticed that Whitney's
bathroom has this amazing toilet.
Flushes like a DC-10 turbine.
Probably exceeds code,
but what's wrong with a little
friendship between departments?
Now how can our committee
be your friend?
Bob?
Excuse me.
Chief Custodian Bob Waite,
Buzz Hickey, Annie Edison.
Hickey and Edison, something
in the job queue...
- Bulletin board. - Yeah, we
were hoping to get that up...
- Let's take a walk. - That's quite
a spread, Bob. I'm impressed.
Well, it's election time.
If I don't break out the fancy sausages,
my ass goes in the grinder next January.
Keeping my people happy,
it's an uphill battle.
For example, look at this.
A lot of the websites we try and visit
get blocked by this weird filter thing.
Now let's say I wanted to move a
work order for a bulletin board
from the bottom of the queue to
the top. Now how can I do that
when I'm dealing with this?
They want their porn unblocked.
Then they'll give
you your board.
That's what that was?
How did you know?
Did you investigate pornography
when you were a cop?
- Eh, something like that.
- So he wants a bribe.
Welcome to the labyrinth, kid.
Only there ain't no puppets or
bisexual rock stars down here.
And at the center of it
all, if you're lucky,
a piece of cork
and a few pins.
So what, is it worth it?
Is that what a bulletin
board is to you, Professor?
A piece of cork? That's not what it
is to people that lose their pets,
people that need rides,
people whose bad bands
need bad bass players.
To them, every pushpin has the
power to change the future.
So yes, Professor, it's worth it.
I know a lady in the I.T.
Department.
Okay, I'll put some
food on the tables,
we'll lower the lights, and
that's a midterm dance.
I guess it could use a
little something theme-wise.
I have an idea.
"Bear Down for Midterms."
- What?
- "Bear Down for Midterms."
You can't just repeat it.
You need to explain yourself.
It's midterm time.
- Mm-hmm.
- People have to bear down,
study hard, get to work.
It's "Bear Down
for Midterms."
Is there a dot I'm
not connecting?
- Uh-uh.
- It's a play on words.
- "Bear down" is an expression.
- I know the expression, Chang.
"Fly on the wall"
is an expression,
but if I want to pitch "Fly
on the Wall for Midterms,"
you might ask, "What
do you mean?"
Chang?
Ar-Are you crying?
I understand I've been
crazy in the past, but...
that doesn't make it any less frustrating
to be completely dismissed like this.
I don't know if you guys even
see me as human anymore.
I don't know if it's
like a joke to you.
- Are all Asian men like a joke?
If it's like a racial thing. - No.
No! No!
I've paid for my crimes.
Underneath all the craziness,
I am still a human, and I...
I do want to make a
difference and...
Can you respect that? Please?
Chang...
What can we do here?
Bear Down for Midterms.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Okay, well...
We'll... put up
some bear things?
We'll bear down.
For midterms.
Okay.
You want me to lift web
restrictions solely for custodial?
They need to have full access,
so they can research, um...
custodian stuff.
If the filter is mistakenly
blocking a site,
they just need to
submit the url,
- and I can... - Okay,
what do you want?
- Excuse me? - Tell us what we can do
for you so that you can do this for us.
Oh. Cool. I... I didn't know
it could work that way.
I guess I could use
decent parking.
Right now they make
me park in Annex B.
Like a...
lunch lady.
Our committee can
talk to parking.
But, Debra, let's be clear.
I want everything to get
through that porn blocker.
- What do you mean everything?
- Everything!
Understood.
I'm very happy right now.
- So just bears everywhere?
- Yep.
And then we'll have
some cakes, party hats,
birthday stuff!
This is coming together
better than I thought.
I'm sorry, birthday stuff?
- Yes, Duncan.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
Birthday stuff.
Well, I've been sad to see that bulletin
board down in the cafeteria for so long.
I've always had a passion
for bulletins.
If parking for the I.T. guy puts
that board back where it belongs,
I won't stand in the way.
You know what you need...
speaking as a fan of bulletins...
you need to have the Dean appoint
someone to oversee them,
to make sure bulletins stay
organized and protected.
- I'll do it.
- We could look into that.
Well, not to be that
guy, but, uh...
You think you could look into
that before I do this for you?
You want to control all the bulletin
boards in the school... why?
You might want to start
talking turkey, Waldron,
because the Macy's parade is almost
over, and grandma's getting drunk.
Do you know where my department's
power comes from, Miss Edison?
- Parking spaces.
- Wrong.
There was plenty of space
to park in dinosaur times,
but not one single
parking department.
My power comes from a
scarcity of parking,
just like your dad's comes
from a lack of hugs.
And you know what
takes my power away?
Carpools.
Carpools organized
through ride shares.
Ride shares posted
on bulletin boards.
You can take the books off your
head because we're done posturing.
You want me to talk turkey,
well, gobble gobble.
I want ride shares gone.
- Let's get out of here.
- All right.
- What?
- I'll talk to the Dean.
I must say, I don't know what we did,
but we sure did the hell out of it.
I guess the key to dance
decoration is just pick an idea.
And then bear down.
Right, buddy?
Here are your sodas.
Oh... my God.
- Yeah, pretty great.
- Yeah. Bear down, baby.
Too soon, you guys.
This is way too soon.
- Too soon for wha...
- Too soon for this!
After this morning
in Wisconsin?
Bear breaks loose at a kid's birthday
party, mauls a whole bunch of people?
Why am I explaining this when this is
obviously a ghoulish reference to it?
The news has been
covering it all morning!
That where I got the idea.
You know how sometimes you hear
something and forget you heard it,
but you think you came up with...
Oh, man. This is bad.
We're in crisis mode now.
We really messed
up, you guys.
An office of bulletin
board oversight.
Ah, what a novel idea.
I'm gonna fill out
this form right away.
But first, a toast.
To hanging a
bulletin board...
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
Uh, first time toasting?
Get in here, buddy.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
I'm not saying that.
Ah, well, I hate
to be that guy,
but I'm not signing this form
until Professor Hickey says
"Easy peasy, lemon squeezy."
Damn it, Annie.
Don't do this.
Whatever you've
got in your butt,
can we get it out later?
When, after he signs it?
After it's all too late?
- Annie?
- You petty old man.
When we started this,
I thought you'd get a taste
of the system and spit it out,
not open a bottling plant.
You're just like all
the people that...
What? The people
that put you here?
The people in the big
machine that made you fail?
You went from being a cop to teaching
criminology because of the system, right?
Unfortunately for Greendale,
you have to prove it by
getting nothing done.
Well, here's a bulletin for you...
"Annie Edison doesn't
get nothing done."
- Yow. - And where should
I put that bulletin, Edison,
on a sham piece of cork
controlled by a parking guy
that lights his cigars
on student ride shares?
My God, Annie.
What kind of labyrinth
have you created?
Certainly not the magic kind with
puppets and macho rock stars.
You whored yourself out, kid.
You wanted that board so bad
that you made every board
on campus worthless,
and in doing so made the
school just a shade dirtier.
I thought better of
you, young lady.
Oh, man. This got Sorkin-y.
Yeah, well, I didn't think anything in
particular of you, and now I see why!
Okay, I didn't follow most of that,
but it feels like I ought to do this.
Hmm?
Oh, hey, Annie. Um...
What do you think?
"Fat Dog for Midterms"?
- Yeah!
- Pretty cool.
- I don't understand.
- It's an expression.
"Fat Dog for Midterm." Like,
don't sweat it, fat dog it.
Hang out, relax,
like a fat dog. Bah!
You can look it up on Wikipedia.
- There's an entry in there.
- Yep.
I never... uh... okay.
I just...
- I feel like I'm missing...
- You know, Annie, um...
Sometimes it feels like...
- you don't take us seriously.
- Aww.
Yeah, I guess we bring it on ourselves,
but it's still pretty frustrating.
Annie, is this a race thing?
- Race!
- No! God, no! You guys!
I accept that it's an expression, but
I don't see the connection to...
You're overthinking, Annie.
It's decorating.
Just pick an idea and
bear down on it.
Um, really poor choice
of words, Ben... Too soon.
But you guys are right. I'm sorry.
I've had a really hard day.
I need to just...
fat dog this concept.
- Fat dog!
- Fat dog it, baby!
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Abed, but to the
spoiler goes the victory.
But I really liked her.
She probably likes you too,
but she also likes cash.
I'm devastated.
Now I feel bad. But...
You learned a lesson, and I gave a
differently abled person a job.
Oh, no, now I really feel bad.
Wait, no. Come back!
Let's be fat dogs about this.
Hello.
What happened to you?
- Nothing. You never called.
- I'm sorry.
That was the year of the gas leak,
but I won't use that as an excuse.
I can be inconsiderate and
a lot of other things.
Me too. I guess I could've
put in some effort.
Would you like to go
to lunch sometime?
No,
I'd like to go to dinner. Now.
I can do that.
I started this coat check
without permission anyway.
♪ I could feel at the time ♪
♪ There was no
way of knowing ♪
♪ Fallen leaves
in the night ♪
♪ Who can say where
they're blowing ♪
♪ As free as the wind ♪
♪ Hopefully learning ♪
♪ Why the sea on the tide ♪
♪ Has no way of turning ♪
♪ More than this ♪
♪ You know there's nothing ♪
Excuse me, excuse me,
excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me!
All right, all right! Enough!
Let's go.
- Thanks.
Let's do it again!
♪ There's a brand-new dance ♪
♪ Based on an old phrase ♪
♪ It's called the fat
dog, and it will amaze ♪
♪ You've heard this
expression your entire life ♪
♪ It's not made up,
it's not made up ♪
♪ There's a brand-new dance
based on an old phrase ♪
♪ It's called the fat
dog, and it will amaze ♪
- ♪ You've heard this expression ♪
- It's a bear dance!
You've reached Greendale
Faculty Office Supply.
For pencils, pens, and
markers, press one.
For tape, glue, and
adhesives, press two.
For staples, paper clips,
and fasteners, press three.
For Marigold, press four.
Marigold. For
Obsidian, press one.
For Aqua Cerulean, press two.
For Arcadia, press three.
Enter activation code.
Confirmed. Arcadia initiated.
- What's your clearance level?
- Top.
You really want to
activate this, sir?
Yeah. Oh! No. No!
Can you... Cancel it.
Wait, who are you?
Who... Who is this?
It's not... I'm...
Right in front
of you, stupid.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther