Oh.
Please stay for complimentary
saltines and full-price sodas.
But first, The Dulcet Tones
of the Bennett boys.
♪ When you were here before ♪
♪ Couldn't look you in the eye ♪
♪ You're just like an angel ♪
- ♪ Your skin makes me cry ♪
- Bro, free crackers.
Want to spend your
life opening lockers?
You don't have to raise your voice!
I'm going as fast as I can!
♪ You float like a feather
Oh, great, now I have
these folders to deal with!
- ♪ In a beautiful world ♪
- Et tu, pencil?
When it rains, it pours.
♪ I wish I was special ♪
Ass Crack Bandit!
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www. Addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Let's settle down!
Guys, what is known...
What's known is that
around noon yesterday,
an unidentified student
dropped a coin
in another student's, you
know, upper buttock fold.
- Yes, yes.
- Gwen Ridley, Greendale Gazette.
Is this the return
of the Ass Crack Bandit?
Okay, that person, Gwen,
if he ever existed,
stopped being active
over a year ago.
- Yeah.
- Tim Briggs, Greendale Mirror.
Is it true
that after the attack,
you received a letter
from the Ass Crack Bandit?
I never said that, Tim, and when did
we split the gazette from the mirror?
And how many photographs
do you people need?
Raul Lopez, Las Noticias
Hispanicas De Greendale.
Will this affect soccer?
We did, in fact, receive a letter
an hour after the incident
including details not
known to the public
about the brand of
Garrett's underwear.
Hanes his ways.
"I am the Ass Crack Bandit.
"Humans make better
banks than piggies.
"Whenever I get more change
at the store,
"I can't wait to drop it
down your butts.
"I think I will go to the
bank and get so much change
"and take all my dollars and make them
into change and drop it all down there."
He should be called
"the run-on sentence bandit."
From this moment, people,
we are at DEFCON 4:
if that's the highest DEFCON, and if
high DEFCONs are worse than low ones.
Ah, you all remember
psychology Professor Duncan.
Hey, buddy.
Where'd you go?
I was taking care
of my sick mother.
She's still alive, but
I've put in my time.
Britta.
Oh, Pierce, good for you.
I always thought that hairpiece
was a bit cowardly.
Duncan is going to help us work
up something called a "profile,"
so we can root
this student out.
For the record, I tried to get something
done about this two years ago.
This is not about you, Annie.
This is about the school.
This is the biggest P.R.
crisis to hit Greendale
since we held that rally
protesting the wrong Korea.
Jeffrey, how can you help?
I'll take a look
at the whole picture,
see if any pieces match up.
Double fruit bonus.
Crikey!
Kiwi combo, mate.
I took a map of the campus
and pinpointed all the locations
- of the Ass Crack Bandit strikes.
- You can't handle the fruit.
During the bandit's
most daring spree,
he cracked
three people in a row.
Today, I sprinted
between all three sites.
My quickest time
was 20 minutes.
- The A.C.B. did it in 10.
- So he's got long legs.
I think he has something
I don't... a shortcut.
- The faculty lounge.
- You think the bandit's a teacher?
The Dean's not gonna
help me pursue this.
I need help.
Pineapple penalty, fool!
No! Unfair and racist.
Look, no way, Annie.
Look, the faculty already hates me,
and the Dean signs my paychecks.
But this is important!
- I can assure you that's not true.
- Fruit, fruit, fruit, fruit, fruit!
Yeah. Collect the seeds, sucka!
After the tone, please
leave a message.
Hey, Abed.
Lab ran late. What'd
Annie get us for dinner?
I hope it's not salad again.
I'd rather just stop
at the meat store.
All right.
Talk to you later.
Oh.
Well, hello.
Oh!
Will you stop with the
cups and the blankets?
This is how they comfort
victims in movies.
Okay, I am hereby banning
change from this campus.
You really think
that's an effective...
Well, guess what, your two cents
is change, and it's banned.
Got something.
Frankie, somebody get me a bag.
Oh, give me that.
"I hope you enjoyed
my work again.
"You can't stop me, because what are
you gonna do, not have butts?" Oof.
Dean, I think it's a teacher.
- I beg your what?
- I have evidence that shows...
Yeah, and I have evidence
that shows I'm not listening.
Exhibit "A," exhibit "B."
Lalalalalala.
This is never gonna end if you keep
choosing politics over justice.
Okay, you want to make trouble? Go
to Parker brothers. You're out.
Take it easy.
Taking it easy is
how Troy ended up
with a quarter of a buck
in his crack.
Annie, nobody's asking you
to do this...
Jeff, come on! You know
how this school works.
We do it, or it
doesn't get done.
The men on our coins
understood that.
Maybe the Ass Crack Bandit's point is
that we're letting our values slide.
Or maybe he's a frat boy
coming from the laundromat.
The important question
is "who cares?"
Look,
let me know
what you need from me...
on the down low.
Way down low.
And no squealing.
Okay, squeal.
Real Neil here, five days into the
return of the Ass Crack Bandit.
It's alive!
Since we last spoke, three more
victims have caught the quarter,
with no end in sight.
Safety pants, 100 bucks a pop.
All sandwiches $5. Sorry,
no change. Blame the bandit.
Here's a song that's been
shooting up the request line
faster than coins are dropping.
♪ It said quarter to five,
but it was quarter to ass ♪
♪ You thought
your plumbing was safe ♪
♪ But your jeans
were half-mast ♪
♪ Another coin down the drain ♪
♪ Now, that's some
change that won't last ♪
The nature of the Ass
Crack Bandit's crimes
would suggest that he's
angry or just fell in love.
We know that he hates
money or loves it
or doesn't care about money
and hates butts or loves them.
Mm. Abed, you're special.
Can't you just stand at the scene
of the crime and see what happened?
I see a man...
Using a social disorder
as a procedural device.
Wait, wait, wait,
I see another man.
Mildly autistic super
detectives everywhere.
Basic cable,
broadcast networks.
Pain. Painful writing.
It hurts.
Okay, ooh, LA LA. Hickey,
what have you got?
Heartburn. It doesn't
help me catch criminals.
Okay. I didn't want to
take drastic measures,
but I've cooked up
a little something.
Chang?
You better put a quarter
in that crack, Mr. Bandit.
Professor hickey.
Whoops.
Hah!
- Gotcha!
- Whoa! Ha, what do you think?
I think this is spending too much money
on a crime that nets you 25¢ a pop.
Ah, no, no.
This was free.
Then I think you just admitted
you already owned a fake butt.
"I am the mad hatter,
if hats were butts.
"I am neither left nor right.
I am the space between.
"To me, you're all like ants
marching to class,
freaks on parade."
I mean, why mix metaphors?
Ants don't have butts.
Wait a minute.
- Ants do have butts.
- No.
These are Dave lyrics.
- Dave?
- Dave Matthews.
Hard-core fans
call him Dave.
Oh, excuse me for being
alive in the '90s
and having two ears
connected to a heart.
Okay, so all we need to
do is assemble a list
of which Greendale teachers
are Dave Matthews fans.
Guess we better get to work.
- Done.
- Oh.
Thought that would take longer.
So please approve the Dean's new
security measure called "Troy's law,"
because a camera
in the bathroom...
Is better than a
quarter in your butt.
As we've seen, the Ass Crack Bandit can
be defeated by using the three "B's:
Belts, briefs, and buddies.
Good.
The bandit always gets his
victims when they're alone.
Bend over with friends over.
There's safety in numbers.
I got cracked!
He's under the bleachers!
Everyone remain calm, please!
All right, free-for-all!
Hey. Where you been?
I questioned Guterman.
We can cross him off.
At the time of the first cracking, he was
chaperoning Greendale's science dance.
The student that attended
can vouch for him.
I checked out Mrs. Plimpton.
Airtight alibi.
She's dead.
Next on my list is this one.
Bublitz.
- We're close, I can feel it.
- Mmm!
This extra long churro tastes
good in my real mouth.
Nom nom nom nom nom.
May I help you?
We'd like to ask you a few
questions if that's okay.
He's bolting!
He's there!
If you're going to confiscate
this, know one thing.
It's a mild, kind sativa,
perfect for playing guitar.
There's been another...
what the hell?
Destroying classrooms?
Secretly investigating
teachers behind my back?
Someone has to
investigate the faculty,
but you're like a single-celled
organism... no nerve.
Annie, you're suspended.
- Wait, you can't do that!
- Don't tell me what I can't do.
What do you think you
are, Cosmo's July quiz?
- She was trying to help you.
- Let me ask you two something.
Let me be, like, the 50th person at
this school to ask, what is this, huh?
- What is this creepy business?
- What?
I think you two like to
partner up on cutesy capers
so you can hold
hands in the dark
and address your urges
in semi-acceptable scenarios.
Whoa, not cool!
You not cool!
You unprofessional!
I'm punishing you, Jeffrey.
Starting next week, you are the
new coach of the water polo team.
- What?
- That's right.
Every morning, in the water...
Mm.
Craig Pelton, Dean and
assistant water polo coach.
What?
This is the Ass Crack Bandit.
- Uh...
- I find it funny
that you ever thought
you could catch me.
Oh, that's very interesting.
Please continue.
I've enjoyed
our game of cat and mouse.
It's funny how close your two
little helpers came to catching me.
I liked watching them
run in circles.
Although sometimes I wonder,
are they chasing me as an
excuse to get near each other?
- I mean, get a room already.
- We're friends!
Why don't you tell us where
you are, and we'll discuss it?
I am the bringer of change.
I am the filler of cracks.
Oh, that's very interesting.
I myself was in 4h.
Oh!
Trace the call, Rhonda!
This means trace the call!
Look at the extension.
594. Okay.
Tracing...
Tracing.
Got it, the stables!
We have stables?
Let's go.
- Creepy.
- I don't know.
Add some doilies and a foot bath,
and this is my mom's house.
Mush! Mush!
Mush! Yah! Mush!
No, run. Mush! Mush!
Starburns?
Since faking his death
to escape meth charges,
Alex "Starburns" Osbourne
has been living in the stables,
eating garbage, and trying
to build a cat car.
He's also confessed
to dropping coins
down exposed butt cracks.
Case closed.
- High five?
- Sure.
- No.
- Oh, American high five. Sorry.
Whoo!
- Oh!
- Ooh!
So much pain.
But now it's time to heal!
You're all invited
to the official
"we caught the Ass Crack Bandit"
dance tonight in the cafeteria!
Jeff!
There's no way
Starburns did it.
- Innocent people don't confess.
- Are you kidding me?
You knew it was a teacher.
You know that doesn't add up.
Maybe I was wrong.
Or maybe the Dean
was right about us.
What? No.
Annie, I took this case
because I wanted to help you.
Then what is this?
It's platonic shoulder holding.
Look.
Leonard, hello, how are you?
It's a guy who puts quarters
down butt cracks, Jeff.
Let's just let it go.
We can do better.
Aah! Change is money!
What are you guys,
millionaires?
T-shirts here! Cracked
but not broken, huh?
Who's in?
T-shirts!
T-shirts here!
20 bucks.
- Professor Duncan?
- Yeah?
- Not going to the dance?
- I'll go later.
Oh, actually, would you mind coming
and getting me when Britta's drunk?
Listen, as Britta's friend,
I should give you this ad...
Yes! That is my jam right there.
- Dave Matthews fan?
- Obviously you're not.
Real fans call him Dave.
♪ Bum bum bum ♪
I've heard this song before.
Hey, Winger, who is this?
What are you talking about?
You don't know who this is?
I remember it from the '90s.
♪ Hee haw haw haw hee haw haw ♪
- It's Dave.
- Lee Roth?
You're not
the Ass Crack Bandit.
Shh! Keep it down, huh?
I made a deal with the Dean.
He said as long as I confessed, he'd
let me slide on the meth stuff,
and then he'd buy me a space
heater for my stable.
Yeah, but why call the
Dean and pretend that...
I didn't call no Dean. I don't
call nobody don't call me.
I got to go backstage once
and meet the whole band,
everyone... Except Dave.
There's a whole album of
photos online if you go to...
you actually wouldn't
be able to access it.
I use an older, British form of
Facebook called "mug-scroll."
- I guess I should be going.
- No, no, stay.
We're just getting to know
each other.
I really shouldn't, I have a...
Oopsie.
Aren't you going
to pick those up?
Yes.
Just... Reach down
with your hand and...
Bye.
This is the Ass Crack Bandit.
I find it funny that you ever
thought you could catch me.
Jeff.
It's Duncan.
Annie?
Jeff?
Very nice.
Oh, bloody hell, my shoe is
untied by British standards.
Here we go. One
bunny, two bunnies.
Oh! Get Britta!
Annie! Did Duncan get cracked?
Where's the bandit?
Do you see him?
- Over there!
- Come on, let's get him!
Shirley, what are you doing?
Looking for you.
Did you see someone
come this way?
Jeff, Annie,
Pierce is dead.
Tonight's celebration was cut
short by some tragic news.
Pierce Hawthorne, 14-year
Greendale student,
entrepreneur, and expert
heart attack faker
has passed away,
for real this time.
Pierce had been recently banned from
campus, but not from our hearts.
He's survived by many ex-wives
and all of us here at Greendale
that called him friend.
If you're listening, Pierce, you
were a hell of a d&d player.
It's time to level up.
Up next on the dial
is Dr. Farts.
I can't believe Pierce is gone.
Yeah.
Life is weird.
It's a container
for all this little stuff,
and you get caught up in it.
And then,
the container just...
Pbbt.
That hallway led to a dead end.
We might've had him.
I should get home.
Haven't slept.
The case goes cold again.
Don't worry.
I got a feeling he'll be back.
Or her.
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ 25¢ at a time he's
taking our souls ♪
♪ Government men can't
help, we're all alone ♪
♪ Are you feeling
the breeze? ♪
♪ Did you pull
your belt tight? ♪
♪ You know that it's wrong,
you know that it's right ♪
♪ Out of the shadows
down the coin goes ♪
♪ Why, oh, why
do you suppose? ♪
♪ Only the bandit knows ♪
♪ Whoa oh oh oh
oh whoa oh oh oh ♪
♪ A-s-s c-r-a-c-k bandit ♪
♪ Whoa oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh whoa oh oh oh ♪
♪ A-s-s c-r-a-c-k
can't stand it ♪
You know, climate change
is threatening our world,
but there is a solution:
The cat car, the world's first
animal-powered vehicle.
My original prototype
was hunger-based.
But sometimes,
cats aren't hungry.
My new model will use
a rear-fixed dog system.
But dogs cost money,
your money.
By donating to this project,
you'll be like an investor,
except without taking
all my profits.
Donate $5, and you get
a thank-you email.
$50 gets you a t-shirt.
100 gets you a t-shirt and
a thank-you email.
All aboard the cat car,
and all aboard helping our
nation's global warming.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www. Addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther