This is Russell Borchert,
computer genius,
anti-deodorant activist,
and millionaire.
He was rich for having invented
the 9-track cassette,
which the 8-track industry
paid to keep quiet.
He funneled that wealth into a
computer school called Greendale,
where he obsessively
pursued a new project,
a machine that can
process feelings.
He apparently used nothing but
gold to assemble his circuitry,
believing it to be a better
conductor of human emotion.
It was a weird time. The
Bionic Woman won an Emmy.
Rumors spread about his
relationship with computers,
and one day, he disappeared,
hence the legend that he died
of the first computer virus.
The city bought the
campus, and life went on.
His body was never found,
nor was his immense wealth.
Some people said he hid his money
using a portal to another dimension.
Those people were on LSD. Everyone else
said he had a secret vault in his office.
- Well, where's his office?
- Good question.
We found this confession written
by Greendale's first Dean.
"To protect the student health
and the school's reputation,
"I have sealed off the
computer department
and removed the stairwell
to that entire section."
A section that remains on this campus
somewhere, its secrets untouched,
including quite possibly
Borchert's millions.
If we found it, we could buy it
from the city before Subway.
Then I could really go
nuts with this place.
This is the kind of adventure
I usually have to force upon us,
and here it is, falling
into our laps.
We're like the Goonies, except
our story tracks logically
and has a chance of holding up
to objective critical scrutiny.
- Can you please stop that?
- Sorry.
Here are your blueprints. Sorry it took
so long. You can't fight city hall.
Apparently you can. That's
why it took so long.
Well, I'll be damned.
Would you look at that?
It's so clear now. The entire
school is shaped like a penis.
No, that. It says right here that this
stairway leads to sublevel three.
Is that where the
teachers' lounge is?
What the hell does
your penis look like?
Obviously a cluster of buildings, so
let's all have a big laugh at the freak.
♪ Give me some rope ♪
♪ Tie me to dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope ♪
♪ To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said
it can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the
reasons I should stay ♪
♪ One by one, they
all just fade away ♪
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
The missing stairwell
would be in this area.
Keep your eyes peeled. I don't
know why, but serial killers
and people that hide treasure
always leave weird little clues.
Check it out.
Look at the bottle
held by the school's
first and least acceptable
mascot, Big Chief Drunky.
X marks the spot, baby.
Hey Hickey, maybe you
shouldn't be... Okay.
- Shirley, will you lock the door?
- Okay.
There you go.
It's just a
bunch of wires.
Exactly what they
want us to think.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait. The sparks may
be spelling out the next clue.
- Is Duncan okay?
He'll live,
but his food's gonna taste like
burnt aluminum for a while.
It's pronounced "al-u-minium."
- See, he's fine.
- Okay, guys, stop it now.
Nobody wants to admit
its over, but come on.
Oh, look, it's Jeff
Winger, fun police,
here to pull over our smiles 'cause
our mouths have tinted windows.
Britta and I are
getting married.
- What?
- Married?
Well, you're gonna need
way more doves than this.
What does this look like, an
hour-long episode of The Office?
There's pick-axing and
electric zapping.
Don't even acknowledge it. We
are not acknowledging this.
You guys are
ridiculous together.
We're ridiculous? What
do you call this?
- Secret trapdoor!
- Booyah.
- Who's got rope?
- I'm offended by that question.
This is Richie and Carl
from the school board.
That's right. We got names.
Open this door now.
Wait, I know where
the keys are.
You hear that? When we get there,
you're gonna be in big trouble.
Here they are.
Which one is it?
Well, it's never the first one,
so we can cancel this one out.
Come on.
I guess now this is the first one,
so it should be the next one.
- Oh, damn.
- You know what?
I got it. Get
out of the way.
- Richie, be careful.
- Don't worry.
I've been drinking.
Oh, hello. Would
you like some tea?
The tea is swell.
- Do you think they...
- Shh.
- I think...
- Oh, come on, shh.
- Shh.
- You know it's just as loud as...
Everybody, shut up!
Guys, I think this is the
lost section of Greendale.
Nobody's been in
here since the '70s.
How do you know?
Because the debate team topic is "Who's
hotter, Elliot Gould or Donald Sutherland?"
Donald Sutherland.
- Scary.
- Oh, relax.
If it's anything like
a regular dungeon,
it's only as dangerous
as whoever invited you.
Abed, if there's killer
robots down here,
you'll tell them we're
on your side, right?
Yes, but we won't know them from
ordinary robots until they kill us.
- So what do we do now?
- Split up.
Leave no '70s reference unturned. This
decade's a little out of my wheelhouse.
Pet rock... Leave no
pet rock unturned.
- Here, let me lead. My light's better.
- Your light's better?
You're that insecure that
your light has to be better?
- Shut up.
- You shut up.
- Anything in there?
- Just spider webs and beanbag chairs.
- Oh, don't cry. The importance of lumbar
support hadn't... - It's not that.
It's just even if we do save Greendale,
which Greendale will we be saving?
First Pierce dies.
Then Troy leaves.
- Now people are...
- Getting married?
Annie, look, I don't know
people, but I know TV.
When characters feel like
the show they're on is ending,
their instinct is to spin off
into something safer,
in Jeff and Britta's case, something
that would last six episodes
and have a lot of bickering
about tweezers and gluten,
starring them and an
equally W.A.S.P.-y
brunette couple with a title
like better with my worse half
or awfully wedded or tying the not,
but "knot" is spelt without a K,
or #CouplePeopleProblems, and
every episode, you get...
- Abed. Abed, stop developing.
- Sorry.
The point is, this show, Annie,
it isn't just their show.
This is our show,
and it's not over.
And the sooner we find that treasure, the
faster the Jeff-Britta pilot falls apart.
Got it. Thank you, Abed.
You're welcome.
- I have a girlfriend.
- What?
You were about to
start a kiss lean.
- I was not.
- Fine. Let's go find treasure.
- Did you find anything?
- No.
We've searched every
crevice of this place,
and the only treasures we've
found are this CB radio,
these basketball cards
with white people on them,
and this little rocket launcher
from some action figure.
Seems like an odd place
for a dead end, though.
Could be a secret door. Maybe
the jukebox is the key to it.
Just remember, it's
okay if we fail.
- Right, Jeff?
- That's right.
Agh, try every button. Just
try every single button ever.
- Are you all right?
- No!
I was dying!
- Try track 127.
- Right.
Because 127 in binary code
would be a palindrome.
Because the song title is "Open
the Door" by The Secret Doors.
- ♪ Open the door ♪
- ♪ Yeah, sweet mama ♪
- ♪ We got to open the door ♪
- ♪ And the door is opening ♪
♪ You're the playing the song
that opens the door ♪
♪ We recorded this song for
when you open the door ♪
♪ Specially timed to the duration
of the opening process ♪
Borchert's secret lab.
That's the machine Borchert
was working on in the film.
Borchert's gold.
We need to get
this upstairs.
Save Greendale.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
You're Russell
Borchert, aren't you?
Hey, I'm gonna peel off
some band-aids here.
Dennis Hopper is dead,
TV shows give no time
for theme songs anymore,
and Woody Allen did the
voice of a cartoon ant.
Jeff!
Sorry, I lose track of
how big I'm getting.
I don't.
You vandalized
private property.
You nearly destroy the school when
it's finally about to make a profit?
You guys are the worst, with your
stupid paintballs and your freeze tags.
- Hot lava.
- That was hot lava?
Dumb.
Tell us where the
others went.
Guys, guys.
- What do you want to do?
- What should we do?
Well, what can we do?
Okay.
I'm gonna need you
guys to stay back
and never tell anyone about
what you saw here today.
You're special, Richie.
Your mind is special.
You know it works differently
from other kids' minds.
♪ Richie's a freak,
Richie's a freak ♪
Thank you.
I know where they went.
They climbed out a window to the
roof, hopped on a hang glider,
and flew it across town to that
Greek restaurant, Papa Cristo's?
I robbed your brain.
I robbed it.
Hey, guys, we found a hatch in the floor
underneath the vending machine.
- I think they went down inside it.
- Was there a hang glider?
You're gonna find out... You're gonna
find a hang glider down there.
That much I know.
So anyway, I sealed
myself up down here
with 50 years of food, 50 years of
toilet paper, and 50 years of cocaine,
which I somehow ran out of
after about 10 years.
Wow, the '80s happened
down here too.
Yeah. Hey, what are you
doing with Raquel?
Mm-mm, uh-uh.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
Russell, we're on a bit of a deadline, and
to put it bluntly, we need your gold.
- Raquel! I'm almost done...
- Uh, guys, little help...
She just needs a
little more time.
Sir, Raquel has taken the best years of
your life and a dozen of your not-so-good.
If she hasn't given anything back,
it might be time to move on.
Stop. You guys,
what are we doing?
- Saving Greendale.
- From what?
We were driven down here
by sellouts with crappy values.
Since when do human beings decide
which dreams are worthwhile?
Look at him.
He's one of us.
We have to respect
each other enough to...
let each other want
what we want,
no matter how transparently
self-destructive
or empty our
desires may be.
If it was money that you guys
wanted, why didn't you say so?
You can just have my leftover cash
that's under the desk over there.
Yeah, I don't think it's
worth much up there.
- Those are Gerald Ford dollars.
- How many?
Eh, couple of million. Back in the
'70s, that was worth millions.
Hey, I've got an idea.
How about you people leave me alone
and I hereby grant that to Greendale?
What?
Glad to hear it.
Get back. This
pickle's a magnet.
- Whoa, whoa.
- I'll wipe her out, man.
Don't you dare use
that pickle...
Get over there with them.
You have no legal
claim to that money.
Take it up with Subway in about
an hour after close of escrow.
Hey, Chang, you've
become a bad guy again?
There's a lot more to it
than that, Britta.
Wait, I'm not
wearing a mask?
Okay, there's no more to it.
I think I'm just mentally ill.
All right, just stay back.
All right?
No, don't.
No!
- ♪ Close the door ♪
- ♪ Yeah, sweet mama ♪
- ♪ We got to close the door ♪
- ♪ The door is closing ♪
- ♪ Faster than it opens ♪
- ♪ For dramatic effect ♪
- Hey!
- Hang in there.
Raquel is the main
operating system.
She controls the door, the lights,
the shower probably, everything,
and now she's dead.
So we're trapped
in here forever.
Or just until we run
out of food and water.
- At least we'll have each other.
- Till death do us part.
You know what? You guys can
have my food and water.
Come on, Raquel. Come on.
Baby. Come on.
Oh, thank God. Her emotional
components are still on-line.
Emotional components?
I have accomplished things down here
you couldn't even possibly imagine.
Here, let me show you.
Ah, right there! That was it.
That was it. Did you see it?
Don't you see? This computer
responds to feelings.
When I started Greendale,
it was for ordinary people
- to be able to access technology.
- Wait, you started Greendale.
Do you have that in
writing anywhere?
I don't know. Somewhere with
all that crap over there.
But without an
emotional component,
computers would strip
us of all humanity
and create a society with
emotionless eggheads at the top
and idiots with feelings
at the bottom,
and I refuse to let that happen,
and that's why I've spent...
What? What is that?
It's a video of a kitten.
And why are those people
arguing about it?
- And what's that?
- That's an emoticon.
That person wants to indicate happiness
but can't convey it with language,
so they misuse punctuation
to form a smile.
That is so...
stupid.
Only an idiot would
think of this.
Idiots won,
which means my work
down here is done.
Good, because according
to what I'm seeing,
if we can get you
up there right now,
Subway won't be
buying this school.
- What?
Uh, yeah, but it's gonna take a
few hours to get that door open,
because Raquel's
logic circuits...
bleh, not good.
You said her emotional
components work.
Well, in theory, a blast of human
passion could shock the mainframe
into a cold start, but that's
only if somebody in this room
has feelings stronger than
I get when I rub my nipples,
so good luck with
that, folks.
Give me that.
Everybody over there.
Turn around.
Turn around now.
You're here to save
me, aren't you?
Let's get out of here
and never look back.
Jeff, in case you ever have
to remember me,
- can I give you some options for
voice-over quotes? - Shut up, Abed.
- Milady.
- Milord.
- What did you do?
- Don't worry about it. Let's go.
The city of
Greendale is proud
to be selling the school
of Greendale to Subway.
This brings to an
end several years
of horrible management
by Dean Craig Isidore Pelton.
Not to throw anyone under the
bus, but he'd be the one.
And by my watch, it is about time to sign
these documents and make it official.
Objection! I teach
law at Greendale,
so believe me, I don't
know much about law,
but I do know a contract
violation when I see one.
This is a legitimate transaction where a
city is selling a school to a restaurant.
It happens somewhere
every day.
Oh, the city can sell the
school all it wants,
but according to his
contract with the city,
the school's original founder retains
the privilege of consultation
on all future scholastic
endeavors taking place here.
So Subway Sandwich University, meet
your new Vice Dean, Russell Borchert.
Oh.
Hi, I guess we're
gonna be partners.
I understand there's
some internet
where I can make my
inner thoughts public.
It seems like
Greendale the city
and Greendale the school
have some stuff to sort out,
and Subway doesn't...
doesn't do conflict.
We do good food
at good prices.
We are but simple
sandwich artists
who want the world
to eat fresh.
Eat fresh!
Subway, ho!
Did we just save Greendale?
- Did we just save Greendale?
- No, no, you did not.
You moved dirt around
Greendale's grave.
Your school is still bankrupt,
it is still unmarketable,
and it is still on the
permanent chopping block
of anyone who has any
say in its future.
Yeah?
Well, around here, we
call that Wednesday.
♪ He wakes up in
the morning ♪
♪ Never changes a thing ♪
Hey, after I was
electrocuted,
didn't you two say you
were gonna get married?
Doesn't electrocuted
technically mean killed?
Do you always have to
correct people like that?
Do you always have
to police correcting?
- That's it. The marriage is off.
- I think you mean the wedding is off.
- Yeah!
- Hey, hey.
Hey, I got to say, you held up
well under that interrogation.
I'm gonna tell you something that
I'd like to stay between us.
Oh.
I was thinking about
a hang glider.
None of this conflict
truly matters.
The only owners of this
land are the Arapaho.
Would it offend you if I asked you to
train me in the use of certain powers?
Sorry, Carl. You
deserve better.
Chang, you get it.
How would you like a job
on the school board?
Okay.
Your first job is to deliver this
to the city bursar's office.
On it.
Hi, yes, I'd like to replace
all my teeth with diamonds.
We live to fight
another day.
Speaking of days, I never got a
chance to wish you a happy birthday
or Halloween or Christmas
or any specific calendar event.
- Well, maybe next year.
- Definitely.
We'll definitely
be back next year.
If not, it'll be because an asteroid
has destroyed all human civilization,
and that's canon.
What? What are you...
Hmm? Nothing.
♪ Lights down,
you up and die ♪
Am I thinking what
you're thinking?
Penny for your thoughts.
Intensive Karen.
Mr. Egypt.
Celebrity beat-off.
Captain Cook.
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther