Welcome back to Greendale,
now ranking fifth
on Colorado's
alphabetical listing
of community colleges.
Rest in peace, Bad Boy
Slim's DJ School.
This school owes its continued
existence to the following heroes.
Jeff Winger, a teacher so
dedicated to clean energy,
he's already parking like
his car is electric.
Britta Perry, currently raising
awareness of homelessness,
not that she has a choice.
Abed Nadir, who actually wrote
this announcement for the sake of,
as he put it,
catching everyone up.
And Annie Edison who led the effort to save
Greendale from 534 critical emergencies.
534?
Frisbee!
Hey Leonard, what, are you
gonna Bogart the disc all day?
Like
tears in rain.
What?
Corrections by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for FiHTV WEB-DL by Rapunzel
I can't believe
the roof collapsed.
- We almost killed Fat Neil.
- That was Garrett.
See, we're monsters.
Okay, if they blame us for
this, let me take the heat.
I'd never see
the inside of a cell.
I have been reliving this day over
and over for a thousand years.
Guys, this is not on us.
That roof was gonna collapse, 80%
of the rubble was styrofoam.
Speaking of guilt,
where's Shirley?
You didn't tell him?
I was waiting until
we were all together.
Abed's not comfortable
with C-H-A-N-G-E.
Hey, screw you.
I can spell.
Screw you.
Is Shirley gone?
Did she spin off?
Nobody spins off in
real life, Abed.
Shirley went to look
after her dad in Atlanta
and ended up taking a job
as a personal chef to a brilliant,
but troubled
Southern detective.
I told her I'd manage her
sandwich shop while she's gone.
Oh, that's very
generous of you.
I have a friend in town, every time
you're gonna need help with that.
- She'll be back.
- Like Troy?
Are any of you white people noticing
what's happening to this group?
Do Abed and I need
to be concerned?
You have my word, as leader of the white
people there's no cause for alarm.
Say hello to new Shirley.
Just kidding.
This is Francesca Dart.
I have brought her on as an
administrative consultant.
I thought it would be fun,
and mandatory for you to add
her to your little committee.
Why, because one
roof collapsed?
No, God, God no.
I'm your friend bringing
you a new friend,
one with training in
not collapsing roofs.
Is she, excuse me, ma'am.
Is she above us or below us?
She is, woop!
I'm getting a call, here,
and I'll have to take it.
Frankie, why don't you explain
what your role will be,
while I leave
to take this call.
My phone is vibrating,
but it is...
In your office, which
you didn't realize,
when you started the fake
phone call move.
- My phone is in my pocket, Jeffrey.
- Mm.
I'm walking away, so I can
get it out and answer it.
Let me know how it goes.
Okay, I'll just
have a seat and—
- No! - Hey!
- No! No, no, no!
Our friend use
to sit there.
She spun off.
I'm sorry, what
about here?
- Yeah, I guess that's okay.
- That's cool.
Okay, so,
I took an informal survey to get
a sense of how Greendale is perceived.
And three themes emerged;
Weird, passionate
and gross.
Now you want to hang
onto that grouping.
In marketing, it's what
we call the Good Belushi.
If I had a magic wand,
I would use it to make sure
Greendale never had to grow up.
I would also probably use it
to cut the Magic Wand class
that I noticed is
actually offered here,
as well as VCR Repair,
a class called Ladders,
and When is it Okay
to Shake a Baby?
In terms of hierarchy, I'm
a big believer in it.
Someone needs to say, I'm in
charge, and that person is me.
That's my decision.
That doesn't mean that
we don't work together,
but all communication
and decisions will go through me.
I'll send out an email later
to set up our next meeting.
- Awesome. - Okay.
- Great seeing you, Professor.
Yeah. Coolios.
- Who in the crazy bitch?
- Did that just happen?
Did you see her binder?
- Pretty nondescript.
- Seems like she may be trouble.
To be fair, she's an additional
white person,
which has clearly
become important here.
No, thank you.
I-I'm just glad I was
able to answer.
My-My phone got
lodged in my pocket.
I know!
I guess that is a thing.
So, you were saying
about the thing,
the reason you were calling was,
what were you talking to me about?
Looks good, Tony.
I'm sorry, I just assume
your name is Tony.
Here you go.
I gave you some
extra heat.
Britta, what is the weekly
cost of this restaurant?
Oh, that's easy.
My dignity.
Seems like this sandwich counter
is consuming your happiness
and converting it into
burnt bread and debt.
So?
Frankie, hi.
Um...
someone removed all the liquor
from the faculty lounge.
I'm sorry, I cannot legally
protect or insure a campus
with free flowing booze.
Well, I can't teach with
free flowing sobriety.
Is that true?
Do you really think
you're an addict?
No.
Dean!
Hello? Oh, oh, hey!
- Yes, I can talk.
- Damn it.
I am available
anytime for you.
Frankie, Frankie.
Hi. I had an idea about how
to deelectrify the pool.
Oh, that's already
been dealt with.
- Okay, well, then, there's—
- Oh, let's see.
Done, done, deloused.
Appraised,
defused, rebuilt.
De-peanut buttered,
debunked, spayed, neutered.
Underway, resanctified,
plunged, deported and exhumed.
Thank you.
Oh, this is pretty.
Huh.
I'm gonna name one of my
sandwiches after her.
My sandwiches suck.
She is improving
Greendale.
Yeah, but how much can
you improve Greendale
before it stops
being Greendale?
She didn't suffer
for this place.
She doesn't understand it.
She's gonna end up messing
with something that—
Abed.
Temporal mutation
in English, Doc.
Simply put Mr. President,
in 12 hours these
dinosaurs will become—
- Mind if I sit here?
- Time-asaurs.
Go ahead, I can reshoot.
How's everything going?
- I have concerns.
- I'd like to hear them.
I'm worried you're not
distinct enough from Annie,
both in terms of
physicality and purpose.
Okay.
I can't determine if you
have any specific flaw,
quirk, or point of view that makes you
a creative addition to the group.
I don't know what that means,
but I'm writing it down.
My umbrella concern is
that you, as a character,
represent the end of what
I used to call our show,
which was once an unlikely
family of misfit students,
and is now a pretty loose knit
group of students and teachers.
None of whom are taking a class together
in a school which, as of your arrival,
is becoming increasingly
grounded, asking questions like,
how do any of us
get our money?
When will we get our degrees, and what
happened to that girl I was dating?
As opposed to questions I consider
more important like, what is real?
What is sanity? Is there a god?
Where's that Pierce hologram?
Jeff said last year he
saw a Pierce hologram.
None of the rest of us have ever seen it.
So, if there's a Pierce ghost on campus,
I'd like to get a head
start on busting it.
All right.
This is the first I've heard
that I'm a character on a show.
I'm excited to be one, but
I agree, I'll be a boring one.
Quirks are not my strong
suit, results are.
I love quirky people.
I come from a big family of
people who are literally insane.
I moved down here to take
care of one of them.
But I myself am
exceptionally boring,
and I am quite proud
to be that way,
because it allows me to help the less
boring people turn quirks into results.
That's the most interesting take on not
being interesting that I've ever heard.
As far as what I represent
about your show,
I wouldn't give me or anyone
else that kind of power.
Good shows change,
I assume.
Personally,
I don't own a TV.
You're the first person to say that that
I didn't immediately delete from my brain.
Thank you.
Emergency meeting
at Shirley's Sandwiches right now.
Everyone freaking out.
New lady is evil.
Crazy frown.
I should go.
Abed, I could really use someone's help
in learning the ropes around here.
I'll ask around.
Friends, dumb hats.
- Totally talking down to you.
- She hates you.
I got it from Jared.
- What are you guys doing back here?
Are you the big chilling? - Yeah,
only there's not a hippie that died
to make us come together and complain.
- It's our school.
- Frankie's taking over the campus.
She cancelled Ladders,
she's banning substances,
she wants to shut down
Shirley's sandwiches.
- She called Annie a bitch.
- She implied I was a bitch.
She implied Annie was a stuck up bitch
who thinks she's better than everyone.
- Okay, now you're just—
- She was nice to me.
In fact we kinda
got along.
Abed, are you sure she wasn't
actually being sweetly condescending?
Yup, I learned to pick
up on that one.
I make a movement that we form
a separate, secret, committee.
I second Britta's motion,
not movement.
I third Annie's number two-ing
of the movement Britta made.
- Gross. - Our mission
to preserve the real Greendale.
Oppose Frankie or drink.
Whatever's easiest.
Are you guys
sure she's bad?
Are you sure you're not doing what
I usually do, overreacting to change?
Nobody's ever doing what you
usually do Abed. You're nuts.
Ugh.
In a good way.
I'm just saying.
- Leave reality to us.
- We always support you.
Don't make it more
dramatic than it is.
It's a blood oath to defy evil.
You're either in or you're out.
Can I hang around if
I don't do the oath.
Oh, gee. You mean
just be friends?
Sure. Great, Abed.
Okay.
Can I have some pretzels?
No.
Those are secret
committee pretzels.
Okay.
Well.
Yes, that was a test.
You guys are bad friends.
Don't think of it
as bad baking.
Think of it as a crushing
blow to a gender stereotype.
Britta, it might help
if every burnt sandwich
didn't come with a self-aware
burnt sandwich bit.
Is that how you're gonna help
increase sales, creative notes?
I had that sign
spinner idea.
We're a restaurant inside a cafeteria
Annie, our weak point wasn't traffic.
Flo, Alice, stop fighting, can't
afford to lose this place.
If I have to start drinking
in the men's room,
the score in my head has
to change from Trent Reznor
to Johnny Cash doing
Trent Reznor.
I'm a bartender Annie, I know a little bit
more about the human side of service.
I can't eat this.
Can I have my money back?
You're human garbage.
Hi, Mr. Winger.
Nice lecture yesterday.
Don't patronize me Dave.
It might not seem like this, but you're
killing small, black owned business.
I'll call it even for
a drink with Mr. Winger.
- That's absurd.
- You will?
Let's see some ID.
You snitch, you die.
- Morning.
Morning.
Well I guess we'll wait for
the others before we start.
I don't think
they're coming.
What? The committee had a meeting
last night and decided you are evil.
Ooh. Wait, you guys had
a meeting last night?
So, we broke
up as friends.
Because I don't
think you're evil.
I think you scare people, because you live
in the real world instead of up your butt.
I'm sorry that
happened, Abed.
It's like I said
yesterday at lunch.
Drama and conflict are
exciting and easy.
Making a difference
can be pretty boring.
You guys had lunch?
I'd like to try to live
in that world.
I'm a little tired from all the drama,
the heroes, the villains, monsters.
Pokemons..
- You're just a person that sees things
the way they are. - Leprechauns. Scary.
I don't know if I can
be like that but
I don't think it makes
sense to be against it.
You guys ever hear
of The Slender Man?
I'd like to try
to help you.
- And if possible, learn from you.
- You guys on Reddit, 4Chan?
- That would be great, Abed.
- Cuz it's awesome.
I think we'd all benefit if
we were more like you, so
what do you say?
Let's order some food.
- Let's save Greendale.
Tacos!
We are something else.
Abed.
- Abed.
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
Someone told me you were
sweeping, straightening clocks.
Why are you cleaning that sign?
I gave you a list.
Yeah, the list felt
pretty similar visually.
I can't picture a montage cutting
from me verifying Diane's invoice
to me emailing
confirmation to Diane.
Right. But a montage
is what, Abed?
It's a movie apologizing
for reality.
And we are where?
- Reality.
- And what do people do here?
They email Diane?
Abed, if you change your clothes
one more time today, you're fired.
Sorry.
- Hey, Abed.
Hey, Todd.
- Are Annie and Britta around?
- No.
Abed,
maybe you should
order the special.
I'll have the special.
The specials are
kept in the back.
You should, you should
go in the back.
I'd like the special.
Vaporizers, Skittles?
- Abed.
- Hey, Annie.
- This place is so conceptual.
- It's practical, too.
We made enough money
to save Shirley's.
And in an ironic way, because if
Shirley saw this, her soul would die.
Hey, Abed, check this out.
- Oh, Britta's still the worst?
- Yeah.
The bar gets dirty.
You're gonna need someone to clean
it, probably after hours,
and those floor polishers
can get pretty loud.
I'd hate for someone
to hear it.
You blackmailing me?
Just talking shop.
- What's the rumpus, Abed?
- Miller's Crossing.
Mm-hm.
This is really great. You guys
should be proud of yourselves.
We missed you.
Have a drink.
Put on an old
timey jacket.
That's okay, I don't
really do this anymore.
All right, come on.
I said I don't
do this, see.
- You dirty rat.
- Guys are all dirty rats.
What's your romper room?
All right, maybe
just one drink.
Then maybe cut
to a montage of drinks.
Drink up!
- Let's never stop being
friends again ever. - Mm-hm.
Cheers!
We shouldn't have made you
choose between Frankie and us.
Oh, she's good
for business.
We're sorry that we made
you choose between—
- You're just repeating what I said.
- No, you're repeating what I said.
Oh, I'm a time traveler?
This is the show.
Abed,
I just got word from Diane that one
of your emails was a little shaky.
Are you okay?
I'm good. Late
night last night.
Yeah?
Yeah, I could use
a little protein.
I'm gonna go get
an early lunch.
You guys know about
tardigrades?
They're these microscopic creatures
that look like robot bears.
- They can survive in space.
- Mm. - Mm-hm.
Get into space, you
dirty tardigrades, see?
And they're everywhere.
There's a lot of little things in real
life that are just as cool as fake stuff.
I learned that
working for Frankie.
You guys would like
her, you know.
Raid!
Is this what
you guys want?
You wanna play cops
and robbers with costumes?
Why is that guy a carrot?
- Because they ran out.
- Who tattled?
In what world, Britta, do you see this
as covert enough to require tattling?
You built a bar
in a school.
There was lumber involved.
I have been letting you
hole up down here,
because it kept you
contained and satisfied,
because you are all
compulsively defiant,
but it wasn't enough.
You had to drag Abed back in,
and Abed deserves better.
- Oh. - Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho,
it finally comes out.
Abed deserves better.
- That's been out.
- Shut up, Leonard.
I once mistook six people
for you at a pharmacy.
It's not their fault, Frankie.
I chose this.
These are my friends.
I hate emailing Diane.
She can't commit to a font.
It's pathological, and so am I.
This is where I belong.
I know you think that, Abed,
but you don't know any better.
Whoops.
But—
shut up, Leonard.
You are.
You are old.
And you deserve less,
because of your age.
I don't, I don't
actually believe that.
I'm just trying to,
I'm trying to, and
everybody here is a,
is a fart a livid fart
from the butt of
a lesser god.
I'm, I'm better than this.
Cut to everyone on campus getting
as drunk as they want montage.
Frankie hasn't come
back to work today.
That's terrible.
The insurance
company dropped us.
- The school has no insurance.
- What was Frankie's salary?
- A lot. - What were
the insurance premiums?
- A lot. - Add those two numbers together,
that's your new school dance budget.
Oh, nice.
Welcome to Ladders!
Yeah!
Ladder!
Who wants to see the ladders
professor go higher?
Ladder!
Aah!
You did it, Jeff Winger!
This is your school now.
- Annie.
- It was worth it.
Aah!
All right, that should be the extent
of the professor's medical bills.
What-What about that
lawsuits from the students?
I think we should
fight those.
Actually, I suggest you
settle out of court.
- This is my fault.
- Obviously not.
- It's my fault.
- Guys, it's my fault.
It's my fault. It's my fault.
All right, all
right, all right.
So, whose fault wasn't it?
And who knows anything about
handling anything like this?
In terms of hierarchy, I'm
a big believer in it.
Someone needs to say, I'm in
charge, and that person is me.
That's my decision.
Wait, what?
- I'm sorry?
- Who talks like that?
Why would anyone hire
someone so pompous?
Miss Dart, word of advice,
change your personality,
or start looking for companies
run by insane people.
- Don't hire this woman.
- Fifth time's the charm.
He's barged the four offices
screaming, don't hire this woman.
- What the hell is going on?
- What are you doing here?
- How did you even find me?
- I emailed Diane.
She knows way too much about
your schedule, by the way.
Whatever he's offering you,
Greendale, well, we can't double it.
We probably can't
even match it.
Whatever he's offering you, Greendale
will give you less, and an apology.
- Do you know—
- Shh.
It's not enough,
but maybe if you added
more apologies.
Like a montage of them?
We're sorry.
I told you I wouldn't be
needing dinner tonight.
I'm guessing you wouldn't.
Not if you're
looking for this.
How'd you know?
Nobody makes more
crumbs than a cook.
Well, the same goes for
clues and detectives.
You're too busy solving murders
to get away with your own.
Well, then, what about the case
of my wife and my legs, Shirley?
Can you solve that one, huh?
Can you?
Cuz if you can't, then I ain't
got nothing to live for.
Begging your pardon,
Mr. Butcher.
I think the people on this
bayou would disagree.
- You rescued a runaway girl today.
- Rescued, balls.
I couldn't even rescue
a, a bulb from a socket.
And you did all the work
today, didn't you?
I'm just a detective from the swamps
of Atlanta, can't even walk.
- Oh.
- Aah!
Then let me be your legs.
Let me do for you what I did today
every week until you find your wife.
Or your legs.
You are a stubborn son of
a bitch, Shirley Bennett.
Now come on.
I have dinner to make.
You got cases to solve.
Feeling someone's gonna murder
some tater tots tonight.
That's no mystery at all.
Next week, on The
Butcher and The Baker,
when a new detective on
the Bayou disappears,
and Butcher is the prime suspect, it's up
to Shirley to cook up some answers.
Corrections by honeybunny
www. addic7ed. com
Resync for FiHTV WEB-DL by Rapunzel