How far to Hexham?
It's not far.
Are you sure?
Yes!
Ragnar! Rollo!
Let's attack
straightaway.
No.
We attack tomorrow.
Why wait?
It is
a large town.
We have only a few men.
Then surprise is
our biggest advantage.
Arne.
What day is it today?
Saturday.
Then we attack tomorrow.
Why?
You will
understand tomorrow.
Wh o we re
th e s e s tra n g e rs?
I cannot say.
Their ship was sighted
sailing up the coast.
It was a ship
unlike any other.
They were not Franks then?
No. They looked
very different
and used axes.
Most were
as tall as giants.
Sire, I fear
that these raiders
are the same pagans
who attacked
the monastery
at Lindisfarne.
It is the letter
Abbot Alcuin wrote to you
of those terrible events.
"They came
to the church
at Lindisfarne.
"Laid everything waste
with grievous plundering.
"Trampled the holy place
with polluted steps.
"Dug up the altars
"and seized
all the treasure
of the holy church.
"They killed
some of the brothers,
"took some away
with them in fetters,
"some they drowned
in the sea."
Where do they come from,
these pagans?
Some say
from the north.
Well, wherever
they come from,
they are not welcome
in my kingdom.
Take care today.
Don't take
any foolish risks.
And don't
get separated
from the others.
I was just going
to say the same thing
to you, my love.
Enough of that talk.
It's getting light,
and we've wasted
too much time already.
We must wait
a little longer.
Wait?
What for?
Just wait!
For what?
And listen!
I don't hear
anything.
Well, what are you
waiting for?
Get out of the way!
In the name of God,
who are you?
Why have you
come here?
This is a place of God.
If you do not resist,
we will not hurt you.
Tell that to your
people, priest.
Tell them
not to be afraid.
God bless.
Mom!
Knut!
Leave her alone!
What do you care
for this Saxon,
you bitch?
Where is Knut?
I killed him.
You killed him?
He raped
a Saxon woman.
Then he tried
to rape me.
Did anyone else
see it happen?
That's a pity.
And where were you?
Hold!
What is it?
Who is there?
Archers to forward!
Shield wall!
Down!
Stand!
Brace!
Open!
Up into the
overturned keel.
Clamber, with a heart
of steel.
Cold is the ocean's spray.
When your death
is on its way.
With maidens
you have had
your way.
Each must die some day!
- Hakon!
- Close the wall!
Shield wall!
Go!
How could this happen,
My Lord Wigea?
Sire, I have
never in my life
seen men fight
as these
northmen fight.
Believe me,
there's something devilish
in the way they look,
in their lack of fear
in the face of death.
My Lord, that is just
a counsel of despair.
Are these pagans
not men, like we are?
Do they not bleed
when they are cut?
Or do they have wings
and tongues of fire?
No, sire.
Who are they?
We captured
two of them who were
guarding their boat.
We couldn't
understand anything
they said at all,
except one word.
Ragnar.
Do you have
any family, priest?
I had four brothers
and a sister.
They all died of a fever,
like my mother and father.
I was only saved
because they had me
placed in a monastery
when I was just a child.
They had too many
mouths to feed.
So you are alone?
No.
God is my father,
so I am never alone.
What does your god
look like?
No one can know what
God looks like.
It would be like
looking into the sun.
It cannot be done.
But he did send his only son
to live on the Earth
and he looked like a man.
Odin, Thor and Loki
are like men,
or are they your gods?
They aren't gods.
They don't exist.
Bjorn.
Death was on its way
to take Kauko.
Don't grieve for him.
Don't pity him.
Guess where
he is now?
Valkyries have
taken him home
to Valhalla.
Right at this moment
he is...
He is drinking ale
with the gods.
Yes.
He is happier
than even we are.
With our boat and...
These goods.
Even so,
he was my kinsman.
We must avenge
his death.
It was done
in the name
of King Aelle,
and King Aelle
must suffer for it.
One day, he will.
If the gods will it.
Look at him,
he's wetting himself.
You kept your word.
You took us to the town,
and I thank you for that.
Drink.
You want to live?
I want to go
to Kattegat.
I want to see
my father
return soon.
He must return soon.
I gave your father
my word that I would
look after you both here.
You are not
looking after us.
We look after ourselves.
I cannot allow you to go
on your own to Kattegat.
Your father
would never tolerate
such a thing.
Then we should
go together.
The three of us.
And who will then
look after the farm?
For what we are
about to receive,
may the Lord make
us truly grateful.
Amen.
Can I have
some ale?
You're too young,
Gyda, to drink ale.
I want to make
a sacrifice to Thor,
for my father's
safe return.
What will you sacrifice?
You!
Where are you, Lord?
Tell me.
Is it your will
that I am here
with these heathens?
How does it serve you?
I don't understand.
And for the first time
in my life,
I am angry with you.
You allow my brothers
to be slaughtered and sold.
Is this really your will?
For the first time,
I feel lonely.
Where are you, Lord?
Where are you?
And why don't
you answer me?
It's just an owl.
Bjorn.
Bjorn, wake up.
What is it?
We'll go to Kattegat.
All of us, tomorrow.
Kattegat!
Ragnar Lothbrok,
my friend,
how was your voyage?
Successful, I hope,
for all our sakes.
The Saxons attacked us
when we returned
to the boat,
in great force,
but we defeated them!
You are the man that
people say you are.
A great adventurer,
and I am happy to salute
your achievements
and to share
in the profit
of your raid.
But I don't see
my friend, Knut.
Where is he?
Knut is dead.
Dead?
Did he die in battle?
No.
Then how did he die?
I killed him.
You killed him.
For what reason?
Because he tried
to rape my wife,
Lagertha.
I find it too convenient
that you would
make an excuse
to kill my friend
and my agent
on your voyage.
What did you think
that you would gain
by getting rid of him?
I didn't expect
to gain anything.
I don't believe you.
Arrest him!
My Lord!
For your wife, Siggy,
would have you
not done the same?
I would counsel you all
against such actions.
There is no way
you could prevail.
Floki.
Bring him away.
Ragnar! Ragnar!
You summoned
me, Lord?
Yes, I want
to talk to you.
Please, sit. Drink.
It's...
It's a delicate matter.
You...
You are the brother
of Ragnar Lothbrok,
are you not?
I am.
A spirited man,
your brother.
Is he a fair man?
Does he treat you equally
when you sail with him?
Up to a point.
Forgive me, but I think
that he likes to rule you.
And that whatever he says,
in actual fact,
he considers himself
to be first among equals.
Am I correct?
I get the impression
that he wants
to take the credit
for everything.
For building the boat,
for sailing west.
He wants to be the hero.
Is that what
it comes down to?
To him?
Would he have achieved
what he has achieved
if it wasn't for you?
What do you say, Rollo?
Of course not.
It would have
been impossible.
As long as I am Earl,
Ragnar Lothbrok
can give you nothing.
I, on the other hand,
can give you a great deal.
I could, for example,
confiscate the treasure
that you brought
back from England.
And offer you
a goodly portion of it.
Would you
do that, Lord?
I might.
Depends.
On what would
it depend?
Your ambition.
You want to stand out.
You want to be
someone, Rollo.
You want the gods
to notice you, yes?
They would have
noticed me already.
Oh, no, my friend.
And do you know why?
Because you still walk
in the shadow
of Ragnar Lothbrok.
Don't you think it's time
you stepped out from it,
and let the gods see you
for who you really are?
Oh.
I want you to say
hello to somebody.
This is my
daughter, Thyri.
She is soon
to get married,
and I must think
very carefully about
her future husband.
He must be
a man of ambition
and prospect,
as you can understand.
I used to have two boys,
but they were killed.
So the man that I choose
to be my son-in-law
will hold a high
and special place,
as if he were
my own son.
Thyri, say
hello to Rollo.
Hello.
Don't forget
about me, my love.
Oh, yes.
And this is Siggy,
my wife.
This is Rollo.
He is the brother
of Ragnar Lothbrok.
Hello, Rollo.
I have heard
a lot about you.
They say that you
are a great warrior.
Bring in the prisoner.
That murderer!
Free him!
Free Ragnar!
Look at him!
He's in chains.
It's all right, boy.
We are all aware
of the sacred nature
of our duty here.
You stand
before us accused
of the willful murder
of Knut, my brother.
Knut, as some
of you may know,
was the bastard son
of my father.
But I loved him
like a brother.
I asked Knut
to go with
Ragnar Lothbrok
to England,
where they raided
a town and brought
back many spoils.
And while they were
raiding this town,
Ragnar Lothbrok
took it upon himself
to cold-bloodedly
kill my brother.
It's easy to imagine
why a man like this
would do such a thing.
This is an ambitious man.
He doesn't care
to share his spoils.
And he resents the fact
that he owes me
loyalty and obedience,
as his chieftain.
This is a man who
does not believe
in our traditions.
This is a man
who does not believe
in our laws.
Silence! Silence!
What do you
have to say,
when you stand before us,
and know that you
must tell the truth?
It is true that
I killed Knut.
Sadly, your brother.
But I killed him
when I found him
trying to rape my wife.
I ask all of
you free men,
what would have you done
if you were in my place?
Would have you
just stood back,
encouraged the culprit?
I don't think you would.
And even if
I had've known
at the time
he was your brother,
I would have carried out
the same sentence.
Do you seriously ask us
to believe your story?
I can confirm the story.
You are the wife
of Ragnar Lothbrok?
I am, Lord.
How extraordinary that
you happened to be there
at the same time.
Your husband is lying.
And you are so
under his thumb
that he has persuaded
you to lie for him.
May Thor strike
you dead!
What did you say?
My husband
did not kill
Knut Tjodolf.
Then who did?
I did!
I killed him.
I stabbed him in the
heart when he tried
his best to rape me.
A murder is committed
and the only witnesses
are a husband and his wife.
Unfortunately, we can't tell
who committed the crime,
because they both
claim credit for it.
You didn't kill
my brother.
Look at you,
how could you?
He killed my brother.
Ragnar Lothbrok
killed my brother.
We have proof.
We have a witness
to the killing.
You say you are
a witness to the death
of Knut Tjodolf?
Yes.
You'll swear this
upon your arm ring?
Yes, I was there.
I saw everything.
So, who killed
my brother?
Ragnar Lothbrok
killed him.
In cold blood?
No, Lord.
For a good reason.
What Ragnar Lothbrok
has sworn is true.
Your half-brother was caught
raping a Saxon woman.
Then he attempted to rape
Ragnar's lawful wife,
Lagertha, the shield-maiden.
So unfortunately,
you cannot punish him.
Now, who has the key?
Come, Bjorn.
Like father,
like son.
It seems I owe you
an eternal debt.
I know.
And I look forward
to collecting it.
Let's drink
a toast to Ragnar!
To his future
and his freedom!
No, no, no, no.
To friends
and freedom!
To friends and freedom!
To you, my friend!
You'll never
be free of us!
Will you drink
with me?
Of course.
Thank you
for taking care
of my children.
You're a good Christian.
I wanted to say
thank you.
You did a fine
good thing, Rollo.
I hope the gods
were watching.
I didn't do
it for him.
I did it for you,
shield-maiden.
I don't want
to believe that.
So, Ragnar!
Did you see Haraldson's face
when he had to acquit you
and then give you
half his hoard?
He looked like this!
Ragnar Lothbrok?
I am unarmed.
Get the children.
Hurry!
Father.
Stones and bones.
What do
you read?
Wait. Not so
impatient, Lord.
Tell me.
Ask me a question.
Are the
signs threatening?
Yes.
There is a quarrel.
There will be violence.
Bones and skulls broken.
I see that.
What is Ragnar doing
sitting on the hillside?
He searches
for your death.
Consults the gods
to whom he claims
kinship.
Who could believe
such a thing?
Does he desire
to be Earl?
If he kills you,
will it not be so?
Do the gods speak?
Do they ever stop?
Gods have always
been favorable to me.
They allowed
your sons to die.
Do the gods
really exist?
I know what he's doing.
He's preparing himself.