Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by Ahmed74
If I spoke about it...
If I did...
what would I tell you?
I wonder.
Would I tell you
about the time?
It happened a long time ago,
it seems...
in the last days
of a fair prince's reign.
Or would I tell you
about the place?
A small city near the coast...
but far from everything else.
Or, I don't know.
Would I tell you about her?
The princess without voice.
Or perhaps
I would just warn you
about the truth
of these facts...
and the tale
of love and loss...
and the monster who tried
to destroy it all.
My Lord Hedak.
So, you are troubled.
Tell me.
I've...
I have sinned.
I've offended the god.
I am deep in sin,
my Lord Hedak.
Let me judge of that.
I've doubted the ceremony
of the sacrifice.
I don't want to go up there.
Why, everybody's got
to go upstairs, Miss Lloyd,
if they wants to go to bed.
The sirens wake you up?
There was a fire.
The chocolate factory.
Do you smell that?
Oh, my!
Toasted cocoa.
Tragedy and delight,
hand in hand.
Oh, my dear child.
I would waste away if you
weren't here looking after me.
I am the proverbial
starving...
Watch this.
It's Bojangles,
the stair dance.
Oh, that's so hard.
Cagney did it.
Different, but beautiful.
- I wanna do that, too.
- All right!
- Are you ready?
- Yup.
Come on.
Ah!
Say, you catch on quick.
Look out now.
Here's your last one!
Elisa!
Next time you come
to bring the rent...
I want you to stay
and see the Bible movie, huh!
I have... I have two
free tickets here.
You bring your neighbor Giles.
He's a good boy.
Bible movie and comedy!
Nobody's coming
to the theater, huh?
I'll throw in a free
popcorn and soda!
Oh, no!
For God's sake,
there are two "S's" there!
Come on! Two "S."
"Mardi Grass!"Mardi Grass!"
Two "S."
All new personnel,
be advised that sector 12
has now been cleared
to level A safety.
Elisa! Come on.
I'm here already.
You gotta learn to be on time.
Hey! What are you doing?
Don't cut in, dummy!
Leave her alone, woman.
I was keeping her place.
I get reported, I come
after you and the mute.
You do that, Yolanda.
You do that.
My feet are already
killing me.
I made Brewster
pigs in a blanket
tonight before leaving...
and boy, he just ate 'em up.
No "thank-yous",
no "yum-yums".
Not a peep.
Man is as silent as a grave.
But if farts were flattery...
honey, he'd be Shakespeare.
Then I get home
and I make him breakfast.
Eggs, bacon,
and buttered toast.
I butter
the man's toast, Elisa.
Mmm-hmm, both sides...
as if he was a child.
And I don't even
get a thank-you.
You'd be grateful
because you're
an educated woman.
But my Brewster,
all he had going for him
was animal magnetism
back in the day.
Hasn't worked in a while.
What in the Sam Hill? No!
You boys mind putting
the trash in the can?
That's what it's there for.
Hard to believe, huh?
All right, all right.
Sorry, Zelda! Sorry!
I don't know
what they're doing.
Making a goddamn mess
is what I think.
Zelda!
Stop that chatter, please.
Yes, sir.
There's no call
for the blasphemy.
Sorry, Mr. Fleming, sir.
A moment of your time!
Today, we are receiving
a new team
and asset here in T-4.
This is Dr. Robert Hoffstetler
from our sister facility
in Galveston.
Now, I don't wanna bolster
or overstate the matter
but this may very well be
the most sensitive asset
ever to be housed
in this facility.
- How was your trip?
- Fine. Who's security here?
Just one moment, please.
Security! Who's security?
Welcome to T-4, sir.
Yes, sir, I am Fleming,
head of Security.
And if there are questions
you have or concerns...
you just come talk to me.
Do you understand?
I'll be in charge from now on.
Get them out.
Help me move this
cylinder into the compressor.
Bring it here.
Bring it over here.
There. Mount the cylinder.
We need to pressurize it
immediately.
- From there to there.
- Elisa! Elisa!
Come on!
Lord, what goes on
in this place?
Did you see that?
Yes, I'm wearing
the hairpiece.
How does it look?
Oh! Be careful of the car.
And it's not a hairpiece.
It's a toupee. It's French.
It's eternal, see?
Tantalus never achieved
the escape of death...
because the fruit
on the branches
was just always
out of his reach...
and the water
in the stream receded
every time he
stooped down to drink.
And so that's why
we say things today like...
"Look at those
tantalizing pies."
Thank you!
Y'all come back now, you hear?
Yes, pies for breakfast.
Just trust me on this.
Hey, folks!
Welcome to Dixie Doug's.
I've seen you
in here before, right?
Yes.
I've been here a couple
of times, as a matter of fact.
Partial to key lime pie?
I am, I am.
Two to go.
Just go with it,
please. Please.
Uh, I, uh, it's a craving
that I indulge in.
Can't possibly be good for me,
but nothing I like is.
No, no, it's a mighty
fine pie, key lime.
You wouldn't happen to be
the famous "Dixie Doug"
himself, would you?
Oh, heck no.
The pies are trucked
throughout the country.
- They call it "franchising," see?
- Oh.
They give us the spinners,
the signage.
That there's "Pie Boy,"
our mascot.
I don't talk like that.
I'm from Ottawa.
No.
I completely bought it.
"That's-a-great-a-pie."
The... The, uh...
The little... little guy,
is he supposed to be Italian?
I guess so.
Well, it's very clever.
Y'all come back now, you hear?
"Y'all come back now."
Do you think he meant it?
He had noticed me.
I mean, you... you heard that.
This pie is rather sordid.
But don't spit it out.
Next time we go,
we'll just try
a different flavor. Hmm?
Save it for later,
put it away.
6:00 AM eastern standard time.
The skies are beginning
to lighten...
as a cool North wind rustles across...
groups of
Negroes have been swarming
in front of and behind
the advancing police.
Oh, dear God!
Change that awfulness.
I do not wanna see that.
I do not wanna see it.
♪ Pretty baby ♪
Oh, that's better,
that's better.
Oh, look at Betty.
Oh, God, to be young
and beautiful.
If I could go back
to when I was 18...
I didn't know anything
about anything,
I'd give myself
a bit of advice.
I would say, "Take better
care of your teeth...
and fuck a lot more."
Oh no, no, that's very good advice.
♪ Pretty baby of mine ♪
Will you look at this?
Look.
Some of the best
minds in the country
peeing all over the floor
in this here facility.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
There's pee freckles
on the ceiling now.
How'd they get it up there?
Just how big a target
do they need, you figure?
They get enough practice,
that's for sure.
My Brewster...
no one's ever called him
a great mind,
but even he manages
to hit the can
70% of the time.
Excuse us, sir.
No, no, no,
that's all right.
Go ahead.
You ladies seem to be
chatting enjoyably.
Girl talk, no doubt.
Don't mind me.
Elisa.
Look, don't touch.
That lovely dingus
right there
is an Alabama Howdy-do.
Molded grip handle...
low current, high-voltage,
electric shock cattle prod.
Name's Strickland, Security.
Fleming's security.
Oh, no.
No, a man washes his hands
before or after
tending to his needs.
It tells you a lot
about a man.
He does it both times...
points to a weakness
in character.
Ladies.
It was very pleasant
chatting with you both.
Short people are mean.
I never met a short man
that stayed nice
all the way through.
No, sir.
Mean little backstabbers,
all of them.
Maybe it's the air down there,
not enough oxygen
or something.
Help! He's losing blood!
Help!
Come on, come on.
You think
the Russians broke in?
I don't think so.
And if they did...
Duane's meatloaf
will kill them all, honey.
It was two shots.
Did you hear them?
All right, three.
And that scream.
Lord, what ever happens
in this place?
You two, come with me.
Right now, Mr. Fleming, sir?
Any chance we get
to conclude our dinner?
Now!
Oh, heavens to Betsy.
We are in a pickle.
We are in such a pickle.
You will have
exactly 20 minutes
to render this... this lab
immaculate, and so on and so forth.
20 minutes.
It's a lot of blood.
What went on in here?
I can handle pee.
I can handle poo.
But blood... Ugh.
Blood just does
something to me.
Here, hon. Help me mop it up.
The sooner we get outta here
the better.
Is that a tater tot?
Oh!
It's a finger.
There's two fingers.
Okay, okay.
Put them away.
And just wait here.
I'm gonna go get Mr. Fleming.
Where are these body parts?
The body parts?
No, I believe you, honey.
But are you sure it was alive?
Because I saw a mermaid once
in a carnival tent...
and it was a monkey
sewn to the tail of a fish.
Looked real to me.
All right, I apologize.
Oh! I have a deadline.
Do you know,
corn flakes were invented
to prevent masturbation.
Didn't work.
Oh, Alice Faye just started.
She was a huge star, huge.
And one day, she couldn't
take the bullshit
and the backstabbing anymore.
She just walked away
from it all.
Ta-da!
That's not bad, is it?
For being shit.
Listen. You eat,
you go to bed, you rest.
And when I get paid...
♪ I'm so blue without you ♪
we get pie!
No, we don't get pie.
I get pie.
You get whatever you want.
Wish me luck.
♪ Then I have
only this to say ♪
♪ You'll never know
just how much ♪
♪ I miss you ♪
♪ You'll never know
just how much ♪
♪ I care ♪
Green. They want the gelatin
to be green now.
- I was told red.
- New concept.
That's the future now.
Green.
Oh, and they want them
happier, the family.
- Happier? Happier?
- Mmm.
The father looks like
he just discovered
the missionary position.
Giles.
Well, what are they supposed
to be happy about?
The client wanted photographs,
I sold them on this.
It's too bad.
This is nice work.
It is nice, isn't it?
I think it's one of my best.
How are you holding up?
You drinking?
No, not a drop. No.
Are you getting any work since
you left Klein and Saunders?
You mean since I was asked
to leave by you.
We are not
getting into this now.
I wanna come back, Bernie.
We'll see.
Now, do this.
I think we're making
great progress.
Good work.
Elisa.
What are you doing in there?
Cleaning, huh?
Listen, honey.
Mr. "I pee with my hands
on my hips"
wants to see us both.
"Zelda D. Fuller."
How long have you two
known each other, Zelda?
About 10 years, sir.
No siblings, Zelda?
No, sir.
That's not common, is it?
For your people?
My mama died after me.
After I was born.
What does that "D" stand for?
Delilah, sir.
On account of the Bible.
Delilah, she betrayed Samson.
Lulled him to sleep,
cut his hair.
Philistines tortured him,
humiliated him...
burned his eyes out.
Guess my mama didn't read
the good book close enough.
And you...
"Elisa Esposito."
Doesn't "Esposito"
mean orphan?
"Our Lady of Sorrows
Orphanage in Putnam."
They found her by the river
in the water.
It was you
that found my fingers.
Oh!
Thanks.
Three hours in surgery.
They rebuilt
the first phalanx here...
sutured the tendons.
Don't know if
it's gonna take or not.
There was mustard on them.
A paper bag?
It was all we had, sir.
I answer mostly on account
that she can't talk.
She can't? She deaf?
Mute, sir.
She said she can hear you.
All those scars on your neck.
That's what did it.
Cut your voice box, right?
She said since she was a baby.
Who would do that to a baby?
The world is sinful.
Wouldn't you say so, Delilah?
Well, let me say this upfront.
You clean that lab,
you get out.
The thing we keep in there
is an affront.
Do you know what
an affront is, Zelda?
Something offensive.
That's right,
and I should know.
I dragged that filthy thing...
out of the river muck
in South America
all the way here.
And along the way,
we didn't get
to like each other much.
Now...
you may think that thing
looks human.
Stands on two legs, right?
But we're created
in the Lord's image.
You don't think that's what
the Lord looks like, do you?
I wouldn't know, sir,
what the Lord looks like.
Well, it's human, Zelda.
He looks like a human, like me.
Or even you.
Maybe a little more like me,
I guess.
That's all.
General Hoyt, thank you
for calling me back, sir.
- Feeling better?
- Oh, yes, sir, much better.
Pain pills is all.
- Close the door.
- You lost two fingers, was it?
Two fingers, yeah.
He got two fingers.
But I still got my thumb,
my trigger,
and my pussy finger.
Sounds to me
like you'll do all right then.
Yes, sir, that's right.
Looking forward
to your visit, sir.
Decisions need to be made
about the asset.
Flavors
of fruity pies await you.
Three new locations
in downtown Baltimore.
The future is here.
Get some rest.
Pumpkin, banana...
Pick me up at 9:30.
2130 hours. Yes, sir.
That's-a-great-a-pie.
I'm home.
I made you an omelet.
- Hey, Dad. Guess what?
- No pancakes?
I've been through half the boxes
and I can't find the griddles.
- Guess what?
- I made you a cheese and broccoli omelet.
How are you feeling?
Does it hurt?
- A little bit. Pills help.
- Guess what?
What?
We're burying a time capsule
at the new school.
I wanted to ask you...
Do you think we'll all have
jetpacks in the future?
Believe it, son.
Oh! Bus is here.
This is America.
Bye, Dad!
Finish your omelet,
then wash your hands
real good...
and come upstairs, sweetie.
I kind of like it here.
The kids like the lawn.
Plus DC is just half
an hour away, isn't it?
It's still Baltimore, Elaine.
No one likes Baltimore.
You know what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking I need a new car.
You need a new car, do you?
How about a Cadillac, mister?
Richard.
Oh, Richard!
Sweetie, Sweetie?
Sweetie, your, um,
your hand is bleeding.
Silence. Don't talk.
Don't talk.
I want you in silence.
Silent, silent. Yes.
Silence.
Dr. Levensen to Aeronautics.
♪ Why do
robins sing in December? ♪
♪ Long before
the springtime is due ♪
♪ And even though it's snowing,
violets are growing ♪
♪ I know why, and so do you ♪
♪ When you smile at me ♪
♪ I hear gypsy violins ♪
♪ When you dance with me ♪
♪ I'm in heaven
when the music begins ♪
♪ I can see the sun
when it's raining ♪
♪ Hiding every cloud
from my view ♪
♪ And why do I see rainbows
when you're in my arms? ♪
♪ I know why
And so do you ♪
♪ I know why and so do you ♪
Hey!
- Gotcha.
- No, you didn't.
"The sparrow nests
on the window..."
What?
"The sparrow nests
on the window sill!"
"And the eagle
takes the prey."
What?
Elisa! Hurry, hurry, come on.
I swear to God, girl.
You're doing
it again, Zelda.
Oh, give it a rest, Yolanda.
Whoo!
Hey, Zelda, want a smoke?
That shit ain't good
for you, Duane.
Yeah, but it feel good.
It does, doesn't it?
Come on, Elisa. Just one.
Come on, come on, come on.
Don't worry about that camera.
We push 'em up at break time.
Mmm-hmm.
- This here is a blind spot.
Man can't make meatloaf...
It adds a little spice.
Sector Five,
must ready energy test
starting in two hours.
Fleming, I have to
finish some things in here.
Fetch the general, will you?
Aww, you missed me, huh?
I took a candy break.
This is what scares you, huh?
Well, gee, you should
be used to it by now.
There you go again,
making that god-awful sound.
Is that you crying, huh?
Is that what it is?
Are you hurting?
Or maybe you're angry!
Maybe you'd like to get
another bite of me.
Go ahead.
I can't tell.
I mean, are you begging?
Because to me,
it's just the worst fucking
noise I ever heard.
Paging Captain Walters.
Captain Walters, please
pick up the courtesy call.
Elisa.
Elisa!
General Hoyt!
Welcome, sir!
Everything's ready.
Glad to have you, sir.
- Good to see you, son.
- Thank you.
Good God Almighty!
Is that it?
Hell of a lot bigger
than I thought.
Ugly as sin.
You know, the natives in the
Amazon worshiped it like a god.
Doesn't look like
much of a god now, does it?
Well, they're primitive, sir.
You know, they would toss
offerings into the water.
Flowers, fruits,
crap like that.
Then they tried
to stop the oil drill
with bows and arrows.
That didn't turn out too well.
He's bleeding.
What happened?
It's an animal, Hoffstetler.
Just keeping it tame.
"Oxygen osmosis
and dioxide exchange."
What the hell
have we got here, son?
This creature, sir...
it can alternate between two
entirely separate
breathing mechanisms.
- A mudskipper can do that.
- No.
Look.
You want to put
a man in space.
He's gonna have
to endure conditions
the human body
just wasn't made for.
This gives us an edge
against the Soviets.
How long can it breathe
outside the water?
The reality is, sir,
we don't know jack shit
about this thing.
Well, the Soviets want it.
We know that much.
Those cockeyed bastards.
You know, we let 'em send
a dog up into space,
and we get a good laugh.
Then the next thing you know,
they send a human up,
a Russki,
orbiting the planet,
doing God knows what.
Who's laughing then?
Khrushchev, that's who.
Let him send a dog up into space, and he laughs.
Then he puts a commie
up in space, and he laughs.
And then he puts
missiles into Cuba.
Have we learned nothing?
Sir, we need to
get him back in the water.
See, these scientists,
they're like artists, sir.
They fall in love
with their plaything.
Now, right here, see?
Along the middle.
This creature has
a thick-jointed cartilage
that separates the primary
and secondary lungs.
Am I explaining
this correctly, Bob?
Yes, but we have...
It makes the X-rays
inconclusive.
In principle, sir, yes. But...
Now, I believe if we want to
get an edge on the Soviets
we need to vivisect
this thing.
- No, no.
- Take it apart,
- learn how it works.
- No.
No! That would
defeat the purpose.
Sir, he's passed out.
Please.
Put him in the tank.
Let him pressurize.
General Hoyt, sir?
You cannot,
under any circumstance,
kill this creature.
Count these stars
with me, son.
There are five of them.
Means I can do
whatever the hell I want.
Now, you want
to plead your case,
I'll listen to it.
But at the end of the day,
it is my damn decision.
So crack the damn thing open,
learn what you can,
and close up shop here.
Give yourself a good
pat on the back, Strickland.
You've done it.
Thank you, sir.
Now, hurry up
and finish the job, son.
Absolutely, sir.
Get him out?
What are you talking about?
No. Absolutely not.
Because it's breaking the law,
that's why.
We're probably breaking
the law just talking about it.
Oh, he's alone? Oh.
Does this mean that whenever
we go to
a Chinese restaurant
you wanna save
every fish in the tank?
So what if he's alone?
We're all alone.
The loneliest thing
you've ever seen?
Well, you just said it right there.
You just said it!
You called it a thing.
It's a thing. It's a freak.
I can understand you.
Calm down. God, calm down.
All right,
I will repeat it to you.
"What am I?
"I move my mouth, like him.
"I make no sound, like him.
"What does that make me?
"All that I am...
"all that I've ever been...
"brought me here, to him."
See, you're saying "him."
It's a "him" now.
You just hit me!
Elisa, let go of me.
I'm looking. I'm looking!
You've never hit me.
"When he looks at me,
the way he looks at me...
"He does not know
what I lack...
"or how...
"I am incomplete.
"He sees me...
"for what I am...
"as I am.
"He's happy...
"to see me, every time...
"every day.
"And now I can either...
"save him...
or let him die."
Oh, God. I'm leaving.
Elisa, no. I have to leave.
Just... Elisa, please stop.
Listen to me.
Just listen to me.
I have to go.
I'm leaving now
because, Elisa,
this is very important to me.
This is a second
chance for me.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Oh, God.
When I come back,
we just will not talk
about this ever again.
Elisa, there's...
All right!
What are we?
What are you and I?
Do you know what we are?
We're nothing!
Nothing! We can do nothing!
I'm sorry, but this...
this is just...
Oh, God, it's not
even human. God!
What?
Giles.
- I've been waiting.
- I know. Sorry.
It's okay.
We going in?
You should have
just mailed the art.
No.
I want to show it to you
and the team in person.
I think it's some
of my best work.
And it's green as can be.
It's, uh, it's not a good time.
Maybe later.
Oh. Well, sure.
No problem.
What would be a good time
for you, Bernie?
You painted that?
Yeah.
Wowee!
You're good.
Apparently, not as good
as a photograph.
But it is good, isn't it?
I couldn't paint
anything like that.
Here. On me.
For me?
Well, we don't get
many like you in here.
You seem very educated,
and I like talking to you.
The thing is that's...
the only reason
that I come in here is...
- The conversation.
- And?
The pie is mighty fine,
too, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's no key lime,
but it's good.
You know, I work alone...
and my best friend's not much
of a conversationalist.
You see, that's part
of doing the job here.
It's like being a bartender.
You serve people pie.
You listen to their problems.
You get to know them.
I'd like to get
to know you better.
What the hell
are you doing, old man?
- Let's sit down.
- Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Hey, no, no, no.
Not the counter.
Takeout only.
You can't sit there.
If you want something,
you order, you take it out.
But it's empty.
The... the counter's empty.
All reserved, all day.
You don't sit down.
Y'all come back now, you hear?
You don't need
to talk to them like that.
You should go, too.
And don't come back.
This is a family restaurant.
♪ So come back to my arms ♪
♪ And show me
how wrong I can be ♪
I have no one.
And you are the only person
that I can talk to.
Now, whatever this thing is...
you need it.
So...
you just tell me
what to do.
♪ So come back to my arms ♪
♪ And show me ♪
♪ How wrong I can be ♪
- "All hope fades."
- "As the spring recedes."
Let's go.
♪ There's a summer place ♪
♪ Where it may rain or storm ♪
♪ Yet I'm safe and warm ♪
Cadillac DeVille.
Best car ever made.
V8, 390 CID, clean and crisp
like a fresh dollar bill.
I'm just idling around.
And I'm just talking.
AM radio, air conditioner,
power windows, power brakes,
power steering, power seats.
All deluxe interior
appointment choices,
143 options.
Now, this...
- is the Taj Mahal on wheels.
- Hmm.
I'm not sure about the green.
It's not green,
my friend. Teal.
- Well, teal looks green to me.
- But it isn't, see?
It's a limited edition,
12 coats of paint...
polished by hand,
all authentic
chrome detailing.
Four out of five
successful men in America
drive a Cadillac.
That a fact?
This here is the future.
And you strike me as a man
who is headed there.
- Where?
- Why, the future.
You're the man of the future.
You belong in this car.
Wow!
Sir, that is a...
that is a beautiful car!
What can I say?
You gotta feel good
driving that, huh?
And what a wonderful
shade of green, huh?
Teal.
Tomorrow, I'll make
a mean meatloaf.
Mmm-hmm.
Just for you, extra raisins.
So, at 5:00 AM,
I drive my car
down the loading ramp.
And the shifts are changing,
and I have...
How much time do I have?
Five minutes? I'll remember.
5:00 AM, five minutes.
Five-five, five-five.
So, you're going
to move the cameras, right?
And I'm gonna be
synchronizing our watches
just like they do
in the movies.
Oh, God! I'm so proud of you.
God! You're not afraid!
You are? Very?
Don't tell me that.
I'm terrified.
I think this is some
of my best work.
"Michael Parker." I think
it's a good, trustworthy name.
It's a little butch.
Yes, age 51.
54?
You don't have to be rude.
57.
If I put the hair on,
I can pull it off.
I can wear this...
or I have...
Thor, go. Off, off, off! Go!
Or I have this.
Now this, I think it says
"working man."
But this, now this says...
this says with
the butterscotch tie...
This says "casual,
but still stylish."
So, you like this?
I agree, I agree.
I think we're ready.
Mr. Strickland!
Sally, could you call
Miss Esposito
to clean up a spill?
You know,
I can't figure it out myself.
You're not much to look at...
but go figure.
I keep thinking about you.
When you say you're mute,
are you entirely silent...
or do you squawk a little?
Some mutes squawk.
Not pretty, but...
Hmm?
I just want you to know...
I don't mind those scars.
I don't mind that
you can't speak, either.
When you come
right down to it...
I like it.
A lot.
It kind of gets me going.
I bet I can make you
squawk a little.
Hey, honey. You okay?
Hurry up.
I wanna be home early.
My feet are killing me.
We need to delay
the procedure.
Knock before
you enter my office.
This is urgent!
Go back out, knock,
then I'll let you in
and we'll talk.
That's the protocol.
Follow the protocol.
Come in.
Would you get the door
for me, please?
See? That's the way.
Now, we talk.
I need more time.
Don't let the fact
that you feel like a loser
now that you've let your
competitive tendencies...
I'm not competitive!
I don't want an intricate,
beautiful thing destroyed!
This thing dies...
you learn, I leave,
out of here.
I settle down.
My family settles down
somewhere nice.
A real city.
This creature
is intelligent...
capable of language...
of understanding emotions.
So are the Soviets, the Gooks.
And we still kill them,
don't we?
The bottom line is,
this isn't a petting zoo
and I don't wanna be
in this shit hole
any longer than need be.
Do you?
Bob. Do you?
No, I don't.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Have you seen Elisa?
Come on, Zelda!
Did you move
the camera on the loading dock?
Is that where
you're taking him?
Through the service tunnels?
That's very smart.
Who do you work for?
His water must be kept
at 5 to 8% salinity.
Table salt will do.
Mix one of these in his water
every three days.
Raw protein diet is a must.
In five minutes...
I'll meet you
at the loading dock.
The lights will go out...
so be prepared.
Mr. Strickland, sir?
Twelve hours to
the vivisection of the asset.
And I need your signature
here, please.
this
sudden, clandestine decision
to station strategic weapons
for the first time
outside of Soviet soil...
Hold it right there.
an unjustified change
in the status quo...
"Michael Parker." Is that you?
My whole life.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't do this, Elisa.
Don't do this!
What's that?
What's that vehicle?
Gosh, sir, I'm not sure.
It's a laundry van?
But it's not scheduled.
And finally,
I call upon
Chairman Khrushchev
to halt and eliminate...
this clandestine, reckless,
and provocative threat
to world peace
and to stable relations
between our two nations.
Sir?
- Meet me at the loading dock.
- Sir!
- Sir, what do you need me to do?
- Get backup.
Step out of the vehicle, sir.
Oh, God. I'm not good at this.
Out of the vehicle now.
I will not say it again.
- Oh, God. Please don't shoot me!
- Get out!
Oh, God.
Don't shoot me. Please.
What are you waiting for?
We're out of time!
Get out now!
You have to go. Hurry!
Oh, woman,
we're gonna burn in hell.
Come on, push.
Push!
I swear, I'm not
doing this on purpose!
Mechanical objects and I
just don't get along!
What the...
She's waiting for you
at the dock. Go! Now!
Who's that man? I think
he just killed someone.
Oh, my God!
Are we ready,
are we ready?
He's so beautiful.
Did I do that?
I'm just not good at this.
Move! Move!
Come on. No.
No!
Salt? What are you
talking about, salt?
Elisa!
There.
Israeli Popper.
You can smell the magnesium.
Russians hate the Jews,
but they can't get enough
of their gadgets.
How'd they get in here?
Forged ID, painted plates,
and so on and so forth.
And they moved the main
video camera on the dock, sir.
Well, no one has to know.
We got 24 hours
before I bounce it up.
No, I called it in.
You called it in?
The moment it happened, I...
Mr. Strickland, sir.
What is it, Sally?
Sir, General Hoyt
is on the phone.
That thing was
our space dog, Strickland.
You know that.
Sir, I'm getting it back.
I can't be in a negative
frame of mind, sir.
So, you're feeling good?
Feeling strong.
Getting it back.
You can get it done.
You're gonna get it done.
For me, son. For me.
That's when you're
planning on releasing him?
On the 10th?
So, what if the rains
are late?
What happens with the canal?
All right.
What's that?
Let me see it.
Is that for me?
Yeah, that's good.
Keep that up.
Looking like
you don't know anything.
Lord help me,
if they ask me if I do.
I'm not a good liar.
Except to Brewster.
It takes a lot of lies
to keep a marriage going.
All personnel,
prepare to present your
identity and clearance cards.
Lord! What in the...
Attention. All personnel,
prepare to present your
identity and clearance cards.
You done got us
in a world of trouble.
My opinion,
we're looking
at a highly-trained
group, sir.
I'm thinking,
conceivably, sir,
like special forces
or so on and so forth.
Red Army Special Forces?
Conceivably.
And they're highly trained.
They were well-financed,
an elite group.
Highly efficient, ruthless,
clockwork precision.
Infiltration took less
than five minutes, sir.
My conservative estimate
is that this was
a strike force
of at least 10 men.
My master sends this dress.
Have you always been alone?
Did you ever have someone?
Do you know what
happened to you? Do you?
Because I don't. I don't know
what happened to me.
I don't know.
I look in the mirror and the
only thing that I recognize
are these eyes...
in this old man's face.
You know, sometimes I think
I was either born too early
or too late for my life.
Maybe we're both just relics.
Security
measures have been increased
to maximum levels.
Prepare to present your
identity and clearance cards.
Attention.
Security measures have been
increased to maximum levels.
Sir, I've got them.
Zelda, Elisa. All right.
Here we go.
Mmm-hmm.
Looks like you two punched out
before the incident.
Still.
If you know something
about what transpired here
it's your obligation...
to report any detail,
no matter how small
or trivial it may seem.
"Trivial" means unimportant.
I didn't see nothing
out of the ordinary, no.
Or trivial.
See, my feet were hurting.
What about you?
She didn't see anything.
Mmm.
Hoffstetler, Dr. Hoffstetler.
Did either of you see him
coming in or out of the lab?
He works there, doesn't he?
I mean in a different way,
doing something different.
Something trivial?
No, sir.
What am I doing,
interviewing the fucking help?
The shit cleaners.
The piss wipers.
You two, go ahead. Leave.
All right, you're clear.
So, back to work. Go on.
What'd you say to me?
What is she saying?
I didn't catch it.
She... she is saying thank you.
Next!
I didn't see you
last night or the night before.
I'm sorry, Ed,
but now that I'm spending
all day long in the office,
Carol feels that I... I should
spend my evenings with her.
Well, if you
spend the evenings with her,
when will I?
There's only
one thing left to do.
Volunteer.
No! No, no, no, no, no!
I wanna get home early.
Brewster's been in
a bad mood lately.
Holy Jesus!
What are you doin'
standing in the shadows
of the women's locker room?
They may be watching me,
and there are no cameras here.
For good reason.
But have you caught us
at an inconvenient moment!
I need to know
that he's alright.
- He is.
- When will you release him?
Soon.
When the rain fills the canal
that flows to the sea.
If you need anything...
Release him. Soon.
What did she say?
She said you're a good man,
Dr. Hoffstetler.
My name is Dimitri.
Honored to meet you.
Hey, dummy!
Phone call for you.
It's urgent.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Believe me. I'm fine.
He ate Pandora.
Wasn't his fault.
He's a wild creature.
We can't ask him
to be anything else.
Elisa, go find him.
Go. Go.
Go!
You're lucky.
Ow.
I stayed awake
as long as I could.
You know,
I'm not even mad anymore.
Is he all right?
You sure?
Where you going?
No, no.
Okay, don't... no, no.
Don't... don't play
with the kitties.
No, no.
Don't play with the kitties.
I'm not... I'm not angry.
Oh, my!
You did that. It's okay.
It's... ooh. I don't
think that's sanitary.
Enough.
Oh, God.
Interesting guy.
All personnel
prepare to present
your identity
and clearance cards.
You wanted to see me?
How's it going?
The investigation?
Well, we have
a promising lead.
Really?
That's good to hear.
You joined us in Galveston,
but where were
you before, Hoffstetler?
- Doctor.
- Excuse me?
Doctor Hoffstetler.
Protocol.
Wisconsin. Madison.
Oh that's right.
You gave up a tenure
track position, didn't you?
Gave it all up for us.
I suppose...
you'll be getting ready
to leave us now then, huh?
Only if the creature
isn't found.
Well, what do you think?
You think we will find it?
Well, you said
you had a lead.
I do.
Why you smiling, hon?
Stop looking like that.
What happened?
Why?
How?
Does he have a...?
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Never trust a man.
Even when he looks
flat down there.
Hmm.
You rang?
Oh, hi, Maynard. I
just signed up for anthropology.
We're gonna hold class in the
Amazon jungle in South America.
South America?
Ooh, man, Dob.
You're gonna have to get up awful early
in the morning. That's a long hike.
No, Maynard, we're gonna stay down there.
- We are?
- Oh, no, you're not coming along, too.
This is a gelatin parfait.
You're gonna love it.
Dad, can we watch Bonanza?
Bonanza is much too violent.
You know what
I was thinking today?
We get the kids
a P-U-P-P-Y.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's get out of here.
What is going on?
I've got water
pouring into my theater!
I have four paying customers!
I've got to offer refunds.
It's probably a pipe.
I'll take care of it.
- You don't fix it, no more rent!
- I will fix it.
Elisa?
Dear God. Elisa!
I'm toweling my hair!
It's my hair.
Ah, just...
Oh! Look at my arm.
The wound. It's like
it was never there.
Look at that.
Now you said that...
you know, he was worshiped
like a god.
Now, is he a god?
I don't know if he's a god.
I mean, he ate a cat,
so I don't... I don't know.
I don't know, but, I mean,
we have to keep him
around awhile.
Little while.
Hello?
Your water, sir.
- And sir, General Hoyt...
- Mm-mm, mm-mm.
Tell him I'm not here.
Tell him I'll call him back.
Don't put him through.
No, sir...
He... he's in your office.
At this point,
our only concern is the asset.
- Do you have it?
- Still in the winds, sir.
Well, that won't do.
Yes, sir, I know.
You've known me
how long, sir?
Thirteen years.
Battle of Pusan.
Yes, sir.
A man is faithful,
loyal, efficient all his life.
All of it. And he is...
useful.
And he expects...
He has certain
expectations in return.
And then, he fails once.
Only once.
What does that make him?
That make him a failure?
When is a man done, sir?
Proving himself?
A good man?
A decent man?
"Decent?"
A man has the decency
not to fuck up.
Now that's one thing.
That's real decent of him.
But the other kind of decency?
It doesn't really matter.
Well sell it,
but it's an export.
We sell it,
because we don't use it.
36 hours from now...
this entire episode
will be over.
And so will you.
Our universe
will have a hole in it
with your outline.
And you will have moved on
to an alternate universe.
A universe of shit.
You'll be lost
to civilization.
And you will be unborn.
Unmade.
And undone.
So go get some
real decency, son.
And unfuck this mess.
36 hours.
36 hours. Well, shit.
You deliver. You deliver,
that's what you do.
You deliver! Right? Right?
know...
♪ You ask me if I'm lonely ♪
♪ Then I have only this ♪
♪ To say ♪
You'll...
never know...
just how much...
I...
love you.
You'll...
never know...
just how much...
♪ I care ♪
♪ And if I try ♪
♪ I still couldn't hide ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ You ought to know ♪
♪ For Heaven told me so ♪
♪ You went away ♪
♪ And my heart went with you ♪
♪ I speak your name ♪
♪ In my every prayer ♪
♪ If there is some other way ♪
♪ To prove that I love you ♪
♪ I swear I don't know how ♪
You'll never know...
if you don't know now.
Elisa...
What is it, honey?
This isn't good.
I'm gonna call Dr. Hoffstetler.
We gotta release him
tonight, honey.
I'll come back and help you.
He's coming out.
Ah, fuck.
Sir, if you don't
mind me saying, you...
you don't look so well.
Shut up.
Can you smell that?
I mean...
I think it's your fingers.
They're... they're...
- Mmm.
- black.
There he is.
Doctor-fucking-shirtbird.
Oh, there's no cause
for cursing, sir.
Get out of the car.
I'm taking it.
This is my car.
Get the fuck out.
Out of my car?
Did I stutter?
Strickland! Thank God!
You were speaking Russian...
Bob.
What's your name?
- Hoffstetler.
- No, no. Don't lie.
You don't need to.
You took a bullet to the gut.
You're dead.
I need the names, ranks
and location
of the entire strike team.
"Strike team?"
The ones who took the asset!
This candy.
It's cheap candy, but I love it.
Ever since I was a kid.
Now some folks favor
more sophisticated snacks,
nougat center
and all that foo-foo shit.
But not me, Bob!
This is it for me.
Now sometimes
if I'm feeling anxious,
I just bite right into it.
But mostly,
I take my time.
I make it last.
Names, ranks,
and location
of the strike team.
Names! Ranks! Now!
No names.
No ranks.
They...
They just clean.
Alright, Brewster, I'm gonna fix your dinner,
and then I'm gonna run out for a
little while and help a friend.
Help with what?
Help a friend.
Zelda...
the door.
Well, you could help me
and answer the door, Brewster.
You're sitting right here
just ten feet away from it!
My back's aching me, woman.
Now, move!
Your back, your back?
Always your back!
Mr. Strickland.
What are you doing here?
Who's that man, Zelda?
Where is it?
- What are you talking about?
- Where did you take it?
- What are you talking about? I... I don't...
- Zelda!
The thing in the lab.
Where is it?
- Listen, fella...
- Sit down!
I'm sorry, sir.
If I knew anything,
I would surely tell you.
That story about Samson.
I never told you how it ends.
After the Philistines
torture him and blind him...
Samson asks God
for the strength he needs.
And at the last minute,
he is spared.
And the Lord gives him
his strength back...
one last time.
And he holds...
the columns of the temple...
with his powerful arms.
And he crushes them.
And he brings
the whole building
down on the Philistines.
He dies...
but he gets every single
one of those motherfuckers.
That is his will!
Now, do you know what that
particular story means...
for us, Delilah?
It means if you know something
you're not telling me
you're gonna tell me
either before or after
I bring
this particular temple...
down upon our heads.
Gal stole that
thing right out the lab,
whatever it is.
Mute girl took it.
I heard my wife talking
on the phone about it.
Thank you very much,
Mr. Fuller,
for your assistance.
What have you done?
Zelda.
I gotta warn her.
He's going after her.
You will do
no such thing, woman.
Why are you worrying about her?
She broke the law.
Shut up, Brewster!
You shut up!
Years, you don't talk...
and now you can't
shut your mouth!
Damn you, Brewster.
You wouldn't understand.
Couldn't understand, not if
you tried your whole life.
- Hello?
- Giles, is that you?
- Yes.
- Okay. Put Elisa on the phone.
It's Zelda.
Elisa, honey, make a sound
on the phone if you can hear.
Okay, good.
He's coming for you.
You gotta go now, and you gotta
take that thing with you.
What? Elisa?
Hey! Watch out!
Learn how to drive!
Damn it.
We have to go.
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you?
I do not fail.
I deliver.
Elisa!
Elisa.
No.
Fuck.
You are a god.
Look, man on the ground.
Watch him.
You there! Call an ambulance!
If I told you about her,
what would I say?
That they lived
happily ever after?
I believe they did.
That they were in love,
that they remained in love?
I'm sure that's true.
But when I think of her...
of Elisa...
the only thing that comes
to mind is a poem
whispered by someone in love,
hundreds of years ago.
"Unable to perceive
the shape of You
"I find You all around me
"Your presence fills my eyes
with Your love
"It humbles my heart
For You are everywhere"
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by Ahmed74