♪ Our glorious city ♪
♪ Was built by the divinities ♪
♪ By gods who saw fit ♪
♪ To bestow ♪
♪ The gift of a paradise ♪
♪ Peaceful and harmonious upon ♪
♪ Us mere mortals below ♪
♪ And made El Dorado ♪
♪ The magnificent and golden ♪
♪ One thousand years ago ♪
♪ El Dorado, El Dorado ♪
♪ El Dora-a-a-a-do ♪
Today, we sail
to conquer the New World.
For Spain, for glory, for gold!
Viva Cortés!
Altivo, eyes forward.
- Seven!
- All right!
- Yes!
- Partner! Hee-hee!
- ♪ Tons of gold for you! ♪
- ♪ Tons of gold for me! Hey! ♪
♪ Tons of gold for we! Hey! ♪
One more roll!
Uh, guys, you're broke!
- You got nothin' to bet with!
- Oh, yeah? I got this!
A map?
- A map?
- A map!
A map of the wonders
of the New World.
Wow! Let's have a look.
Uh, Tulio!
- Excuse us, for one moment, please.
- Tulio, look!
El Dorado, the city of gold.
This could be our destiny, our fate.
Miguel, if I believed in fate,
I wouldn't be playing with loaded dice.
Not with the face.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
I said one more roll!
My map against your cash.
Hmm?
- All right, peewee. You're on!
- Not with those!
This time we use my dice.
Got a problem with that?
No.
I'm going to kill you.
Come on, baby.
Papa needs that crappy map.
Stop that!
Show me seven!
- Seven!
- All right!
Yes!
There it is!
Well, nice doing business with you!
I knew it!
Your dice are loaded!
What? You gave me loaded dice?
He gave me loaded dice!
- Guard, arrest him!
- You dare to impugn my honour?
He was the one who was cheating! Arrest him!
He tricked these sailors and took their money!
- Now I'm the thief?
- Yes.
Take a look in the mirror, pal!
You better get that money back or I'll...
- En garde!
- En garde, yourself.
I will give you the honour of
a quick and painless death.
But not with that.
I fight fairly. A-ha!
- Well, any last words?
- I will cut you to ribbons, fool!
Such mediocrity.
Let your sword do the talking.
I will. It will be loquacious
to a fault!
- Ha! Take that!
- Ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
- You mincing, fencing, twit.
- You fight like my sister!
I fought your sister, that's a compliment.
- Blackguard!
- Heathen!
Not the face! Not the face!
- Ladies and gentlemen, we decided it's a draw.
- Thank you all for coming.
- You've been great. See you soon.
- Adiós!
- Congratulations. Very good!
- No, you...
- We should've kept our swords I think.
- Yeah.
I've got a plan.
- What is it?
- Er, well... you... pet him...
- Yeah?
- And I'll...
run!
Well, thanks a lot!
There they are!
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
Bye! Thank you!
♪ Olé! ♪
Whoa!
Oh!
- I bet we can make that.
- There they are!
- Two pesetas says we can't.
- You're oooon!
You lose!
Whoa! What's happening here?
We're both in barrels.
That's the extent of my knowledge.
Okay, Miguel, we gotta move fast. On three,
we jump out and we head for the dock.
- Good, good. Okay. Excellent.
- One, two, three...
Th-three!
Three! Ohh!
Three!
You ready?
Okay. One more. Let's go.
One... two... three!
- Excuse us.
- Okay, we're outta here.
- Who ordered the, uh... pickles?
- Yeah.
Cortés!
My crew was as carefully chosen
as the disciples of Christ.
And I will not tolerate stowaways.
You will be flogged.
And when we put into Cuba to resupply,
God willing, you will be flogged more,
and then enslaved on the sugar plantations
for the rest of your miserable lives.
- To the brig.
- All right! Cuba!
- Hah!
- Ugh!
Hey, Altivo. Ah-ta-ta, not for you!
You're on half rations, orders from Cortés.
So, um, how's the escape plan coming?
All right. All right, wait!
- I'm getting something.
- Yeah
Okay.
Here's the plan: In dead of night,
you and I grab some provisions,
hijack one of those longboats,
and then we row back to Spain
like there's no mañana!
- Back to Spain, yeah?
- Yeah.
- In a rowboat.
- You got it!
Great. Sensational. And
that-that's your plan, is it?
- That's pretty much it.
- Well I like it.
- So, how do we get on deck?
- Hmm.
In dead of night, you and I grab some
provisions, hijack one of those longboats...
- Great.
- Okay what's your idea, smart guy?
What do you mean? Don't ask me that!
You're the one with the plans!
Wait, actually I have an idea.
Uh, c'mon, give me a boost.
Hey, Altivo. Altivo!
You want a nice apple?
Come and get it.
But you have to do a trick first.
Huh?
All you do is find a pry bar.
A long piece of iron
with a hooky thing at the end, yeah?
- Miguel, you're talking to a horse!
- Shh!
That's it, Altivo, find the pry bar.
Yes, find the pry bar.
He can't understand "pry bar"!
He's a dumb horse, there's no way...
Well, it's not a pry bar.
Oh, Altivo.
Oh, thank you, old boy.
Listen, if we can
ever return the favour...
For Pete's sake, he's a roofless
warhorse, not a poodle.
- C'mon before he licks you to death.
- Adiós.
- Shh, quiet please.
- What's the matter with him?
He wants his apple.
Give it to him
before he wakes the ship!
- Fetch!
- Huh?
Hmm?
Huh?
- Altivo!
- Huh? Miguel!
- Altivo, I'm coming!
- Miguel!
Hang on! I'm here, old boy!
- Have you lost your mind?
- I'm coming!
Oh!
Ho-o-ly ship!
Whoa!
- Loop the rope under the horse!
- Yes!
On the count of three,
pull back on the rope!
- What?
- Three!
Pull!
Tulio! Hey, it worked!
Did any of the supplies make it?
Well... yes and no.
Ohhh, great!
Tulio, look on the positive side.
At least things can't get...
Excuse me.
Were you going to say "worse"?
- No.
- No? You sure?
Absolutely,
I've revised that whole thing.
- We're at least in a rowboat.
- We're in a rowboat. Exactly. You miss nothing.
Whoaaaa!
Tulio, did you ever imagine
it would end like this?
The horse is a surprise.
Any... regrets?
Besides dying? Yeah.
I never... had enough...
gold.
My regret, besides dying, is...
our greatest adventure
is over before it began
and no one will even remember us.
Well, if it's
any consolation, Miguel,
you... made my life...
an adventure.
And if it's any consolation, Tulio...
you made my life... rich.
- Hmm.
- Is it?
- It is! It's...
- It's...
It's land!
All in favour of getting
back in the boat say "aye".
- Aye!
- Aye! Go!
Hey, Miguel!
I could use a little help!
Miguel! Hello!
Tulio! We've done it!
- What's that? The map?
- It's all right here!
You still have the map?
Whistling rock! The stream!
- You kept the map but you couldn't grab a little more food?
- Even those mountains.
You said so yourself,
it could be possible. And it is!
It really is the map to El Dorado!
- You drank the seawater, didn't you?
- Oh, come on!
I'm not coming on! I wouldn't set foot in
that jungle for a million pesetas!
- How about a hundred million?
- What?
- I just thought that after all since El Dorado is the city of gold.
- What's your point?
You know, dust, nuggets, bricks, a temple of gold
where you can pluck gold from the very walls.
But you won't go,
so let's get back into tha boat
and row back to Spain.
After all it worked so well last time.
Wait! Mmm. Wait a minute. New plan.
We find the city of gold,
we take the gold...
- Then we go back to Spain.
- And buy Spain! Yeah!
That's the spirit!
- Come on, Tulio! We'll follow that trail!
- What trail?
The trail that we blaze!
That trail that we blaze!
Phewee.
Oh, no, you don't.
Yeow! Your horse
bit me in the butt!
♪ Look out New World here we come ♪
- ♪ Brave, intrepid ♪
- Charge!
♪ And then some ♪
♪ Pioneers of maximum audacity ♪
♪ Whose résumés
Show that we are just the team ♪
♪ To live where others merely dream ♪
- What are you looking at?
- ♪ Building up our head of steam ♪
♪ On the trail we blaze ♪
♪ Changing legend into fact ♪
♪ We shall ride into history ♪
♪ Turning myth into truth ♪
♪ We shall surely gaze
On the sweet unfolding ♪
♪ Of an antique mystery ♪
♪ All will be revealed ♪
♪ On the trail we blaze ♪
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
♪ On the trail
On the trail we blaze ♪
- Dinner is served.
- Hello.
♪ Paradise is close at hand ♪
♪ Shangri-La ♪
♪ The promised land ♪
♪ Seventh heaven on demand ♪
♪ Quite unusual nowadays ♪
♪ Virgin vistas undefiled ♪
♪ Minds and bodies running wild ♪
♪ In the man behold a child ♪
♪ On the trail we blaze ♪
♪ The trail we blaze ♪
♪ Is road uncharted ♪
♪ Through Terra incognita
To a golden shrine ♪
♪ No place for the traveller ♪
♪ To be faint-hearted ♪
♪ We are part of a sumptuous
Grand design ♪
♪ Changing legend into fact ♪
♪ We shall ride into history ♪
♪ Turning myth into truth ♪
♪ We shall surely gaze ♪
♪ On the sweet unfolding ♪
♪ Of an antique mystery ♪
♪ All will be revealed... ♪
♪ On the trail we blaze ♪
Hmm.
Miguel. Miguel, wake up. We're there.
- We found it?
- Oh yeah, we found it.
- Fantastic! Where is it? How far?
- Right here.
- Where?
- Here.
- Behind the rock?
- No, no. This is it.
Give me that! This ca... What?
Apparently, "El Dorado"
is native for...
"great, big rock"!
rock... rock... rock... rock...
Hey but I tell you what, I'm feeling
generous, so you can have my share.
You don't think Cortés could've
gotten here before us and...
And what? Taken all
the really big rocks? The scoundrel!
Tulio, we have to think about this.
- I mean, we've come all this way, and we should really...
- Get on the horse!
No, no, not with the face. Stop.
Looks like
a pass right over there.
Oh!
Hyah!
Heh. I've...
Uh, hello. This your rock?
Sorry, we were just looking.
We're, um... We're tourists! Tourists.
We lost our group. May we go now?
- Ah!
- Heh-heh. Spears.
Hey! Hey!
Oh, my...
It's... It's...
El Dorado!
Well, it was nice
working with you, partner.
Tulio... I just want you to know. I'm
sorry about that girl in Barcelona.
- So, you... You...
- Behold!
As the prophecies foretold,
the time of judgement is now!
Citizens! Did I not predict
that the gods would come to us?
Hmm.
My lords, I am Tzekel-Kan,
your devoted high priest,
and speaker for the gods.
Hey.
I am Chief Tannabok.
What names may we call you?
Hm? I am Miguel.
And I am Tulio.
And they call us Miguel and Tulio!
Your arrival has been greatly anticipated.
My lords, how long will you stay?
Aha! I see you've captured
this temple-robbing thief.
- How would you have us punish her?
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
My lord, I am not a thief.
See, the gods sent me a vision to bring them
tribute from the temple to guide them here.
My only wish is to serve the gods.
Release her, don't ya think?
Then you will begin by returning this
to its rightful place.
My lords, why now
do you choose to visit us?
Enough! You do not question the gods!
That's right, do not question us,
or we shall have to unleash
our awesome and terrible power!
And you don't want that!
Well, yes! We do!
- You do?
- Of course we do.
Visit your wrath upon this non-believer.
Show us the truth of your divinity!
Divinity! One moment.
Miguel, you know that little voice that people
have that tells them to quit when they're ahead?
You don't have one!
- I just got carried away!
- Way away!
- Maybe we should tell the truth and beg for mercy.
- Are you nuts? We'd be butchered alive!
Yes, but they're suspicious. And if we don't
come up with some sort of mega-cosmic event...
I'm trying. I'm trying. These distractions!
- You, horse...
- Think! Think, think, think!
I'm on the verge of... stop!
stop... stop... stop...
Don't make me start it up again,
'cause I will.
Oh, mighty lords!
Come. Let me show you to your temple.
All right! Temple.
Step aside.
To commemorate your arrival, I
propose a reverent ceremony at dawn.
Ah, then perhaps I could prepare
a glorious feast for you tonight.
Which would you prefer?
- Both?
- Both.
- Both!
Both is good.
- My lords.
And so dawns the Age of the Jaguar.
Happy New Year.
- Hey!
- Hey hey.
Tulio. Tulio, they actually
think we're gods.
It's an entire city of suckers!
We just keep this up long enough to load up on
the gold and then get the hell out of here!
Tulio, we'll be living like kings!
- Miguel and Tulio!
- Tulio and Miguel!
- Mighty and powerful gods.
- Hello.
Ahhh!
Depart, mortal, before we
strike you with a lightning bolt.
Beware the wrath
of the gods! Be gone!
Save it for the high priest, honey.
You're gonna need it.
Miguel, it's not working.
Miguel! We've been caught.
Oh, no, don't worry about me, boys.
"My only wish is to serve the gods."
- Remember?
- How?
Well, if you guys want the gold
and you don't want to get caught, right?
- You're going to need my help.
- What makes you think we need your help?
Are you serious?
I... What... We... Okay.
- So, uh, who are you?
- Yeah, what's your angle?
- No angle. I want in.
- In?
On the scam.
There's no scam!
Why would you think there's a... Why?
So I can get out.
- I thought she wanted in?
- She wants in so she can get out.
Aha! Got it... Why?
Think only you dream of
better things? Of adventure?
You've got your reasons
and I've got mine.
Let's not make it personal, okay?
- It's just business.
- Oh.
So when you guys
are ready to go back to...
wherever you came from,
I'm going with you.
No, don't think so.
All right. Fine.
After all, I'm sure you know proper rituals for
blessing and tribute, the holiest days on the calendar,
oh, and of course you know
all about Xibalba.
OK? Good luck.
See you at the execution.
Wait! Hold it.
- Deal?
- Hmm.
- Deal.
- Not yet! Let's see how this works out.
Uh-huh. Well, then I suppose
that means you'll want these back?
- How'd you get those?
- Where was she keeping them?
- Call me, Chel, your new partner.
- Uh, that's partner-in-training.
Now, put these on.
Your public's waiting.
Do you mind?
No.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Right. Uh, excuse me.
Bye.
Mm-mm! Maybe they should call
this place "Chel Dorado".
She's whoo...
- Whoa, she's trouble! Wait a minute.
- What?
The little voice, remember the little voice?
Just for a second imagine that you have one.
What would it be saying about Chel?
No, no... listen. We are partners.
- We're partners.
- We have a plan, remember?
- Get the gold. Go back to Spain.
- Yes! And we're pretending to be gods.
Now, put Chel in the mix.
What does the voice say?
Listen carefully.
Chel is off-limits, hmm?
Bravo! Chel is off-limits!
Shake on it.
- Off-limits. Mm, mm.
- Mmm.
Besides, we're supposed to be gods.
We must avoid giving in to temptation.
Gods. Oh. This is
gonna be tougher than I thought.
Tulio, relax! All you have to do is
smile, act godly and follow my lead.
Big smile. Like you mean it.
A-one, two, three.
♪ I hardly think I'm qualified ♪
♪ To come across all sanctified ♪
♪ I just don't cut it with the cherubim... ♪
- Ow!
- Julio, what're you talking about?
♪ There again they're on their knees ♪
♪ Being worshipped is a breeze ♪
♪ Which rather suits us in the interim ♪
♪ Interim, interim, it's me and him ♪
♪ Oh, my God! It's tough to be a god ♪
♪ Tread where mortals have not trod ♪
♪ Be deified
When really you're a sham ♪
♪ Be an object of devotion ♪
♪ Be the subject of psalms ♪
♪ It's a rather touching notion ♪
♪ All those prayers and those salaams ♪
♪ And who am I to bridle ♪
♪ If I'm forced to be an idol ♪
♪ If they say that I'm a god ♪
♪ That's what I am ♪
♪ What's more if we don't comply ♪
♪ With the locals' wishes ♪
♪ I can see us being
sacrificed or stuffed! ♪
You have a point there. Very good.
♪ So let's be gods
The perks are great ♪
- ♪ El Dorado on our plates... ♪
- Thank you.
♪ Local feelings should not be rebuffed ♪
♪ Never rebuff
I never rebuff a local feeling ♪
♪ No, my friend ♪
♪ It's tough to be a god ♪
♪ But if you get the people's nod ♪
♪ Count your blessings
Keep 'em sweet ♪
- ♪ That's our advice! ♪
- It's great advice!
♪ Be a symbol of perfection ♪
♪ Be a legend, be a cult ♪
♪ Take their praise, take a collection ♪
♪ As the multitudes exalt ♪
♪ Don a supernatural habit ♪
- ♪ We'd be crazy not to grab it... ♪
- You got it!
♪ So sign on two new gods for paradise ♪
♪ Par-a-dise... ♪
- Ahh!
- Good morning, my lords!
- He's back!
- Oh, no.
And now it's my turn!
The gods have awakened!
Whoa! Ooh.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Chel, what's going on?
It's not gonna be good.
Thank you.
This city has been granted
a great blessing!
And what have we done
to show our gratitude?
A meagre celebration.
The gods deserve a proper tribute!
The beginning of a new era,
the dawning of a new age...
demands...
sacrifice!
- I don't like this.
- Tulio, we've got to do something.
Stop!
Hmm?
This is not a proper tribute!
- You do not want the tribute?
- No! No no, we want tribute.
Uh, it's just that, um...
Tulio, tell him.
The stars are not in position
for this tribute!
Like he says, the stars...
Can't do it.
Not today.
Ah. Perhaps it is possible
I misread... the heavens.
Don't worry about it.
To err is human, to forgive...
My lords, may the people of El Dorado
offer you our tribute.
Ooohhh.
My lords, does this please you?
- Yes, very nice. Certainly acceptable.
- Yeah, lovely, it'll do.
The gods have chosen!
To Xibalba?
- Xibalba!
- No, no!
To Xibalba!
Oh, great.
Hey, Chel, um,
what are they doing?
They're sending it to Xibalba,
the spirit world.
- The spirit world.
- I'll take care of it.
Um, excuse me, Chief? The gods have
changed their minds about the Xibalba.
They wish to bask in the reverence
that has been shown them.
Stop!
They wish to bask!
Take the tribute to the gods' temple!
Nice going.
Smile while you can.
Well, well, well.
What have we here?
♪ Tons of gold for you, hah! ♪
- ♪ Tons of gold for me! ♪
- ♪ Tons of gold for we! ♪
- Not bad for a day's work.
- Not at all.
We just became richer
than the king of Spain.
Speaking of kings, the chief and
high priest seem a bit, uh, tense.
Buenos días!
Listen, all we have to do
is keep playing
the one against the other.
You know, do a little god dance,
chant some mystic mumbo jumbo,
dazzle 'em with some smoke and mirrors
and then get the hell back to Spain!
Um, Tulio, how are we gonna
get all this back to Spain?
Ummm...
- A boat?
- Yeah.
We really hate to be ascending so soon
but some urgent business has come up.
- Family matters...
- Family.
Badda-bing... You know.
Oh, we expected you to be staying with us
for the next... thousand years.
Well, as we say in the
spirit world, there's
your plan and then the gods' plan.
Our plan calls for a boat,
'cause we're gonna ascend kind of in a
horizontal pattern first.
And then we're gonna go vertical
as we get further out to sea.
To build a boat
large and glorious enough
would take about a week.
- A week?
- Um...
I wonder how long
it would take Tzekel-Kan to do it.
But for the gods... three days.
Uh...
Well, if that's the best you can do.
Oh, perhaps if you were not burdened
with so much tribute,
you could leave sooner.
- Hmm?
- Hmm? I like it here. Miguel?
Yep, yep. Three days is just fine.
No, three days is not fine.
- This is a real...
- Mmm.
- These. These are the ones.
- Thank you.
Problem.
Miguel, how are we gonna
keep this up for three days?
You worry too much.
No, I worry exactly the right amount.
You can never worry too much.
We just have to lie low.
But, Tulio, this place is amazing!
I mean, I wonder what's...
No! Don't even move!
- Tulio.
- You're moving!
- A little, just a...
- Hey! Hey!
- C'mon. I gotta put...
- Stay!
- I just put...
- Just stand there!
For three days?
Yes! Exactly.
For three days.
Don't even breathe. All right?
All right. We lie low.
Nah, ah, ah, ah. Promise?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right, all right.
Great! Good. Okay.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to gloat over my gold.
Oh, yum, yum, yum.
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
- Yeah!
- You know, you really shouldn't miss it.
- I know.
But I-I couldn't.
Go ahead. I'll cover for you.
Oh, good. Thanks.
- So, what happened to Altivo?
- I don't know.
♪ Tulio goes for paradise ♪
- Hey, what happened to Miguel?
- I don't know.
Oh, my God!
He's gone! Miguel's gone!
He's loose! What am I gonna do?
Oh, no, no!
Oh, Miguel is right.
You worry too much.
Oh. Ooh.
Oh, yeah. Oh, down, down, down, down. Down.
No! No! Big trouble.
Whoa!
Look, sweetheart,
we're in the middle of a con here,
walking the razor's edge.
On the one hand, gold!
On the other hand,
painful, agonising failure!
Ahem. I can't afford
any tempta... distractions.
So, I'm sorry.
So sorry.
But perhaps another time?
Another place?
Too bad. I'm free now.
I'm... not really sure I trust you.
I'm not really
asking you to trust me.
- Am I?
- Whoo.
Okay.
Ooh, yeah.
Excuse me. Excuse me?
Hey, where is everybody?
They've been cleared from the streets my lord,
so the city can be cleansed, as you ordered.
- Cleansed?
- Yes.
So the Age of the Jaguar
can begin, as you ordered.
- Get back in!
- Where are you going?
Hey! Hey, stop that!
- Move!
- Hey stop that!
What are you doing? Stop that!
But my lord, anyone who disobeys your
orders are punished, as you ordered.
Seems I've been giving
a lot of orders, haven't I.
- Tzekel-Kan has made your commands clear, my lord.
- Really?
Here's an order. Take the day off.
Are you all right?
Here.
Oh, no!
It's all right. Please.
Hey, Altivo. There you are.
♪ The more I learn ♪
♪ The more I see ♪
♪ The less the world impassions me ♪
♪ The hungry heart ♪
♪ The roving eye ♪
♪ Have come to rest
Do not apply ♪
♪ The frantic chase ♪
♪ The crazy ride ♪
♪ The thrill has gone ♪
♪ I step aside ♪
♪ I'd believe in anything ♪
♪ Were it not for you ♪
♪ Showing me by just existing ♪
♪ Only this is true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Without question ♪
♪ I'd believe in anything ♪
♪ Were it not for you ♪
♪ Showing me by just existing
Only this is true ♪
♪ Oh, I love you ♪
Hmm. This is not what I expected.
Perhaps Lord Tulio will enlighten me.
- How do I look?
- Oh, uh... Well, you...
Oh, shut up.
Oh! Whoa!
My lords? Hello?
- The high priest.
- Ow!
What's he gonna think if he
finds one of the gods like this with me?
Uh, lucky god?
Just... just... just...
- Hello?
- Whoa!
Oh, Tzekel-Kan! What brings you here?
I-I-I humbly request
an audience with you, my lord.
Lord yes, what can I do for you?
My lord, I have just seen Lord
Miguel out among the people.
Really?
If I may be so bold as
to offer some advice?
- All right. Shoot.
- Ahem.
- My lord, you are perfect.
- Oh, well. Go on.
But in your perfection, you cannot
know how imperfect humans are.
Like snakes they are.
Spineless and slippery.
They are as untrustworthy as rats,
stealing and cheating, with no remorse.
Spinning webs of lies, like spiders!
Stop it! That's disgusting.
- They're beyond disgusting!
- Yeah, yeah, way beyond.
Then we're in agreement. I'll begin the
necessary preparations immediately.
Now, do you wish to have your victims bound to
an altar, or do you prefer them free-range?
Sheez.
And will you be devouring their
essence whole or piece by piece?
Tzek, you've lost me.
My lord, these people will not
respect you if they do not fear you.
And of course we'll make them fear us by...
A sacrifice, as is prophesised.
The history of the Age of the
Jaguar will be written in...
- Ink?
- Blood!
Blood! Oh, right!
Of course! I should probably
consult though with Lord Miguel.
This is fairly important stuff. I should discuss
the entire, uh, blood issue right away.
Excuse us, won't you? Let's go!
Finally... we're connecting.
This way.
Ooh.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Lying low.
Look, change of plans.
We have to grab what we can
carry and get out of here, now.
What? Why?
Because the high priest is nuts!
- This is unacceptable!
- Yeah. Yeah! Like he said!
The gods should not
be playing ball like this!
- Well, exactly!
- This is how gods should play ball!
- Well, don't blame me.
- I blame you.
- What is the object of this game, pray tell?
- Gotta knock the ball through the hoop.
- What hoop?
- That hoop.
- That's impossible! We're gonna lose!
- Gods don't lose.
Heep-ha!
My lords, Chief Tannabuk's warriors
are the finest ball players in the city.
15 mere mortals against two gods.
I realise it's a bit uneven but I do hope
they challenge you enough to make it...
interesting.
Play ball!
- Crush them into the dust. Enjoy!
- Go! Go! Go!
Ahh!
D'oh. D'oh.
My lords, were you not supposed
to put the ball into play?
Oh! Ha. Well, no, no, no, no, no...
We were demonstrating
the traditional...
first avoidance manoeuvre.
Ah. I've never heard
of such a thing.
Excuse me. Who invented this game?
Why, the gods! Of course!
I'm warning you, don't push
your luck with this guy.
But, Tulio, we're the gods.
Tulio! The hip! The hip!
Listen, it's impossible.
Yaaa!
Excuse me?
Heep... haaa!
Heep-ha! Heep-ha! Heep-ha! Heep-ha!
Heep-ha! Heep-ha! Heep-ha!
Foul! That was a foul!
Ah!
New ball!
- How long does this go on anyway?
- The game is over when the shadow touches this line.
- We need a miracle.
- No, we need to cheat.
Yes!
- Huh?
- Ooh!
Hey!
Whoo-hoo!
Olé!
Huh?
Hmm.
Yes!
- Who's the god?
- You da god.
- No, you the god.
- You da god. Fine.
Yeah! Yeah!
Guys, it's here! It's right here with me!
I love this game!
Yes!
- Yes! Woo!
- Well done, partner.
- Yes! Yes!
- My lords, congratulations on your victory.
And now, you will of course
wish to have the losing team...
sacrificed to your glory.
- Not again. Look, Tzekel-Kan!
- Uh, Miguel?
- Forget the sacrifices.
- Miguel.
We don't want any sacrifices.
But all other sacred writings say that you'll
devour the wicked and the unrighteous.
Well I don't see anyone here
who fits that description.
Well as speaker for the gods, it would
be my privilege to point them out.
The gods speak for themselves now!
This city and these people
have no need for you any more!
There will be no sacrifices!
Not now, not ever!
Now get out!
Mmm. As the...
gods... command.
Whoa! Who-o-oa!
Hey, not bad for
my first commandment, huh?
Miguel, the little voice...
Yeah, fine.
Do you know why
the gods demand blood?
I don't know.
Because gods don't bleed.
It's time to take the future
into my own hands,
and this city will be cleansed.
Even if I have to do it myself.
Uh, how?
There are dark magics here...
and power... and...
Ooh. My, my, my, my, my.
It's not called
the Age of the Jaguar for nothing.
This will be a delightful way
to bid the false gods... goodbye.
Hmm!
Adiós, muchacho!
- Well, it's, um, uh, nice.
- Nice?
- Yes, nice.
- But?
Um, but, uh,
is it really fit for the gods?
My lord.
I have been around boats, believe me,
and that, um, the pointy, tall, um,
the-the long up and down thing...
- The mast?
- Mast, yes. Mast is good.
Well, look at it. There's not
nearly enough, uh... rope.
- Rope?
- Yes, rope. Exactly my point.
Vertical ascension requires
a lot more... rope.
- My lord.
- And look at this.
This doesn't look at all secure.
Chief, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but
all in all, it is a complete do-over.
You know, Lord Miguel,
if you wish to stay,
you only need to say so.
You mean... forever?
Of course.
Oh, no, I can't. I have to go back
with Tulio. We're... we're partners.
Big plans in the other world, huh?
Yep. Big plans.
Well, then, I'd better
go get some more rope, huh?
Oh, Chief, um,
forget about the rope.
Um, my mistake.
Hey, to err is human.
Half?
I don't think so.
I'll tell you what.
I'll let you come back to Spain with us,
like you wanted, and, yeah, I can see my way
clear to throwing you, mmm, ten per cent?
You know, maybe I won't go to
Spain with you and take a third.
Ohh! Like you
don't wanna go to Spain.
Oh, like you don't want me
to want to go to Spain.
- I want you to want...
- Hmm?
- What you want.
- Mm-hmm. Go on.
All right. Cards on the table.
Uh, I want you to come to Spain
with me and Miguel.
Mostly me. Especially me.
Only me. Forget Miguel.
Well... as long as
that's what you want.
- Me too.
- Okay.
Deal?
Deal. Mmm.
"Forget Miguel"? Well, forget Tulio.
Well, is it ready yet?
Ooh!
Ah!
Ahh! Hmm.
It seems to be missing something.
Ah, that's it.
It needs more... body.
Do... as I command!
- The gods deserve a proper tribute.
- Stop! There will be no sacrifices!
That kid does you
better than you do.
Some send-off, huh?
Finally at the "go back to Spain
and live like kings" part.
Well, isn't king
kind of a step down from god?
What? Whoa, wh-whoa, whoa, whoa.
Miguel, we can't stay here.
We have a plan, remember?
How about...
we forget the plan? Hmm?
What?
Now everyone will know
the truth of your "divinity"!
I'm okay!
I'm still okay!
Come on! Get on!
Altivo, hyah!
No!
Tulio!
Hey, over here,
you big Tzekel-Kan cat creep!
Altivo, get Chel out of here.
Duck!
Move! Move!
Jump!
Whoa!
I know what you are,
and I know what you are not!
And you are not gods!
Y... You're not a god?
You lied to me?
- How dare you!
- Hey, it was his stupid plan!
- What?
- Oh, oh...
My plan was that we should lie low!
But your plan was to run off and be
all "Oh, look at me, look at me, I'm a god."
- That's not true!
- No? Who are you kidding? You're buying your own con!
At least I'm not dating mine.
I... Ooh, low blow.
Listen, mister high and mighty.
We'd both be sailing with a mountain
of gold if you had just listened to me!
Well, you've got all the precious gold
and Chel. So what do you need me for?
Well, maybe I don't need you any more.
Well, the why don't you just go back to Spain and
I'll stay here, and we'll both get what we want!
- That's fine with me, pal!
- Fine with me too!
- Fine!
- Okay!
All right!
Tie him up!
What?
Whoa.
Jump!
No!
My lord.
Where did you get this?
That was good, huh?
Hey, a little help, please?
Chief Tanni! Chief Tanni!
- I've decided to stay.
- Oh, this is wonderful news!
What a glorious day for El Dorado.
Lord Miguel has decided
to live among us!
Tulio!
Is everything okay?
Everything is... fine.
♪ There isn't much ♪
♪ I haven't shared ♪
♪ With you along the road ♪
♪ And through it all
There'll always be ♪
♪ Tomorrow's episode ♪
♪ Suddenly that isn't true ♪
♪ There's another avenue ♪
♪ Beckoning the great divide ♪
♪ Ask no questions ♪
♪ Take no side ♪
♪ Who's to say who's right or wrong ♪
♪ Whose course is braver run ♪
♪ All I know is all we had ♪
♪ Is over, said and done ♪
♪ Friends never say goodbye ♪
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
Ha!
♪ Friends never say goodbye ♪
- We'll miss you!
- Thank you!
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
♪ Friends never say goodbye ♪
♪ Friends ♪
♪ Never say goodbye... ♪
Well, good luck.
Yeah. You too.
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
Whoa, boy, what is it?
- Cortés.
- My lord, what is it?
Chief Tanni! Chief Tanni!
Approaching the city...
is an army of strangers.
We are safe here. They'll never
find the gate to the city.
But, sire, they are being led
by Tzekel-Kan.
He survived?
Warriors, prepare yourself for battle!
Chief, you cannot fight them!
Then how can we stop them?
We can't.
Hmm.
Uh, one moment, please!
- Okay, here's the gate. Here's the boat.
- And?
- Here's the gate. Here's the boat.
- Okay. Got that. And?
- Well, here's the goat and here's the bate.
- Tulio!
Ah! That's it! We'll
crash the boat into the pillars.
That's it? I mean... But...
- What about the gold?
- Well...
Chief! Ahem...
Chief!
I've got a plan.
Hold the line steady!
They're almost in place!
It better be there, for your sake.
Okay, Chief, on my signal!
Ready! Hit the pillars!
Now!
- They're breaking too fast!
- Tulio, the sail!
It's stuck!
They're not gonna make it. Altivo!
Ah!
Are you crazy?
Get off the boat, Miguel, or
you'll never see the city again!
I know. You don't think I'm gonna
let you have all the fun, do you?
Come on, we've got a wave to catch!
Whoa!
- Get out of the way!
- Huh?
Hold on!
We're gonna have to hit it broadside!
That's your plan? But the gold!
I know! Just turn the boat!
On impact, everybody jump!
We made it. It worked.
It worked! Ha ha ha!
- Quiet. Get down!
- Ouch. Ow!
There they are.
No.
You lying heathen.
There is nothing here at all.
No. Wait. Wait.
- Men, seize him!
- What?
There is no El Dorado here.
Onward, men!
Wait! No, wait!
Wait!
Now, that was an adventure.
Yes. Yes, it was. And, um...
It was so much gold!
- I'm fine.
- Good.
Let's go.
Partner.
Hey, guys, come on! You don't wanna
stay here forever, do you?
- But we don't have a map.
- We don't have a plan.
That's what makes it interesting!
- You're right!
- What are we waiting for?
Let's follow that trail!
Hyah!
♪ Oh, the sweet unfolding ♪
- Kill her, boy!
♪ Of an antique mystery ♪
- Hey! Altivo!
♪ All will be revealed... ♪
- Sit, boy, sit!
Chel, we're not on the horse!
♪ On the trail we blaze ♪
♪ Here comes the night ♪
♪ Here come the memories ♪
♪ Lost in your arms ♪
♪ Down in the foreign fields ♪
♪ Not so long ago ♪
♪ Seems like eternity ♪
♪ Those sweet afternoons ♪
♪ Still capture me ♪
♪ Someday out of the blue ♪
♪ In a crowded street ♪
♪ Or a deserted square ♪
♪ I'll turn and I'll see you ♪
♪ As if our love were new ♪
♪ Someday we can start again ♪
♪ Someday soon ♪
♪ I still believe ♪
♪ I still put faith in us ♪
♪ We had it all ♪
♪ And watched it slip away ♪
♪ Where are we now ♪
♪ Not where we want to be ♪
♪ Those hot afternoons ♪
♪ Still follow me ♪
♪ Someday out of the blue ♪
♪ Maybe years from now ♪
♪ Or tomorrow night ♪
♪ I'll turn and I'll see you ♪
♪ As if we always knew ♪
♪ Someday we would live again ♪
♪ Someday soon ♪
♪ I still believe
I still put faith in us ♪
♪ Here comes the night ♪
♪ Here come the memories ♪
♪ Lost in your arms ♪
♪ Down in the foreign fields ♪
♪ Not so long ago ♪
♪ Seems like eternity ♪
♪ Those sweet afternoons ♪
♪ Still capture me ♪
♪ Someday out of the blue ♪
♪ Maybe years from now ♪
♪ Or tomorrow night ♪
♪ I'll turn and I'll see you ♪
♪ As if we always knew ♪
♪ Someday we would live again ♪
♪ Someday soon ♪
♪ The more I learn ♪
♪ The more I see ♪
♪ The less the world impassions me ♪
♪ The hungry heart ♪
♪ The roving eye ♪
♪ Have come to rest ♪
♪ Do not apply ♪
♪ The frantic chase ♪
♪ The crazy ride ♪
♪ The thrill has gone ♪
♪ I step aside ♪
♪ And I'd believe ♪
♪ In anything ♪
♪ Were it not for you ♪
♪ Showing me ♪
♪ By just existing ♪
♪ Only this is true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Without question ♪
- ♪ The more I want ♪
- ♪ The more I steal ♪
- ♪ The more I hold ♪
♪ The more I hold ♪
♪ The less is real ♪
- ♪ All worldly things ♪
- ♪ I follow blind ♪
- ♪ In hope, not faith ♪
♪ In hope, not faith ♪
♪ Was paid in kind ♪
♪ The line is drawn ♪
♪ The change is made ♪
♪ I come to you ♪
♪ I'm not afraid ♪
♪ And I'd believe ♪
♪ In anything ♪
♪ Were it not for you ♪
♪ Showing me ♪
♪ By just existing ♪
♪ Only this is true ♪
♪ I love you ♪